<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>Jay Kim</author>
            <date>2010-03-20T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>아주 유용한 정보 감사합니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>제가 깜빡했네요.&lt;br&gt;영어가 불편하지않으시면,&lt;br&gt;UT에 DEEDS프로그램에 가입하세요.&lt;br&gt;이민 초기에 입학했다.다른일로 &lt;br&gt;졸업을 안(못)한게 정말 후회되는 약 6개월 짜리, Co-op 프로그램입니다.예전에는 4개월에 7000불정도의 고급코스였는데(Graduated Course),입학하려면,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;배워서 어디에 사용할지 묻는 플랜을 내야 합니다.이력과 이걸 기준으로 &lt;br&gt;뽑는것 같습니다. 아직도 그대로 있네요.저는 도중에 나와서 모르겠지만,그때 같이 공부한 친구들이,거의다 취업한걸로 보아,취업전선에 도움이된것 같습니다.&lt;br&gt;그리고,지난 몇년 어려운중에도 ,&lt;br&gt; 서로 땅기고 밀고 하는것 같습니다.....&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;http://www.utoronto.ca/deeds/training/ftcourse/fwelcome.htm&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oracle Workforce Development Program officially sanctioned course.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a full-time course, lasting twenty-five weeks. Our students have access to realistic and relevant hands-on practice in our Computer Labs, using Oracle and other enterprise level software. Our Instructors are always available in our Computer Labs for guidance and support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For twenty-two weeks of the course a lecture or demonstration is provided each day by one of our Instructors. Lectures are normally two to three hours long. For the rest of the course day, each student has an assigned Lab Practice period. Lab Practice sessions start at 8am and continue until the start of the Lecture, or start after the Lecture and continue until 5pm.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final weeks of the course are either co-op work experience or Lab Practice time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students should be prepared to devote between 2 and 3 hours per day to preparatory reading and research. Legal holidays are observed during the course. There are no Lectures and no Lab Practice sessions on Legal Holidays or weekends.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This course is carefully designed to blend academic instruction and hands-on practice with real workplace experience. The DEEDS Project uses an instructor-led methodology. Our Instructors are carefully picked for both technical and instructional excellence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A typical course work day is split between a two hour lecture and three to four hours of hands-on lab practice. At least two professionally experienced Instructors are always available to assist students in our computer Labs. Students can also benefit greatly from interaction with the experienced programmers who work on the DEEDS research project.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each major topic in the course includes practical assignments, practice work with examples and an evaluation test.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;안녕하세요.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;오래전 OCP-DBA를 가졌는데 ERP관련 컨설팅을 하다 보니 Renewal 할 필요성을 모르고 있다가 이곳 캐나다에 와서 보니 단기간에 다시 일할 수 있을것 같은 것이 DBA인것 같아 최신버전의 DBA과정을 이수하고 OCP-DBA 자격 시험을 보려 합니다. 미시사가에 오라클 브랜치가 있는지요? 아니면 추천할 만한 교육장소 있는지요? 저는 현재 Coop 프로그램(국젝적으로 훈련된 전문가들을 위한 프로그램)을 이수 하고 있습니다.&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>2ED4A995-A2E5-4213-B228-A273DF9D2A18</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>UT Deeds Program(강추)</title>
</post>
