<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>What is open source?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the opensource.org website, 'open source promotes software reliability and quality by supporting independent peer review and rapid evolution of source code.' &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The term open source designates programs that abide by these rules: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* its source code is available publicly and can be redistributed&lt;br&gt;* it can be redistributed without any charges&lt;br&gt;* derived works are permitted and can be redistributed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The premise of open source is very simple. When programmers have the possibility to read, redistribute, and modify the source for a piece of software, it then evolves. People will improve it, adapt it and fix bugs, very quickly. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are its advantages?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many benefits to using open-source software. First of all, such programs are almost always more secure than proprietary ones. As a matter of fact, the US Computer Emergency Readiness Team encourages internauts to use other browsers other than Internet Explorer because of its security breaches. Thus, many people are changing over to Firefox. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is also very interesting to note that open source software is free! For example, you can use Linux for your operating system and Open Office, which offer a free alternative to Windows and MS Office, allowing you to create text documents and creating spreadsheets without having to pay for expensive software. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another main advantage of using open-source software is its active community, which is always ready to greet neophytes and help them learn more about their product and community. Plus, since the source code is freely available, skilled individual can contribute to improve it and release it back into the community. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discover a few open-source programs...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FireFox is a web browser which is quickly gaining in popularity on the web. In addition to the usual webbrowsing tools, FireFox also offers tabbed browsing. Thus, you can browse more than one website in your browser window and easily switch between the tabs that are oppened within it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sound editor Audacity allows the user to record live audio, convert records into digital recordings or CDs and edit audio clips.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gimp is a freely distributed program for image editing. It can be used as a simple paint program, a photo retouching program, and image format converter and more. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OpenOffice is a great alternative to the MS Office suite which includes Writer (for word processing), Calc (for spreadsheets), Impress (a presentation creation tool) and Draw (a graphics tool). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note that these links are provided solely as a convenience to you and not as an endorsement by CBC of the contents of such third-party web sites. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;headlines@cbc.ca</content>
    <postId>95178619-6737-4640-B236-DAB0D2E070D3</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Did you know...?</title>
</post>
