<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Please see Job Description below:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our government client is looking for an Intermediate Developer(x3) for their Winnipeg location.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duration of contract&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The term for these three roles will begin July 2nd, August 5th and September 2nd 2008 and end on or about December 31, 2008. A 1 year additional term is possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the direction of the Lead Developer role, the Java Developer (intermediate) is responsible for the core activities of the software development effort. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A post secondary university degree in computer science or a related discipline&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Three (3) years experience in programming; two (2) years experience specific to Java J2EE programming&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Knowledge of object-relational database mapping technology&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience programming object-oriented applications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience in specifying database changes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience performing junit testing and supporting system testing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience in developing user interface design and prototyping&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience using Spring, Hibernate and MyFaces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience with Eclipse development tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience with building applications targeted to Oracle Application Server.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience with methodologies such as the Rational Unified Process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Must have Java certification.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Must have Government of Canada Enhanced Reliability Clearance (ERC) and be eligible for Secret.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deliverables&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Contractor will perform the following services for the Client on behalf of IBM. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; As a developer work under the direction of the Lead Developer to develop the application areas as assigned based on the agreed tools and standards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Understand and follow coding standards and assist in documenting deviations if required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Effectively interact and collaborate with the Lead Developer, DBAs, Business Analysts and other Developers on design interpretation and other development matters. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Develop quality SW as measured by defects during System, Integration and User Acceptance Test cycles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Participate in code reviews and ensure appropriate junit code coverage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Perform unit testing to verify component functionality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Support the testers in their efforts and &amp; correct problems as required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#376;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Collaborate and assist the Lead Developer &amp; Project Manager with estimating, planning, workload balancing, tracking to schedule and as requested.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are qualified, available, interested, planning to make a change, or know of a friend who might have the required qualifications and interest, please contact me ASAP at gvasquez@ca.ibm.comeven if we have spoken recently about a different position. If you do respond via e-mail please include a daytime phone number so I can reach you. In considering candidates, time is of the essence, so please respond ASAP. Thank you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sincerely yours,&lt;br&gt;Gloria Vasquez&lt;br&gt;gvasquez@ca.ibm.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>0116A6DB-1EA8-4415-8473-09833311E374</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title> Intermediate Java Developer</title>
</post>
