<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>ate Posted: March 10, 2010&lt;br&gt;Job ID: 11702&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our downtown Toronto based client is currently seeking one (1) Java Web Developer. This is a contract opportunity slated to begin immediately, and is projected to be six (6) months in length with the possibility of extending.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will be responsible for:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Performing analysis, design, programming and testing, based on SDLC methodology;&lt;br&gt;Providing after-hours support of production systems when required;&lt;br&gt;Working closely with senior Developers/Architects on the application design;&lt;br&gt;Working closely with Project Manager and providing input on project timelines;&lt;br&gt;Working closely with Business Analyst to translate business requirements into technical solutions;&lt;br&gt;Technically implementing small, medium and large sized systems development projects;&lt;br&gt;Applying analytical skills for problem solving and resolution;&lt;br&gt;Conducting and participating in code reviews;&lt;br&gt;Participating in knowledge transfer with the team; and,&lt;br&gt;Keeping up-to-date with latest industry standards.&lt;br&gt;Skills and Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The qualified candidate must have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five to eight (5 &amp;#8211; 8) years of Java development experience;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Java technologies: J2SE, J2EE, JSP, Servlets, JDBC;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of other technologies: SQL, HTML, XML, CSS , OpenSSO;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Java frameworks (SPRING, Struts 2, Hibernate, IBATIS);&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of infrastructure and network technologies;&lt;br&gt;Experience with BPM and Workflow engines;&lt;br&gt;Experience with development tools: Ant, Apache, Tomcat, CVS;&lt;br&gt;Experience with development and development platforms: Windows, Linux;&lt;br&gt;RDBMS knowledge: SQL Server, DB2;&lt;br&gt;Experience working with XML and XSLT;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Java Design Patterns;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Web application development;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Web page design;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of applied software development principles and methodologies;&lt;br&gt;Strong research skills and analytical ability; and,&lt;br&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don't miss out on this opportunity, apply on-line today!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants for their interest; however, only candidates under consideration will be contacted.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please note that your application does not signify the beginning of employment with Eagle and that employment with Eagle will only commence when placed on an assignment as a temporary employee of Eagle.</content>
    <postId>0226502E-6737-4025-B0D9-DD210E9283ED</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java web Developer(Agent)</title>
</post>
