<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김세환</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>장선미</author>
            <date>2002-07-25T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>답변 감사드립니다, 많은 도움이 되었습니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Welcome to COSKA...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In response to your request, I would like to give you my personal&lt;br&gt;opinions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. A Univerisity Degree is definitely a big asset to attract &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; a potential employer's attention in future.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please study hard .....&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;2. It is not known to me whether you have a working permit.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; However, most of time, they value work experience more than&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; a Degree or a Certificate (Oracle).&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Of course, any certificate related to your skill set will &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; be a nice thing to have.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. While you are in school, please try to get some work experiences&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; thru a Summer Job, Part-time or Co-op program if there is any.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Even if you delay the graduation, it will be a big advantage&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; if you have some work experience when you graduate.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Also those opportunity might lead you to a permanent Job &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; later on when you graduate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. I understand that the University has a 'Job Placement Center'&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; where you can get advices or job informations.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please use it efficiently and do job search dilligently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Prepare a GOOD Resume and a Cover Letter.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please have an expert to help you even if you have to pay.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Remember.. The Resume and letter are the only thing between&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; you and a potential employer.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; So you have to impress them with the resume and somehow you have&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; make them interested in you with it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Also learn 'Interview skill' in case. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Establish some personal connections somehow with companies&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; or people working out there. (Seminar, etc)&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; It sometimes help a lot in job search .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Considering the job market now, you may NOT have many choices &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; in terms of the area you want to be in . (i.e. DB, Network).&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;However, it is good to have a career plan.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope it is some help to you..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Luck..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SK</content>
    <postId>0320C2E6-D8E5-47D2-9814-C1D8DA44803C</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] 학생인데, 취업준비를 하고자 합니다.</title>
</post>
