<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Quality Assurance Engineer (SAP R/3) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NRX Global Corp. provides solutions that enable Asset Lifecycle Management in capital-intensive industries. NRX helps organizations leverage plant asset data and existing applications to optimize maintenance, operations and engineering activities that support world-class asset management objectives. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently looking for an SAP R/3 Quality Assurance Engineer to support the development of our SAP Enterprise Portals applications and R/3 integration packages. The candidate will be responsible for the quality assurance and deployment of these applications, and the support and maintenance of NRX’s SAP development environments. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The candidate will:&lt;br&gt;- Support, administer and upgrade&lt;br&gt;·SAP/R3&lt;br&gt;·SAP Enterprise Portal, &lt;br&gt;·WebLogic,Oracle or WebSphere J2EE platforms&lt;br&gt;·Oracle or SQL server RDBMS&lt;br&gt;- Perform regression, scalability, performance and systems level testing of J2EE and XML based applications utilizing R/3&lt;br&gt;- Interface with our software and hardware partners’ technical personnel&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The candidate must possess: &lt;br&gt;- Experience in ABAP, BAPI, RFC, JCo, Business Connector, iDoc interfaces&lt;br&gt;- Experience with configuration and management of SAP R/3 specifically PM and MM modules &lt;br&gt;- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills &lt;br&gt;- Ability to analyze, define and document requirements for data, workflow, operating systems environment&lt;br&gt;- College or University degree in Computer Science &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The position is located in downtown Toronto. Please submit your resume and salary expectations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers@nrx.com&lt;br&gt;NRX Global Corp.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>06C19209-7B2A-461D-B741-854FD9AC41FC</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-03-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Quality Assurance Engineer (SAP R/3)</title>
</post>
