<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Temporary full time position to April 2003.&lt;br&gt;The position is located within the following governmental organization(s): Department of the Environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALARY: $50,663 - $60,541 per annum.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANGUAGE: English essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL LANGUAGES: USEFUL INFORMATION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO CAN APPLY: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open to persons working or residing in an area where the postal code begins with L, M, N or P.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDUCATION: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graduation with an acceptable Bachelors degree (BSc.) from a recognized university in Computer Science, Meteorology or a related branch of earth science. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPERIENCE: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience in software design, computer programming, software documentation. &lt;br&gt;Experience in the configuration, transfer, or processing of scientific data. &lt;br&gt;Experience in programming languages such as C, C++, Perl, FORTRAN, Java. &lt;br&gt;Experience with operating systems such as HP-UX, SUN Solaris, Linux, UNIX. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS / COMMENTS: &lt;br&gt;The Eligibility list established for this position may be used to staff similar vacancies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONDITION OF EMPLOYMENT: Enhanced Reliability Check. &lt;br&gt;All costs related to travel and/or relocation for the purposes of the selection process may be the responsibility of the candidate. &lt;br&gt;Work will be conducted primarily at the King Radar and occassionally at Meteorological Service of Canada (MSC), Downsview. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REFERENCE NUMBER: DOE12742GZ05&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLOSING DATE: April 30, 2002&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Submitting by postal mail:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We encourage you to submit your application using our on-line application form which accompanies each job posting, but some positions will require that you use the traditional mail method. In such cases, you are likely to be asked to submit an official application form in addition to your resume. This is to ensure that certain important information is not omitted. Application forms can be obtained from any of our District Offices and is available for download (via FTP) from this web site. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Application form PSC 3391, the most commonly used, is available for download in Word Perfect and Microsoft Word. For your convenience, those files have been made self-extracting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Word 6 emploiw6.doc (48k) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UP TO TOP &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By fax:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Unless it is specified in the posting that applications must be sent by mail (usually only for inventory loading postings without deadlines) you may simply fax your resume and other requested information to the appropriate District Office. The fax lines are open 24 hours a day, but may be busy during peak periods. You will find a link to the appropriate District Office fax number at the end of each posting. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>0757A4A2-349F-45FD-8DF5-ECF5B3280303</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-04-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>FPA SCIENTIFIC PROGRAMMER AND TECHNICAL LIAISON</title>
</post>
