<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Roger's Product Management team is currently seeking an experienced mobile Content Programmer to fulfill a 11 month contract. The incumbent will be part of a diverse and dynamic team responsible for life cycle management of entertainment services&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Group Product Manager, Entertainment, the successful candidate will be responsible for the merchandising management of the Rogers and Fido portals. Leveraging your excellent communication skills, you will work closely with the Content Programming team to ensure that merchandising efforts can be completed based on release dates and promotions. You will also keep in regular contact with key content providers to facilitate merchandising plans and scheduling ingestion of their assets, engaging the technical operations team when issues arise.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;This role encompasses a range of important functions so the ability to multi-task and effectively solve problems while demonstrating attention to detail is paramount to ensure we meet the expectations of our providers and end-users.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The successful candidate must have a good understanding of mobile entertainment and content, mobile devices and data products and be ready to ready to employ best practices for content life cycle management: content merchandising and analysis, content development, content procurement and change control.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Act as a gatekeeper, working with product managers or other internal departments to capture, consolidate and manage the implementation of changes to the portals&lt;br&gt;Ensure content programming decisions are quantifiable and the content available is relevant and targeted to the right user at the right time&lt;br&gt;Work closely with product marketing on developing &amp; supporting promotional programs that leverage the portals&lt;br&gt;Maintain a programming and project schedule and work to communicate timelines, impacts and relevant roadmaps to all internal stakeholders&lt;br&gt;Work closely with New Product Development on developing and supporting new and existing services in the Rogers Multimedia Service Delivery Platform.&lt;br&gt;Tracking revenue and growth opportunities to evaluate the success of current services, competitive activity and emerging opportunities to devise growth strategies.&lt;br&gt;Support and management of the portal style guide and user flow (ie. Micro-site creation, purchase flow management, style sheet deployment)&lt;br&gt;Work closely with Quality Assurance and Care teams to resolve any content or other technical issues&lt;br&gt;Develop and publish marketing plans (including detailed financial plans) and report progress regularly.&lt;br&gt;Update and manage content programming guides and process&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;documentation that is understandable by business stakeholders and technical stakeholders.&lt;br&gt;Maintain expertise and thorough understanding of content merchandising and music / media trends.&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;University Degree or College Diploma with a concentration in Marketing/Business or Technology.&lt;br&gt;Experience working with content providers (i.e. Mobile Storefronts, Music Labels, TV/Movie Studios, Game/Application providers).&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with Mobile Service Delivery Platforms&lt;br&gt;Experience merchandising, marketing and promotion programs in the mobile or web content space; experience in Mobile Telecom is preferred&lt;br&gt;Experience working with a content management system is required combined with familiarity of content authoring workflow.;&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with mobile web standards and best practices.&lt;br&gt;Project management experience preferred.&lt;br&gt;Must be reliable, independent, highly organized, and proactive.&lt;br&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills.&lt;br&gt;Proficiency at multi-tasking in a fast-paced environment; ability to prioritize and juggle to consistently meet multiple, short deadlines.&lt;br&gt;Detail oriented and accuracy driven&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated success in problem-solving, generating solutions, efficiency improvements and managing a heavy workload.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Rogers is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The future is exciting and Rogers is leading the way.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Canadians count on Rogers to keep them in touch with those who matter most to them - whether at their desk, on the couch, or on the go. As Canada's telecommunications leader, we keep everyone informed, connected and entertained, with our exciting array of products and services. Our drive to provide the latest and most innovative products ensures that our customers enjoy unmatched convenience, reliability, and flexibility. Rogers continues to set the pace by investing in our networks, platforms, products and people. Are you ready for a high-energy career that feeds your enthusiasm? Join us now.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Job Posting Feb 16, 2010&lt;br&gt;Job Product Management&lt;br&gt;Primary LocationCA-ON-Toronto&lt;br&gt;Schedule Full-time&lt;br&gt;Employee Status Temporary&lt;br&gt;Travel No&lt;br&gt;Target Start Date Mar 28, 2010</content>
    <postId>08BCCC65-D51B-4DAF-BA9B-69E659577996</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Portal Product Manager, Mobile Content Programming-16892</title>
</post>
