<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임정숙</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>EAGLE PROFESSIONAL RESOURCES INC.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Web Developer&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto; ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Category: Computers-Internet&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Industry: Recruitment/Staffing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Company URL: http://www.eagleonline.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Date Posted: Feb 13, 2004&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Reference # :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;11493SY Remember this reference # if you are interested in this opportunity. &lt;br&gt;Date Listed :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Friday, February 13, 2004&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Category :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Application Dev. &lt;br&gt;Job Title :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Web Developer Qty: 2 &lt;br&gt;Skill :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;J2EE; BEA Weblogix &lt;br&gt;Position :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;6 months&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Location :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto Prov/State: Ontario &lt;br&gt;Description :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Our prestigious Telecommunications client is currently seeking two (2) Web Developers. These opportunities are located in Toronto, Ontario and are slated to begin immediately. The duration period of these contract positions are for six (6) months. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidates for these positions will possess:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-- Functional experience with customer service and order management applications;&lt;br&gt;-- Extensive hands-on experience with J2EE, BEA Weblogix;&lt;br&gt;-- Telecommunications industry experience is a must!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the above description matches your current skill set please do not hesitate and apply on-line now!! Due to the large amount of applicants for this fantastic position, only qualified candidates will be contacted. We thank all those who have applied. &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Branch :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto &lt;br&gt;Phone :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(416) 861-1492, (800) 281-2339 &lt;br&gt;Submit Resume :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you would like to submit your resume for this opportunity, as well as all opportunities saved in your Job Cart,simply click the Send Resume Now button above and complete the form provided. You will be given the option of reviewing your Job Cart before completing the form.&lt;br&gt;If you are viewing this posting from a third party website, please note the Reference # above and click here to submit your resume. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>08DC18D4-CD77-467A-9C8B-8C3FF8B7BB25</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-02-14T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Developer: J2EE, BEA Weblogix</title>
</post>
