<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강재형</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Advertisement number: 68412 &lt;br&gt; Title: Internet site designer (Content Focused) (NOC: 2175)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Terms of Employment: Permanent, Full Time, Day &lt;br&gt; Salary: To be negotiated, Bonus &lt;br&gt; Anticipated Start Date: As soon as possible&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Location: Toronto Centre, Ontario (1 vacancy) &lt;br&gt; Skill Requirements:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Education: Completion of high school, Completion of college/CEGEP/vocational or technical training, Other: Content Management Experience an Asset. &lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Other: Credentials required. &lt;br&gt;Experience: 3 - 5 years, Other: Portfolio! &lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Speak French, Read English, Read French, Write English, Write French, Other: French a strong asset. &lt;br&gt;Work Setting Experience: Consulting firm, Internet Service Provider, Software developer &lt;br&gt;Operating Systems: MS Windows 95/98/NT/2000 &lt;br&gt;Programming Languages: ASP, HTML, DHTML, XML, Java Script, CSS &lt;br&gt;Applications: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Aldus Freehand, Flash, MS Excel, MS FrontPage, MS Office, MS PowerPoint, MS Visio, WordPerfect &lt;br&gt;Management Systems (erp or db): MS SQL Server, MySQL &lt;br&gt;Communication Protocols: LAN &lt;br&gt;Generic Skills: Math skills (ex., use math related to money, measurement, calculation, estimation, budgeting, scheduling, data analysis), Computer use (ex., use software packages; knowledge of hardware; work with computer-operated machinery), Writing skills (ex., enter information on forms; write to inform, persuade, or analyze), Reading skills (ex., follow written directions; interpret documents like charts, maps; acquire specialized knowledge), Working with others (ex., work with individual or team; build consensus), Planning and organizing skills (ex., manage priorities; order tasks efficiently), Problem-solving skills (ex., identify problem causes; determine steps to resolve; assess solution), Speaking and listening skills (ex., communicate clearly and effectively; follow directions; mediate disputes) &lt;br&gt;Other Information: Knowledge of and Experience with Cold Fusion a strong asset. . IMPORTANT: SEND RESUME THROUGH EMAIL ONLY. . PLEASE DO NOT CALL OR SEND RESUME THROUGH FAX OR MAIL. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Employer: Web Impact Inc.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; How to Apply:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;By E-mail: info@webimpact.com &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Business Profile: Since 1996, Web Impact has been helping organizations of all types to employ the Internet as a powerful business and communications medium. &lt;br&gt; Web Site: www.webimpact.com &lt;br&gt; Advertised until: 2002/08/09 &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>0CD5A9A6-64D1-48B0-973B-08E19247F70B</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Internet Site Designer</title>
</post>
