<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-Intermediate Software Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Semaview is looking for a talented and motivated software designer with a passion for semantics. As an intermediate software designer, you will be working with the senior software designers to effectively design and implement Semaview software solutions. &lt;br&gt;As a developer for the flagship product, you will be challenged to deliver complex C# client applications that interface with semantic databases, office applications and remote web services. If you are highly experienced at interfacing with the Microsoft Office suite, the Microsoft Windows operating system or have experience with RDF or OWL, we’d like to hear from you. As part of a new start-up, join a fast paced but exciting opportunity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Be actively involved in all phases of software development, utilizing the XP software development process &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Participate effectively in group meetings and design reviews, proposing innovative solutions to complex problems &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Assume full responsibility for software packages assigned to him/her &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Provide schedule and task descriptions to the Technical Manager and report any issues with the schedule. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Competencies: &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; University degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering, or the equivalent&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; At least 2 years of experience in software development with emphasis on Windows Development &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience and Expertise in: C, C#, XML, C++&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Knowledge in: Web services, .NET, Microsoft Office APIs, Win32 APIs, COM/COM+/DCOM&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Sound knowledge of software engineering practices &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Sound knowledge of software architectures, object-oriented design, design patterns&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with Software Modeling is an asset (Rational Rose, UML or similar.) &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; TCP/IP, Multi-threading, Database experience mandatory.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Familiarity with common Internet protocols (SMTP, POP, HTTP, FTP, SOAP)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applicants must submit a cover letter indicating why they want the Semantic Web. All applications without a cover letter will be discarded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: competitive&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Paul Cowles&lt;br&gt;paul@semaview.com&lt;br&gt;Semaview&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>0F6780DE-5ACA-4173-B52C-1BF0990E604E</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-04-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Intermediate Software Developer  - Monster</title>
</post>
