<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이상훈</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Greetings. I came across your resume from Monster.ca and is contacting you regarding positions mentioned below. Please review the details below and respond if interested. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;.NET Developer or Team Lead &lt;br&gt;Locations:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Travel:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Minimal&lt;br&gt;Salary:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 50K - 70K plus bonus &lt;br&gt;Start Date: ASAP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When reply, please &lt;br&gt;- include a current resume&lt;br&gt;- include a summary of your experience with ALL TECHNOLOGIES LISTED BELOW, and for team lead role, please also include &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Years of experience with team lead&lt;br&gt;- Number of team member managed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Technologies:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- ASP.NET&lt;br&gt;- C# and/or VB.NET (including ADO.Net)&lt;br&gt;- ASP&lt;br&gt;- HTML / DHTML / JavaScript&lt;br&gt;- SQL Server (TSQL)&lt;br&gt;- XML / XSLT / CSS&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft Visual Source Safe&lt;br&gt;- Assets: Microsoft's Content Management, Commerce or SharePoint servers; Java; CSS or COM&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Client Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Founded in 1995 as a software development and Internet hosting company, our client's focus is on innovative solutions that take advantage of the&lt;br&gt;Internet and Internet related technologies. They have an international&lt;br&gt;client base with customers throughout North America and Europe and have&lt;br&gt;become experts in the creation of multi-lingual software and Web Sites. They also create browser based, database driven business solutions and create and host innovative and interesting Web sites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Experience:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A MINIMUM OF 3 YEARS EXPERIENCE WITH .NET PROGRAMMING REQUIRED.&lt;br&gt;- Strong application development experience and broad exposure to web&lt;br&gt;application technologies (ASP.NET).&lt;br&gt;- Exposure to object oriented technologies is required and practical&lt;br&gt;experience implementing object-oriented systems is a benefit.&lt;br&gt;- The ability to isolate issues with strong debugging skills is highly&lt;br&gt;valued.&lt;br&gt;- Experience with / Exposure to: Conceptual Application Development, Object Oriented Concepts, .Net Framework Concepts, Multi-Tier Architecture, Project Life Cycle, Problem Solving / Debugging Techniques, and Development Best Practices.&lt;br&gt;- Assets would include experience with / exposure to: Enterprise Application Development, Time Management and Task Management Skills or Documentation / Technical Writing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal Attributes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Candidate should excel in self-directed environments and be able to&lt;br&gt;demonstrate strong problem solving skills.&lt;br&gt;- The ideal candidate will demonstrate understanding of enterprise project issues, knowledge of multi-tier architecture and be able to communicate principles of sound architecture and design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ruth Tan&lt;br&gt;Senior Account Manager&lt;br&gt;*****************************************&lt;br&gt;RJS ASSOCIATES INC.&lt;br&gt;(Tel) 416-291-4417 (Fax) 416-291-5819&lt;br&gt;Toll Free: 1-877-218-0218&lt;br&gt;e-mail: ruth@rjscanada.com&lt;br&gt;HR Solutions... SIMPLIFIED&lt;br&gt;www.rjscanada.com&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>10FAC890-2F22-414E-B2DE-8BF558B5053B</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-08-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>.NET Developer or Team Lead - PERM - Etobicoke</title>
</post>
