<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Mobile Applications Developer&lt;br&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;VTRAC Consulting Corporation&lt;br&gt;"Solutions for Growth"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please e-mail your resume as a MS-WORD document in confidence subject Mobile Developer, JOB Number: 2543, Attention: peterc@vtrac.com or call: (416) 366-2600 x 222.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Mobile Developer&lt;br&gt;Location: Entertainment District&lt;br&gt;Position Type: Permanent&lt;br&gt;Job ID: 2543&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;Developing new blackberry/iPhone/Android, Windows Mobile applications&lt;br&gt;Releasing new versions of applications, as new devices are released to the market&lt;br&gt;Enhancing application performance, memory use, application size, and usability&lt;br&gt;Completing projects on time in a proper manner&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required skills and experience:&lt;br&gt;Expert in either J2Me, Object C or C++, Visual Studio, Windows Mobile 6.1 and/or 6.5, Brew or Blackberry development&lt;br&gt;Additionally experience with either Android SDK, iPhone SDK, or Palm SDK would be a bonus&lt;br&gt;Must have at least 1 year experience knowing your way around and understanding what it takes to develop applications on the following platforms:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Blackberry, iPhone, Android&lt;br&gt;Understand what it takes to develop software for devices with much more limited resources than a typical desktop. You also know how to debug on remote devices, or understand what can and can't be done remotely.&lt;br&gt;Windows Mobile: You have experience developing apps on this platform and could tell us in detail why we should use C++ or C# when creating applications for Windows Mobile.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is not mandatory, but a plus.&lt;br&gt;Web Services: You know how to interface with various web services and understand technology like SOAP, XML-RPC, JSON, REST&lt;br&gt;C/C++: Pointers &amp; memory management are your friends.&lt;br&gt;Ability to work independently, take action and contribute new ideas required in a diverse, fast-paced, team environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all the candidates in advance. Only those candidates that are selected for interview will be contacted. For other exciting opportunities, please visit us at www.vtrac.com .</content>
    <postId>110168BE-528D-4FB7-A5F8-62443E299D72</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mobile Applications Developer</title>
</post>
