<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At BMO Financial Group, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potential. As one of North America's highly diversified financial services providers, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Java Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking for Senior Java Internet Developers to participate in a wide range of web-based projects to support strategic initiatives within various lines of business, throughout the Bank.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of core Java, API plus, J2EE APIs, JDBC, Servlets, JSPs, EJBs, XML, RDBC (Oracle), SQL and Websphere 4.0.&lt;br&gt;Good understanding of Object Oriented design and analysis Methodology (UML).&lt;br&gt;Previous experience developing websites and/or e-commerce applications within a business setting.&lt;br&gt;Experience with the full development life cycle and source control system.&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of C/C++ on the Sun Solaris platform is preferred, along with exposure to creating and managing Make files and shared libraries.&lt;br&gt;Must be able to work in a team environment, have good communication skills (written and verbal) and the ability to deal with a demanding client base in a fast-paced environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group thanks all applicants. We advise that only those who qualify for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At BMO Financial Group, we are committed to diversity and equitable opportunity for all individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: BGKMG01178&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group - BMO Groupe Financier&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>120B470F-62B7-42C5-9185-8D9ECED76952</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-26T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Java Developer, BMO Financial Group</title>
</post>
