<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Chihoan:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How are you doing? My name is Wilfred and I am a senior IT. Recruiter from Rosscam/Universal. Rosscam/Universal is an agency company which has been specializing in IT professional recruitment for more than 20 years. We have some very, very urgent job offering opportunities for permanent Senior Java/J2EE&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Programmer/Developer for MFX Farifax in Toronto.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This job is 50% development and 50 % product support (but no on-call support or anything extra ). The salary is around $70 K to 90 K base plus bonus.What is your expected salary range?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you know anybody who will be interested in the above job opportunities, could you please send me your or their resume (preferably with attachment in Word format) to my work email wshek@rosscam.com and also CC the email to my home email wilfredshek@rogers.com and give me a call to my office# or cell# or home# to discuss the details of the job AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Here attached is the job description for your reference. If you or you know anybody who will be interested, please kindly phone me, email me resume together with 4 to 6 lines describing your key experience and number of years such as&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Java 7 years, J2EE 5 years, Team Lead 3 years, Oracle, Ms-Sql, vb, vb.net, EJB, JSP,Unix, MQ Serires, LDAP n years, etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In case, other of my co-workers from Rosscam/Universal contact you, please kindly let them know that you are already dealing with me to avoid confusions and redundancies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks so much,&lt;br&gt;Have a wonderful day,&lt;br&gt;Best wishes and warmest regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yours sincerely,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wilfred Shek&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universal Rosscam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Tel: (416)405 8389 ext 124 (office time)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cell Tel: (416)388 5432 (anytime)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home Tel: (905)927 1511 (non-office, night time)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Email: wshek@rosscam.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home Email: wilfredshek@rogers.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visit us at www.rosscam.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1-866-405-8395&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>13AD4AFC-4884-49F7-BFB0-20A2A133C795</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Very, very urgent permanent Senior Java/J2EE Developer for MFX in Toronto</title>
</post>
