<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Terra Marketing Corp is a market place leader that delivers E-Commerce customer acquisition, product development, customer retention, and information measurement solutions. Our clients are market leaders and acknowledged as among the most trusted brand names.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a result in our clients' growth, opportunities exist for experienced Web Developers/ masters. Reporting directly to the Business Solutions Manager you will be empowered to maintain and develop online portals. The incumbents will be responsible to design, develop and support web applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Design and develop web applications (web pages, banners and other promotional requirements) based on pre-defined user requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Design and develop data interface components between existing applications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monitor web portals, forums, polls, banner and mail list administration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Act as a web master for the maintenance of large web sites and perform web-programming tasks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Understand online purchasing, online marketing of products etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Experience/ Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3+ years Strong experience with web applications in Internet/Online marketing environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online buying experience i.e.buying from Overture, Altavista&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong internet marketing skills (postings to websites etc.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to design and code HTML and Java Scripts for cross-browser compatibility.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Photoshop, Macromedia products (Dream Weaver, Flash, Home site), ASP, PHP is a must&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal Attributes:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must be a team player.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must have web master capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent organizational skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work to stringent deadlines in a fast paced environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to follow instructions and maintain meticulous attention to detail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Willing to take initiative and be creative and original.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must enjoy learning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company URL: www.terramc.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: Web&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Sonia Dhoofar&lt;br&gt;jobs@ipmktg.com&lt;br&gt;IP Marketing / IP Devco&lt;br&gt;67 Mowat Ave Suite # 440&lt;br&gt;Toronto&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>14F8F329-F6F5-44ED-8666-4E22E1A1AC7A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Master/ Developer</title>
</post>
