<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>stevenkim</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you for the inquiry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personally I feel that the overall job market is not so good,&lt;br&gt;especially the Sep. 11 incident chilled the job market in North America.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nevertheless there would be some companies still hiring.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, in an attempt to get more opinoins, I have contacted a&lt;br&gt;job placement agent and have a response and a part is quoted here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Quote -&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot; As far as SAP is concerned - we are working with a few clients that have a need for SAP people, however, the positions are team lead or project manager positions so the communication skills have to be very good. &lt;br&gt;Our clients are not necessarily looking for only North American experience but some experience in Canada or the US would be beneficial - even Europe is OK. &lt;br&gt;If you have a copy of this person's resume, I would like to take a look at it - it would be more easier for me to determine his qualifications. &lt;br&gt;-End quote-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope this is some help to you .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Hello,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I am considering immigration and looking for information about IT jobs.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I did some ERP implementation project in Accenture and my skill set includes SAP R/3 MM and PM.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I also have experiences in IT Strategy, and pure strategy work like industry analysis.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I would like to know how I can develop my career in Canada.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Are there many jobs available that suits me?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;How is ERP market in Canada?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I am afraid that I could not use ERP skills due to language barrier.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I would appreciate if you reply to me with any job information.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sung-Yun Jung &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;syjung@popsmail.com&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Hello Every one,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;I&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;went to that Brass Ring's recent Job Fair on June 18th and 19th&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;at Toronto Convention Center&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;There wasn't that much of participants from recruiter side even though &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;you had quite a number of job seekers.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;After Internet bubble burst,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;the paradigm in IT might have been changed.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Most recruiters are from manufacturing or financial related. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;I apolosize my mistyping ^.^ I can not help but to mis-type. ^.^;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Anyway,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; communication skill might be considered more important in recent&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;job search because financial and brick and motar compnaies usually want somebody &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;with industry knowledge-domain knowledge. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;For the skill set, they need C, C++ and UNIX more than ever. This is quite a paradigm &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;shift.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Mission-Critical enterprise application and system development expereince is &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;also valued (ERP, H/A, SAN and that type of thing)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Anyway, even for those system administors, specific package experience (such as SAP) &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;seems to be valued by employers.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Is there anybody who happened to have SAP or Oracle Financial related project &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;expereice? We might form a stduy group because getting SAP or Oracle app.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;project experience is die-hard to get regardless of places.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Even in Korea(I had 1 year contract in Korea upuntil alst month), SAP or Oracle App.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;project has been sustained, postphoned and canceled for last three years. This lack is &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;causing a lot of trouble in Korea like no Korean ERP consultant. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Anybody with enough of industry specific work process and BPR knowledge can be &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;trained as SAP or Oracle App. consultant.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I have very large collection of SAP ERP&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;books on consulting, BPR, pjt, implementation and etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;I even have ISP(IT Strategic Planning )consulting project with HP consulting Korea, &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;AT Kearny Korea and Gap Gemini Earnst and Young Korea.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;If interested, please contact me at cosmos@visto.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Thank yu,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Jay S. Ha &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>15071D3B-390E-465E-8D05-0E9628A8CC2C</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-11-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] [2001/06/24] About Job Fair on June 18th &amp; 19th at Front St. (작성자: Jay Ha)</title>
</post>
