<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Company: SOOLEY &amp; ASSOCIATES INC&lt;br&gt;Position: Mobile Content Manager&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada&lt;br&gt;Description: Title: Mobile Content Manager&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Skills: Review and edit video and audio content&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Type: Contract converts to Permanent&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Downtown &amp;#8211; Dot.com environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Content Manager is responsible for the reviewing and editing of video and audio content that is supplied by the clients Content Partners and reports directly to the Director of Media Operations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Planning and maintaining the presentation layer of product offerings using Content Management tools. * Maintain relationships with clients and suppliers. * Provide ongoing guidance and support to internal and external clients. * Test video and audio content for use on devices. * Transcode content from source video and audio formats to required formats for consumption by devices. * Certify devices to support clients products and services. * Analyze and troubleshoot issues related to clients platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* General knowledge of video and audio signal processing, encoding and formats * Strong understanding of audio and video codecs. * Experience working within development and production environments. * Basic understanding of the software development life cycle. * Excellent interpersonal and customer service skills with the ability to function effectively in a team environment. * Excellent written and verbal communication skills. * Strong analytical skills along with the ability to prioritize tasks and make decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must be a current resident of Canada to apply for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are not a Canadian citizen or a permanent resident, you will need an employment authorization before you begin to work or continue working in Canada.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience Required: yes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paid or Volunteer: paid&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Category:&lt;br&gt;Information Technology&lt;br&gt;Data &amp; Info Services&lt;br&gt;IT/MIS &lt;br&gt;Internet/New Media&lt;br&gt;Job Type(s):&lt;br&gt;Full Time &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Posted by: &lt;br&gt;SOOLEY &amp; ASSOCIATES INC</content>
    <postId>15227DEF-55A8-45CC-B33F-01D96F37C748</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mobile Content Manager</title>
</post>
