<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Web Development Administrator &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Toronto Symphony is looking for a new Web Development Administrator to join their dynamic marketing team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you&amp;#47981;e got a web marketing and design background, with a passion for the arts and classical music, this position could be for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job responsibilities include maintaining and further developing 3 TSO websites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#47968;l be a key participant in the marketing team, reporting to the Marketing Director, further developing and implementing on-line marketing initiatives that play an integral role in the daily functioning of the TSO.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#47968;l be required to create effective permission-based e-marketing pieces that are aligned with the style, strategy and brand of the TSO marketing campaign.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You&amp;#47968;l be able to effectively manage projects, meet deadlines, and work to budget.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Marketing background&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Must be skilled in converging graphic design into web design.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Excellent Illustrator, Photoshop &amp; Dreamweaver skills mandatory&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Some Flash required&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Demonstrated knowledge of HTML, JAVA and other associated programs&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; An understanding of databases&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Ready to hit the ground running in a dynamic marketing department&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Demonstrated familiarity with fonts and font usage&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Demonstrated understanding of colour, graphics and layout&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Proficiency with image optimization, including designing for optimum download time based on your knowledge of HTML&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Understanding of FTP protocol&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Able to manage development projects and work with web development partners&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The website is a reflection of the TSO both in its marketing and as a cultural institution. It plays a key and integrated role in its marketing incorporating the marketing strategy and promoting the brand by incorporating the voice, design, and current advertising campaign. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you share this vision and have the skills...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Send URL of your online portfolio and CV to webmaster@tso.ca. Type Web Developer in the subject heading. If you have additional comments, that relate to the job description, add them in your email. Your portfolio should include examples of all required skills and experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Due to the large number of responses only those selected for an interview will be contacted. No phone calls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;mforrester@tso.ca&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>16A88856-97C8-4A8A-84BD-CAFE1E35CD48</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Development Administrator</title>
</post>
