<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Temporary full time position to March 31, 2003.&lt;br&gt;The position is located within the following governmental organization(s): Department of the Environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALARY: $50,663 to $60,541 per annum&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANGUAGE: English essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL LANGUAGES: USEFUL INFORMATION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO CAN APPLY: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Persons residing or employed in the Greater Toronto Area, bounded in the East and including Oshawa, in the North by the including Newmarket, in the West by and including Oakville.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDUCATION: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graduation with a degree from a recognized university with acceptable specialization in computer science, engineering or mathematics. &lt;br&gt;EXPERIENCE: &lt;br&gt;Experience in System Analysis and Design of software; &lt;br&gt;Programming applications based upon the C programming language and C++ or Java object-oriented programming language on Linux/UNIX-based and MS-Windows-based environment; &lt;br&gt;Experience in at least one of the following, preference will be given to candidates with both:Design and development of Client-Server applications or Design and development of Graphical User Interfaces. &lt;br&gt;ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS / COMMENTS: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security: An enhanced reliability check is required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please Note: The required qualifications for the following factors: &lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;Knowledge\\&amp;quot;,\\&amp;quot;Ability\\&amp;quot; and \\&amp;quot;Personal Suitability\\&amp;quot; that are listed in the attached &lt;br&gt;Statement of Qualifications are compensatory and will be evaluated globally by factor. &lt;br&gt;A global pass mark will be established for each of these factors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REFERENCE NUMBER: DOE13338GZ05&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLOSING DATE: September 10, 2002&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates who meet the above criteria will also be assessed against the Statement of Qualifications for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you apply online, DO NOT send a duplicate by fax or regular mail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note: If you are applying by fax or by regular mail, we would ask that you fill out form PSC 3391, \\&amp;quot;Application for Employment\\&amp;quot;. If you are unable to obtain a copy of this form, you must clearly indicate your citizenship as well as the title and reference number of the position for which you are applying. Your resume must demonstrate that you meet all of the above mentioned requirements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates with foreign educational credentials are required to provide proof of Canadian equivalency. You may consult The Canadian Information Centre for International Credentials at http://www.cicic.ca for further information. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please clearly indicate your citizenship. Preference will be given to Canadian citizens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all those who apply. Only those selected for further consideration will be contacted. As the Public Service of Canada promotes Employment Equity, we also encourage candidates to voluntarily self-identify if they are an Aboriginal person, a member of a visible minority group or a person with a disability. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public Service Commission of Canada&lt;br&gt;1 Front Street West,&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;M5J 2X5&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAX: (416) 973-1883&lt;br&gt; </content>
    <postId>16B7D999-D786-46A3-A349-8DE4D00D646A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SYSTEMS ANALYST/PROGRAMMER</title>
</post>
