<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Graphic Designer/Web Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are growing e-learning and web development company located in Markham, Ontario (Toronto region) and are currently seeking a Graphic Arts Designer/Web developer. This person needs to demonstrate an excitement about being the key creative contributor to a variety of synchronous projects. Thus making tea&amp;quok and communication a critical requirement. Candidates should have a broad creative flair with a strong web-based graphics background. Presentation of professional examples, including an online portfolio, will be required for consideration. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- 2+ years of professional experience&lt;br&gt;- A college degree or professional equivalent&lt;br&gt;- Artistic aptitude. Ability to generate concepts that attract and engage.&lt;br&gt;- Knows the principles of project planning, layout, and storyboarding with the flexibility required to achieve the highest quality while maintaining deadlines and budget. and placement of copy and logos. &lt;br&gt;- Pays attention to detail. Approaches work in a meticulous and thorough manner. Is flexible and can adjust to shifting priorities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills and willingness to give and take direction&lt;br&gt;Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, &lt;br&gt;Flash 5.0 and 6.0 action script, Swish,&lt;br&gt;Strong understanding of communication between Flash, HTML and back-end databases&lt;br&gt;Understanding browser / Internet server settings and implications of a variety of bandwidth environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preferred Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Javascript and HTML&lt;br&gt;Experience with XML, ASP, SQL, PHP&lt;br&gt;Experience in audio editing with Cool Edit or similar&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with Flash animation &lt;br&gt;Experience with streaming media&lt;br&gt;Experience with 3D software&lt;br&gt;Experience in instructional design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Additional duties include the design and development of logos, other branding materials as needed, and generating web site content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A full benefits program will be part of the compensation package.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please forward a resume, salary requirements, cover letter and links to any online examples to chevronsolutions@rogers.com .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: groct2702&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;chevronsolutions@rogers.com&lt;br&gt;Markham/Richmond Hill Ontario&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>16DA00E5-438C-4499-9A2C-5D18A6F065A0</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-10-30T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Graphic Designer/Web Developer</title>
</post>
