<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>저에게 온 메인프래임에관한 직장을 올립니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The position below is currently available through Procom. If you meet the qualifications and are interested in this opportunity please apply as per the instructions below. Please note, this automated email has been sent to you as the result of a successful keyword search on your resume within our database. Please use discretion by only applying to positions that best suit your qualifications. If you wish to remove yourself from future mailings, please click the link supplied below. &lt;br&gt;Position: IT Analyst - Mainframe &lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills: IMS, DB2, COBOL, JCL, MQ Series &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice-to-Have Skills: &lt;br&gt;Location: Mississauga &lt;br&gt;Duration: 1 Year &lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary: $27-$32/hr. &lt;br&gt;Start Date: April 1, 2005 &lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking for a customer focused contractor with strong mainframe skills and financial services background. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;. is responsible for building and maintaining server and host test environments for development projects. &lt;br&gt;. provides support to QA, developers and the business during the testing phases of a project. &lt;br&gt;. must have good understanding of many banking applications and complete knowledge of the technical test environment. &lt;br&gt;. is responsible for the bank&amp;#54475; test environment assisting with upgrades to mainframe components, trouble shooting issues and communicating information to developers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications, Competences, Accreditations &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will possess to following: &lt;br&gt;. Strong organizational and time management skills along with the ability to multitask effectively and meet deadlines &lt;br&gt;. Good communications both verbal and written are necessary to effectively interact with co-workers and clients across two campuses &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Skills: &lt;br&gt;. In-depth Knowledge of the mainframe including: IMS, DB/DC, DB2, COBOL, JCL, MQ, etc &lt;br&gt;. Good understanding of a variety of Banking Applications &lt;br&gt;. 3 to 5 years of mainframe experience &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;담당자: RonC@procom.ca&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The position below is currently available through Procom. If you meet the qualifications and are interested in this opportunity please apply as per the instructions below. Please note, this automated email has been sent to you as the result of a successful keyword search on your resume within our database. Please use discretion by only applying to positions that best suit your qualifications. If you wish to remove yourself from future mailings, please click the link supplied below. &lt;br&gt;Position: PL/1 Developer (Securities) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills: PL/1 , Cics , DB2 , MQ Series &lt;br&gt;Securities industry experience (clearing or account transfer, etc) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto &lt;br&gt;Duration: 6 Month Contract to a year &lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary: &lt;br&gt;Start Date: ASAP &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;담당자:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Peter Kalafatis &lt;br&gt;peterk@procom.ca &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>1A111B5C-EADA-454E-B1D1-7A48DCF0E197</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-04-01T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mainframe</title>
</post>
