<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Java Developers - T57530,&lt;br&gt;PROCOM SERVICE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 2800 consultants on assignment and place hundreds of people in permanent positions annually. For over 30 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our candidates. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and candidates consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Java Developers&lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills: None Specified&lt;br&gt;Nice-to-Have Skills: None Specified&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto&lt;br&gt;Duration: 3 Months&lt;br&gt;Start Date: March 29, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking for several intermediate to senior Java developers with the following background:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Hands on WebSphere Application Server WAS 6.1/RAD 7 platform with Clear Case &lt;br&gt;- object-oriented programming and object-oriented design practices and principles &lt;br&gt;- Strong Java/J2EE &lt;br&gt;- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSP, servlets, EJB, Struts, and JDBC &lt;br&gt;- Experience in Web Services or other back end integration technologies (MQ, ESB, etc.) &lt;br&gt;- web application performance and security coding practices &lt;br&gt;- Oracle 11g database tables and SQL queries (will consider strong 10g)&lt;br&gt;- Working knowledge of Web 2.0 technologies (AJAX, Flash etc.) would be an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;financial industry experience nice to have &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROCOM SERVICES&lt;br&gt;A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 2800 consultants on assignment and place hundreds of people in permanent positions annually. For over 30 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our candidates. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and candidates consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES are committed to employment equity and make every attempt to allow equal representation for all within the workplace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please submit your most recent resume online by clicking "Apply Online" below. meghayud@procom.ca</content>
    <postId>1A972D3E-5E96-4D88-9561-23C5B527282C</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developers - T57530,(Agent)</title>
</post>
