<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>K. Kwon</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;From: "Kerriann Miller-Kreuz" &amp;lt;kmiller-kreuz@hollisterinc.com&amp;gt; | This is spam | Add to Address Book &lt;br&gt;To: kwon96@yahoo.com &lt;br&gt;Subject: Contract Opportunity...Do you know anyone? &lt;br&gt;Date: Tue, 30 Sep 2003 10:13:29 -0400 &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hello, &lt;br&gt;My name is Kerriann Miller-Kreuz. I am a recruiter with Hollister, a Boston, MA based staffing agency. I am doing a search for one of my clients in MA who is looking for a Contract Middleware developer.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The key skills needed are strong C++ development and Tuxedo Middleware development experience.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I was doing a search on the internet and I came across your name. I'm not sure if you're looking for a new position or if the job description below would be something of interest, but please take a look and let me know what you think. If the position is not a fit but you know someone who might be interested any referrals would be greatly appreciated. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks, &lt;br&gt;Kerriann &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Job Purpose: &lt;br&gt;Join a fast-paced software engineering team developing a next generation distributed middleware product that bridges disparate middleware's including CORBA, MQ-Series, Tibco, Tuxedo and Web Services. Work as a member of the transports team developing adapters to one or more of these middleware systems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;Responsible for developing the Tuxedo transport adapter to the system described above. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience and Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solid C++ programming skills with a &lt;br&gt;Minimum of 5 years experience with and understanding of Tuxedo middleware products. &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of distributed systems and middleware. &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of SOAP, HTTP, XML, Web Services, CORBA and Java are a plus &lt;br&gt;BS degree in CS, EE, or equivalent is required. &lt;br&gt;MS degree with emphasis in operating systems, distributed systems, or real-time systems is a plus. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kerriann Miller-Kreuz &lt;br&gt;Senior Consultant &lt;br&gt;Technology Division &lt;br&gt;Hollister &lt;br&gt;31 Milk Street, 6th Floor/Boston, MA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;02109 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;617.654.0225 &lt;br&gt;mailto:kmiller@hollisterinc.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>1B91C312-D0B5-456F-9C26-724BFA50178F</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-10-01T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Middleware developer</title>
</post>
