<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>신덕현</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>임정숙</author>
            <date>2003-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>추가 목록 &lt;a href=http://www.newmedialinks.com/ target=_blank&gt;http://www.newmedialinks.com/&lt;/a&gt;</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>임정숙</author>
            <date>2003-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>more &lt;a href=http://www.thinkpath.com/ target=_blank&gt;http://www.thinkpath.com/&lt;/a&gt;</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>Sun Park</author>
            <date>2003-06-24T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>more sites: www.eagleonline.com and www.infotek-consulting.com</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[사이트 목록]&lt;br&gt;http://www.procom.ca/&lt;br&gt;http://www.isteq.com/ (한국인이 경영)&lt;br&gt;http://www.dgsinfo.com/&lt;br&gt;http://www.xycorp.com/&lt;br&gt;http://www.isgjobs.com/en/&lt;br&gt;http://www.globalrecruit.com/&lt;br&gt;http://www.w5.net - James Lee(한국인 1.5세)를 찾으세요&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[사이트 보충설명]&lt;br&gt;http://www.procom.ca/&lt;br&gt;PROCOM has an enviable reputation among the IT consulting community as \\&amp;quot;The Contractors Company\\&amp;quot;. For over 20 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our contractors in a fair and ethical manner.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Information Technology is our specialty and we have a solid understanding of the market across Canada, as well as in the US. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ranking as the 6th largest IT Professional Services firm in Canada (Financial Post, March 1999) is evidence of our success.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We are a performance-based company, holding the status as the largest Canadian contracting firm with a growing market share in the US.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; PROCOM currently represents over 1500 contractors on assignment throughout North America. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.isteq.com/&lt;br&gt;- 한국인이 경영하는 Agent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.dgsinfo.com/&lt;br&gt;Ajilon Canada has been providing Information Technology staffing solutions since 1978. We have worked with thousands of the most talented IT professionals in Canada and have developed lasting business relationships with clients across the country. &lt;br&gt;Today we are the best IT staffing firm in the industry. &lt;br&gt;Building on our ability to recruit technical talent, we have extended our services to include Technology-based Professional Services including Management Consulting, e-Business Solutions and Software Quality Assurance and Testing. &lt;br&gt;Our Permanent and Contract Staffing Solutions help clients find the technical expertise they require.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.xycorp.com/&lt;br&gt;Xycorp Inc., Established in 1974, places experienced IT Professionals looking for permanent or contract positions in all operating system environments. As a client seeking IT expertise Xycorp searches the globe on your behalf to find the right individuals to match your skills and cultural requirements. As an IT Professional, whether you currently live in Canada or aboad, finding the right job with the right company and living in a place you and your family really love is very important. We invite you to check out our web-site and call us today. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.isgjobs.com/en/&lt;br&gt;Company Overview: &lt;br&gt;Computer Horizons ISG is a subsidiary of Computer Horizons Corp., founded in 1969 and headquartered in Mountain Lakes, New Jersey. We are a global organization with over 50 offices worldwide, including Canada, the United States, the United Kingdom and Germany, and are ideally positioned to serve the needs of clients and IT professionals in all locations around the world. &lt;br&gt;Computer Horizons Corp. (CHC) became a publicly held corporation in 1972 (NASDAQ: CHRZ). Approximately 30 million shares are currently outstanding. Complete financials, including SEC forms 10K and 10-Q are available upon request. Revenues in 1999 were US$538 million, making CHC one of the largest Information Technology service firms in North America. CHC is financially sound and has earned and maintained an AAA1 rating from Dun &amp; Bradstreet. &lt;br&gt;CHC has been repeatedly recognized by such leading publications as FORBES, Integration Age, Business Week, and Business Software Review, and identified as one of the best-managed companies in America. In September 1999, CHC was named to Deloitte &amp; Touche's prestigious \\&amp;quot;Fast 50\\&amp;quot; Program as a result of the company's increase in revenues of 198 percent over the five-year period between 1994 to 1998. The \\&amp;quot;Fast 50\\&amp;quot; program is a ranking of the 50 fastest growing technology companies in North America. &lt;br&gt;As part of Computer Horizons ISG's expanding efforts to serve customers more effectively, we currently have offices in Calgary, Ottawa, Toronto and Vancouver with key additions planned in Montreal and Halifax. &lt;br&gt;Since commencing operations in Canada in 1990, Computer Horizons ISG's main focus has been the provision of Information Technology professionals for client organizations. At Computer Horizons ISG, we specialize only in IT staffing and eBusiness Solutions. This specialization has allowed Computer Horizons ISG to become one of the largest, most respected IT staffing and solutions firms in the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.globalrecruit.com/&lt;br&gt;With more than ten years of experience, GCG has a proven track record and a long list of established clients &amp;#8212;key corporations, both large and small, that understand our dedication to their business and our crucial role in their successes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>1C281253-7D80-4D8B-899A-D4891447A7E8</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-09-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>취업대행회사(Agent) 모음</title>
</post>
