<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Details&lt;br&gt;Dexterra Sybex Mobile Developer &lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Date Posted: March 17, 2010&lt;br&gt;Job ID: 11851&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Bay Street client is currently seeking one (1) Dexterra / AMT-Sybex Mobile Application Developer. This is a contract opportunity slated to begin in April, and is projected to be one (1) year in length.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will be responsible for:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assisting the line of business in developing mobile applications using the new enterprise mobile solution;&lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Project Manager for the Mobile IT projects, this position will translate the business requirements from the business primes and will convert them into design documents; and,&lt;br&gt;Developing mobile applications that are fully integrated with the enterprise service bus.&lt;br&gt;Skills and Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The qualified candidate must have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six plus (6+) years of technical experience in an IT environment as a Business Analyst and Developer;&lt;br&gt;An understanding of the system development lifecycle policies and procedures;&lt;br&gt;A demonstrated ability to communicate and document design of solutions;&lt;br&gt;The ability to work in a diversified environment with little supervision and meet tight deadlines;&lt;br&gt;Experience with the following technologies:&lt;br&gt;Java&lt;br&gt;Visual Studio&lt;br&gt;VB.Net and/or C#&lt;br&gt;Microsoft SQL Server&lt;br&gt;WebServices / BEA service bus;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of the Dexterra and/or AMT-Sybex tool kit is an asset; and,&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of SAP integration is also an asset.&lt;br&gt;Don't miss out on this opportunity, apply on-line today!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants for their interest; however, only candidates under consideration will be contacted.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please note that your application does not signify the beginning of employment with Eagle and that employment with Eagle will only commence when placed on an assignment as a temporary employee of Eagle.</content>
    <postId>1CEF6039-A77A-48E3-A41A-D83B69ED8A44</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Dexterra Sybex Mobile Developer-Eagle Professional</title>
</post>
