<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이상훈</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>권칠환</author>
            <date>2009-03-16T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Thank you for your reply!!!!</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Job Description을 첨부합니다. 참고하시기 바랍니다.&lt;br&gt;일단 1년 Temporary로 구인 광고가 나간 걸로 알고 있습니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;회사는 South West Community Care Access Centre입니다.&lt;br&gt;(3월 19일까지 지원 마감입니다.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Title: Senior Developer, Business Solutions&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Status: Temporary Full Time &lt;br&gt;Reports To: Regional Manager, Business Solutions &lt;br&gt;Department: Corporate Services &lt;br&gt;Non-Union or Union: Non-Union &lt;br&gt;Posting Date: 3/13/2009 &lt;br&gt;Application Deadline: 3/19/2009 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Summary &lt;br&gt;This is a temporary full time Senior Developer/Coder, Business Solutions position for approximately one (1) year with a flexible home office location. Reporting to Regional Managers, Corporate Services, with primary accountability to the Regional Manager, Business Solutions. The Senior Developer, Business Solutions is responsible for research, architecture, design, development and coding Information Technology applications for the SW CCAC. This role provides support to the Regional Managers in all areas of technological development and includes support for a centralized Service Desk serving the Head Office, branch and satellite offices within the SW CCAC. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum degree or diploma from a recognized University or Community College or relevant work experience equivalent.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Responsible for architecture, design, code/development, implementation and support of new technologies. &lt;br&gt;Perform supervisory duties as assigned.&lt;br&gt;Capability to share technical strengths and identify/improve any technical weaknesses. &lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to isolate and identify the source of technological issues.&lt;br&gt;Excellent communication and interpersonal skills with team members. &lt;br&gt;Capacity to work independently with minimal supervision and also effectively as part of a team. Ability to multitask and prioritize. &lt;br&gt;Talent to perform job functions under stress and pressure as you adapt quickly to new technologies and change. &lt;br&gt;Desire to contribute to new and improved processes.&lt;br&gt;Minimum 2 years or relevant experience or equivalent using Microsoft SQL Server, Net Framework, Visual Studio, Team Foundation Server, IIS, and ASP.Net.&lt;br&gt;Ability to prioritize demands and deliver projects on a timely basis.&lt;br&gt;Ability to work in a relatively unstructured busy environment with rapidly changing priorities essential.&lt;br&gt;Strong problem-solving and trouble-shooting skills. &lt;br&gt;Willingness to travel.&lt;br&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;많은 지원 바라겠습니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;어느 정도의 개발 능력을 가진분을 찾는지요?&lt;br&gt;- 개발 능력은 뛰어날 수록 좋겠지요. 최소한 .NET framework를 이용한 웹 애플리케이션 개발 경험은 있어야 할 것으로 생각합니다. 특히 CSLA.NET이나 기타 엔터프라이즈 레벨 아키텍처에 경험이 있으면 일하기가 수월하실겁니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;어느 정도의 급여를 회사는 생각하는지요?&lt;br&gt;- 이건 제가 답변 드릴 수는 없구요.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;회사에서 제공하는 benefit package는 어떤 건지도 궁금하구요?&lt;br&gt;- 기본적인 베니핏은 다 제공되는 것 같구요. 템포러리의 경우는 어떻게 되는지는 잘 모르겠지만, 일반적인 경우와 유사할 것이라 생각됩니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;회사에서 일하는 환경(각박하다, 뭐, 여유있다)..등등...&lt;br&gt;- 여유있습니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;뭘 하는 회사인지 궁금하네요 (회사 사이트라도 알면 볼수 있을거 같은데요).&lt;br&gt;- Health care organization입니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;리크루트가 올린게 아니라, 본인이 다니는 직장이라서 더 자세한걸 올릴수 있다고 생각했기에 이렇게 질문을 드립니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;아마 다른분들도 비슷한 질문을 가지고 있을거라 생각됩니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;다름이 아니라, 저희 팀에서 .NET 개발자를 찾습니다. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;기본적인 스펙은 다음과 같습니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;- .NET 3.5&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;- ASP.NET, C# in Visual Studio 2008&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;- SQL Server 2008, (Windows Server 2003/2008 R2)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;- Visual Studio Team System&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;- CSLA.NET, (LINQ)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;위치는 Stratford, ON 입니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;메일로 연락주시기 바랍니다. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;leeksh_at_gmail_dot_com&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>1D7DDCFA-5C3C-45FD-BA3E-F8BEBC47E385</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] 질문?</title>
</post>
