<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-Consultant - Toronto &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;FAME specializes in the delivery of historical data management products and services for the world's financial, energy, and public sector markets. Recognized industry-wide as a leader in time-series data management for quantitative and economic analysts and risk management and research professionals since 1982, we have provided the financial sector with a powerful database management system for data storage, retrieval, analysis and distribution. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAME is currently looking for an exceptional software developer with good communication skills and experience in the financial industry to work in a fast-paced, dynamic and challenging environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;Applicants for this position should possess the following qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A degree in Computer Science, Mathematics, Engineering, Finance or Economics&lt;br&gt;- Full life cycle development experience&lt;br&gt;- Object-oriented design and development experience in Java and C++ on UNIX &amp; Windows platforms&lt;br&gt;- Database design (Sybase or Oracle) experience&lt;br&gt;- Perl and other UNIX shell scripting experience&lt;br&gt;- Experience in the financial industry&lt;br&gt;- Good communication skills - verbal &amp; written&lt;br&gt;- Ability to get up to speed quickly in a changing technical environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following will be a definite plus:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Object-oriented analysis and design expertise using UML and Rational Rose&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you wish to pursue a career with us, please contact Email: klila@fame.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;klila@fame.com&lt;br&gt;FAME Information Services, Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>1E5CE56B-2EBD-4CA1-A195-81A7AC581029</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-Consultant - Toronto</title>
</post>
