<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Dear Chil-Hoan:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope all is well with you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My name is Jason Park, an associate with Pacific Bridge, Inc. (PBI). As you may know, PBI is a recruiting company focused on placing bilingual/bicultural candidates in excellent jobs in Asia (www.pacificbridge.com).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am contacting you because our database lists you as a Korean speaker.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Our client, a leading manufacturer and supplier of battery separators for rechargeable lithium batteries is currently seeking an Account Manager for their office in Seoul, Korea.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The job description is listed below and can also be accessed at http://www.pacificbridge.com/job/html/10284.htm.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Remuneration for this position will be around US$100K.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are qualified for this position, please email your resume and cover letter to jasonpark@pacificbridge.com or fax them to 301-469-3409. If you know of an individual who would be interested in this position, please feel free to forward this email to them.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks and best regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Park&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recruiting Associate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pacific Bridge, Inc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;jasonpark@pacificbridge.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Title: Account Manager&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Seoul, South Korea&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Languages: Korean, English&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company Profile:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client is a leading manufacturer and supplier of battery separators for rechargeable lithium batteries.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;They are currently seeking an Account Manager for Korea.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The position will be located in Seoul and will report to the Vice President of Sales located in the US. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has manufacturing facilities in the US and China serving global markets, with Sales Offices in Japan, Korea and China.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The company employs highly skilled technical and business professionals to drive technology and business development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Formulate account strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Develop sustainable supply positions with major Korean Li-2 battery accounts (Samsung, LG)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Develop and maintain relationships with customers’ key decision makers and organizational leadership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Manage customer accounts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Develop and achieve annual sales budget, including customer mix, product mix, pricing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Negotiate price/volume supply contracts and monitor price/value of the company’s products vs. competition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Provide regular reports on sales activities and forecasts (revenue, product mix).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; International travel to headquarters in the US (1 &amp;#8211; 2 times per year).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Provide inputs on new product development, marketing and product positioning plans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4-year degree in a technical field.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 10 plus years of sales experience in technical value added sales, preferably in battery, electronics or electrochemical industries.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Must have key account experience with large major Korean chaebols (Samsung, LG, Hyundai, etc.) or large multi-national accounts.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Must be able to develop account strategies and plans, forecast sales and negotiate contracts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Must be fluent in the Korean language and have good English language capability (Writing, Reading, Listening &amp; Speaking).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Japanese language capability (basic level) is preferred.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Needs knowledge of Korean Customs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To Apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send your resume and cover letter to Jason Park at jasonpark@pacificbridge.com.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;No phone calls please.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>1E8A27F4-0F8E-482C-9792-25DE0026414D</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-05-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Account Manager position for Seoul</title>
</post>
