<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Systems Analyst, Information Technology Services Department&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Toronto Transit Commission, we are proud to be recognized as one of Canada&amp;#47977; Top 100 Employers. We place a high value on establishing a workplace where people are challenged and respected everyday, and we keep Toronto moving with a dedication to service, safety and convenience that is unparalleled in our industry. Explore this exciting opportunity and get your career on track today!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using your skills in programming languages and data processing techniques, you will establish the technical and economic feasibility of proposed administrative or technical applications. This entails formulating statements of business systems requirements, designing, developing and testing sub-systems, and resolving operational problems encountered in production systems. Your post-secondary education in a Computer Science, Business Administration or related discipline is complemented by your good knowledge of minimum 3 years application development and maintenance projects experience. Programming skill includes PL/I, COBOL, CICS preferable in DOS/VSE mainframe environment and/or experience in VB, MS SQL, Crystal Report and Oracle is a definite asset. $56.34K - $70.45K&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TTC offers competitive wages, comprehensive benefits, and rewarding opportunities to apply yourself in an environment that values those who go the extra mile to serve our fellow citizens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information on this position and other opportunities, please visit our website. www.ttc.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To respond, please apply online by August 21, 2002, quoting Ref.# 5108-MN. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Committed to the principles of employment equity, the TTC encourages applications from Aboriginal people, people with disabilities, racial minorities, and women. We thank all applicants for their interest, but advise that only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Toronto Transit Commission&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>24B214EE-5EAC-4B5E-9748-CC057202ECBA</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-01T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Information Technology Services Department</title>
</post>
