<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Infosys Technologies Ltd. (NASDAQ: INFY) is a leader in providing IT consulting and best of breed software solutions to the finest global organizations. We’re renowned throughout the world for being able to leverage existing knowledge and develop new, high impact, and exciting business solutions. These solutions include everything from E-commerce to supply chain management to customer relationship management for a variety of industry leaders. We currently have openings for Project Leads at our Toronto Global Development Center. So if you’re passionate about working with bleeding-edge Internet technologies, we’d love to see your resume.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities Include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Manage one or multiple projects. &lt;br&gt;· Resource planning/allocation, needs analysis.&lt;br&gt;· Respond to RFI/RFPs, proposal preparation, and escalation path for project related issues within the projects.&lt;br&gt;· Project planning, scheduling, and change management. &lt;br&gt;· Guiding the team or teams on technical issues to achieve overall development objectives.&lt;br&gt;· Ensuring a high level of team morale at all times.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· 6-10 years of software development experience with 2-4 years in managing large projects (6-10 developers) end to end.&lt;br&gt;· Experience in front ending with customers is a must. &lt;br&gt;· Experience in open systems and/or Internet based technologies projects such as such as Microsoft or Java based architectures.&lt;br&gt;· Familiar with Object Oriented (OO) methodologies, &amp; Unified Modeling Language (UML) Software Development Processes, as well as quality processes.&lt;br&gt;· Graduate in Computer Science or Engineering, or Masters in Computer Science.&lt;br&gt;· Possess Strong leadership and teamwork qualities.&lt;br&gt;· Excellent communication skills (both verbal and written).&lt;br&gt;· Able to travel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We work in a fast paced, flexible, and professional environment with a supportive work culture that rewards initiative and performance. This position offers great scope for growth and independent functioning, while contributing to the crucial initiative of the company. Compensation and benefits are driven by qualifications &amp; experience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please include the reference code: PL-TOR-0902&lt;br&gt;Please visit www.infosys.com for more information on Infosys.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: PL-TOR-0902&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers.canada@infy.com&lt;br&gt;Infosys Technologies, Ltd.&lt;br&gt;5140 Yonge Street, Suite 1400&lt;br&gt;Toronto Ontario M6P 1E3&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>26429FF8-84AA-4736-9BB7-96262254C853</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>North York-Project Lead</title>
</post>
