<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Toronto Area - Downtown, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;We are currently recruiting mainframe resources to join our organization on a full time permanent basis. The opportunities will be located in Waterloo, Ontario.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a consultant within CGI, you will be based on client site delivering high quality solutions based on our client business objectives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking for Senior Mainframe Systems Analysts and Senior Mainframe Programmer Analysts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ideal candidate will possess a bachelors degree in Computer Science or Information Systems. You must have 6+ years of Development and/or Systems experience in a Mainframe environment using COBOL, DB2, JCL, extensive experience in application testing and UAT with a strong knowledge of Software development methodology. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applicants must have excellent communication and presentation skills. Ability to work in a consulting environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration, and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join a winning team. CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration, and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start day one and includes a minimum of 3 weeks vacation, profit sharing and a stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cobol&lt;br&gt;JCL&lt;br&gt;CICS&lt;br&gt;DB2&lt;br&gt;Testing&lt;br&gt;System Analysis&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>2C498C95-2836-4E5D-8EF6-733B3E621C48</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>FUTURE- Mainframe P/A and S/A</title>
</post>
