<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This is a position within the&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Distributed Systems team. As part of a group of highly skilled individuals, you will be responsible for all aspects of the administration of the distributed UNIX and Linux environment consisting mainly of Sun Solaris,Redhat Linux and some HP-UX servers. &lt;br&gt;Your duties will include a wide variety of day-to-day administration activities as well as project participation including: Maintenance, performance and capacity planning/monitoring, availability monitoring of administered systems, maintaining establish baselines and reporting on variances. &lt;br&gt;Third level technical support for operating systems and related systems software (including 7/24 pager support). &lt;br&gt;Working with the systems management team and with systems management architects to develop a systems management infrastructure capable of delivering operable distributed systems. Participating as part of the project team to install, test and document new servers/software. &lt;br&gt;Provide implementation support throughout all phases of the project. Assisting with the preparation and maintenance of systems design documentation. &lt;br&gt;Providing research and development to ensure that the systems infrastructure is well positioned to support current and emerging distributed systems solutions. &lt;br&gt;Communication with application developers and systems integrators, outlining the distributed systems engineering standards. &lt;br&gt;Maintenance of systems administration documentation outlining the current systems administration policies and practices as applied to the administered system. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fluency in UNIX/Linux scripting (Perl, Korn Shell, Bourne Shell) and the ability to design and write operating system and platform utilities. &lt;br&gt;Expert technical knowledge of Linux System Administration. &lt;br&gt;Senior technical understanding of Solaris and Enterprise class servers &lt;br&gt;Hands-on experience with one or more of Veritas suite of products, Oracle Strong TCP/IP internetworking knowledge is a must. &lt;br&gt;Hands-on experience with various SAN technologies that include Brocade Switches and Hitachi disk arrays is essential. Excellent technical documentation skills. &lt;br&gt;Proactive approach to system maintenance and problem avoidance. Demonstrated problem solving skills. &lt;br&gt;A well-developed understanding of the need for operational policies and procedures. &lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to be an active contributor in a team work environment and be willing to take on problem ownership within the team. &lt;br&gt;Excellent communication, organizational and teamwork skills. &lt;br&gt;The ability to work under pressure and tight deadlines. &lt;br&gt;Strong, demonstrated team leadership skills, willing to mentor team members. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This role will initially be located in the Toronto office, but may eventually be relocated to their Markham office. &lt;br&gt;Rotation between the two offices is required. &lt;br&gt;This position will require the incumbent to work non-traditional work hours. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For example, noon until 8:30 PM. Start times may vary and the incumbent will need to be flexible in order to support business needs &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you feel you have the qualifications for this role or know of anyone who does, Please forward a resume.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you &lt;br&gt;Tiffany Peterson&lt;br&gt;Sr. account manager&lt;br&gt;www.systegra.ca&lt;br&gt;tiffany@systegra.ca</content>
    <postId>2D368559-6B5F-43DF-9D95-E1EBBB604693</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-04-01T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Unix Adminisrtator - permamnent - Toronto</title>
</post>
