<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Number - J0603-0361 - Full Time&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Title Java Developer-FX &lt;br&gt;Category Information Technology &lt;br&gt;City Toronto, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;Job Location Toronto &lt;br&gt;Posting Date (dd/mm/yyyy) 12/06/2003 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Job Description/Accountabilities Business Unit Description:&lt;br&gt;Business Unit Description:&lt;br&gt;World Markets, Wealth Management and TBRM Technology &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Markets, Wealth Management and Treasury Balance/Risk Technology holds an abundant wealth of expertise in application and experience in infrastructure development. You will be a part of a team that believes in providing &amp;#48214;orld class?service and support in a collaborative global framework. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our offices expand worldwide and our primary services include: infrastructure support and services, technology strategy, architecture development, vendor management, application development/support and implementation of technology solutions. Our leadership and dedication to excellence will contribute to our exceptional global Infrastructure support and service organization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities / Activities:&lt;br&gt;Accountabilities of Position (key outcomes and activities):&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;?This results-oriented individual must work well both independently and as a part of a team. &lt;br&gt;?Analyze, design and development for new project initiatives and participates in technology evaluation of new products.&lt;br&gt;?Participate in production support of existing applications.&lt;br&gt;?Perform unit test.&lt;br&gt;?Participates in estimation of development tasks.&lt;br&gt;?Conducts quality review of deliverables.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;Competencies ( i.e. skills and knowledge):&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;?5+ years Experience in the areas below:&lt;br&gt;?Must have strong skills in Java, C++, MQ Series, relational databases, OO design and programming&lt;br&gt;?Working experience with application server (preferable WebLogic)&lt;br&gt;?Knowledgeable in J2EE &lt;br&gt;?Understanding of Jakarta project, Struts, Rational Rose and source control tools (such as ClearCase) would be an asset&lt;br&gt;?Strong understanding of UNIX-Solaris and NT environments &lt;br&gt;?Ability to effectively interact with business analysts, support analysts, QA analysts and clients&lt;br&gt;?Strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;br&gt;?Creative thinker and problem solver&lt;br&gt;?Strong time management skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special conditions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIBC is an equal opportunity employer. It is the Company's policy to recruit and select applicants for employment solely on the basis of their qualifications, with emphasis on selecting the best qualified person for the job. CIBC does not discriminate against applicants based on race, color, religion, sex, national origin, or disability or any other status or condition protected by applicable federal, state or local law.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Skills C++&lt;br&gt;ClearCase&lt;br&gt;J2EE (Java 2 Enterprise Edition)&lt;br&gt;JAVA&lt;br&gt;MQSeries&lt;br&gt;Rational Rose&lt;br&gt;UNIX&lt;br&gt;WebLogic&lt;br&gt;Windows NT&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>2EAA4770-341F-49E9-8D35-F13439C7A13F</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer-FX --CIBC</title>
</post>
