<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Database Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;POSITION DESCRIPTION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;D3 Management Inc. a subsidiary of Playcentric is an interactive Marketing Agency supporting a consumer based transactional site on behalf of our clients. We are currently searching for individuals to expand our team in the role of:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title: DATABASE DEVELOPER (Intermediate/Senior)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department: Information Technology Group&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports To: Director, Technology&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Mandate:&lt;br&gt;A database specialist that can apply extensive experience in data modeling, &lt;br&gt;database administration and application development to design, implement, &lt;br&gt;deploy and support the enterprise&amp;#47977; database resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Identifying and correcting database application performance problems both prior &lt;br&gt;deployment and in production.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Planning database backup, replication and distribution in a highly distributed, &lt;br&gt;high availability environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Development of data migration and data integration, strategies and services&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comprehensive database disaster recovery planning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developing database standards and reviewing adherence to standards by the &lt;br&gt;development team&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working with clients to develop collaborative data exchange and data sharing solutions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data Modeling/Reverse Engineering, logical and physical database design using a CASE tool, Visio, ERWin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft SQL Server 2000, MCDBA Certification an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with inbound and outbound data exchange practices using various &lt;br&gt;formats, XML, CSV, EDI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exposure to Data exchange servers, preferably Microsoft Biztalk Server, development and utilization of XML schemas, Web Services, SOAP, WDSL and UDDI&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5+ years of SQL programming/DBA full life&amp;#48857;ycle database administrator and architect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last position should be related to 'database developer' or 'DBA'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with designing database gateways would be an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you would like to be considered for this position, please email your resume &lt;br&gt;with the position you are applying for in the subject line of the email to: &lt;br&gt;careers@playcentric.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interviews are targeted to start immediately.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While we thank everyone who submits a resume, due to time constraints, we will &lt;br&gt;only be able to contact those chosen for an interview. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers@playcentric.com&lt;br&gt;PlayCentric Corp.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>2EE57E26-BCBD-4907-A173-BFC5CFE2A372</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-28T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Database Developer</title>
</post>
