<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>CA-ON-Toronto/GTA-Sr. Analyst/Programmer (AS400) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Mandatory Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experienced AS400 Developers and Analyst/Programmers with at least 5-7 yrs of RPG programming skills required to develop solutions in a customer environment. Must have excellent written and spoken English skills. Must have a strong desire to work as part of an energetic team to create quality solutions under tight deadlines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specific skills required:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Full cycle application development experience&lt;br&gt;* Advanced RPG IV, RPG II, DDS, CL, OCL, PC (Client Access/400) programming languages&lt;br&gt;* Familiarity with Integrated Language Environment (ILE)&lt;br&gt;* Ability to develop quality interactive and batch programs&lt;br&gt;* Familiar with AS/400 programming utilities and general system concepts&lt;br&gt;* Knowledge of System/36 environment an asset&lt;br&gt;* Excellent problem solving skills&lt;br&gt;* Ability to work independently in an unstructured environment&lt;br&gt;* Clear English written and verbal communication skills in customer, peer, and management environments&lt;br&gt;* Broad knowledge of development tools such as SDA, SEU, PDM, Query, DBU&lt;br&gt;* Knowledge of Windows NT operating environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allied International Credit Corp. is a leading international Debt Collection and Accounts Receivable Management Company. We were recognized as one of Canada's 50 Best Managed Private Companies in 1999, 2000, and 2001. We seek career-minded, entrepreneurial-spirited individuals to join our dynamic growing company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are interested in this opportunity, please forward your resume to hr@aiccorp.com. Quote COMPETITION SA/P 201 when applying for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please visit our web site at (www.aiccorp.com)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;hr@aiccorp.com&lt;br&gt;Allied International Credit Corp.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>310BB317-2D35-4FDF-B2D2-CE687085BA30</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-08T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Analyst/Programmer (AS400)</title>
</post>
