<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior Web Developer (TR)&lt;br&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;Platform Computing is the leader in cluster, grid and cloud management software ― serving more than 2,000 of the world’s most demanding organizations. For 17 years, our workload and resource management solutions have delivered IT responsiveness and lower costs for enterprise and HPC applications. Platform has strategic relationships with Cray, Dell, HP, IBM, Intel, Microsoft, Red Hat, and SAS. Visit www.platform.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently looking for 1 individual to fill the role of SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sr. Web Developer is responsible for the day-to-day development, maintenance and operation of all corporate web applications and assures that all web applications comply with appropriate policies, guidelines, and standards. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Director of Information Technology, he/she will be responsible for the design and development of web applications that respond to business needs. The ideal candidate must display excellent written and oral skills with demonstrated interpersonal and organization abilities. A candidate for this position must be able to work in a varied, fast paced environment. Flexibility and tolerance is a necessity. This individual must have attention to detail, be able to effectively organize, prioritize and lead multiple projects, and be able to communicate effectively with all levels and functional areas within the organization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Develop new Web applications as identified by supervisor and management through packaged and customized applications. &lt;br&gt;Develop external Web portals allowing users to input and retrieve accurate information &lt;br&gt;Maintain and enhance existing Web applications and all internal systems that are integrated. &lt;br&gt;Contributes to user functional requirements and translates them into technical design and development projects. &lt;br&gt;Perform complete testing of Web applications&amp;#8211;unit and system, engaging users as necessary. &lt;br&gt;Prepare and maintain technical documentation that includes database structure, server and user access rights. &lt;br&gt;Works with customers and technical staff to resolve problems with software and responds to suggestions for improvements and enhancements. &lt;br&gt;Continuously monitor industry trends, technologies and standards and be able to research, recommend, and apply new web technologies as they emerge. &lt;br&gt;Candidate must be a team player and willing to teach and to learn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Background and Skill Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven Website Management experience with a degree in Computer science or related field. Additional formal training and professional experience in internet technologies/design strongly desirabl</content>
    <postId>331871CD-B4CB-4145-B015-A6E335A4CB3C</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Web Developer (TR)</title>
</post>
