<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>박인석</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>방금 공고한것입니다.&lt;br&gt;최소 18개월가량 진행되는 프로젝트에 투입될 예정입니다.&lt;br&gt;현재 사람을 뽑는 중?◆근.&lt;br&gt;잘 읽어 보기고 지원하시기 바랍니다.&lt;br&gt;MS 관련 기술이 필요하고, XML,WML관련 경험이 있으면 Asset입니다.&lt;br&gt;웹 사이트 : www.famousplayers.ca/Static/fp_corporate.asp&lt;br&gt;Good luck !&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;==========================&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities / Duties:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work closely with I.T. Development and Technical team to provide overall project management for systems related projects as assigned by I.T. Directors and Vice President. &lt;br&gt;Perform business analysis and document workflows and processes for the development of project requirements and functional/technical specifications. &lt;br&gt;Participate in the planning, design and development of new systems. &lt;br&gt;Provide project management for I.T. projects including MS Project plans, timelines, resource management, budget monitoring, status reports, update meetings and presentations. &lt;br&gt;Perform and/or coordinate Quality Assurance testing for new systems. &lt;br&gt;Work with I.T. team and users to conduct User Acceptance testing including creation of business cases, test scripts, and manage change requests. &lt;br&gt;Coordinate the implementation of new systems and enhancements including rollout schedules and resource management. &lt;br&gt;Participate in projects and perform various duties as assigned by Directors and Vice President. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills and Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education:&lt;br&gt;University education or equivalent experience required. &lt;br&gt;Computer Science related degree or certification desired. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience:&lt;br&gt;2-3 years of I.T. related Project Management. &lt;br&gt;Good working knowledge of the Application Development Life Cycle, Client/Server SQL Platforms, Networking within an NT OS environment, LANS, WANs, TCP/IP. &lt;br&gt;Resource management and budgeting experience a must &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills:&lt;br&gt;Must be proactive and possess strong interpersonal, customer service, communication, presentation and organizational skills. &lt;br&gt;Must be self motivated and able to motivate &lt;br&gt;Excellent Project Management skills and facilitation skills. &lt;br&gt;Must be proficient with MS Project and MS Office Pro in a Windows environment. &lt;br&gt;Must be able to handle mutiple priorities and manage available resources accordingly. &lt;br&gt;Some on-call availability required. &lt;br&gt;Some off-hours work required. &lt;br&gt;Some travel may be required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested candidates are encouraged to send their resume, cover letter and salary expectations to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famous Players Inc.&lt;br&gt;Human Resources&lt;br&gt;146 Bloor St. W.&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;M5S 1P3&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Email: jobs@famousplayers.ca &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fax: (416) 964-6450&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>35557245-21E6-4E60-A85C-DEF8DEA941C2</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-02-07T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>구인 : Famous Players ( Manager급)</title>
</post>
