<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>SAP Netweaver Mobile Architect&lt;br&gt;Skills:&lt;br&gt;SAP, Architect, IT, consulting, system, applications, Director, architecture, development, SAP ABAP, ABAP, Management&lt;br&gt;Date:&lt;br&gt;4-17-2010&lt;br&gt;Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description SAP Netweaver Mobile Architect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAP Netweaver Mobile Architect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Founded in 1976 in Montreal, CGI Group Inc. provides end-to-end IT and&lt;br&gt;business process consulting services to clients worldwide from our Centers&lt;br&gt;of Excellence throughout North America, Europe and India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI one of the largest independent information technology and business&lt;br&gt;process services firms in the world, employing approximately 26,000&lt;br&gt;professionals in more than 100 offices globally. We have enjoyed over 30&lt;br&gt;years of sustained growth, during which time our team has built partnerships&lt;br&gt;with organizations that we are extremely proud of, and of whom we are&lt;br&gt;dedicated to serving with the utmost skill.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you ready to make a difference with a world-leader in Information&lt;br&gt;Technology consulting? If you want to experience the spirit of an&lt;br&gt;entrepreneurial organization, while enjoying the impressive resources of a&lt;br&gt;global company, we invite you to join us. We offer a challenging and&lt;br&gt;rewarding work environment. Theres always room for you to grow at CGIthats&lt;br&gt;our commitment to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GTA team of CGIs SAP Practice is responsible for providing our clients&lt;br&gt;value added SAP services within the local marketplace. We focus on new&lt;br&gt;implementations, enhancement projects, system upgrades, and advisory support&lt;br&gt;to our client base.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We currently have an exceptional career opportunity based in the Greater&lt;br&gt;Toronto Area for a SAP Netweaver Mobile Architect to assist with providing&lt;br&gt;mobile solutions to our clients ensuring their SAP applications are tightly&lt;br&gt;integrated with the Mobile Infrastructure (MI) to meet their daily business&lt;br&gt;needs. Advising and guiding our clients through your knowledge of SAPs&lt;br&gt;mobile offering and experience in architecting and configuration of the&lt;br&gt;solution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Director of the GTA SAP Practice and working in a team&lt;br&gt;environment, you will be primarily accountable for the architecture, design&lt;br&gt;and configuration of SAP mobile solutions.&lt;br&gt;The principal functions of this position that will characterize your success&lt;br&gt;are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Design and development of mobile infrastructure solutions for clients&lt;br&gt;Development of a mobile framework including standards and integration&lt;br&gt;architecture&lt;br&gt;Responding to clients needs within the scope of SAP mobile requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This unique role further allows you to utilize your full complement of&lt;br&gt;skills and experience by working with other consultants to build your&lt;br&gt;experience base, share and contribute to the success of the practice,&lt;br&gt;participate and provide input into estimation efforts and bids, and&lt;br&gt;contribute to developing collateral.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESSENTIAL SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS&lt;br&gt;Minimum 3 years experience in designing and implementing SAP mobile&lt;br&gt;solutions&lt;br&gt;Experience in configuration of the SAP mobile infrastructure (at least one&lt;br&gt;MI 7.0/7.1 implementation)&lt;br&gt;Experience in developing a mobile framework&lt;br&gt;Experience with mobile integration with MM and WM functionality&lt;br&gt;Experience in implementing connected and non-connected solutions&lt;br&gt;SAP ABAP including BAPIs&lt;br&gt;Strong coordination skills between functional and technical teams&lt;br&gt;Troubleshooting and resolving SAP functional issues&lt;br&gt;Ability to analyze problems and provide clear recommendations&lt;br&gt;Facilitation skills and ability to lead client meetings&lt;br&gt;Excellent written and verbal skills&lt;br&gt;Strong organizational skills&lt;br&gt;Understanding of new SAP mobile offerings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional consideration will be given to candidates who also possess the&lt;br&gt;following:&lt;br&gt;Experience in a consulting environment&lt;br&gt;Mobile Asset Management &amp; Utilities (MAM/MAU)&lt;br&gt;Ability to identify value-added opportunities within mobile&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have strong sense of drive, flexibility, willingness to build upon&lt;br&gt;your current skills and are looking for the kind of career youve always&lt;br&gt;wanted working with the GTA division of the SAP Practice, then we would be&lt;br&gt;very interested in speaking with you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We offer the opportunity to work with Canadas largest information technology&lt;br&gt;outsourcing and management consulting company with a true global presence in&lt;br&gt;a fast-paced and energetic atmosphere where your own professional growth is&lt;br&gt;guaranteed your desire, commitment and impact.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anticipated start date for this position is June 2010, so please&lt;br&gt;consider putting your resume together and apply online to CGI Careers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regrettably, we are unable to interview all applicants. We will contact the&lt;br&gt;best responses for an interview, so please make sure you tell us about what&lt;br&gt;you think we should know about you and how this position fits with your&lt;br&gt;career goals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At CGI, were a team of builders. We call our employees members because all&lt;br&gt;who join CGI are building their own company one that has grown to 25,000&lt;br&gt;professionals in 100+ offices worldwide. Founded in 1976, CGI is a leading&lt;br&gt;IT and business process services firm committed to helping clients win and&lt;br&gt;grow. We have the global resources, expertise, stability and dedicated&lt;br&gt;professionals needed to achieve results for our clients and for our members.&lt;br&gt;Come grow with us. Learn more at www.cgi.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join a winning team. CGI offers a competitive&lt;br&gt;compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional&lt;br&gt;development. Benefits for full-time, permanent members start on the first&lt;br&gt;day of employment and include a paid time-off program and profit&lt;br&gt;participation and stock purchase plans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying&lt;br&gt;for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be&lt;br&gt;contacted.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>37625D8F-67D5-4035-8F49-4D89FE411FE0</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SAP Netweaver Mobile Architect</title>
</post>
