<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Peter</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>That board is called Betaville.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Most multimedia companies post jobs there.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Those companies are usually small, so there are larger employment possibility than other job boards. But for your career if you get job offers from big IT companies or banks while you go to one of those small companies, don't hesitate to move.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you hesitate because of loyalty or friendship, you will be unemployed at some point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year, there are not many positions even in Betaville.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;That means both large or small companies don't have enough jobs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lots of positions are not advertised.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is called hidden job market.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Sometimes hidden job market reaches 90% of all the job market. That is one of the main reasons that immigrants can't find a job easily.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a method called \\&amp;quot;cold-calls\\&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is for networking.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;When the job market is really dead, network is almost only way to get a job. You research in libraries or through the Internet to make a candidate companies list.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;And then just call them to make an appoinment with inside developers.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Just talk to them in the appointment about job market and preparations for the positions.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You could get valuable job information or they will notify you if there are job opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You are making a network through them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But if you have really good skills in IT or high-techs, then don't waste your time to do these kind of things.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You can compete in the opebsp;rket.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;What you need are a good resume that shows your skills and effective English for interviews.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have to find jobs in Betaville or in the hidden-market, that means your skills aren't marketable enough.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Even if you get a job there, it is just a start.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are really hard-road in front of you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reason I wrote this not-short passage is that I hope you to think twice about immigration.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you think it is too late to go back, do your best.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are always ways to solve the problems.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Take a look at the job posting section on this site (http://forums.sympatico.ca/WebX?14@18.jQpmaw32rEz^1@.ee93b00).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are some good and fresh postings.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Also don't forget to take a look at all the list of Multimedia and New media firms in Canada to look for any opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It's under 'Company directory' (http://www.multimediator.com/cgi-local/mmsg.pl?)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;FYI&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I found my first employer through this site when I was sending my resume to all the company from list A to K....&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;;-)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Good Luck!&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>37CFCFC6-E13A-41A1-9093-7AD7CD438892</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] Job Posting at www.multimediator.com</title>
</post>
