<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-Web Designer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Date.com Inc. (http://www.date.com) is a leading Internet social portal. Date.com requires an experienced Web Designer for its downtown Toronto, Canada office.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Description:&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will be responsible for the design, implementation and maintenance of all web site projects and associated common components, and staying up-to-date with research on web programming design. The individual should be skilled at presenting work in an organized and articulate manner and be comfortable contributing in meetings with various departments. Expertise in web scripting is required, as is a firm understanding of production within the design constraints of the web (including browser differences, html limitations, palette issues, file sizes). Applicant must have a strong working knowledge of hand-coded HTML. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required skills include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Superior written and oral communication skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 4+ years experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Strong documentation skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Good understanding of Perl/CGI programming in a Unix Web environment&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Basic knowledge of Unix System Administration &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Expert understanding of HTML / JavaScript / Java servlet/ PHP / MySQL&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Strong analytical and problem solving skills.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Expert understanding of Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent understanding of Cascading Style Sheets (CSS).&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Creative and imaginative.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Some URLs or a portfolio of previous work would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Be prepared to show samples of your work.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;kris@date.com&lt;br&gt;Date.com Inc.&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>380C1819-7135-49E8-9981-6820253BF275</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Designer</title>
</post>
