<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Project Manager, Mobile Applications&lt;br&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;VTRAC Consulting Corporation&lt;br&gt;"Solutions for Growth"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please e-mail your resume as a MS-WORD document in confidence subject Project Manager (Mobile/Wireless Applications), JOB Number: 2543, Attention: peterc@vtrac.com or call: (416) 366-2600 x 222.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Project Manager (Mobile/Wireless Applications)&lt;br&gt;Location: Entertainment District&lt;br&gt;Position Type: Permanent&lt;br&gt;Job ID: 2601&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking for a talented and passionate individual to help us deliver the next generation of mobile applications in a thriving start-up environment. You should be out-spoken, eager and ready to help us manage exciting new mobile applications that will have a positive impact on the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Summary:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Creating leading-edge applications on virtually every smartphone platform including iPhone, BlackBerry, Android, Palm Pre, Windows Mobile and Mobile Web.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; To ensure that software solutions are delivered to customers on time, on budget and to the expected quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsible For:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project/Practice Management&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Create and execute project work plans and revise them as appropriate to meet changing needs and requirements&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Identify resources needed and assign individual responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Manage day to day operational aspects of the project&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Review deliverables prepared by team before passing to client&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Prepare for engagement reviews and quality assurance procedure&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Proactively minimize and mitigate risks on projects&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Ensure project documents are complete and stored appropriately&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Review deliverables prepared by team before releasing them to client&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Ensure that management and client sign off defined approvals at appropriate stages throughout the project&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Control Change Request authorizations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project Profitability&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Track and monitor hours claimed for the project against pricing and development budgets&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Identify and explain variances to budgets&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Recommend action plans to keep project on budget&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communication&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Facilitate team and client meetings effectively&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Hold regular status meetings with project team&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Keep management and client informed of project status&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Resolve and or escalate issues in a timely fashion&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Inform Director of Sales of milestones to be billed to the customer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human Resources&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Develop staff on an informal basis through coaching and mentoring&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Provide feedback regarding team's performance to Development Managers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must have mobile applications experience for smartphones&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; A proven track record of successful project implementation in a software environment.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Team management experience and comfortable managing project teams of 5-10 people.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Excellent client-facing skills.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Experience with the entire project life cycle and able to operate in the initial conceptual design stage, in the depths of system testing, and at each stage in between&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; The ability to foster motivation within the project team to meet tight deadlines.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; The ability to have a strong impact and influence key decisions.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Experience with agile methodologies and practices&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Experience with tools such as JIRA, MS Project and Confluence&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Competitive salary&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Full benefits&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Casual work environment&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Location: Downtown Toronto (entertainment district)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61623; Games Room: XBox on a big screen!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all the candidates in advance. Only those candidates that are selected for interview will be contacted. For other exciting opportunities, please visit us at www.vtrac.com .</content>
    <postId>38DE994D-7EC2-4A58-B481-19C5C0EDBE66</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mobile Applications Developer (Consulting)</title>
</post>
