<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>VB/ASP Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We currently have a position for a VB/ASP Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fast growing niche industry brokerage located in Oakville, Ontario is looking for a dynamic, results oriented, resourceful individual with strong problem solving and communication skills to join its Information Technology team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professional aptitudes:&lt;br&gt;- Proactive with excellent organizational skills.&lt;br&gt;- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.&lt;br&gt;- Excellent time management skills: successful completion of multiple projects.&lt;br&gt;- Enthusiastic in dealing with new challenges and career development opportunities.&lt;br&gt;- Capable of working under pressure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities of the position:&lt;br&gt;- Development and maintenance of custom desktop software used in the day-to-day operation of our company&lt;br&gt;- Development and maintenance of web-based “thin client” software using ASP/ADO&lt;br&gt;- Coding of SQL queries and stored procedures&lt;br&gt;- Provide technical support to company employees as required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Computer Skills:&lt;br&gt;- Strong background (3+ years) in Visual Basic 6 distributed application development&lt;br&gt;- Strong background (3+ years) in ASP development&lt;br&gt;- Strong experience (3+ years) with SQL Server 2000 / ADO&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The following would be an asset:&lt;br&gt;- Experience with Crystal Reports&lt;br&gt;- IIS/Network skills&lt;br&gt;- Experience developing multi-lingual applications&lt;br&gt;- Some .NET knowledge&lt;br&gt;- Bilingual (English/French)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary Range: $38,000 - $42,000&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To apply for this position, please send your resume in MS Word format to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;vbdeveloper@pethealthinc.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only those selected for an interview will be contacted. No recruiters or phone calls please.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Salary: CAD 38,000.00 to CAD 42,000.00 per year &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Oakville ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>3A97B3E8-C8B5-4D3A-8237-CA8E64FCADC5</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>VB/ASP Developer</title>
</post>
