<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>SQL Server, C#, .net Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TDBFG Description&lt;br&gt;TD Bank Financial Group is the seventh largest bank in North America by branches and serves approximately 17 million customers. Ranked among the world's leading on-line financial services firms, our 74,000 employees around the world offer and support a full range of financial products and services through:&lt;br&gt;. Canadian Personal and Commercial Banking&lt;br&gt;. Wealth Management &lt;br&gt;. Wholesale Banking&lt;br&gt;. Insurance&lt;br&gt;. U.S. Personal and Commercial Banking &lt;br&gt;. Corporate Support Areas&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We operate in a number of locations in key financial centres around the globe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department Overview&lt;br&gt;TD Financing Services is a newly created business unit, representing the integration of the TD Indirect Lending business and VFC. The management team is entrepreneurial and dynamic and very keen to take advantage of this unique opportunity in the Canadian Indirect Lending space. TDFS is the first and only full spectrum indirect lending business within the Canadian market place. The product offering includes, auto, home improvement, recreational and leisure vehicles, non- prime mortgage and non-prime uloc/personal loans financing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description&lt;br&gt;Under the direction of the Director of IT, the Senior Programmer is responsible for ensuring the proper functioning, operation and ongoing development of TD Financing Services' in-house proprietary loan administration system, a .NET platform and SQL based application.&lt;br&gt;Design, develop, document and maintain application code, applying standard SDLC processes. &lt;br&gt;Provide time estimates for requested changes to the application. &lt;br&gt;Perform development level testing of each modification. &lt;br&gt;Prepare code for promotion to a test environment. &lt;br&gt;Interact with in-house QA testers and business users to ensure proper functionality of changes. &lt;br&gt;Prepare code for production releases. &lt;br&gt;Ensure roll-back procedures are available for all releases. &lt;br&gt;Address user inquiries related to application features and functionality. &lt;br&gt;Keep all requirements, design and program documentation up-to-date.&lt;br&gt;Assist in annual testing of Disaster Recovery and Business Continuity solutions to ensure plan remains relevant and system functionality in place. &lt;br&gt;Assist in month-end processes relating to reporting and data queries. &lt;br&gt;SQL Server and IIS server maintenance. &lt;br&gt;Research regularly using the Internet for any new patches or upgrades.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Requirements&lt;br&gt;In-depth knowledge of SQL Server, C#, .Net platform development. &lt;br&gt;Experience in system development, testing and deployment. &lt;br&gt;Strong technical skills, with ability to troubleshoot issues. &lt;br&gt;Superior customer service skills with the ability to communicate effectively with staff on a non-technical level. &lt;br&gt;Extremely detail-oriented, able to multitask and prioritize work in response to requests and inquiries. &lt;br&gt;Able to work independently and make decisions / problem solve based on sound judgment. &lt;br&gt;Excellent communication skills (both oral and written) with demonstrated ability to interact with peers, management, and other departments in a pleasant and professional manner.&lt;br&gt;Post-Secondary Education (University Degree, College Diploma or equivalent) in Computer Science or Software Engineering. &lt;br&gt;Minimum 3 years programming experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;www.workopolis.com에서 발췌...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;그럼 건투를....</content>
    <postId>3ACA6725-0330-423E-9E29-CA6804AB3039</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>TDSB JOB OFFER</title>
</post>
