<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At Bank of Montreal, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potential. As one of North America's premier financial institutions, with more than 30 lines of business within our group of companies, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Be part of a small team of approximately six individuals in the Market Risk application area. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Develop new applications and provide application support in both production and UAT/test environments for market risk management applications&lt;br&gt;Enhance system features and resolve application production problems as requested by users&lt;br&gt;Write high-quality and well-documented code using C++ and Unix scripts following the department's coding standard&lt;br&gt;Write and execute test cases, assist with integration and UAT&lt;br&gt;Assist System Administrators with software configuration management and implementation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;work with our Infinity application (vendor is Sungard)&lt;br&gt;initially 50% new development and 50% maintenance &amp; support then flexibility on upcoming projects&lt;br&gt;deal with internal market risk clients&lt;br&gt;must be able to work independently but be a team player in helping team achieve goals&lt;br&gt;important to have positive attitude, make judgement calls, be motivated and flexible &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 7 years of hands-on experience with C++, UNIX script languages, Sybase and/or Oracle &lt;br&gt;Familiar with Unix Sun OS/Solaris, AutoSys (Unix job scheduler), ClearCase and DDTS are beneficial &lt;br&gt;Ability to manage multiple tasks in a fast-paced work environment&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated flexibility and initiative&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Risk Management or Derivatives is mandatory and especially with popular vendor such as Summit, Eagle, Infinity or RiskWatch&lt;br&gt;extensive business knowledge mandatory such as: building derivatives pricing model, quantitative analytics, valuation, market &amp; credit risk, pricing algorithms, etc.&lt;br&gt;University degree in Computer Science, Engineering or equivalent &lt;br&gt;an advanced degree in Mathematics or risk management courses are advantageous&lt;br&gt;Successful applicant may need to be available for on-call duties after hours although it will be minimal&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate may be required to participate in system integration test for certain risk applications. The incumbent will also be process oriented and will be involved in some project implementation work in the team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bank of Montreal thanks all applicants. We advise that only those who qualify for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are committed to an equitable workplace and a diverse workforce. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: DSBJC00648&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Bank of Montreal&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>3EB77785-9A0B-4F61-8CDA-52FB784CCB23</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Derivatives Application Developer-Bank of Montreal</title>
</post>
