<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior Business Analyst/Project Manager &lt;br&gt;Ottawa, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join the CGI Group in Ottawa in providing leading IS/IT services to our broad client base as a Senior Business Analyst/Project Manager.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Role&lt;br&gt;Responsible for analyzing client's business intelligence and performance metrics requirements and leading consulting projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join a winning team. CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start on the date of hire and include minimum 3 weeks vacation, potential profit sharing and a stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business Intelligence/Data Warehousing experience.&lt;br&gt;Business/Systems Analysis experience.&lt;br&gt;Nice to Have Skills&lt;br&gt;Mathematical/Statistical background.&lt;br&gt;Government experience.&lt;br&gt;Performance Metrics/Balanced Score Card experience.&lt;br&gt;Use and implementation of BI Tool Suites (Cognos, SAP BW, Peoplesoft EPM, Crystal Decisions).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>3FB73FB7-7992-4F87-80E6-0198637F1323</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Business Analyst/Project Manager -CGI</title>
</post>
