<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Research In Motion Limited® (RIM)® is a world leader in the mobile communications market and has a history of developing breakthrough wireless solutions. RIM's portfolio of award-winning products, services and embedded technologies is used by thousands of organizations around the world and includes the BlackBerry® wireless platform, the RIM Wireless Handheld™ product line, software development tools and software/hardware licensing agreements. RIM is seeking driven individuals who can take our wireless data products to the next level in the global wireless market. Are you ready to make a difference in the world of mobile communications with RIM?&lt;br&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will be joining a group of dynamic, talented and professional developers with the BlackBerry Provisioning Software team in the BlackBerry Infrastructure Software organization. The candidate will develop innovative technology for management of the current and next generation of RIM's wireless products and services.&lt;br&gt;The position is in the group responsible for overall architecture of the BlackBerry Provisioning System (PRV). PRV is a mission-critical, highly-available system based on Java/J2EE and associated technologies.&lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;br&gt;The overall responsibility of the architecture team is to evolve the architecture to enable the system to continue to deliver value to its stakeholders and oversee all design quality of new features, while taking into account the changing business environment and technology. The architecture must address reliability, security, scalability, performance, availability and internal design quality. As such the candidate must have superior technical skills (in an Enterprise Java context) as well as the ability to grasp business processes, keeping in mind impact and requirements on systems and technology as well as opportunities to reduce complexity and optimize. The candidate must be to communicate complex ideas, provide compelling technical leadership to a variety of individuals of differing skill/experience levels, and to champion new initiatives that span multiple teams.&lt;br&gt;The PRV development process is ISO-compliant. Our main focus is the development of a high-quality product that meets or exceeds the expectations of our stakeholders.&lt;br&gt;Additionally, the individual will have the opportunity to develop and contribute to RIM's intellectual property related to wireless technology and/or software development.&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;ESSENTIAL SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS&lt;br&gt;B.Sc. in Computer Science or Electrical Engineering or equivalent discipline&lt;br&gt;10+ years of experience in enterprise software development&lt;br&gt;2+ years in a leadership role&lt;br&gt;Advanced Java knowledge (Standard and Enterprise editions including: EJB, Servlets/JSP, JMS, JDBC, unit testing frameworks such as JUnit)&lt;br&gt;Advanced knowledge of software architectures, OOA/OOD, design patterns, UML and Software Modeling tools&lt;br&gt;Background in Service Oriented Architecture (SOA) in a large enterprise&lt;br&gt;Sound knowledge of software engineering practices&lt;br&gt;Superior analytical, critical thinking and problem determination skills&lt;br&gt;Superior verbal and written communication skills&lt;br&gt;Strong interpersonal skills, positive attitude an ability to engage and create trust in others and facilitate/coordinate and navigate through complex problems&lt;br&gt;ADDITIONAL ASSETS&lt;br&gt;J2EE Application server knowledge including configuration, monitoring and administration&lt;br&gt;Background in database design and RDBMS technologies&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with wireless technologies and concepts (including GSM/GPRS, CDMA, iDEN, EDGE, UMTS&lt;br&gt;If you're driven to take wireless technologies to the next level, it's time you join the team at RIM. We offer a challenging environment that fosters creativity and rewards excellence. Employees also have use of our award winning BlackBerry!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ⓒ 2009 Research In Motion Limited. All Rights Reserved. The BlackBerry and RIM families of related marks, images and symbols are the exclusive properties of Research In Motion Limited. RIM, BlackBerry, "Always On, Always Connected" and the "envelope in motion" symbol are registered with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office and may be pending or registered in other countries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research In Motion is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&lt;br&gt;Job: Research &amp; Development&lt;br&gt;Primary Location: Canada-Ontario-Mississauga&lt;br&gt;Schedule: Full-time&lt;br&gt;Hire Type*: Experienced (Regular)&lt;br&gt;Relocation*: Available</content>
    <postId>40A25E8C-4B19-47C2-8DB5-E8CBE756AF2B</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-01T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software Architect (Java EE)-Mobile</title>
</post>
