<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;WYSDOM JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;br&gt;Wysdom (www.wysdom.com) empowers mobile operators to deliver high-value data services to their consumer and enterprise customers with their flagship software, Wysdom MAP-OS™. Wysdom MAP-OS aggregates the functionality that resides within the mobile operator's existing network and makes it possible to develop truly innovative services and applications in a scalable, streamlined process. By allowing controlled and billable access to existing network and support infrastructure, Wysdom MAP-OS enables the development of services and applications by third parties that go beyond simple device functionality. Mobile operators benefit by leveraging their network investments to generate lucrative new revenue streams. Incorporated in 1999, Wysdom serves its global customer base from locations around the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;POSITION: TECHNICAL ARCHITECT TEAM LEAD X2 REQUISITION #: TO-TN-02-003 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scope of Position:&lt;br&gt;To analyze and design complex software products and client solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;· Conduct extensive research and analysis of complex system requirements in developing designs that meet product needs.&lt;br&gt;· Write use cases, build system use case model, analyze the requirements and build analysis object models (domain object models).&lt;br&gt;· Design, model, code and deploy multi-tier and distributed applications according to specifications.&lt;br&gt;· Make recommendations for changes to software development guidelines and standards.&lt;br&gt;· Plan and carry out the testing and debugging of complex, multi-tier, distributed applications.&lt;br&gt;· Identify, analyze and resolve software issues within complex multi-tier and distributed systems.&lt;br&gt;· Participate in product design meetings, design reviews and code reviews. &lt;br&gt;· Mentor more junior members of the team.&lt;br&gt;· Make recommendations and suggests alternative approaches for the development project.&lt;br&gt;· Maintain an in-depth understanding of current projects follow schedule, informs management of any unplanned slippages, and proposes corrective measures.&lt;br&gt;· Maintain an in-depth understanding of current software department approaches and standards through interaction with clients, communication with company experts and independent research.&lt;br&gt;· Work as project team leader and/or provides technical leadership to project leads, as required.&lt;br&gt;· Conduct JAD sessions, as well as both internal and external technical presentations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education and Experience Required: &lt;br&gt;· Bachelor degree in Computer Science.&lt;br&gt;· 8 - 10 years (minimum) experience in software design/development.&lt;br&gt;· Understanding of full product life cycle and development methodologies&lt;br&gt;· Broad experience in more than one industry, including telecommunications.&lt;br&gt;· Strong multi-product and multi-domain knowledge.&lt;br&gt;· In-depth understanding of development standards.&lt;br&gt;· Extensive experience with OO Technologies (OOAD, OOP).&lt;br&gt;· Working knowledge of Unix and NT operating systems.&lt;br&gt;· Extensive experience in a product development environment.&lt;br&gt;· Proven configuration and coding management techniques.&lt;br&gt;· Prior experience working with external clients.&lt;br&gt;· Ability to work with no supervision.&lt;br&gt;· Strong oral, written and presentation skills.&lt;br&gt;· Demonstrated ability to create technical requirements and design documentation. &lt;br&gt;· Demonstrated analytical skills. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specialized Skills: &lt;br&gt;· Thorough and demonstrated knowledge of OOAD and OOP methodologies.&lt;br&gt;· Thorough knowledge of Java, J2EE and XML technologies.&lt;br&gt;· Thorough knowledge of UML.&lt;br&gt;· Thorough knowledge of Unix, Oracle, Windows NT based solutions.&lt;br&gt;· Strong leadership skills.&lt;br&gt;· Customer service skills with the ability to work independently at customer sites.&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with wireless infrastructure issues and trends in wireless domain.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;hotjobs@wysdom.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>40D4606C-B354-47C8-9818-4CF6D6F71EEC</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-01T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Team Lead</title>
</post>
