<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이상윤</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Dave&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Diverse Technical Professionals, on behalf of our client, is looking for an experienced MS Sharepoint Developer for a 6 month contract position.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;If you or anyone you know who might be interested, please contact me at zeeshanb@diversetechnical.com. Your help in this regard is highly appreciated.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Specific details of this position are as follows.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto (Downtown)&lt;br&gt;Position: Sharepoint Developer&lt;br&gt;Type: Contract&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Initial 6 months&lt;br&gt;Rate: Negotiable&lt;br&gt;Start date: ASAP&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Technical Requirements: (MUST HAVE)&lt;br&gt; 1. Hands-on experience with SharePoint Services Web Services (List Data Retrieval Service, Lists Service etc. etc.)&lt;br&gt; 2. Hands-on experience with creating and deploying WebParts.&lt;br&gt; 3. Hands-on experience with C# and ASP.NET (1.1 or 2.0)&lt;br&gt; 4. MS-Office programming (Excel, Access, PowerPoint, Word)&lt;br&gt; 5. Database design and RDBMS like MS SQL Server and MS Access&lt;br&gt; 6. Minimum 5 years of Software development experience.&lt;br&gt; 7. XML and XSLT&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Other Skills:&lt;br&gt; 1. MUST have excellent communication and interpersonal skills&lt;br&gt; 2. Ability to own a project from start to finish, including technical documentation, user guide and implementation documentation.&lt;br&gt; 3. Must work independently as well as contribute to team efforts.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;If you meet the requirements, please send your resume to zeeshanb@diversetechnical.com with subject id: Sharepoint_DTP001&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Note: If you do not wish to receive future opportunities from Diverse Technical Professionals, please reply to this email notifying us of such intent.</content>
    <postId>43FE77CA-43BB-4B2A-9E39-82F8815A3715</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-08-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SharePoint Developer Contract</title>
</post>
