<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>mannerh</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;I have the following positions available with a digital media company located in Toronto. If you know of anyone, please ask them to contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Interface Developers&lt;/strong&gt; - Contract - Front-end, web development, in-depth knowledge of jQuery&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;!--[if !supportLineBreakNewLine]--&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;!--[endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Interface Developer&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent - Back-end, web development, in-depth knowledge of jQuery;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consultant, Technical Operations&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent (client may also consider contract) - J2EE, WebSphere;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interface Development Manager&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent - Minimum 5 years of experience developing consumer-facing web based applications, ability to hand-code accessible, SEO-friendly web pages using semantic (X)HTML and CSS, Strong understanding of cross-browser issues and workarounds for older browsers including IE6, Expertise in object-oriented JavaScript development including DOM manipulation, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, experience working with third-party web service APIs such as Facebook, Twitter, Google Maps, etc, familiarity with web security vulnerabilities, 1+ years of experience with JSP, JSLT, XSLT, familiarity Apache HTTP server and mod-rewrite, familiarity with a source code systems (Subversion, Git, etc), Experience with Agile development, Experience working within a consulting agency. Assets not mandatory: experience in HTML5, CSS3 &amp;amp; jQuery Mobile, experience in Java, PHP, Ruby, Python, MySQL, DB2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Java Developer&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Contract or Perm &amp;ndash; Leadership ability, proficient knowledge of one or more of the following: WebSphere, Java, Strong knowledge of Webcentric technologies including HTML, DHTML, XML, XML, JavaScript, Strong Java knowledge, &lt;strong&gt;Assets:&lt;/strong&gt; Perl/CGI, WebSphere Commerce.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Interface Development Manager - Permanent - Minimum 5 years of experience developing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Systems Administrator&lt;/strong&gt; - Contract - IBM pSeries, System x &amp;amp; BladeCenter, AIX, Linux, Windows, IBM WebSphere Application, N-tier product systems, WebSphere MQ;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Manager&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent - 3 years experience as a PM managing major interactive or web development initiatives and 4 years experience managing budgets of $500k;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endeca Developer&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent - 4-6 years experience and considerable exposure to multiple technologies, mastery of Endeca and Java, strong knowledge of Webcentric technologies including HTML, AJAX, XML, JavaScript, Perl and WebSphere Commerce are assets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital Strategist&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent - Superb communication skills with the ability to clearly articulate ideas, verbal and written, 2+ years of experience creating content strategies for public-facing websites, a strong understanding of user-centered design and navigation principles, Expert knowledge of Microsoft Word and comfortable with PowerPoint, ability to analyze and apply Google metrics results to various platforms&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Thanks Very Much,&lt;br /&gt; Debbie Rae&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue;"&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:debbiera@intps.com"&gt;debbiera@intps.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; INTPS Inc&lt;br /&gt; (International Placement Services)&lt;br /&gt; 416-640-7466 x 7048&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <postId>443E991F-0D3D-4268-90CF-ABBDD0663E58</postId>
    <pubDate>2012-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>java 관련 구인입니다. </title>
</post>
