<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SALAR Systems Inc. is a system consulting company specialised in providing enterprise and e-commerce solutions. We produce and market enterprise software tools for our clients to run their businesses effectively. We offer a wide range of customer services including consulting, analysis, design, development, implementation and classroom training.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are firmly committed to customer satisfaction and professional excellence. Our business foundation is anchored on our customer, our people and our technology. We rely on our people to deliver the best technology solutions to achieve the highest customer satisfaction. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALAR Systems is located in Toronto, Ontario with sales presence in USA.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opportunities: Currently SALAR is launching an Enterprise Resource Planning solution program aiming at the mid-range software market. To complete the formation of our ERP team, we invite you to join us in working in a positive team-working environment. We offer attractive compensation plus performance driven bonus plan.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48599;evelop innovative Client/Server, Web-based solutions for our clients&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;articipate in system development activities including analysis, coding, testing and implementation - responsibilities will differ depending on the scope and phase of the project.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48606;nterface with clients during various phases of system development including design, user acceptance testing and implementation&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48601;nsure successful implementation of application&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48615;esolve technical problems.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48594;ttend trade shows and seminars &lt;br&gt;&amp;#48618;ravelling required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48595;achelor of Computer Science or equivalent experience &lt;br&gt;&amp;#48610;icrosoft Certified Professional: MCSD (must)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48610;inimum 2 to 3 years solid Internet application development experience using relevant technologies&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48601;xpertise in Internet programming including ASP, Visual Basic, C++, Java, SQL, ActiveX, ADO, COM, SQL server and Oracle &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------Contact Information &lt;br&gt;SALAR Systems Inc.&lt;br&gt;Richmond Hill&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>449C481F-D95F-42E1-8FF3-14402F7C56CC</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-01T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>CA-ON-Richmond Hill-Programmer/Analyst</title>
</post>
