<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>참고로 이 회사는 제가 volunteer로 일하던 회사가 다시 수주받던,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;IBM Japan, Toshiba..등등...주로 큰 프로젝트를 하는걸로 알고 있습니다.미국에 있는 본사(인도계입니다.)와 인도쪽에서 거의 모든 프로젝트를 하는걸로 알고 있습니다. 그리구 음..요점은 조건이 나쁘지 않은 회사라는 겁니다....^__^&lt;br&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;NO RELOCATION AND NO SPONSORSHIP AVAILABLE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Summary:&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will use their software build engineering experience to participate in the building, packaging, and automated testing of our leading edge, 4-tier software. Emphasis is on innovation, velocity, and quality through repeatability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position requires a flexible team player that can work with developers to quickly resolve build issues, and with QA to assist with the more complex installation and configuration tasks for i2 products and 3rd party software. Only the individual who is driven to succeed will thrive in this challenging environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duties &amp; Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;evelop / monitor execution of automated nightly builds&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53632;apidly resolve build issues to keep the release cycle on target&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;evelop / monitor execution strategies for pre-existing automated test suite&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;evelop / enhance install programs using InstallAnywhere multi-platform installation tool&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;evelop / enhance strategies for rapid standardized deployment of 3rd party software&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accountability:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53638;ork efficiently and effectively to build high quality software applications which meet stated business requirements within stated timelines&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53632;esolve build and install issues with lasting solutions in a timely manner&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;eliver fully functional products on multiple hardware platforms(Windows 2000, AIX, HP/UX, Solaris) within stated timelines and which meet quality standards&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53633;how initiative and ownership in all assignments&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum Qualification:&lt;br&gt;?+ years of related software build engineering experience in a multi-platform Unix and Windows environment.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53618;xperience with a recognized revision control tool (ClearCase, PVCS, MKS, etc) &amp;#8211; ClearCase is preferred.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53615;Sc or MSc in Computer Science or Engineering&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53618;xperience with relational databases (Oracle, DB2, SQL Server, etc.) &amp;#8211; Oracle and DB2 are preferred.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53622;nstallAnywhere or InstallShield development experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53619;lexible, detail-oriented, driven to succeed&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53620;ood written and verbal communication skills in English&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53616;++ and Java J2EE development experience in UNIX and/or Windows NT/2000&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53621;ands-on experience with AIX, Solaris, and HP-UX including Unix scripting&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53618;xperience with Web Servers, Web Application Servers(WebLogic and/or Websphere), messaging&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Temporary/Contract/Project, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;i2jobs@i2.com&lt;br&gt;i2 Technologies&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>44B3A03D-D717-4977-B6A8-E7DD787AD4A8</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Build/Release Engineer</title>
</post>
