<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>배길상</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Procom 에서 아래와 같이 Sr .Net Developer 를 찾고 있습니다. 관심 있으신분들은 Apply 하세요.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are searching for a seasoned .Net Developer to work for a major financial institution on a permanent basis. This opportunity is based in Kitchener/Waterloo and a full job description is below. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you or anyone you know is interested please let me know as soon as possible. &lt;br&gt;Best Regards, &lt;br&gt;James Campbell &lt;br&gt;JamesC@procom.ca &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-=JOB OPPORTUNITY=-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Software Developer- C#/VB/ASP.Net &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills: &lt;br&gt;-5+ Years previous demonstrated design/development experience in the following technologies; Crystal Enterprise, Crystal Reports or other reporting tools, PowerCenter or similar ETL tools, Microsoft .Net (VB.NET, ASP, C#) , Mainframe JCL &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Proven development/analyst skills preferably with a degree in Computer Science, related technology degree/diploma, or equivalent experience. &lt;br&gt;-Demonstrates problem solving skills with ability to analyze situations/problems systematically and deliver effective right-sized solutions in a timely manner. &lt;br&gt;-Proven technical lead capabilities, able to co-ordinate work tasks for other developers. &lt;br&gt;-Ability to work independently as well as being a strong team player with the ability to work effectively in a multi-site environment. &lt;br&gt;-Experience with integrating vendor packages into an established production environment consisting on various technologies and platforms. &lt;br&gt;-Strong working background with client-server environments and exposure to web based applications. &lt;br&gt;-Excellent organizational skills with the ability to handle several tasks efficiently. &lt;br&gt;-Excellent verbal and written communications skills. &lt;br&gt;-Experience with relational databases (SQL Server) and stored procedures. &lt;br&gt;-Experience with System Development Life Cycle Methodologies &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice-to-Have Skills: &lt;br&gt;-Background of Change Management process, GCC requirements &lt;br&gt;-Knowledge of source code management (PVCS Dimensions) &lt;br&gt;-Understanding of web application development &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Kitchener/Waterloo (Ontario, Canada) &lt;br&gt;Duration: Permanent, Full Time &lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary: Negotiable &lt;br&gt;Start Date: Immediate &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description: On behalf our large, financial services client, an Employer of Choice, Procom KW is searching for a software developer with strong mix of .Net development experience. &lt;br&gt; </content>
    <postId>44DC611F-9448-4D89-BC6A-56BE844A591F</postId>
    <pubDate>2007-05-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr .Net Developer</title>
</post>
