<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Semaview is looking for an individual willing to take a leadership role within R&amp;D. As a senior software designer, you will be working directly with the VP Software Development to collaboratively design and architect the next generation of Semaview solutions. As a development lead for the Semabrowse product, you will be challenged to deliver complex C# client applications that interface with semantic databases, office applications and remote web services. If you are highly experienced at interfacing with the Microsoft Office suite and Microsoft Windows operating system, we’d like to hear from you. As part of a new start-up, join a fast paced but exciting opportunity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Be actively involved in all phases of software development, utilizing the XP software development process &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Participate effectively in group meetings and design reviews, proposing innovative solutions to complex problems &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Assume full responsibility for software packages assigned to him/her &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Provide schedule and task descriptions to the Technical Manager and report any issues with the schedule. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Competencies: &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; University degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering, or the equivalent&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; At least 7 years of experience in software development with emphasis on Windows Development &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience and Expertise in: C, C#, XML, C++&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Knowledge in: Web services, .NET, Microsoft Office APIs, Win32 APIs, COM/COM+/DCOM&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Sound knowledge of software engineering practices &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Sound knowledge of software architectures, object-oriented design, design patterns&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with Software Modeling is an asset (Rational Rose, UML or similar.) &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; TCP/IP, Multi-threading, Database experience mandatory.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Familiarity with common Internet protocols (SMTP, POP, HTTP, FTP, SOAP)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: competitive&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Paul Cowles&lt;br&gt;paul@semaview.com&lt;br&gt;Semaview&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>4608B90C-D670-46C8-A556-87D32EEFB5FC</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-Senior Software Designer</title>
</post>
