<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Investment Administration Sciences &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IA Sciences provides premium business process outsourcing (BPO) of front-, mid- and back-office administrative services for investment counsel, fund companies and investment dealers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our core business activities include consulting and development of Individually Managed Account programs for sponsor organizations, out-sourced individually-managed account administration programs and business process re-engineering and operational reviews. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information on Investment Administration Sciences, please visit: www.iasciences.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work with Business Analysts to prepare technical specifications for operational flow and control applications; &lt;br&gt;Application development/maintenance; &lt;br&gt;Database administration and operations support. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three years experience in application development / systems analysis in the financial services sector; &lt;br&gt;Web based development using MS Visual Studio 6.0 (Interdev) and .NET ;&lt;br&gt;MS SQL Server based development and administration; &lt;br&gt;MS Access; &lt;br&gt;Visual Basic; &lt;br&gt;Crystal Reports; &lt;br&gt;Completion of the Canadian Securities Course would be helpful; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Application Submission: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you feel you are an ideal candidate for this position, please e-mail your resume in confidence to: Manager Human Resources HR@iasciences.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants for your interest, however only those candidates selected for an interview will be be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: IAS-5&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;HR@iasciences.com&lt;br&gt;Investment Administration Sciences Inc.&lt;br&gt;60 Yonge Street, Suite 1100&lt;br&gt;Toronto Ontario M5E 1H5&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>4974ECAD-D487-44C2-B2C0-490EF8B7C062</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Database Analyst / Developer</title>
</post>
