<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intermediate Application Developer &amp;#8211; J2EE&lt;br&gt;Overview:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Intermediate Application Developer &amp;#8211; J2EE is responsible for the Design, Development, Release, and Support of software applications for both internal external clients using J2EE. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements Gathering&lt;br&gt;Design, implementation and maintenance of applications from given requirements specifications &lt;br&gt;Application detailed design, coding, unit test development and conduct, integration and testing, and system performance assessment &lt;br&gt;Creation of technical documents for system design &lt;br&gt;Maintenance of existing modules and applications. &lt;br&gt;Development of new applications. &lt;br&gt;System Documentation &lt;br&gt;Application security testing. &lt;br&gt;Development of unit tests for new modules developed &lt;br&gt;Reconfigures and extends existing solutions so that new and existing solutions operate as an integrated system &lt;br&gt;Provide Production trouble-shooting analysis &amp; resolution &lt;br&gt;Mentoring &lt;br&gt;Data Analysis and Reporting &lt;br&gt;Technical R&amp;D&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must HAVE:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;College/University Degree &lt;br&gt;Web Development &lt;br&gt;3+ Years Web application development&lt;br&gt;Understand SLDC principles&lt;br&gt;Able to capture/refine business requirements into technical specifications &lt;br&gt;Able to create test plans from provided business requirements &lt;br&gt;Ability to mentor junior staff&lt;br&gt;Experienced in J2EE Core Patterns&lt;br&gt;Experienced in various MVC frameworks - Struts and JSF preferred &lt;br&gt;Solid understanding in HTML/DHTML/CSS and JavaScript &lt;br&gt;Experienced in CSS &lt;br&gt;Exposure to Spring framework &lt;br&gt;Experienced in ORM frameworks - Hibernate and iBatis preferred &lt;br&gt;Experienced in AJAX based frameworks - DWR and Dojo preferred &lt;br&gt;Solid understanding in HTTP protocol &lt;br&gt;Experienced in XML and XSLT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Shub&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resource Manager&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7965 Goreway Drive, Suite 2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brampton , Ontario L6T 5T5&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;P: 905-799-4550 Ext. 325&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;C: 416-820-5119&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;F: 905-799-4551&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;E: sshub@isgSearch.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;www.isgSearch.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>4A2D8859-E8A1-423E-AA8F-76270817A446</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-07-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Intermediate Application Developer &amp;#8211; J2EE</title>
</post>
