<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GestureTek is a world leader in computer vision technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Computer Vision team is seeking a Senior Software Engineer to support our ongoing software development efforts in the computer vision space. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Summary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GestureTek’s Vision team is comprised of a number of research engineers focused on developing world class tracking technologies using single camera, multi-camera, time of flight and 3D camera technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The efforts of the Vision team has led to numerous GestureTek patents and of course forms the foundation of all our products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will handle the non-vision aspects of GestureTeks’s various software projects, thus enabling other members of the team to focus on research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’re looking for an experienced individual as there will be a large architectural component in addition to real, “hands on” coding and will extend to all aspects of the product including networking, inter-process communication and UI development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ideally the candidate will have excellent Windows programming skills, however the preferred candidate will also be able and willing to contribute on ports of our technology to embedded platforms as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Main Duties&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Design, implement, test, maintain and debug Windows software, Windows GUI programming,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Write technical design specifications,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Create and/or contribute to highly portable software architectures,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Write technical design specifications,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Computer science / engineering degree or equivalent technical experience,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran Windows progrmmer with at least 5 years experience,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong programming background in C/C++, Strong Windows MFC Programmer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proven ability to develop Windows software with a “plug-in” architecture,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Windows Presentation Foundation (WPF) experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solid understanding of embedded platforms,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embedded Linux programming experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mobile platforms (Windows Mobile, BREW, Symbian and Mobile Linux)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology hungry with a keen interest in learning about and owning the hottest new technology,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with: C# / .NET Assembler Java,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XML TCP/IP Avid gamer,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tenacious, “whatever-it-takes” personality,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agile development experience (Extreme Programming)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perforce expertise&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About GestureTek Inc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GestureTek Inc. is the world leader in camera-enabled, gesture control technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GestureTek technology is employed in a wide array of applications and environments: videogame consoles; museum/trade show exhibits; location based entertainment facilities; physical rehabilitation programs; corporate boardrooms for executive presentations; military control rooms; retail kiosks; interactive floors/windows and interactive billboards.</content>
    <postId>4A942271-F8BB-4585-B6BE-D152D68E24D9</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Software Engineer (Vision )-Computers/Info Tech,Internet/New Media</title>
</post>
