<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Graphic Designer&lt;br&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;This position is located in Bermuda. Please apply only if willing to relocate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;#8226; Please note: This position is based in Bermuda!&amp;#8226;&amp;#8226;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We require a highly motivated individual capable of working on their own initiative whose core objective is to improve the client experience via the implementation of technology and the development of informative easy to read marketing and client materials. Successful applicants will pride themselves on their graphic design capabilities, their total accountability for deadlines and accuracy; their excellent verbal and written communication skills; and most importantly their maturity, enthusiasm, and commitment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities include:-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Write, design and produce quarterly newsletter, marketing literature, media and investor relations communications in print and electronic mediums. &lt;br&gt;- Write and design of straightforward advertisements for placement in local press.&lt;br&gt;- Raise the image of the firm through branding.&lt;br&gt;- Improve and upgrade the corporate website, as well as the company intranet.&lt;br&gt;- Improve and create a series of investment slide show presentations.&lt;br&gt;- Manage client seminar schedules and other marketing initiatives.&lt;br&gt;- Assist in training users, image manipulation and improving graphics.&lt;br&gt;- Assist in web casting and other related film projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who we're looking for&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A university degree or college diploma combined with one year of related work experience, or three years of related work experience without.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Sound knowledge of Adobe InDesign CS2, Adobe Photoshop CS2, Macromedia Freehand MX, Adobe Audition 2.0, Adobe Premier Pro.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of: Crystal Xcelcius, Microsoft Producer, Adobe Acrobat 6.0, Mambo Server.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Office and particularly Power Point.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Work experience in the Financial Industry essential.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ability to adapt to ever changing technologies and methodologies.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Proactive attitude and an ability to think laterally, providing ideas and solutions.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Dedicated individual; achieving a reputation for constantly going beyond what is required.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Must demonstrate a strong propensity for "follow-through".&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Willingness to work long hours and weekends as necessary to meet deadlines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About our client&lt;br&gt;Our Investment Advisory Services client is an Asset Management Company with offices in Bermuda and Cayman and is seeking an individual to join a team of energetic and committed professionals as Graphic Designer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's on the offer&lt;br&gt;Salary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position is located in Bermuda. Please apply only if willing to relocate.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>4D30D421-1C01-4EA6-B4ED-CDE8ED0F25A9</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Graphic Designer-Bermuda</title>
</post>
