<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title: QA Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QA departments in some companies have individuals who are less technically inclined than the development group. This is not the case at Sitraka. Since our products are for software professionals, our testers must have real technical ability. Accordingly, you have a solid footing in OO programming (Java or C++) and you look forward to highly technical challenges as you find ways to test our products in the same way our customers will. Key challenges include ensuring that Sitraka’s products are reliable and perform well under load.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Above all, you have an infectious problem-finding mentality. You take a customer's point of view in your approach to testing, so you appreciate the importance and enjoy the challenges of testing for bugs and usability issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Creation and execution of functional, regression, and performance test procedures &lt;br&gt;· Analyzing and documenting test results, filing defect reports and enhancement requests &lt;br&gt;· Collaborating with product development teams to resolve defect reports and enhancement requests &lt;br&gt;· Participating in creation of test environments &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· 3+ years of software QA experience, or 2+ years of software development experience &lt;br&gt;· Significant experience planning, designing, and writing test cases &lt;br&gt;· Excellent written and oral communication skills &lt;br&gt;· Strong Windows and UNIX (including Solaris, Linux or AIX) experience &lt;br&gt;· Basic familiarity with J2EE technologies and leading Application Servers such as BEA WebLogic or IBM WebSphere &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of the following will be added advantages: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Quality assurance methodologies, white/black box testing, system/integration testing methodologies &lt;br&gt;· Profiling and application tuning tools such as JProbe and PerformaSure &lt;br&gt;· QA automation tools, scripting languages, and defect-tracking tools &lt;br&gt;· Testing frameworks such as JUnit &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To Apply: e-mail jobs@sitraka.com and enter the job title in the subject line. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;jobs@sitraka.com&lt;br&gt;Sitraka Inc.&lt;br&gt;260 King Street East&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON M5A 4L5&lt;br&gt;Ph: (416) 594-1026&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>4E4CA21C-8ED9-4B90-B11A-A7FE751967D7</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>QA Developer</title>
</post>
