<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>관심있는분은 저에게 이력서보내주세요. -- 직장에서 소개비를 조금 주네요. alexna2003@yahoo.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;========================================================= &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software Developer - Intermediate/Strategic Team &lt;br&gt;Location: Waterloo, ON &lt;br&gt;Job Code: 07TBHTZ &lt;br&gt;# of openings: 1 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description &lt;br&gt;Do you want to come to work knowing that the code you generate and the architecture you design is powering the IT centres of some of the world’s largest and most renowned organizations? We need passionate and talented software developers and we want to talk to you about a career with our Research &amp; Development team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’re a visionary with a desire to improve and evolve the customer experience, while keeping current with competitive technologies in order to help to ensure MKS stays at the industry forefront, then you may be a good fit for our Strategic team. Here, you’ll have a hand in determining the long term direction of the MKS Integrity Suite. &lt;br&gt;To be successful at MKS you must enjoy being surrounded by bright and ambitious software developers who are enthusiastically working to make MKS the number one choice for Application Lifecycle Management. You must enjoy brainstorming, solving complex problems and having the opportunity to work with and be mentored by top-tier senior developers and architects in a cooperative and fun team environment. &lt;br&gt;Software development experience &amp;#8211; 3+ years &lt;br&gt;University Degree in Computer Science &lt;br&gt;A really great attitude and a results-oriented work ethic &lt;br&gt;Excellent communication skills &lt;br&gt;Here’s what would be a huge plus: &lt;br&gt;Java development experience &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with client/server architecture &lt;br&gt;Experience designing user interfaces &lt;br&gt;Experience with Swing, JSP, Servlet, AJAX &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's exciting knowing that your work is driving the internal processes of the world's largest enterprise organizations. Do you think you can write code that will stand up in that environment? It won't even get out the door unless it does. &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>4F1B3856-0685-4D83-8E03-36DEC63AE48B</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>근무하는 회사에서 자바개발자 모집합니다(1).</title>
</post>
