<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임정숙</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>You can always negotiate the time and duration.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The employer might ask you for Minimum hours per week but you don't have to say 'OK' to everything they asked you to do.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Tell the employer about your situation such as distance from your home or family.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You can work little longer hours some days and get a or two days off on certian days and so on.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;They will understand if you have the right reason.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;And anyway, they know they are not paying anything for your service... &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLEASE do not think this is a waste of your time or money.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It is a good investment for your future and will be a good chance to test how you can fit in this industry... right?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I know~~Now you will feel that those companies are using your highly skilled service for nothing, but you have to remember that you are also using them for better oppoertunities ahead of you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are not employeed currently, it is better than doing nothing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You will have more chance to practice your English and have more opportunity to make friends in the same industry...&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;there is so many good thing than bad things.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Be positive and good luck!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It will usually be 5 days a week and the working hour depends on the company you will be working for, but mostly between 7 and 8 hours a day.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;안녕하세요. 한가지 문의드립니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;코업으로 회사에서 일할경우 보통 일주일에 몇일, 몇시간 일하는지요?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;이번에 코업인터뷰하게 되었는데, 거리도 차없이 가기엔 너무 멀고, 만약 하게되더라도 또 3달동안 돈까먹을 생각하니 답답한 마음에 여쭤봅니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;아시는분 답변주시면 감사하겠습니다. Merry Christmas ~&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>4F6EF625-1A61-4661-B210-E63AABC7761A</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] 코업관련 문의드립니다.</title>
</post>
