<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Dear Member:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the online candidate profile you provided us, we've added &lt;br&gt;the following new opportunity to our website that may be of interest to &lt;br&gt;you. Please visit our web site at &lt;br&gt;http://www.cedara.com/careers/careers.htm to review it, apply for it, &lt;br&gt;or forward it to a friend.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listing: ists&lt;br&gt;Opportunity: Technical Support Specialist&lt;br&gt;Category: Technical Support&lt;br&gt;Location: Mississauga&lt;br&gt;Opportunity Details:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you looking for an opportunity to build on the skills&lt;br&gt;you’ve developed in your 2+ years on a helpdesk? Would you like&lt;br&gt;to be part of a team of highly technical mentors? Do you love&lt;br&gt;helping people with their technical problems? Well, if you’ve&lt;br&gt;answered YES to these questions then we believe we have the&lt;br&gt;challenge for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join our team of technical support analysts in a front line&lt;br&gt;internal technical support role. Your duties will include&lt;br&gt;providing quick response to internal customers on their&lt;br&gt;hardware, software, network and enterprise application queries.&lt;br&gt;You will spend approximately 70-80% of your time responding to&lt;br&gt;front line technical support items and the remaining portion&lt;br&gt;participating on various assignments that interest you,&lt;br&gt;projects and general departmental support activities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bring your independent problem solving skills and customer&lt;br&gt;service focus to the next level. You will have the opportunity&lt;br&gt;to increase your skills in and knowledge of Dell, Sun, HP,&lt;br&gt;Silicon Graphics; and the following operating systems: Win 98,&lt;br&gt;Win NT, Win 2000, Solaris, Irix, and HPUX.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keys to your success in this role are your dedication to&lt;br&gt;customer service, ability to solve technical issues, solid&lt;br&gt;knowledge and experience with MS Office/Windows 2000/XP,&lt;br&gt;combined with good verbal and written communication skills and&lt;br&gt;your ability to hit the ground running.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.cedara.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>50E9C6ED-616F-4DA8-8D95-63278B4A4C87</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-01-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Support Specialist</title>
</post>
