<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Ihn-Sok</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>내 나름대로의 답안을 다른 사람들에게는 준비하라고 하면서 정작 나는 준비한것이 없어서 한번 해볼려고 생각만 하던중. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;같이 Running을 하는 친구가 Barbara Moses라는 유명한 Career Counseller의 질문을 나에게 전달해 주었습니다. 조금 긴데 나만의 답을 적어보았습니다. 한번 읽어보시고 본인들만의 답을 한번 준비해 보십시요. 질문이 참 좋습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to answer common questions? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2005-04-21 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) Tell me something about yourself &lt;br&gt;o I act as a Project Manager, a Director or individual consultant. When I have new projects or new challenges. I will use two methodologies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o One is process of eliminating myself that means filter the option objectively first and make decision subjectively rather than subjectively first then objectively later &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o The other is thinking flow of Socrates, Plato and Aristotle. First ask questions to myself what I know for sure and what I do not know about the project. After that think about how to deliver it professionally and painlessly possible which involves good communication, teamwork, project management skill, and leadership. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Lastly think about how I can serve my stakeholder/client/user better. Obviously think about my values. Did I make my client life better or happier? I am here to serve my clients. My clients could be my boss, company, clients, my employees and so on. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) How would you describe your strength? &lt;br&gt;o I used to think my strength is my smartness. I possess the talent to understand things quicker than others and to put the puzzles together meaning to see bigger pictures. But now I like to embrace others, which will bring bigger leadership and bigger influence. I do not have to be a winner as long as my team becomes a winning team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) How would you describe your weaknesses? &lt;br&gt;o Usually my strengths turn against me and could act as my weakness. If my smartness is my greatest strength, I should acknowledge it and make sure I would not fall into trap of trusting it too much. Also the same token If I emphasis embrace too much, I could lose comparative edge of making timely decision. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) What is most important to you in a job? &lt;br&gt;o Probably three factors I need to perform at my best they are having fun while I am doing the work, co-workers I can trust and I can relate to and meaningful projects that I can be proud of. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) What is your management style? &lt;br&gt;o My management style is not micro managing but I also care for result-oriented performance. In order to achieve the goal I will use the written report-based management style. I like to have appropriate reporting schedule, weekly and monthly reports with result. If tasks are completed, I like to know how much and if not, I like to know clear reason and next action items. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o I do believe there is huge gap between the written-report and verbal report. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) How would you handle a failing employee? &lt;br&gt;o I better not hire failing employee in the first place. I have my own guideline of hiring. They are person with smile and thinking level based not knowledge-based. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o Still I have to deal with current failing employee. I need to face the facts. I need to have the honest conversation of the situation and not only I need to speak of my thoughts but listen the other side of story also. Then set the clear guideline what I do not want to encounter anymore and what kind of improvement I expect. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) How do you run meeting? &lt;br&gt;o ‘Very carefully’ &lt;br&gt;o My personal preference of meeting format &lt;br&gt;§ Send the agenda to attendees prior to meeting &lt;br&gt;§ At the beginning of the meeting I state clearly what is the objectives and what my expectation is. Also what I like to accomplish the end of the meeting &lt;br&gt;§ At the end summary the meeting and prepare the action items &lt;br&gt;§ After meeting I sent the summary of discussion and action items with name and date. Without action items with name and completion date the meeting has not completed. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) What do you think of committees? &lt;br&gt;o A committee is only as good as the chairperson’s clear goal setting and expectation. We all know how difficult to run the meeting with chiefs. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o I usually use the same technique or format as the regular meeting but there is more impact to the committees’ decision. I like to adapt to six thinking hats methodology. The good example of Six Thinking hats is the meeting of ‘Star Trek next generation’. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o If they can save the planet every week, we can handle the complex issues and project initiation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Q) How did you achieve your accomplishment? Why were they successful? &lt;br&gt;o I used my common sense and knowledge. And perseverance a lot most of my achievement were the result of hard work and try &amp; errors. I only can plan 80% of any projects. Other 20% are moving target. Everything continuously changes due to circumstantial variances. I should aware of changes and make timely decisions continuously. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Why should we hire you? Why do you want to work here? &lt;br&gt;o My proven track record is the living proof and I will bring more than just technical knowledge and professionalism. I possess very simple lessons of what the life brings to us. &lt;br&gt;o I read the book called ‘What I really need to know I learned from the kindergarten’ few years ago. It stated five common senses. &lt;br&gt;§ A lot of Smile &lt;br&gt;§ Punctual &lt;br&gt;§ Team work: we are only good as our team result &lt;br&gt;§ Take break: enjoy the journey as well as the fruit of hard work &lt;br&gt;§ Tell the problems to the boss before too late &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o If I would not like the job, I would not apply it in the first place. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø How do you know when you’re successful at your job? &lt;br&gt;o First of all I should be satisfied with the performance of my accomplishment &lt;br&gt;o Secondly my team should feel good about the team effort and result &lt;br&gt;o Thirdly the result should be contributing to the company’s bottom line &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Tell me about positions you’re held, and what your responsibilities? What did you like about those responsibilities? What didn’t you like about them? &lt;br&gt;o My title is the director of technology and a senior project manger. &lt;br&gt;§ As a director I set the direction of technology group after careful consideration of the company’s direction. &lt;br&gt;§ As a PM I deliver the projects with the same goal setting of direction. Also manage and mentor other project managers &lt;br&gt;o I love my responsibilities because I need to bring it out my best of ability and the best of other members. Time to time I need to make unpopular decisions due to many reasons but I trust my decisions and the end of day my team member will understand my decisions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø How would you describe your last organization? &lt;br&gt;o I enjoyed my tenure with my last company. My last organization is the venture type Storage Service Provider Company and it was very organic and dynamic mixture. &lt;br&gt;o If I have the chance to do it again. Probably I can do my job better but we all learned from our mistakes &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø If you could do it all over again, what changes would you make in your career? &lt;br&gt;o Not much because all my efforts and mistakes made me the person I am today. If I can add, not change, I will accept more risk and more time to reflect my projects and myself. And before I quit ask one more question ‘Did I do everything I can and did I put the best of my ability and soul?’ &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø What would your references say about you fit what you would say about yourself? &lt;br&gt;o Thomas is a mailman. He will deliver. &lt;br&gt;o I have asked the same question before to people I know. They told me I would perform the best as a director of good organization. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø Describe the person who influenced you the most in your career. &lt;br&gt;o Two groups &lt;br&gt;Ø From the history Christ, Buddha, Socrates and Ben Franklin &lt;br&gt;· Christ and Buddha taught me the best I can be and be a good person with love and grace. &lt;br&gt;· Socrates inspired me to become a man with curiosity &lt;br&gt;· Ben Franklin showed me to become practical person. &lt;br&gt;Ø My former bosses. &lt;br&gt;· Right or wrong they show me many things, good, bad and ugly &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø What kind of people do you have difficulty with? &lt;br&gt;o The persons who are different than I in thinking method &lt;br&gt;o Whenever I have the difficulty with others. I become them. Act/think/speak like them. I usually find the solutions. If I can’t find the solution, there is always other way. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø What are you likely to do that could annoy me? What sorts of things could I do that would annoy you? &lt;br&gt;o It must be trick question. Today I like to pass it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ø How can our company help you to achieve your goals? &lt;br&gt;o First of all offer me a position as the starter. &lt;br&gt;o Communication: we talk and listen. What we both want is the same, success of the company. Company grows then I grow &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>511DF093-8F23-494A-992A-9AA9AE26687C</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-04-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Interview 질문 답하기</title>
</post>
