<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Intermediate Delphi Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;As a leading producer of real-time manufacturing industry solutions worldwide, PINpoint Information Systems has the resources to offer you a great opportunity. You'll find a unique set of challenges and rewards that only a leader like PINpoint Information Systems can provide. As a growing, innovative software company, we are seeking a detail oriented, flexible and resourceful individual. You will be part of a dynamic development team. We are proud of our ability to push the limits of technology (and set new ones) in software development and engineering.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PINpoint&amp;#47977; success is based on our belief that our people are our Company's greatest asset. We provide a challenging and rewarding experience in a fun and friendly environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PINpoint has an immediate opening for a candidate with excellent technical and problem solving skills to join our highly focused development team as a permanent employee in the role of an intermediate developer. We are looking for a candidate that has above average software skills and is extremely comfortable in developing software in a small, highly motivated development team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The duties required for the position:&lt;br&gt;* New software development and debugging&lt;br&gt;* Functional and technical specification writing&lt;br&gt;* Troubleshooting&lt;br&gt;* Work with client services to resolve production issues&lt;br&gt;* Some design and analysis in collaboration with the project manager and architects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The following competencies are mandatory :&lt;br&gt;* BS degree in Computer Science or related degree. &lt;br&gt;* 4+ years of development experience&lt;br&gt;* Currently using Delphi 5.0/6.0&lt;br&gt;* 2+ years of Delphi development experience on Windows NT/2000 platform&lt;br&gt;* Multi-tier development experience&lt;br&gt;* Work well independently and within small teams. &lt;br&gt;* Strong documentation and communication skills &lt;br&gt;* Formal design skills&lt;br&gt;* Must display an understanding of software lifecycle methodology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, it would be beneficial for the ideal candidate to possess some combination of the following;&lt;br&gt;* At least one formal object-oriented methodology with UML&lt;br&gt;* Knowledge and use of third-party Delphi components &lt;br&gt;* Knowledge and use of Crystal Reports&lt;br&gt;* Understanding of Delphi VCL/CLX internals &lt;br&gt;* Development of Delphi components &lt;br&gt;* Win32 API&lt;br&gt;* Web development, XML, XSL, [D|X]HTML, javascript, SOAP&lt;br&gt;* Experience with testing protocols &lt;br&gt;* Industrial controls experience&lt;br&gt;* Development of hardware interfaces&lt;br&gt;* Embedded systems experience&lt;br&gt;* Wonderware&lt;br&gt;* Kylix&lt;br&gt;* Unix operating systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates must posses strong English and interpersonal communication skills, as well as commitment to quality, enthusiasm and drive. Candidates must be able to travel and work in the USA and abroad on occasion. No telephone calls please. We thank all applicants but advise that only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&lt;br&gt;Salary: Dependent Upon Experience &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: DEV0209DEL2&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLEASE USE THE FOLLOWING STANDARDS WHEN EMAILING WITH PINPOINT ?your email may otherwise be discarded;&lt;br&gt;1) Begin the subject of your email with DEV0209DEL2 followed with your full name&lt;br&gt;2) If you including attachments, convert all attachments into one before sending&lt;br&gt;3) Begin the name of your attachment with DEV0209DEL2 followed with your full name&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;hr@pinpointinfo.com&lt;br&gt;PINpoint Information Systems&lt;br&gt;Burlington ON&lt;br&gt;Fax: 905-639-8529&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>524E7B3A-137E-4CD7-9951-1BD47F383FD3</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Intermediate Delphi Developer</title>
</post>
