<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이상훈</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>오라클 R12입니다.&lt;br&gt;장소는 앨버타 되겠습니다. &lt;br&gt;단기 계약입니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Alberta&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start: Aug 4th&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOA: 8 months&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workweek- 4/10 is fine&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project: Client is doing and upgrade from 11.59 to R12. They are in the planning/scoping phase and starting to do a little AS IS-TO BE. Their go live is scheduled for April 1st 2009.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position 1- Functional Lead&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They need a functional consultant to come in to work with the director to understand the department’s current state and help develop the project plan for the R12 upgrade. This consultant will also need to be able to advise and give strategies to support where they what it to be in R12. They need to determine which modules they will need to upgrade at a minimum for the first roll out. Their might be additional roll outs to follow. The consultant will actually be the one leading the upgrade.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consultant must have been a functional lead in multiple projects and have hands upgrade experience (design, configuration, testing, support, ect). They will be leading between 5-10 ppl. They need to have hand on experience with R12, and has experience with GL , AR , AP, Project Costing, and Cash Management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUST:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;R-12 Hands On exp.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upgrade exp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lead Exp. (Multiple Projects)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AR, AP, GL, Project Costing, Cash Mgmt, Purchasing Good Communication&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLUS:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Full Implementation of R12&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consolidation Module exp.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multi Org Access Control&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-----&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position 2- Technical Lead&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They need a consultant that is hands on technically and knows about all of the new technology in R12. This consultant need to drive/lead the testing, interface, conversion, and cutover. They also need to be very strong with BPEL’s. They will be leading 5 ppl. and must have worked on multiple upgrades.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUST:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;R12 Hand on exp.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Know all of the technology changes in R12 AR, AP, GL, Procurement, Project Costing BPEL Lead Exp. (Multiple Projects)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLUS:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Full implementation of R12&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iProcurement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>52FBC7A5-AA8B-40DF-9005-881A5C384EA3</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-08-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>오라클 in Alberta (2 positions)</title>
</post>
