<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Programmer Analyst - ASP.NET Experience&lt;br&gt;Walmart Canada&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Category:&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Technology&lt;br&gt;Location:&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Mississauga, ON&lt;br&gt; &amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&lt;br&gt;Req ID&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;755BR&lt;br&gt;Job Title&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Programmer Analyst - ASP.NET Experience&lt;br&gt;Location&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Canada-ON-MISSISSAUGA&lt;br&gt;Employment Type&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Full Time&lt;br&gt;Position Summary&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#8226; To help support the increasing demand for in house applications and internal support. The volume of approved requests surpasses the time available by our resources and does not allow for production and execution in a timely manner&lt;br&gt;Position Responsibilities&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#8226; Work directly with customers to create scope documents and project plans to determine project or program feasibility &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Develop applications to include the following: process maps, application front-end design, code, database design, implementation, documentation and training &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Conduct review meetings with key users in the business to ensure new projects being developed will meet the customer’s needs &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Support and maintain existing applications, including such activities as: repairing intranet links, replacing material on the intranet, adding functionality to existing applications, migrating applications from one platform to another, creating logins for users of internal applications, etc. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Troubleshoot errors both in production and pilot applications &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Develop program to meet ad-hoc requests from the business, including: reportsdata-pulls, application access requests, project feasibility, support users of internal applications etc.&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#8226; Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science andor other related disciplines &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 2 &amp;#8211; 5 years related field experience an asset &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must have strong analytical and research skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent communication skills (both verbal and written) and detail-oriented &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to communicate effectively with both technical and non-technical members of the business &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to write proposals and technical documents such as flow charts, Gantt charts, and ERD’s. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience in ESSBASE is an asset. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to work both independently and as part of a team &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to adapt to rapidly changing technology, environments, and direction &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to take a project through the entire Systems Development Life Cycle &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to code in the following languages: Visual Basic, VBA, HTML, ASP, T-SQL, JavaScript (VB.NET, C#, ASP.NET, XML, JCL, COBOL an asset) &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to work with the following databases: SQL Server 2000/2005, Microsoft Access (DB2, Teradata, Informix, Oracle, CICS an asset) &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to work with the following project management tools: Microsoft Project, Visio &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must have extensive knowledge of the Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) and Outlook &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be willing to learn and adapt to change quickly&lt;br&gt; &amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160; </content>
    <postId>5384ED30-4D0E-4858-BFA3-94341B4D101B</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Programmer Analyst(ASP.NET)Walmart Canada</title>
</post>
