<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Java Developer,&lt;br&gt;THE DOMINION OF CANADA GENERAL INSURANCE COMPANY&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON, CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;Posted Mar 11, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GROWTH. OPPORTUNITY. SUCCESS. "Make a difference!" in Your Career. The Dominion has been serving the insurance needs of Canadians for more than 100 years. Still 100% Canadian owned, today we are one of Canada's largest property and casualty insurance companies. With offices across Canada and nearly 1000 employees, we are proud to provide high quality home, automobile and business insurance products to Canadians. &lt;br&gt;The Environment &lt;br&gt;The Dominion has a multi-faceted integrated systems environment comprised of Java-based web applications, legacy mainframe systems, end-user client computing, and a business intelligence environment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The web applications run in a WebSphere/Oracle environment on our AIX platform and are developed in Java following J2EE standards.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The legacy systems run in a CICS/COBOL environment on our z/OS mainframe. &lt;br&gt;We have an established Enterprise Architecture that is used to guide updates and improvements to the application and infrastructure portfolios.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We use a Software Development Lifecycle Methodology, a Project Management Methodology, and employ standards in executing the projects.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Clarity and Open Workbench are used to assist in planning and monitoring our project portfolios.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The Position &lt;br&gt;We need an experienced Application Designer/Developer to define and build solutions for projects within the Application Services department. You will take a leading role in projects from designing through to delivery of systems. You will bring your advanced knowledge of multi-tier, services oriented systems in designing component based solutions for business problems. You will ensure consistency with the overall company Enterprise Architecture. Having identified strategies and solutions, you will go on to implement in The Dominion environment, building new systems and integrating commercial applications as needed. &lt;br&gt;Good experience of Java/J2EE architecture and Object Oriented Analysis and Design methods is required. You will be conversant with WebSphere, and database systems and will ideally have some knowledge of legacy systems.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You will use your knowledge of design patterns and frameworks to provide leadership and guidance to development teams working on new application development. Having used the Rational Unified Process and Rational Rose in previous development projects, you will direct the production of artifacts through The Dominion tailored methodology.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;You enjoy being part of a company large enough for career opportunities, yet small enough to provide a sense of belonging and give you the chance to make a difference. &lt;br&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt; ·Investigates and analyzes existing systems and business requirements in order to provide cost effective and efficient solutions to business needs.&lt;br&gt; · Designs and develops application code for solving complex problems in order to meet The Dominion's business requirements. &lt;br&gt; · Performs all levels of testing, including unit, integration, regression, system, and user acceptance testing to ensure that applications will perform error &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; free and according to business specifications when promoted to production.&lt;br&gt; · Provides planning, organization, and control while leading a small team of one or two programmers in project work&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;to ensure that&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; high quality solutions are developed to meet&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;business requirements.&lt;br&gt; · Identifies opportunities for Application Services to ensure high quality in all deliverables and continuous improvement in application development.&lt;br&gt; · Provides mentoring to the Programmers and Programmer/Analysts in order to help them progress in their professional development and optimize&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; performance.&lt;br&gt;Education&lt;br&gt;Minimum - three year college diploma, with a major in computer science, or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;Experience&lt;br&gt;Minimum - one and a half years experience as a programmer, plus two and a half years as a programmer/analyst.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience in project development using a system development life cycle methodology, experience in mentoring junior staff, and three years coding experience (with at least two of those coding complex business requirements).&lt;br&gt;Technical Skills &lt;br&gt;Advanced knowledge and experience of Java/J2EE Design patterns. Complete lifecycle development experience of component based solutions using OOA and OOD.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Sound Knowledge and experience in using the Rational Unified Process and UML.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Sound Knowledge and experience in developments using WebSphere. Good understanding of database systems, including data modelling ability, preference give to candidates with a background in Oracle.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Good understanding of application maintenance and support process.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of the property and casualty insurance industry is desired.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Previous integration experience with vendor solutions would be an asset.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Performance Skills &lt;br&gt;· Technical Ability&lt;br&gt;· Employee Development&lt;br&gt;· Team Player&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants who apply however, only those considered for an interview will be contacted.</content>
    <postId>54202033-2E84-4FDE-B712-A4E6DE8E35FC</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer- Insurance Company</title>
</post>
