<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working at i2 Technologies in a team of accomplished professionals you will apply your software development skills diligently towards the development and testing of state-of-the-art Logistics Applications. You will participate in the full system development lifecycle from requirements to release utilizing current technologies such as Java/EJB, XML etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duties &amp; Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53635;nderstand business requirements for software application&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53630;articipate in creation/extension of software design&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53622;mplement code of high quality&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53614;dhere to adopted design and coding standards &lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;ocument design and code produced&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53630;articipate in reviews of software design and code&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53626;aintain software in an efficient and timely manner&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accountability:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53638;ork efficiently and effectively to produce high quality software application which meet stated business requirements within stated timelines&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53632;esolve software issues with lasting solutions in a timely manner&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;eliver fully functional products on multiple hardware platforms within stated timelines and which meet quality standards&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53635;nderstand objectives of application in its deployment in industry&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53633;how initiative and ownership in all assignments&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum Qualification:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53615;Sc or MSc in Computer Science or Engineering&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53623;SP, JavaScript, EJB, J2EE standard, XML&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53618;xperience with Web Servers, Web Application Servers(WebLogic and/or Websphere), Internet Security, messaging&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;atabase design knowledge using databases such as Oracle, SQL Server, etc.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;evelopment on Windows NT/2000 and one or more of Solaris, HP-UX and AIX&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53634;ools experience - code management (e.g., ClearCase), compilers, debuggers, (RDBMS and OO) CASE tools (e.g., Rational Rose)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53620;ood English language written and verbal communication skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;?+ years of strong C++ development experience on UNIX and/or Windows NT &lt;br&gt;&amp;#53629;bject Oriented Analysis and Design experience (knowledge of UML preferred)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;evelopment experience on large-scale Internet application involving high transaction volumes, large number of users etc.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;i2jobs@i2.com&lt;br&gt;i2 Technologies&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>548AA615-BBB3-4A39-93D5-108298D82648</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Markham-Software Engineer</title>
</post>
