<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title: Java Developer&lt;br&gt;Posted On: 3/17/2010 10:53:30 AM&lt;br&gt;Designation: Java Developer&lt;br&gt;Number of Vacancies: 1&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: Bachelor degree in Computer Science&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: &lt;br&gt;Java - 2 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Minimum Experience: 2 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Job Tenure: Full-time Only&lt;br&gt;Salary Offered: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Job Location: Toronto, ON, Canada&lt;br&gt; Job Description &lt;br&gt;Knowledge and Skills Required: &lt;br&gt;· Bachelor degree in Computer Science or related discipline or an equivalent combination of education and experience from which comparable knowledge and skills may be acquired. &lt;br&gt;· 2-3 years of technical experience in design, development, testing and deployment of software using Java, Servlets, JSP, JDBC, RMI &lt;br&gt;· Effective oral and written communication skills &lt;br&gt;· Must be able to work independently and in a team &lt;br&gt;· Display good time management skills and work in a deadline environment. &lt;br&gt;· Experience with Unix, Linux shell scripting and/or Perl scripting &lt;br&gt;· Solid experience using a Relational Database Management System preferably Sybase ASE 12), in database modeling and with SQL-92 or equivalent. &lt;br&gt;· Experience in web developemnt Java Script, HTML, XML. &lt;br&gt;· Good problem solving skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pass on to your friends too and check out www.iitjobs.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# This position is for Toronto, ON, United States.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Company Details&lt;br&gt;Name: JumpPoint Technologies Inc.&lt;br&gt;Type: Consulting Organization&lt;br&gt;Total Employees: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Turnover: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Address: &lt;br&gt;Commerce Gardens,&lt;br&gt;30 Wertheim Court, #13,&lt;br&gt;Richmond Hill,&lt;br&gt;Ontario,&lt;br&gt;Canada&lt;br&gt;Profile: &lt;br&gt;JumpPoint Technologies specializes in creating customized service solutions to better identify and satisfy your company's unique IT needs. We offer services such as buying and leasing personal and mid-range computers along with providing networking equipment from many of the most trusted names in the Information Technology industry - names like IBM, Cisco, HP/Compaq and Sun Microsystems.</content>
    <postId>55C0DFF0-5299-4973-AD5A-F5AA446BE672</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer -2 years EXP</title>
</post>
