<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>Water bra</author>
            <date>2011-07-23T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>I just added this blog site to my rss reader, great stuff. Can't get enough!</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Job Number - J0503-0744 - Full Time&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Title Senior Systems Developer (Mainframe &amp; Java Application Development) &lt;br&gt;Category Information Technology &lt;br&gt;City Toronto, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;Job Location 750 Lawrence Avenue West &lt;br&gt;Posting Date (dd/mm/yyyy) 04/06/2003 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Job Description/Accountabilities Business Unit Description:&lt;br&gt;Technology Solutions is responsible for the delivery of technology in support of CIBC lines of business and customers. Through a combination of in house systems development and working with leading technology partners, the division delivers world-class solutions in support of business strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities / Activities:&lt;br&gt;The incumbent will be involved in a fast-paced environment and will need to deal effectively with a variety of project team members. &lt;br&gt;The incumbent is to plan, coordinate, direct and manage all development activities, including use of testing environments and facilities to ensure that they are carried out in a cost effective and timely manner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other activities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Planning, analysis and design activities in conjunction with other development specialists &lt;br&gt;- Under general supervision, participates in analysis of complex business opportunities/problems to deliver designs meeting requirements&lt;br&gt;- Participates in estimation of tasks and assists in the development of project&lt;br&gt;- Under minimal supervision, codes or makes modifications to programs of high complexity, according to specifications&lt;br&gt;- Coaches junior members within the project &lt;br&gt;- Conducts walkthroughs and quality review of deliverables&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;- Good organization, planning and basic management principles. &lt;br&gt;- Good interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br&gt;- Solid knowledge of the assigned business areas&lt;br&gt;- Decision making and problem solving skills &lt;br&gt;- Time management skills &lt;br&gt;- Expert knowledge of information technology principles&lt;br&gt;- Expert knowledge of software development, testing and evaluation procedures&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must meet the following requirements:&lt;br&gt;- Object Oriented Technology: 2-3 years Object Oriented Analysis and Object Oriented Programming&lt;br&gt;- Web Technology: (Java, Beans, HTML): 2-3 years&lt;br&gt;- TSO/ISPF: 5-6 years&lt;br&gt;- Cobol, JCL, MPP, BMP, Batch, IMS: 3-4 years&lt;br&gt;- DB2: 3-4 years&lt;br&gt;- GDF (asset)&lt;br&gt;- CMM (asset)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contacts: &lt;br&gt;- Business clients &lt;br&gt;- Management and senior Development staff to receive guidance and direction as well as status reporting &lt;br&gt;- Specialist groups within CIBC &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Challenges/Complexities: &lt;br&gt;- Performing business analysis and design, and implementing information technology solutions to fully address clients' business problems &lt;br&gt;- Strong appreciation of the assigned business area with respect to applications supported/developed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Physical Demands/Working Conditions: &lt;br&gt;- Works in a normal office environment &lt;br&gt;- Requires attention to details in system analysis/design and problem resolutions &lt;br&gt;- Strong initiatives in getting things done&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attributes:&lt;br&gt;- Accountability&lt;br&gt;- Conceptual Thinking&lt;br&gt;- Results-Orientation&lt;br&gt;- Teamwork/Partnering&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special conditions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIBC is an equal opportunity employer. It is the Company's policy to recruit and select applicants for employment solely on the basis of their qualifications, with emphasis on selecting the best qualified person for the job. CIBC does not discriminate against applicants based on race, color, religion, sex, national origin, or disability or any other status or condition protected by applicable federal, state or local law.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Skills COBOL&lt;br&gt;DB2&lt;br&gt;EJB (Enterprise JavaBeans)&lt;br&gt;HTML&lt;br&gt;IMS/DB&lt;br&gt;JAVA&lt;br&gt;Accountability&lt;br&gt;Conceptual Thinking&lt;br&gt;Results Orientation&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5768268A-8EC0-4479-91CA-45BF7BCB4F5E</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Systems Developer (Mainframe &amp; Java Application Development)</title>
</post>
