<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>PeopleSoft Lab Consultant :. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Status:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Summary: &lt;br&gt;Analyzes PeopleSoft customizations for upgrades; runs Lab upgrade projects for HRMS, FN, SA Applications; assists Lab team members with their upgrade projects. May deliver upgrades at customer sites. This is a technical role and is based out of Toronto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PeopleSoft experience: Must have upgrade experience on the technical side.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: This position is based out of our Toronto office&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travel requirement: 50% travel. However, you must be willing to travel throughout North America.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Duties/Tasks:&lt;br&gt;· Responsible for evaluating lab upgrade level of effort, analyzing customer modifications, migrating overlapping modifications to the upgrade database and testing to ensure that PeopleSoft maintains a high level of quality.&lt;br&gt;· Effectively communicates with the customer to provide upgrade status, answer questions related to the upgrade and provide post-upgrade support.&lt;br&gt;· Work with lab members to improve lab processes and customer communications. Provide technical support to all resources in the lab.&lt;br&gt;· Running the lab project for HRMS, FN or SA Applications. Guide and ensure timely completion of upgrades.&lt;br&gt;· Responsible for mentoring Associate Consultants on the HR, SA or FN functional areas within an upgrade. Assists lab team members with upgrades.&lt;br&gt;· Preparing detailed upgrade logs and notes and preparing regular status reports, time and expense reports&lt;br&gt;· Assists customers with project management responsibilities.&lt;br&gt;· May deliver upgrades at customer sites.&lt;br&gt;· May be assigned to field consulting projects.&lt;br&gt;· Performs other duties as directed by the Team Leader or Lab Manager.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specific Knowledge, Skills, Education:&lt;br&gt;· 1-2 years PeopleSoft upgrade experience; Functional and technical Knowledge of one or more PeopleSoft Products ( Human Resources, Financials, Student Administration).&lt;br&gt;· Ability to view PeopleSoft upgrade process through the eyes of the customer.&lt;br&gt;· Required technical skills; working knowledge of Unix or OS390, one of PeopleSoft supported database platforms ( Oracle, Informix, SQL Server, DB2 or Sybase); RDBMS: Sybase, Oracle or SQL Server; languages and tools: SQL, Microsoft Project; OS and environments: Windows ( 95,NT), Unix, MS-Dos.&lt;br&gt;· Good understanding of PeopleCode and PeopleTools.&lt;br&gt;· Good understanding of ISO process for Lab upgrades. Recommends and assists in implementing process improvements within the Lab.&lt;br&gt;· Outstanding time management and project management skills.&lt;br&gt;· Excellent communications and organizational skills.&lt;br&gt;· Ability to work in a team environment.&lt;br&gt;· Flexible and easily adapts to change.&lt;br&gt;· Customer passion. Ability to handle customers effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;· Travel up to 50% of the time.&lt;br&gt;Other duties as assigned by manager&lt;br&gt;PeopleSoft (Nasdaq:PSFT - News) is the world's leading provider of application software for the real-time enterprise. PeopleSoft pure Internet software enables organizations to reduce costs and increase productivity by directly connecting customers, suppliers, partners and employees to business processes on-line, in real time. PeopleSoft's integrated, best-in-class applications include Customer Relationship Management, Supply Chain Management, Human Capital Management, Financial Management and Application Integration. Today more than 4,900 organizations in 140 countries run on PeopleSoft software. For more information, visit us at www.peoplesoft.com. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PeopleSoft is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Contact Information :.&lt;br&gt;Frances Song&lt;br&gt;frances_song@peoplesoft.com&lt;br&gt;PeopleSoft Canada&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>578D4F18-4743-4830-A47A-767EA02E6966</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-03-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>PeopleSoft Lab Consultant</title>
</post>
