<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Database Analyst &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At CustomerWorks, we're experts in the Customer Care industry, providing customer relationship management services to our clients, Enbridge Services International, Enbridge Consumers Gas, Enbridge Gas New Brunswick and BC Gas. We've built our expertise on the foundation of quality service combined with advanced technology that makes us a leader in our field. Find out how you can make a difference as a major contributor to our success, by exploring this opportunity in Toronto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Database Analyst&lt;br&gt;In this entry-level position, your main responsibility will be to assist us in automating manual processes. More specifically, you will be called upon to determine reporting requirements, schedule interfaces between multiple systems and liaise with external vendors to resolve technical problems. Initially, you will be expected to possess the aptitude to quickly learn our existing systems, but you must be able to grow into your role enough to lead technical issues on future system upgrades. Your experience with payroll and HRIS databases, ideally gained in an ADP environment, is strengthened by your knowledge of Crystal and Access, and grade 4 certification. You must also be well versed in report writing, data extracts, queries and process mapping.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send your resume to the attention of Elaine Mills, 1st Floor, 500 Consumers Road, North York, Ontario M1K 5E3 Fax: (416) 495-6114 OR E-mail: elaine.mills@ecsi.enbridge.com www.customerworks.net&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Elaine Mills&lt;br&gt;elaine.mills@ecsi.enbridge.com&lt;br&gt;CustomerWorks&lt;br&gt;500 Consumers Road, 1st Floor&lt;br&gt;North York ON M1K 5E3&lt;br&gt;Fax: (416) 495-6114&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5915B569-E382-4438-94AF-E3F0267E245E</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Database Analyst _Entry-level</title>
</post>
