<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Positions Open for Scientists and Engineers &lt;br&gt;(The 1st Korean Brain Pool Program in 2006) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Korean Federation of Science and Technology Societies (KOFST) invites the outstanding scientists and engineers from overseas to work in various research institutes in Korea. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fields; All fields of Science and Technology &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number of Open; Approximately 00 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements; &lt;br&gt;- Doctoral degree holder; more than 5 years overseas experiences in R&amp;D post-doctoral; All nationalities are invited. &lt;br&gt;- Regardless of his/her degree, outstanding overseas Korean or foreign scientists/engineers who have proven achievements &lt;br&gt;and in-depth experiences for more than 5 years in his/her field(s). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invitation Period; - From 3 moths to 2 years &lt;br&gt;- Invitation period may be extended. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial Support; Visiting expenses are paid on monthly basis, in addition Living expenses, round trip airplane tickets and moving expenses will be reimbursed at the beginning of the term. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tasks; &lt;br&gt;- Joint R&amp;D projects as requested by the host organizations in Korea. &lt;br&gt;- Joint R&amp;D projects with new or existing research/development teams. &lt;br&gt;- Special lectures, seminars, conferences. Etc. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Host Organizations; - Government Financed Research Center (Institution) &lt;br&gt;- National/Public Research Center (Institution) &lt;br&gt;- University or University Research Center &lt;br&gt;- Non-Profit Corporation Research Center &lt;br&gt;- Industrial Research Center &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Application Period; By 16th December, 2005 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to apply; Apply for On-line Brain Pool Homepage (http://www.brainpool.or.kr/) &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>59E36402-2E5A-4532-A350-0975D08C0AA3</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-11-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Positions Open for Scientists and Engineers</title>
</post>
