<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;OS/400 Software Developer &lt;br&gt;Type: Full-time employment&lt;br&gt;Location: Markham&lt;br&gt;Department: Research and Development &lt;br&gt;Your primary responsibility will be to design and develop products for our client’s product line. You must be highly motivated, have excellent verbal and written communication and organizational skills, and function well in a team environment. &lt;br&gt;Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;?Design and develop products on OS/400&lt;br&gt;?Design and develop products on UNIX and Windows Platforms&lt;br&gt;?Research new related technologies that may require integration with the existing product line.&lt;br&gt;?Work with Technical Writers to develop product documentation.&lt;br&gt;?Work with QA Testers and Product Support Services to resolve customer and code issues.&lt;br&gt;?Follow the company’s Software Development Methodology.&lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;?Bachelor of Science degree in a technical discipline or 4 years equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;?Minimum of 4 years of C++ design and development experience and minimum 2 years of JAVA&lt;br&gt;?Minimum of 5 years of C and C++ development on the OS/400 platform&lt;br&gt;?Expertise working with Object Oriented techniques&lt;br&gt;?Knowledge of formal language technologies (eg. compilers, interpreters, parsers).&lt;br&gt;?Ability to work in and develop software for multiple operating system environments including Windows, Unix, and OS/390.&lt;br&gt;?Knowledge of all phases of the Software Development Process.&lt;br&gt;?Excellent written and oral communication skills. &lt;br&gt;?Self-disciplined, self-motivated, team player.&lt;br&gt;?Able to work independently on schedule and within resource constraints, given a high-level set of objectives.&lt;br&gt;?Self-disciplined, self-motivated, team player.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Evan Hume&lt;br&gt;ehume@spherion.ca&lt;br&gt;Spherion Workforce Architects&lt;br&gt;2 Bloor st w&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON m4w 3e2&lt;br&gt;Ph: 416 - 944 - 3434&lt;br&gt;Fax: 416 - 944 - 8859&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5AD97AC3-3F6B-4FC7-ABD1-96986F999A26</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-06T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>OS/400 Software Developer</title>
</post>
