<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Toronto Area - Mississauga, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;The Integrated Technology Management Services Business Unit located in Mississauga is actively recruiting for an Analyst - Oracle DBA at the intermediate to senior level to join their team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job responsibilities would include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- installation, upgrades and daily maintenance of the database servers&lt;br&gt;- maintain and monitor a set of standard database processes to ensure the regular database tasks are properly executed&lt;br&gt;- carry out perforamance tuning to leverage the RDBMS capabilities&lt;br&gt;- implement and monitor database security&lt;br&gt;- perform database backup and recovery&lt;br&gt;- participate or lead in the database capacity planning and the server upgrade process&lt;br&gt;- work with database vendors to resolve database related issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will possess a minimum of 5 years experience with hands on Oracle Database Administration in a UNIX environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent understanding of the Outsourcing Services market in Canada and Globally would be preferred.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must have exceptional communication skills (listening, written and oral). You are extremely motivated, well organized and resourceful.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must possess an extremely high comfort level dealing with clients and understanding of the client/service provider relationship.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must be able to travel to other CGI sites within the GTA. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this role, you will be required to carry a shared on call duty pager for after hours support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration, and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join a winning team. CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start day one and include 3 weeks vacation, profit sharing and a stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please. (MR)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of Oracle Database Administration in a UNIX environment&lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of Oracle Database Administration in an Oracle Financial/Peoplesoft environment&lt;br&gt;Nice to Have Skills&lt;br&gt;Hands on working knowledge of AIX Operating System&lt;br&gt;Hands on working knowledge of Shell scripting&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5BB293F7-FF39-4697-8387-FCF93983BE37</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Analyst - Oracle DBA - Intermediate</title>
</post>
