<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>QUESTIONS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1) How many years of experience do you have with the following?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8226; J2EE Development&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8226; .Net/C#&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8226; Tomcat&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2) (If currently employed) Why are you looking for a new job?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3) Why did you leave your last job?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4) How much do you currently earn (Or what did you earn in your last position)?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5) What salary rate are you looking for to make your next move?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6) This job is based in Brampton, On are you willing/able to commute to this location?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7) How soon would you be able to start if a job offer was to be made?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8) What is the best phone number to reach you on during business hrs?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Senior Java/J2EE Developer&lt;br&gt;Location: Brampton, On&lt;br&gt;Duration: Permanent&lt;br&gt;Apply via email to: nick@gurulink.ca &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SENIOR J2EE/JAVA DEVELOPER &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client is looking for senior Java/J2EE Developers with a solid background in C#/.Net technologies a successful candidate will have some of the following attributes;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 6+ years in software development with relevant academic qualifications. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Hands on experience in Java/J2EE development as well as associated technologies.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Previous or current experience or background with C#/.Net technologies&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Design Patterns and any mainstream application server e.g. Tomcat, Weblogic. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Should have strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to competitive salary and benefits the position also offers the following;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; A 7.5 hour work day and no weekends required.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Overtime pay even for SALARIED employees, like this position.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; An Employee Share Accumulation plan (matches 25% first year, 33% second year, 50% third year and each year after).&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; A Guaranteed pension plan.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 50% Discount on all the company products and services (on average savings of up to $5000/yr)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Free Parking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Makata&lt;br&gt;Tel: 416.644.3096 - Fax: 416.352.0106 &lt;br&gt;Email: nick@gurulink.ca Web: www.gurulink.ca &lt;br&gt;Recruitment Consultant&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;GuruLink www.gurulink.ca </content>
    <postId>5BCB79BD-6E15-4D96-90CF-43D985716BB6</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>JAVA/J2EE DEVELOPER</title>
</post>
