<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>프로콤에서 저한테 보낸 이메일입니다.&lt;br&gt;참조하세요.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The position below is currently available through Procom. If you meet the qualifications and are interested in this opportunity please apply as per the instructions below. Please note, this automated email has been sent to you as the result of a successful keyword search on your resume within our database. Please use discretion by only applying to positions that best suit your qualifications. If you wish to remove yourself from future mailings, please click the link supplied below. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Programmer/Analyst &lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills: COBOL (5 years); IMS (5 years); DB2 (5 years); &lt;br&gt;Nice-to-Have Skills: Banking (1 year); &lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto (Ontario, Canada) &lt;br&gt;Duration: 6 Months &lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary: Negotiable &lt;br&gt;Start Date: ASAP &lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking for a Mainframe developer, must have recent banking experience and IMS DC experience. &lt;br&gt;Required skills: &lt;br&gt;-COBOL &lt;br&gt;-DB2 &lt;br&gt;-IMS DB/DC &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROCOM SERVICES &lt;br&gt;A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 1700 consultants on assignment. For over 25 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our consultants. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and consultants consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please submit your most recent resume to: &lt;br&gt;Ross Cadastre &lt;br&gt;rossc@procom.ca&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5CE67DC0-AADC-4CD5-A9DC-F6330678343F</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-05-31T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mainframe Position</title>
</post>
