<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Quality Assurance/Beta Manager&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Careers that know no boundaries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOL Canada Inc. is a strategic alliance between America Online, Inc., the world&amp;#47977; leader in interactive services and Royal Bank, Canada&amp;#47977; premier global financial services group. Working in our dynamic, creative and stimulating environment you will have the opportunity to influence how the Internet impacts on the world. Check out the following opportunity that we have to offer and prepare for a career without limits. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quality Assurance/Beta Manager&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE JOB&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48610;anage a Team of 4-6 QA Test / Beta Staff&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48605;iring, Training and Development of QA Test / Beta Staff&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48610;anage an English and French software BETA program&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48610;anage all aspects of QA Testing: GUI testing, functionality testing, performance/stress testing, system and regression testing, and integration testing&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48609;ead development and execution of Test Plans, Test Cases/Suites by the team&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48609;ead bug scrubs&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48610;anage the implementation of a new Development and QA Test Lab&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48594;utomate the Testing Process with Test Tools and Techniques&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48606;mplement new Test Processes and QA Standards&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48615;egularly Track ColQuality Levels of software products&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48601;ffective collaboration with Product Management, Project Management, Technology Development (local and in the US) and Customer Support&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48615;eporting and Presenting of QA Testing Results&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48594;pplication of Statistics and statistical methods to QA Testing where appropriate&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;ossess and Demonstrate Strong Written and Verbal/Presentation Skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48598;ommit to additional hours when required for urgent project completion from time to time&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;ossess and Demonstrate excellent organizational, prioritization and analytical skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;articipate in the selection process for new hires for Technology and Development department&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48605;ands-on management of the QA Test / Beta staff: coaching, counseling, evaluations, and discipline&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology Experience Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48612;ne or more of Test Automation Tools: Mercury WinRunner, Rational TestStudio/Robot, Seque SilkTest, Compuware QACentre, Empirix/RSW eTest Suite&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48606;nternet Technologies (HTML, XML/XSL, etc.) and Standards&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48598;onfiguration Management Technology (CVS, Visual SourceSafe or RCS)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48595;ug Tracking Technology (Bugzilla, Vantive)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;lus to have experience with all phases of software/web application design, development testing&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;lus to have Programming experience with Visual Basic/Visual C++, C/C++, Java&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48621;indows 95/98/Me/2000/XP&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48619;NIX (Solaris, Linux)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48615;DBMS (Sybase, Oracle)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Experience:&lt;br&gt;?+ years of QA Management of at least 3-4 person QA team&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;referably some previous experience with coordinating BETA programs&lt;br&gt;?+ years of Project Management&lt;br&gt;?+ years of a QA Experience&lt;br&gt;?+ years of software development Experience&lt;br&gt;Preferably experience with managing/operating a QA Test Lab&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48595;achelors Degree in Computer Science, MIS, Engineering or related Technical Degree&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REWARDS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOL Canada has a lively team environment and deploys state of the art technology . We offer a competitive compensation package and excellent benefits, along with an outstanding career opportunity. Apply your skills with a worldwide leader and experience the rewards we have to offer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send your resume with salary history in confidence to Human Resources Department, Recruiter, AOL Canada; e-mail llhawke@aol.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: LH 41&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;llhawke@aol.com&lt;br&gt;AOL Canada&lt;br&gt;55 St. Clair Ave West&lt;br&gt;Toronto&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5D12CB1A-C0B2-466F-830E-BED3DA732A79</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-26T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Quality Assurance - Beta Manager</title>
</post>
