<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Profile &lt;br&gt; Advertisement number: 249954 &lt;br&gt; Title: E-commerce (electronic commerce) software developer (VB.net ASP.net MCSD Certifed) (NOC: 2174)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Terms of Employment: Permanent, Full Time, Day &lt;br&gt; Salary: $35,000.00 to $45,000.00 Yearly for 40 hours per week &lt;br&gt; Anticipated Start Date: As soon as possible&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Location: Toronto Centre, Ontario (2 vacancies) &lt;br&gt; Skill Requirements:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Education: Completion of college/CEGEP/vocational or technical training, Other: MCSD with at least exam 70-305/315 VB.net/VC#.net 1 of 70-306/316 &lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Other: MCSD &lt;br&gt;Experience: 1 - 2 years &lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Read English, Write English, Other: Comfortable speaking with clients &lt;br&gt;Work Setting Experience: Consulting firm, Software developer &lt;br&gt;Operating Systems: MS Windows 95/98/NT/2000 &lt;br&gt;Programming Languages: ASP, Visual Basic &lt;br&gt;Applications: MS Office &lt;br&gt;Management Systems (erp or db): MS SQL Server &lt;br&gt;Other: Object-Oriented design &lt;br&gt;Generic Skills: Computer use (ex., use software packages; knowledge of hardware; work with computer-operated machinery), Writing skills (ex., enter information on forms; write to inform, persuade, or analyze), Reading skills (ex., follow written directions; interpret documents like charts, maps; acquire specialized knowledge), Working with others (ex., work with individual or team; build consensus), Planning and organizing skills (ex., manage priorities; order tasks efficiently), Problem-solving skills (ex., identify problem causes; determine steps to resolve; assess solution), Speaking and listening skills (ex., communicate clearly and effectively; follow directions; mediate disputes) &lt;br&gt;Other Information: Designing solutions using web technologies: Windows Architecture. Experience with Interface design&amp; development of database architectureASP, VB, VB.net, C#, ASP.netExchange, SharePoint, Commerce ServerMS Office/MS Project, MSDN. Excellent communication skills. Please send resumes in a Word attachment to jennifer@definityglobal.com &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Employer: Definity Global Solutions Inc. (Placement Agency) &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; How to Apply:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;By E-mail: jennifer@definityglobal.com &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Business Profile: Our organization provides IT, Sales &amp; Marketing and General Office staffing for a variety of industries. &lt;br&gt; Web Site: www.definityglobal.com &lt;br&gt; Advertised until: 2003/03/11 &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5DB3C09B-19FE-4A82-9F9E-7CF86476752F</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-26T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>E-commerce (electronic commerce) software developer (VB.net ASP.net MCSD Certifed)</title>
</post>
