<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>ARE YOU PASSIONATE ABOUT DEVELOPING GAMES ??&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Now is your chance to join the Ganz team that has brought you such products as Webkinz and Webkinz Jr.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You can be a part of developing new&lt;br&gt; adventures !!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Now is your chance to join the creative team that has brought these vibrant worlds to life. Ganz is seeking talented and motivated people with a proven love of online entertainment for these positions:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;JAVA DEVELOPER&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Design and develop high performance, scalable applications that integrate with a Flash client.&lt;br&gt;Design, develop and maintain high performance scalable applications for a high user volume environment.&lt;br&gt;Design and execute performance and load tests using proprietary tools, as well as commercial tools such as JMeter or other open-source tools.&lt;br&gt;Create and maintain detailed and accurate documentation.&lt;br&gt;Collaborate with Architects and Developers from the Flash, PHP and Java teams to ensure the applications are integrated and working efficiently.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Computer Science/Engineering degree is preferred.&lt;br&gt;A minimum of 5 years experience with JAVA/J2EE development, involving both front and back end development.&lt;br&gt;Experience with IDEs, such as Eclipse and NetBeans.&lt;br&gt;Experience with source control tools, such as SVN and CVS.&lt;br&gt;Experience with XML, XSD and JAXB.&lt;br&gt;Experience with Java frameworks (Spring, Struts, and Hibernate) is an asset.&lt;br&gt;Good communication skills.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Nice to have qualifications include experience with any of the following:&lt;br&gt;JBoss, Tomcat, PostGreSQL and MySQL.&lt;br&gt;Velocity, iBATIS and Web Services.&lt;br&gt;Java socket servers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Interested candidates are invited to forward resumes by email to &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;careers@ganz.com. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Please check out our websites at: www.webkinz.com and www.webkinzjr.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Apply V</content>
    <postId>5E6D5061-24E7-4B60-87D2-BBB29E6538BC</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GANZ Games -Java Developer</title>
</post>
