<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>신덕현</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>임정숙</author>
            <date>2003-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>&lt;a href=http://www.multimediator.com target=_blank&gt;http://www.multimediator.com&lt;/a&gt;  (job posting section)</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[사이트 목록]&lt;br&gt;http://worksearch.gc.ca/english/index.pl - Worksearch (캐나다 정부가 운영)&lt;br&gt;http://www.canadajobs.com&lt;br&gt;http://www.netjobs.com/&lt;br&gt;http://www.canadiancareers.com/&lt;br&gt;http://www.headhunter.net/jobseeker/jobs/jobfindica.asp?ch=ICA&lt;br&gt;http://www.monster.com/ , http://www.occ.com/ &lt;br&gt;http://www.brassring.com/&lt;br&gt;http://www.workopolis.com/&lt;br&gt;http://www.employmentnews.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[사이트 보충설명] &lt;br&gt;http://worksearch.gc.ca/english/index.pl&lt;br&gt;- 캐나다 정부가 운영&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.canadajobs.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.netjobs.com/&lt;br&gt;netJobs offers you fast and easy job searching and resume posting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.canadiancareers.com/&lt;br&gt;CanadianCareers.com is one of the original career sites on the web for Canadians.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;First online back in 1996 (then known as the Canadian Career Page), we have established a reputation for providing reliable career and employment information for Canadians from coast-to-coast. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.headhunter.net/jobseeker/jobs/jobfindica.asp?ch=ICA&lt;br&gt;With over 250,000 job postings representing more than 10,000 of the nation's employers, Headhunter.net is the fastest growing job awareness site today. Headhunter.net is rated first among cross-industry, national online recruiting services in quality of results and user satisfaction. Its highly functional interface and dedication to customer service has earned Headhunter.net a reputation for dependability and results among job seekers and job posters. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.monster.com/ , http://www.occ.com/ &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.brassring.com/&lt;br&gt;Introducing BrassRing.com, a technology based information and career portal. BrassRing brings together the best resources for the high-tech professional. Formerly incpad by Westech, BrassRing changes the face of online recruiting by dramatically expanding the site's services while retaining its greatest strengths. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.workopolis.com/&lt;br&gt;Canada's Biggest Job Site, now hosting over 31,000 Jobs. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.employmentnews.com/&lt;br&gt;If you are looking to hire or be hired with your premiere career and job resource in the Greater Toronto Area as well as Ottawa, Ontario, Canada. &lt;br&gt;Our searchable resume database, career and training ads, and resume writing assistant are here to serve you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</content>
    <postId>5F138811-8BF3-482D-A9F0-DC792CE9D2A2</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-09-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>취업검색사이트 모음</title>
</post>
