<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Send your resume to khboo@hotmail.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;==========================================================&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DESCRIPTION:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working as an Actuate Developer in the Product Development and Implementation team that is in the process of developing a global web based financial application. The potential candidate will develop complex reports. They will need to understand the basic concepts of the application as well as the specifications for the reports and will interact heavily with the Business Analysts to ensure that the reports meet stipulated specifications. The project will also involve the customization of Actuate web templates using Actuates’ Active Portal, version 6 and also solving any issues relating to DHTML conversion of Actuate reports. The candidate will need to customize the default menu items (search menu, navbar etc.) provided by Actuate in DHTML. They will also need to provide appropriate documentation and will be required to assist in testing, and implementation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Develop complex Actuate 6 web reports that present data from various relational database environments including Oracle, DB2, and SQL Server&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Design Actuate web templates and customize Actuate Active Portal&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Assist in the design and development of multi-tier web based applications utilizing primarily HTML, DHTML, JavaScript and Java Server Pages (JSP) with some possible exposure to XML and the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Produce technical documentation of all applications and reports that are developed and assist in implementation and post implementation support&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; University degree in computer science or equivalent in combined formal education and work experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; SQL Knowledge and understanding of relational databases specifically Oracle 9i&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Result oriented individual&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Ability to interpret and translate functional specifications into Actuate Reports&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Capable of working under tight schedules and deadlines&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; 2+ years of experience utilizing Actuate Active Portal and creating complex Actuate reports&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; 2+ years of extensive experience in Java and J2EE such as JavaScript, Servlets, JSP, EJB, and JDBC&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Experience in the financial services industry and knowledge of the securities industry is an asset&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; A team player with a flexible and positive attitude&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Good time management skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61553; Knowledge of SQL Server 2000, XML, and Data Warehousing concepts will be considered an asset&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>6231BC1F-5516-4FE2-AAC5-F917D4A36E70</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-04-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Looking for Actuate Developer</title>
</post>
