<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bold. &lt;br&gt;Entrepreneurial. &lt;br&gt;Flexible.&lt;br&gt;At Atos Origin, we believe in our unique approach to traditional IT consulting and services, yet temper it with the sophistication you'd expect from a 25-years-strong global leader. While taking enterprises into perennially rewarding territory, we've grown to employ 27,000 employees in 33 countries and earn $2.4 billion (US) in annual revenue. Considered one of the top ten consulting firms worldwide, we've also been rated by Gartner as a leader in ERP lifecycle management. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read on to learn more about our newest Toronto based opportunity. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Application Support team is seeking a Senior Cobol/CICS technical consultant to provide remote support services to one of their clients in the manufacturing industry. You will be working together with your team members to investigate problems, create and implement solutions while providing excellent customer service at all times. You will be able to utilize your sound communication skills and your deep knowledge to mentor some of the junior members on the team. This role requires initial travel to the US but will be purely Toronto based after the transition period. This is a full-time, permanent position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate must have 4+ years consulting (on-site) experience as well as senior/team leader skills. You have a proven ability (4+ years) to maintain / further develop an application that is written on CICS/COBOL in an IDMS dB environment. Ideally, you have 1+ year RMDS (reporting) experience and have worked in a Support Group environment before. You are open to be available on stand-by 24x7. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preferably, you have experience in one or more of the following: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Training&lt;br&gt;SAS Reporting&lt;br&gt;Vision: Results&lt;br&gt;ConnectDirect (ftp client) for EDI &lt;br&gt;APICS certified&lt;br&gt;FOCUS reporting.&lt;br&gt;Education&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Computer Programming Diploma / Degree is required. Certifications in CICS &amp; IDMS are preferred.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Third party firms need not submit resumes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visit us at:&lt;br&gt;Atos Origin, Inc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Submit your Resume here:&lt;br&gt;careers@atosorigin.com&lt;br&gt;Contact Information&lt;br&gt;National Recruiting Center&lt;br&gt;careers@atosorigin.com&lt;br&gt;Atos Origin Inc.&lt;br&gt;430 Mountain Ave&lt;br&gt;Murray Hill, NJ 07974&lt;br&gt;Ph:(866)JOIN-AOI&lt;br&gt;Fax:(888)551-8223&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: JC-1672-CC&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;National Recruiting Center&lt;br&gt;careers@atosorigin.com&lt;br&gt;Atos Origin&lt;br&gt;430 Mountain Ave.&lt;br&gt;Murray Hill NJ 07974&lt;br&gt;Ph: (866) 564-6264&lt;br&gt;Fax: (888) 551-8223&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>64131E22-00C5-4540-A1FD-B60367DD7E60</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>COBOL / CICS Tech Consultant HOT HOT HOT</title>
</post>
