<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ACCPAC International, Inc., a subsidiary of Computer Associates International Inc. (NYSE: CA), provides small and mid-size businesses a broad range of end-to-end business management applications designed to enhance customers’ competitive advantage. Product lines include ACCPAC Advantage Series™, ACCPAC Pro Series™, ACCPAC HR Series™, ACCPAC Business Analysis Suite™, ACCPAC eTransact®, ACCPAC Exchange™, ACCPAC eCRM™, ACCPAC Warehouse Management System™, ACCPAC ePOS™, Simply Accounting®, FAXserve™ and ACCPAC Messenger™.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based in Pleasanton, Calif., USA, with offices in Australia, Canada, India, Ireland, Mexico, the Middle East, the Netherlands, South Africa, Southeast Asia and the United Kingdom, ACCPAC has more than 500,000 customers and more than 6,500 business partners in more than 130 countries worldwide. For more information about ACCPAC and our products, call 1-800-945-8007 in North America, or visit ACCPAC at www.accpac.com and www.accpaconline.com. We have an immediate opening for a Windows Programmer in our Toronto, ON office to join our Research &amp; Development team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Windows Programmer - Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be a part of a successful software development team that designs and develops trend-setting applications using state-of-the-art database, user interface and Internet technology? We are looking for motivated individuals with hands-on experience who want to be involved in the development of market-leading products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience/Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·Minimum 2-3 years of programming experience in a Windows environment.&lt;br&gt;·Thorough knowledge of C/C++, VB, DAO, ADO, Windows API, and SQL.&lt;br&gt;·Experience with Java: JDBC, MS JAVA (WFC), XML.&lt;br&gt;·Experience with MS Access and MS SQL Server.&lt;br&gt;·Accounting background and/or experience with Point of Sales highly desirable.&lt;br&gt;·Experience with IBM DB2 and Pervasive SQL are definite assets.&lt;br&gt;·Excellent communication skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·University degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACCPAC® offers a competitive salary, full benefits package, and training and career development opportunities in a casual but professional work environment. We also provide daily breakfast for all our staff! To apply, submit your r&amp;eacute;sum&amp;eacute; (referencing the position title) in confidence to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Human Resources&lt;br&gt;canada.jobs@accpac.com&lt;br&gt;ACCPAC International, Inc.&lt;br&gt;13700 International Place, 3rd Floor&lt;br&gt;Richmond BC V6V 2X8&lt;br&gt;Fax: 604.233.3050&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>64709AEC-7298-4737-B621-CD0D97B0B0D2</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-Windows Programmer</title>
</post>
