<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Programmer Analyst (3)&lt;br&gt;SEARS CANADA INC.&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario, CANADA&lt;br&gt;Posted Aug 6, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unit Name: Sears Headquarters - Downtown Toronto, Yonge and Dundas &lt;br&gt;Relocation Plan Applies: No &lt;br&gt;Hours of Work: Full Time - 40.00 hours per week&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Channel/Dept: Retail Systems &lt;br&gt;Reports to: Project Manager Retail Systems &lt;br&gt;Duration of Posting: August 6, 2010 to August 13, 2010 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Information Technology department is a large, diverse IT shop that develops innovative technology solutions for all of our internal Sears customers including retail, merchandising and corporate business channels. We are committed to understanding our customers' business challenges and helping them achieve their goals by using technology to fit their needs. Because of the diverse businesses we support, you'll have the chance to work on multiple platforms, utilizing a number of different languages, tools and software. We offer a supportive team environment that is focused on learning and encourages our associates to build their skills &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you passionate about designing and integrating new applications for our business partners? Then consider Programmer Analyst 3 as a possible next step in your career path. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position is responsible for the development, integration and maintenance of complex business applications to support opportunities identified by customers. This involves performing: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;. systems analysis, systems architecture and functional design for new systems or enhancements to existing ones; &lt;br&gt;. application provisioning for complex platform systems, including solving related problems; &lt;br&gt;. project management and providing guidance and direction to other team members; and &lt;br&gt;. system implementation, including testing and training activities to integrate the system into users' environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a Programmer Analyst 3 you will also be responsible for providing operational support to highly complex production systems, including resolution of problems in an efficient and timely manner. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Success in this role calls for advanced computer skills, including the ability to work on multiple platforms and projects of high complexity. The ideal job candidate will have completed a three-year community college degree in Computer Systems or Computer Engineering (or equivalent). Experience as a Programmer Analyst would also be an asset. Other qualifications for this job include: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;. Leadership skills, including the ability to coach and train les experienced team members &lt;br&gt;. Organization/planning skills and the ability to meet deadlines, and work effectively under stressful conditions &lt;br&gt;. Good verbal and written communication skills &lt;br&gt;. Analytical and problem-solving skills &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position provides an excellent opportunity to broaden your technical knowledge pertaining to complex systems/processes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We offer competitive benefits, incentive compensation, and a generous employee discount on Sears merchandise and services. We are committed to encouraging internal development and providing career enrichment opportunities wherever possible. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please be advised that only those applicants who are selected for interviews will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Posting Code: ITOPP</content>
    <postId>64D3C5AD-5E61-41BE-982C-34D089CBC3F4</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-08-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Programmer Analyst - SEARS</title>
</post>
