<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>One of TEKSystems largest Media clients is currently seeking a Flash Developer for a 3 month contract in the downtown Toronto area.&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;-Designing, developing, and unit testing of Flash based Internet applications and games, utilizing object oriented ActionScript.&lt;br&gt;-Ensuring that best-practices are followed and that code is optimized in order to ensure that applications are operating as efficiently as possible on a high traffic websites.&lt;br&gt;-Participating in the software development process from design to release.&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;-Experience in developing Flash or ActionScript and/or Flash based games.&lt;br&gt;-Development experience with Flash, CSS and XML.&lt;br&gt;-Experience with multi-use environments and high traffic websites.&lt;br&gt;-Strong analytical and problem solving skills.&lt;br&gt;-Excellent written and verbal communications skills.&lt;br&gt;-Detail-oriented, well organized, quick learner with very strong technical aptitude and the ability to work concurrently on multiple projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please be aware that we are anticipating a large volume of applications; only qualified candidates will be contacted for this role.&lt;br&gt;Join TEKsystemsⓒ and get your career on the fast track. As one of North America's premiere technology staffing and services companies, we are passionate about deploying high-caliber IT and communications expertise. To satisfy our constant need for expertise, we actively seek talented technical professionals with all levels of information technology and communications skills. Because of our industry-specific focus, expertise, and connections, we can find you highly desirable positions you might not otherwise know about. From customized training and flexible hiring options to dedicated teams of recruiters working to find you the right opportunity, TEKsystems offers all the tools you need achieve to your long-term career goals.&lt;br&gt;Make your next career move with TEKsystems!&lt;br&gt;We respect your right to privacy. Your personal information is only collected, used and disclosed by TEksystems Canada Inc. in accordance with our Privacy Policy . Your personal information is never sold or leased to any external company.&lt;br&gt;TEKsystems Canada Inc. is an Allegis Group, Inc. company.&lt;br&gt;Contact: Meaghan Jacqueline Stewart&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, ON</content>
    <postId>64F31215-44C7-40EE-BEE4-48DBFD63D894</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Flash Developer - TEKsystems</title>
</post>
