<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Snapshot&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;Other Pay: $20'000 - $50'000 (up to $80'000 OTE)&lt;br&gt;Employee Type: Full-Time Employee&lt;br&gt;Manages Others: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Information Technology&lt;br&gt;Experience: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Post Date: 04/03/2010 Contact Information&lt;br&gt;Ref ID: holophrastic-0&lt;br&gt;Description&lt;br&gt;Pipelines is our internal and proprietary web development platform -- written on top of Perl, of course. Call it a template language if you must, but basically it automates away 90% of typical web development -- connecting to the database, user logins, security, user preferences, et cetera. It also throws umbrella features over everything. It's really cool. As most of pipelines pulls from the world of Perl, and it's perl core is constantly upgraded, Perl developers are particularly suited to this job -- actually a career. Pipelines includes dozens of sub-syntax languages of natures similar to regular expressions, so if you can parse a regular expression in your head, cryptic as it may be, pipelines becomes crazy easy. Work is explosive now, so we're hiring immediately. It is expected that you'll take afew months to get up to speed -- the learning curve is quite steep, but the work itself is really easy, and we have a lot of fun with it.Required: raw perl (no modules), javascript, mysql, html, css. An understanding of the general flow of a web-site from database, to backend server, to output stream, to browser client and back again. An understanding of the general problems in web development like caching and speed and security.Desired: jscript, english writing, regular expressions, basic graphic work (cropping, colour correction, sizing, compressing)</content>
    <postId>66C504A4-9A5D-4CEA-94AF-26C127F2C77F</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Perl/JavaScript Web Developer</title>
</post>
