<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>D Park</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Purpose&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The position belongs to a development team that develops, maintains, and supports applications for Scotia Capital, primarily in Scotia Capital Finance, Securities Operations, and Group Treasury areas. The incumbent will be reporting to the development manager and the project manager. The candidate will participate in project meetings and business requirement analytics. Hence the candidate must interact effectively with other functional teams in the Department such as Business Analysts, Database Administrators, Change Control, and Production Support. It is essential that the incumbent be proactive and eager to learn.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Complexity of Position&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At least 3 years of experience in developing applications with Visual Studio 2003/2005&lt;br&gt;At least 3 years of experience and strong knowledge with MS-SQL and/or Oracle&lt;br&gt;Good knowledge and working experience in C#, ASP.NET&lt;br&gt;Knowledge and programming experience in Java, JSP, MQ and UNIX an valuable asset&lt;br&gt;Good working knowledge in object oriented programming&lt;br&gt;Good working knowledge in secure web application development&lt;br&gt;Disciplined in development methodology and knowlegde of full development life cycle.&lt;br&gt;Familiar with source code version control process&lt;br&gt;Finance and banking experience an asset&lt;br&gt;Self-starter and be able to handle multiple tasks and priorities&lt;br&gt;Strong communication and interpersonal skill&lt;br&gt;Strong analytical and problem solving skills to provide effective user support&lt;br&gt;Must be flexible to adapt to a dynamic environment.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Skills&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or related disciplines&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Participate in the development and support of cost effective and efficient applications or prototypes of low to medium complexity according to standards to meet the demands of the high availability, complex, on-line transaction processing environment. This involves participating in the system design, developing the required programs, performing unit testing and participating in the integrated system tests.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide production and user acceptance testing application support to assigned applications by identifying, evaluating and resolving problems of low to medium complexity and escalating to management as per documented procedures. The incumbent is required to carry a beeper to provide timely user support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participate in the implementation of new systems or enhancements by running required conversion programs, performing shakedown testing of the production environments, preparing the Change Control Release documentation and running the parallel test cycles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keep current on rapidly changing technological trends, self teach new technologies and maintain a broad understanding of the Division's business and technology strategies.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Hiring Officer:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Christopher Bieniek&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Manager, Staffing &amp; Recruitment&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Branch/Department:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Staffing &amp; Planning - Central Canada&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Mailing Address:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 56846 &lt;br&gt;44 King Street West&lt;br&gt;21st Floor&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Canada M5H1H1 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;E-Mail Address:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; chris.bieniek@scotiabank.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Phone:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 416-866-4586&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;Fax:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 416-866-3837&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>671A63D4-D566-438A-A25B-39AEE2634141</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-12-11T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Scotia-Capital: Programmer Analyst II</title>
</post>
