<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Sae Whan Kim</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>임 정숙</author>
            <date>2001-11-09T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>faster loding time???</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hello Ladies/Gents;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First of all, my apology for not writing in Korean...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you for visiting this GeSiPan. &lt;br&gt;I would like to take this opportunity to introduce myself to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My name is Steven Kim, and as a member of Web Maintenance/Operation&lt;br&gt;team, I am assigned to this Gesipan to take a good care of it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not having had much experience in this sort of responsibility,&lt;br&gt;I am a bit afraid and ,at the same time, excited about what we are&lt;br&gt;going to do with it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, I will try to make the Gesipan rolling strong and &lt;br&gt;a useful vehicle to have lots of members enjoying the ride.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another words, I will try to do my best to keep this Gesipan &lt;br&gt;useful and ,in consequence, it will contribute positively to members who are in job market or not directly or indirectly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The main goal of this Gesipan is to share information on jobs and anything related.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For example, you could post a job information if your company has&lt;br&gt;an opening, or your job search experience, etc. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone is welcomed to post any job related information, any if there is any questions asked, of course, I or other members will try to &lt;br&gt;answer it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would you not join me to make this Gesipan a successful one ?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope to meet a lot of people thru this Gesipan in future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>67313560-E211-40E8-8442-DF7A92EC0E75</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-09-24T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Hello...</title>
</post>
