<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>IT Specialist&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TDBFG Description&lt;br&gt;TD Bank Financial Group is the seventh largest bank in North America by branches and serves approximately 17 million customers. Ranked among the world's leading on-line financial services firms, our 74,000 employees around the world offer and support a full range of financial products and services through:&lt;br&gt;. Canadian Personal and Commercial Banking&lt;br&gt;. Wealth Management &lt;br&gt;. Wholesale Banking&lt;br&gt;. Insurance&lt;br&gt;. U.S. Personal and Commercial Banking &lt;br&gt;. Corporate Support Areas&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We operate in a number of locations in key financial centres around the globe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department Overview&lt;br&gt;Provides Detail Design, Build, Unit Test, Level 2/3 Support of software deemed Middleware across all hardware/OS platforms. This includes products such as WebSphere Application Server, WebSphere Portal, Apache Web Server, IBM Web Server (IHS), Pega Workflow, File net, Data Power, WESB. and others.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Service Manager (TSM) of Pega and Filenet shared services will provide technical management and oversight for these shared services including the underpinning infrastructure platform(s) they require. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description&lt;br&gt;Job Description/Accountabilities: Mandatory qualifications include excellent communication (both written and oral) and interpersonal skills. The candidate must be organized, self motivated, as well as a team player and be able to participate in the knowledge transfer of information with peers and management. The candidate will also be accountable for technical coaching and developing of other team members. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory technical skills include:&lt;br&gt;. consult and advise project teams on the best practices for infrastructure related configurations&lt;br&gt;. Comfortable with working in a rapidly changing, technically complex environment.&lt;br&gt;. Proficiency with MS office product suite (Word, Excel PowerPoint etc.).&lt;br&gt;. experience in designing infrastructures for web services&lt;br&gt;Service Strategy&lt;br&gt;. Ensures alignment between service and platform strategy &lt;br&gt;. Provides input to Technology Strategy &lt;br&gt;. Single accountability for service infrastructure solution&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Service Marketing &amp; Consumer Mgmt.&lt;br&gt;. Provides technical support to the Shared Service Owner in the marketing and consumer management of the service&lt;br&gt;. Provides Guidance in forecasting platform and shared service consumption &lt;br&gt;. Accountable to translate business requirements into technical requirements for non-functional platform requirements - working with Platform Owners and Architecture&lt;br&gt;. Responsible for understanding how functional business requirements are translated and provide consulting as required &lt;br&gt;. Coordinates Platform Owners to manage service consumption of platforms &lt;br&gt;. Accountable for measurement and reporting of shared service infrastructure&lt;br&gt;. Identify business opportunities to better leverage services or reduce consumption / cost&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial Mgmt.&lt;br&gt;. Consults on planning and management of infrastructure and service investments &lt;br&gt;. Responsible for financial management of shared infrastructure (e.g. platform consumption)&lt;br&gt;. Reports to ISET in Quarterly Service Review &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Service Quality Mgmt.&lt;br&gt;. Work with Service Owner to create Service SLA&lt;br&gt;. Responsible for ongoing service delivery&lt;br&gt;. Accountable for interoperability of underpinning platforms&lt;br&gt;. Proactively manages shared service capacity and workload Provide oversight and management of consumption of infrastructure platforms used to deliver shared service &lt;br&gt;. Provide input to Platform OLAs &lt;br&gt;. Accountable for execution of standard operational disciplines of incident, problem and change management to meet service requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Requirements&lt;br&gt;. Specific Educational Requirements/Accreditations: College Diploma or University degree in Computer Science &lt;br&gt;. Design, Deployment, Operational experience with Pega Business Process Management and Filenet Document Management systems&lt;br&gt;. Practical experience with Windows, x/OS technologies.&lt;br&gt;. Technical knowledge of TDBFG legacy business web applications &lt;br&gt;. Familiarity with the other Web and Application Servers, Workflow infrastructure &lt;br&gt;. The successful applicant must have a solid understanding of Development, Project Management, Incident, Change, and Problem Management methodologies as well as solid experience in a large Production environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;www.workopolis.com 에서 펌...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;그럼 이만</content>
    <postId>67A39448-A2EF-48F3-B173-6544073DD0A7</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>IT Specialist From TDSB</title>
</post>
