<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Oracle Developer,&lt;br&gt;CHRISTIAN CHILDREN'S FUND OF CANADA&lt;br&gt;GTA, ON, CANADA; Markham, ON, CANADA; Toronto, ON, CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;Posted Mar 17, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian Children's Fund of Canada (CCFC) is an international development organization committed to helping children and their families who live in poverty around the globe. Help that includes education, clean water, nutritious food and health care. CCFC works side-by-side with trusted and proven colleagues in developing countries emphasizing child-centered community development.&lt;br&gt;Christ's example of personal, caring love inspires the dedicated workers of Christian Children's Fund of Canada. And the power of one caring team member to influence the successful development of a child, a family and a community is all it takes to launch global change. Work with us. Work through us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Summary:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position with Information Technology is responsible for providing critical and important database related services to CCFC as a whole. Including but not limited to :&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Primary production database (Oracle 10g) development and support/database administration&lt;br&gt;PL/SQL Development&lt;br&gt;Development/ testing database (Oracle 10g/11g) support/administration&lt;br&gt;Oracle Forms&lt;br&gt;Oracle Reports&lt;br&gt;Project planning and reporting&lt;br&gt;Role Details:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsible for the development of all IT related database infrastructure and services, including but not limited to:&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Oracle 10g and 11&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;PL/SQL&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Oracle Forms&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Oracle Reports&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Navision&lt;br&gt;Enhance the quality of database reporting and forms to support CCFC users.&lt;br&gt;Maintain detailed and up-to-date documentation on all CCFC IT systems.&lt;br&gt;Administration of corporate critical Oracle databases.&lt;br&gt;Practice and maintain accepted Project Management concepts, principles and reporting for all IT related projects.&lt;br&gt;Delivery of IT projects and IT related cross-functional assignments.&lt;br&gt;Assist in solution design and delivery within assigned projects while working closely with project team and consultants to meet business requirements and to ensure database considerations are represented.&lt;br&gt;Assist in specialized and complex analysis for the purpose of enhancing and upgrading existing programs/processes and problem solving diagnostics by researching, analyzing and assessing the impact, effectiveness and feasibility of proposed changes.&lt;br&gt;Assist in Business Continuity/DR plan to minimize the negative impact that such an event may cause and to ensure that all systems are restored as quickly as possible.&lt;br&gt;Assist in maintaining and developing relations, with external vendors and with internal departments.&lt;br&gt;Perform other related duties as assigned.&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;Experience in a Windows/Active Directory environment&lt;br&gt;Solid knowledge of Oracle Database technology&lt;br&gt;5 + years experience in Oracle Reports+ years experience in Oracle Forms&lt;br&gt;Solid PL/SQL knowledge and associated skills&lt;br&gt;5+ years experience developing complex business applications using Oracle Forms as the development tool.&lt;br&gt;2+ years experience in Oracle database administration&lt;br&gt;Experience with Oracle 10g and 11g.&lt;br&gt;Project management and documentation skills&lt;br&gt;Ability to integrate well with other IT team members&lt;br&gt;Knowledge current with latest technology changes&lt;br&gt;Ability to express complex technical concepts effectively, both verbally and written, to both technical staff and to business staff with proven presentation and facilitation skills&lt;br&gt;Satisfactory current Candian criminal record check required for successful candidates&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated commitment to CCFC's Christian mission, vision and values&lt;br&gt;To apply for this opportunity, please email your resume and cover letter.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please ensure you reference the name of the position for which you are applying.&lt;br&gt;Only those candidates selected to proceed to the next stage in the recruitment process will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Adziovsky&lt;br&gt;Human Resources Generalist&lt;br&gt;Christian Children's Fund of Canada&lt;br&gt;1200 Denison Street&lt;br&gt;Markham, Ontario&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; L3R 8G6&lt;br&gt;E-mail: hr@ccfcanada.ca&lt;br&gt;www.ccfcanada.ca</content>
    <postId>689852A8-F242-4F2D-BDCD-BB40F54963F5</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Oracle Developer, CHRISTIAN CHILDREN\\'S FUND OF CANADA</title>
</post>
