<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Sr. Systems Support Analyst &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At Bank of Montreal, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potential. As one of North America's premier financial institutions, with more than 30 lines of business within our group of companies, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are the six main areas of the role:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;System/Network Maintenance &amp; Resource Management&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coordinate and direct the work of assigned analysts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Installation &amp; configuration of system hardware &amp; software, third party software&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perform upgrades &amp; testing for system/network hardware and software, firewall and third party tools&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analyze and resolve complex performance user/system problems and outages to software and firewall products&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monitor &amp; fix/patch operating system and tools vulnerabilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Compilation, packaging, installation &amp; debug of security shareware software&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;System security administration, hardening and auditing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;System and security tools performance tuning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;System resources monitoring, tuning and planning for production needs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Network naming services configuration and administration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Network and firewall hardware installation and configuration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scripting of automation tools for system maintenance/monitoring activities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research &amp; evaluation of third party software according to production needs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow change management procedures to implement changes in production&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documentation of security, system maintenance procedures and system/security tools usages&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Production Support&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide on-call support for daily firewalls and Unix systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report and coordinate resolution of production problems to Production Support Managers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide implementation support to users and development/application support teams&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communication/Reporting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide weekly status to Production Support Managers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attend individual and group meetings as required by management&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong vendor relationship management and troubleshooting experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teamwork&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Able to contribute to group activities and objectives&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;High professionalism&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Able to communicate effectively with peers and managers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide effective assistance to group members in problem resolution &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;University degree in either Computer Science, or a related engineering discipline (electrical/electronic engineering, etc.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum 3+ years experience of Unix operating system administration in Solaris including system security e.g. SSH, LDAP, CA.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum 2+ years experience in firewall administration using one of CheckPoint, Cisco PIX and Netscreen&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong knowledge of firewall technologies and principles (e.g. NAT)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong knowledge and solid working experience of Solaris 8 and CheckPoint-NG and one of Cisco PIX or Netscreen firewalls&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong knowledge of networking protocols (TCP/IP, PKI, NIS, DNS, HTTP, NFS, DHCP, various Microsoft network protocols, etc)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working experience of Cisco IOS and Apache/Netscape web servers an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working experience of Unix shell scripting (ksh, sh, perl)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solid analytical skills for problem solving&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good communication and project coordination skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Able to work under pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimal travel may be required &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desired:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working experience of Cisco switch and routers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working experience of VPN technologies e.g IPsec&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CCNA and/or Checkpoint certification&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with market data feeds e.g. Reuters, Telerate, Bloomberg etc an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of web related development languages/tools, e.g. Java, JavaScript, Servlets, CGI programming&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Windows NT/2000 system administration and security hardening&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bank of Montreal thanks all applicants. We advise that only those who qualify for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are committed to an equitable workplace and a diverse workforce. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: DSBAK00644&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group - BMO Groupe Financier&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>69416764-550B-4D89-BE3A-B9FF41C1062D</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Systems Support Analyst</title>
</post>
