<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Saint Elizabeth Health Care has almost 100 years of experience in delivering home and community care. Now more than a service provider, we offer a range of integrated international consulting services, @ YourSide™ online information technology products and forums for knowledge exchange. We attribute our success to our talented people who are committed to research, innovation and knowledge development and we believe our future lies in fostering creativity and continuing to embrace new technologies to improve care support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working from the corporate office of Saint Elizabeth Health Care, you will play a key role in the maintenance of our in-house financial management system. You will also be responsible for the investigation, analysis and recommendation of new system design needs, the creation of new software, and the enhancement of current programs and services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Qualifications&lt;br&gt;A related two-year college diploma or equivalent in a relevant discipline&lt;br&gt;Three years of related experience&lt;br&gt;A broad knowledge of current microcomputer systems and software &lt;br&gt;The ability to read, comprehend and analyze FoxPro 2.6 programming language &lt;br&gt;The ability to work independently and in a group environment&lt;br&gt;Excellent analytical, problem-solving and communication skills&lt;br&gt;A willingness to acquire new skills and knowledge &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assets&lt;br&gt;University degree &lt;br&gt;Familiarity with Web technologies (VB, ASP, ISAPI, COM Servers), FoxPro 6, and MS SQL &lt;br&gt;The ability to maintain applications written in Visual Basic for ASP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please forward your r?um? stating salary expectations, to: Human Resources, Saint Elizabeth Health Care, 90 Allstate Parkway, Suite 300, Markham, ON L3R 6H3. Fax: (905) 940-8977. E-mail: hresources@saintelizabeth.com. Web-site: www.saintelizabeth.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Human Resources&lt;br&gt;hresources@saintelizabeth.com&lt;br&gt;Saint Elizabeth Health Care&lt;br&gt;90 Allstate Parkway, Suite 300&lt;br&gt;Markham Ontario L3R 6H3&lt;br&gt;Fax: (905) 940-8977&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>69DA083D-A6FF-4FAF-A954-DA4F017B855E</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Markham-Programmer - Full-time (Markham): 3 yrs. related exp.; college diploma; FoxPro 2.6</title>
</post>
