<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Brendan</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>위니펙이라서 좀 올리기엔 그렇지만, 혹시라도해서... 보수는 좋군요. 어쩌면 이사 비용도 보태줄지??&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*Internal Description:&lt;br&gt;Intermediate Java Developer&lt;br&gt;8 Months (with strong possiblity to extend)&lt;br&gt;Winnipeg&lt;br&gt;ERC SECURITY REQUIRED - We can process Enhanced Reliability Clearance for you at no charge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*Must Have Skills:&lt;br&gt;Java Certification - (3-5Y)&lt;br&gt;Java Objects development - (2-3Y)&lt;br&gt;Spring - (1-2Y)&lt;br&gt;Hibernate - (1-2Y)&lt;br&gt;Struts - (1-2Y)&lt;br&gt;Eclipse - (1-2Y)&lt;br&gt;WSAD - (1-2Y)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*Role: Application Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the direction of the Lead Developer, the candidate will be responsible for the core activities of the software development effort for the OPS project. The Application Developer must:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Follow coding standards where they exist and raise or assist in documenting deviations if required.&lt;br&gt;- Effectively interact and collaborate with the Lead Developer, DBA and other Developers on design interpretation and other development matters.&lt;br&gt;- As a developer work under the direction of the Lead Developer develop the application areas as assigned based on the agreed tools and standards.&lt;br&gt;- Develop quality SW as measured by defects during System, Integration and User Acceptance Test cycles.&lt;br&gt;- Perform unit testing to verify component functionality.&lt;br&gt;- Support the testers in their efforts and &amp; correct problems as required.&lt;br&gt;- Collaborate and assist the Lead Developer &amp; Project Manager with estimating, planning, workload balancing, tracking to schedule and as requested.&lt;br&gt;- Support the test team to resolve technical issues as required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skill Requirements :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum 2 years experience in J2EE programming - must have Java certification and Federal Gov't Enhanced Reliability Clearance (ERC)&lt;br&gt;Experience programming object-oriented applications.&lt;br&gt;Experience using Spring, Hibernate, Struts.&lt;br&gt;Experience with Eclipse and WSAD development tools.&lt;br&gt;Experience in developing user interface design and prototyping.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*Additional Nice to Have : Experience building applications targeted to Oracle application server preferred.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take care,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melanie Sapishchuk&lt;br&gt;Resource Manager&lt;br&gt;msapishchuk@cncglobal.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNC Global Limited&lt;br&gt;177 Lombard Avenue, Suite 701&lt;br&gt;Winnipeg, Manitoba R3B 0W5&lt;br&gt;Tel: 204.942.1208&lt;br&gt;Fax: 204.957.0762</content>
    <postId>6DC54E63-E3C1-4D3B-AA99-8DCBE0F893F1</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-07-28T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[Winnipeg] Java Developer - Contract, starting 8 mths</title>
</post>
