<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Front End Web Developer,&lt;br&gt;TORSTAR DIGITAL&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON, CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;Posted Mar 2, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Available:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Front End Web Developer&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Are you looking for a fast-paced, creative and challenging work environment?&lt;br&gt;Is working with energetic, passionate people right up your alley?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Torstar's portfolio of world-class internet sites currently includes workopolis.com, toronto.com, thestar.com, wheels.ca, Olive Media and a mix of other regional sites.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Forward your resume to:&lt;br&gt;techjobs@torstardigital.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;TECHNICAL SKILLS SUMMARY: Expert level XHTML, CSS, OO JavaScript, strong server side scripting, preferably ASP.NET and C#, Web 2.0 related technologies and platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;As a member of Professional Services team work on creating web solutions for existing and new online media clients such as Toronto Star, toronto.com, wheels.ca, eyeweekly.com etc.&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Execute technical implementation, integration and customization of our proprietary CMS to client sites&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Extend the CMS functionality and build custom site solutions based on the CMS API&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ensure cross browser compatibility and web standards on all solutions.&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Participate in application testing, documentation and deployment.&lt;br&gt;DESIRED EXPERIENCE AND KNOWLEDGE:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3-5 years demonstrated web development experience (provide URLs of sites worked on), preferably with .NET &lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience in working with and developing Content Management Systems (CMS)&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience with high volume, interactive consumer web site development &lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Understanding and interest in Web 2.0 concepts - online communities, blogs, wiki, UGC etc.&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Strong knowledge of front end web technologies: XHTML, CSS, OO JavaScript, AJAX and Web Services&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience developing cross-browser compatible code based on web standards&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Extensive experience in server-side scripting, preferably ASP.NET platform, C# language and Visual Studio&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Understanding of XML, XSLT and XPath&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of RDBMS, preferably MS SQL Server.&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience working in a Test Driven/Agile Development environment &lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience with Information Architecture and building user interfaces for customer facing applications&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of Flex/Flash/ActionScript would be a plus&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Postsecondary education in IT related field&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;DESIRED PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES:&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Creative and passionate about the web user experiences and new technologies&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Thrives on working under pressure in a fast paced multi-project environment&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Works effectively in an agile, collaborative team of developers and graphic designers&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Self-motivated,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;can also work independently without constant supervision&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Applies initiative and creativity when approaching challenges&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Able to communicate effectively within a development team and with clients&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;High attention to detail and commitment to quality&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Welcomes being challenged and pushed professionally&lt;br&gt;§&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Takes active interest in the company&lt;br&gt;About Torstar Digital:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;http://www.torstardigital.com&lt;br&gt;Torstar Digital's mission is to deliver technology and strategic leadership to its online-only properties, create winning online businesses that can leverage Torstar Corporation's wealth of media assets and assist in online enabling of Torstar Corporation's existing portfolio of print businesses. Torstar's current portfolio of leading digital properties includes thestar.com, toronto.com, workopolis.com, wheels.ca, Olive Media, eyeReturn Marketing and a variety of regional sites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also please visit Torstar Digital on Facebook</content>
    <postId>6FE278F6-8198-4A58-BE65-B89DDC2C53E9</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Front End Web Developer-Toronto Star</title>
</post>
