<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>[REALLY GOOD POSITION]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software Support &amp; Development Specialist&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Posted Date:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;10-11-2006&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Mississauga, Ontario, Canada&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Description:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Atomic Energy of Canada Limited is an integrated nuclear technology company providing services to nuclear utilities worldwide. Our 4,000 employees are focused on delivering R&amp;D support, nuclear services, design and engineering, construction management, specialist technology, and waste management and decommissioning in support of CANDU reactor products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;The Engineering and Project Management Tools Branch (E&amp;PMT), is responsible for the ongoing development, support and implementation of database and information systems associated with the design, engineering, procurement, construction, operations, refurbishment and life-extensions of CANDU power plants. This includes the implementation and ongoing support of AECL´s key engineering and project management tools such as TRAK (AECL´s electronic document management and control system), IntEC (AECL´s cabling, wiring and equipment management system), CMMS (CANDU Material Management System), PDS (Plant Design System) and SmartPlant-3D the 3D CADD modelling systems, Solid Edge (3D Solid Mechanical Modelling), P3e (scheduling) and AutoCAD/Microstation 2D drafting tools. A major responsibility of the group is to work with users to define or redefine their work processes to best take advantage of these tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two (2) vacancies exist in the branch for software development specialists to provide a leadership role in the development, implementation and ongoing support of the TRAK and IntEC systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duties:&lt;br&gt;As lead senior software engineers and team leaders, the successful candidates will be responsible t&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maintain enhance and troubleshoot the Power Builder based AECL framework, the foundation on which IntEC and TRAK reside. &lt;br&gt;Maintain, enhance and troubleshoot IntEC - Equipment, Cabling, Raceways, User Access, Information Support. &lt;br&gt;Maintain, enhance and troubleshoot TRAK and associated applications - Records Information System, Projects Deliverable Management, Action Tracking, Data Item Management. &lt;br&gt;Maintain and troubleshoot the Report Online System (RON). &lt;br&gt;Maintain and troubleshoot the AECL IntEC and TRAK Databases on AECL´s domain, includes schemas, data, triggers and stored procedures. &lt;br&gt;Mentor and train other E&amp;PMT software development engineers in the advanced use of the software development tools used in the branch to maintain and advance IntEC and TRAK. &lt;br&gt;Provide IntEC and TRAK support to E&amp;PMT Application Specialists responsible for 1st line user support and project implementation within AECL. &lt;br&gt;Provide support services per the Maintenance Agreements between AECL and its external clients who are using IntEC and/or TRAK - NB Power, Bruce Power, OPG (Darlington), TQNPC, HQ, Cernavoda 2, etc. &lt;br&gt;Take a leading role in the execution of new commercial contracts involving the implementations of IntEC, including Data Conversion, system set-up and customer training. &lt;br&gt;Prepare documentation related to the use and operation of IntEC and TRAK. &lt;br&gt;Prepare and deliver user training. &lt;br&gt;Develop interfaces to conveniently exchange and share data between IntEC, TRAK and other project applications. &lt;br&gt;Develop other labour saving utilities and procedures. &lt;br&gt;Recommendations (to various levels of staff and management) regarding new, improved and more efficient work processes. &lt;br&gt;Expected to analyze and bring to a satisfactory resolution, technical issues associated with his/her area of responsibility. &lt;br&gt;Interface with other internal groups as well as external organizations such as software vendors, AECL´s partners, customers, etc. &lt;br&gt;Occasionally travel to customer and other AECL sites. &lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relevant honours degree in Engineering or Engineering Science from a university of recognized standing with a strong background in computer science plus a minimum fo 3-5 years practical experience plus significant additional related experience. &lt;br&gt;An excellent understanding of AECL's design, engineering, documentation and procurement processes. &lt;br&gt;Highly experienced in all aspects of the software development cycle, must be able to perform business process analysis, data modeling and database design, software design &amp; development, software certification and production roll-out. &lt;br&gt;Minimum 15 years working experience developing engineering related database applications using SQL + SPL with the Informix IDS database engine, is a must. &lt;br&gt;Highly experienced working with both the Windows (NT/2000/XP Server 2000/2003) and the UNIX (Sun SOLARIS and HPUX) Operating systems. &lt;br&gt;Minimum 15 years experience performing DBA functions with Informix IDS database engine. &lt;br&gt;Working experience with MS/SQL Server and Oracle database engines. &lt;br&gt;Minimum 10 years working experience with PowerBuilder &amp; PB foundation class, .Net development (ASP.net, VB.net), C/C++, HTML, Java and MS MTS, in a client server and 3-tier environment. &lt;br&gt;Experience with common Internet technologies such as COM+, XML, Web servers, and application servers, ASP, MS IIS. &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of the IntEC product includes: &lt;br&gt;Thorough knowledge of the IntEC applications from a business perspective, has an in-depth knowledge of raceway, cabling and wiring design practices, and business rules, equipment definition, asset management, instrumentation, DCC and DCS signal management &lt;br&gt;Thorough knowledge of the IntEC applications software, able to enhance and maintain it as required or to train/mentor others to do it &lt;br&gt;Intimate knowledge and understanding of the IntEC database structure and how it relates to the schemas of other applications such as TRAK and CMMS &lt;br&gt;Able to perform data manipulation to correct problems or to assist projects and external clients to perform bulk changes to wiring and cabling data correctly, while ensuring the relevant business rules are met &lt;br&gt;Has conducted several migration projects form DICON databases to IntEC and has a thorough understanding of the Cabling and Wiring data in both environments, knows how to identify data inconsistencies and is able to suggest and implement corrective actions &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of the TRAK product and related application includes: &lt;br&gt;Thorough knowledge of AECL´s documentation classes, processes and related workflows, information structure, file types and related 3rd party authoring and publishing tools &lt;br&gt;Thorough knowledge of the TRAK applications software, able to enhance and maintain it as required or to train/mentor others to do it &lt;br&gt;Intimate knowledge and understanding of the TRAK database structure and how it relates to the schemas of other applications such as IntEC and CMMS &lt;br&gt;Able to perform data and file manipulation to correct problems or to assist projects and external clients to perform bulk changes correctly, while ensuring the relevant business rules are met &lt;br&gt;Has participated in several document migration projects to TRAK, has developed methods and automated procedures to facilitate the task &lt;br&gt;Excellent analytical analysis skills. &lt;br&gt;Excellent problem solving skills. &lt;br&gt;Excellent verbal, written and presentation skills. &lt;br&gt;Good organizational skills. &lt;br&gt;Be able to seek practical solutions to engineering and information management problems related to the delivery of large engineering, procurement and construction projects. &lt;br&gt;Must be able to work effectively in a team environment, as a team leader and mentor to more junior staff. &lt;br&gt;Must be able to deal with interruptions. &lt;br&gt;Must be able to multi-task. &lt;br&gt;Must be able to cope with changing requirements. &lt;br&gt;Must be able to cope with tight schedules. &lt;br&gt;Plan and carry out development programs with minimal but supportive supervision. &lt;br&gt;Prioritize activities to achieve project goals. &lt;br&gt;Ability to tactfully influence decision makers to adopt new technologies and processes. &lt;br&gt;Ability to strike a balance between the individual user needs and the overall project/organization needs. &lt;br&gt;Results oriented. &lt;br&gt;Pro-actively identify opportunities for beneficial change. &lt;br&gt;AECL has an Employment Equity Program and encourages applications from women, Aboriginal Peoples, visible minorities and persons with disabilities. AECL provides a smoke-free workplace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; http://www.recruitingsite.com/csbsites/aecl/en/JobDescription.asp?JobNumber=509005&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>71916D57-1A9E-4B69-A40D-0E3D1DD7D104</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-11-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software Support &amp; Development Specialist  -AECL</title>
</post>
