<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-Senior Java Developer :. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Status:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full Time, Temporary/Contract/Project&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Java Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We need strong software engineers to assist in building enterprise wide &lt;br&gt;application framework. The work requires strong understanding of software &lt;br&gt;engineering principles in distributed software technologies, object oriented &lt;br&gt;technologies, security and large scale data processing techniques.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About Acumen:&lt;br&gt;Founded in 1998 and located in Toronto, Acumen&amp;#47977; development and consulting &lt;br&gt;teams have gained recognition for their expertise in high-profile &lt;br&gt;infrastructure development. Our core expertise is based on Web Services &lt;br&gt;Standards, Connectivity, Collaboration and Enterprise Security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location:&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description:&lt;br&gt;* In this position you will be required to understand high level design and &lt;br&gt;produce detail design in UML and implement and test the final design. The &lt;br&gt;project is for a large retail US client. Development will be done in Acumen &lt;br&gt;office in Toronto.&lt;br&gt;* This position starts on a contract basis and has an option to become permanent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;Must have:&lt;br&gt;* A minimum of 3 years of Java and J2EE experience&lt;br&gt;* Good Communication Skills&lt;br&gt;* Strong background in Object Oriented Software development&lt;br&gt;* Strong background in modeling using UML&lt;br&gt;* Professional experience using WebLogic Server&lt;br&gt;* Solid understanding of web technologies like XML, HTML, JSP, Javascript&lt;br&gt;* University degree in a related discipline or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to have:&lt;br&gt;* Experience with the Struts Framework&lt;br&gt;* Be able to travel to the US.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only applicants that have been retained will be contacted. Selected &lt;br&gt;applicants will have to take Acumen designed Java test before qualifying for &lt;br&gt;interviews. Interested applicants are invited to submit their resume &lt;br&gt;online at jobs@acumentechnologies.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Contact Information :.&lt;br&gt;Nahid Keshmirshekan&lt;br&gt;jobs@acumentechnologies.com&lt;br&gt;Acumen Advanced Technologies&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON&lt;br&gt;Ph: 416-491-1419 x220&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>725E930E-488E-4432-A0A9-A810F574692F</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-Senior Java Developer (from Monster.ca)</title>
</post>
