<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>SENIOR SOFTWARE TEST ENGINEER &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDATA Corporation, the leading provider of high availability enterprise switches and related software for connecting servers and storage systems in enterprise Storage Area Networks, has an exciting opportunity for a Senior Software Test Engineer in Toronto. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SENIOR SOFTWARE TEST ENGINEER &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position requires a BSEE, BSCS, or related discipline and 5 to 8 years experience designing and developing test programs and tools or communications software in C/C++ or other high level programming language. Must have test project lead experience. A combination of formalized education, military training in Computer Science or electronics and/or experience in software test development or communications software equal to 4 years may be substituted for the degree. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requires experience with white box testing using automated test tools and test programs including simulators, interoperability test tools, and code coverage analyzers. Must have experience at all levels of test development: unit, integration and system. Proficient in the design and development of programs using structured and object oriented methodologies. Must understand network concepts and topologies such as LAN/WAN communications, channel technology and layered protocols. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will design and develop software programs including test programs, tools, and automated test suites. Will work closely with senior software and hardware engineers and customer support representatives for the specification and development of test tools and test programs. Will work as a project leader providing guidance, training, and support to other team members and support to DVT and Alpha test teams. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please apply online at: www.mcdata.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please reference ad code: SSTET 11 &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: SSTET 11&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;SSTET 11&lt;br&gt;careers@mcdata.com&lt;br&gt;McDATA Corporation&lt;br&gt;380 Interlocken Crescent&lt;br&gt;Broomfield CO 80021&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>72B519AF-630E-49CE-A064-C763C23A4A24</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-04-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SENIOR SOFTWARE TEST ENGINEER</title>
</post>
