<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My name is Richard Goldglass and I am Staffing Consultant with iVedha.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;iVedha is a Business Solutions Provider offering strategic Enterprise Solutions &amp; Managed Services to help companies with their Information Technology, Business Processes and Human Capital requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I came across your resume on Monster.com and I have an opportunity that may be of interest to you or someone you know.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In particular I have Sr. Java Developer opportunities that you may be a strong fit for.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;These are full time/permanent roles located in Toronto .&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;More information about these opportunities can be found in the attached files.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please let me know if this opportunity is of interest to you or someone you know.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Also, if you could please send a copy of your resume in a word document along with your current salary, salary expectations, and availability, it would be greatly appreciated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;---&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Goldglass B.A. I.T., Psych.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iVedha&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;People.Technology.Outsourcing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;p:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;416.424.6614&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;x 2007&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;p:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;347.534.1429&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;c:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;416.949.7770&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;f:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 416.385.8165&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;richard@ivedha.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;www.ivedha.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1370 Don Mills Rd. Suite 300 || Toronto ||&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ontario || M3B 3N7&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;244 Fifth Avenue . Suite 2561|| New York || New York || 10001-7604&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This e-mail (including attachments, if any) is for the addressed person only. Initial introduction of a candidate Via E-Mail, or Fax, is considered by law to be represented by iVedha Inc. Canada iVedha USA . Our Fee is due and payable when a candidate is referred to within a 12 month period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7421C279-C169-497A-8EA0-1DDC49ECD584</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-09-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Java Developer opportunities</title>
</post>
