<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>The Canadian Depository for Securities Limited (CDS) is...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's national securities depository, clearing and settlement hub, holding nearly $2 trillion on deposit, settling between $100 and $200 billion daily and handling up to 57 million securities trades annually for banks, brokers, trust companies and other financial industry members&lt;br&gt;A gateway to the U.S. and other international securities markets&lt;br&gt;A provider of a growing range of other securities information and processing services meeting ever-changing market demands (e.g., SEDAR®, ATONTM)&lt;br&gt;A 500-employee company working for more than 30 years to continuously improve the efficiency, effectiveness, and global competitiveness of Canada's capital markets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDS' recruiting objective is to identify and acquire the best qualified candidates available to fill job vacancies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DESCRIPTION: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purpose of Job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We require a key resource to control and manage all configuration issues for E-REG. This individual will introduce and enforce industry-standard software configuration management practices including system administration, change control and development methodologies. This individual will also be required to educate the user community about configuration management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAJOR RESPONSIBILITIES: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schedule, perform and coordinate software configuration management builds&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Complete code builds&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perform configuration audits - implement and enforce processes introducing only approved and known code changes into the baseline.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Implement and apply controls, audits, and change and defect management to release builds&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research and implement change management solutions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Administer and manage Code Repository&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Administer branching, labeling strategies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baseline code as required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Administer and manage Defect Reporting System&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report on defects and enhancements included in each release&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manage software configuration of all environments&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide reports on releases and environments&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maintain internal standards for software configuration management&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigate and implement version control solutions &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Administer and manage version control solution&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply branching, labeling strategy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baseline code&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Document Configuration Management processes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Document Configuration Management plan &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATIONS: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post Secondary Education in Information Technology is preferred, 5 plus years relevant experience will substitute&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7 - 10 years relevant experience in a development environment, with 5 years configuration management experience is required, including:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong working experience with Visual Source Safe&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong working experience with Rational ClearCase&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of ClearQuest or ClearDDTS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shell scripting or Perl language skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong Unix knowledge. (AIX, Solaris)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good knowledge of Java (J2EE), and Application Server Technologies. (Websphere/iPlanet)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good understanding of Web Technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants in advance for their interest in CDS Ltd. Only those applicants selected for interview will be contacted directly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We regret, no Agency candidate submissions or solicitations for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please click here to apply directly to CDS Ltd.&lt;br&gt;Visit our Web-Site. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: CAAR58141&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Canadian Depository for Securities&lt;br&gt;85 Richmond Street West,&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON M5H 2C9&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>754BB78A-5EBE-43AB-A37A-7C4319087815</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-01T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Technical Specialist (Configuration Management)</title>
</post>
