<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Crystal Reports / SQL Lead Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Aon Reed Stenhouse, Canada’s leading insurance broker is seeking a Crystal Reports / SQL Lead Developer to join our IT department.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lead Developer will be responsible for the day to day management of work flowing in and out of Aon Central Canada as well as being the main contact for all content being released to Production from the group. The Lead Developer will work hand in hand with the third party development team, the business analysts and the quality assurance analysts to ensure that changes are accurate, reliable and properly planned. The Lead Developer is also responsible for implementing the necessary changes to policy management reports, detail sets and the creation of (and changes to) document templates. Additional responsibilities may include assisting with data conversion and QA efforts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDE:&lt;br&gt;Development and maintenance of detail sets in our proprietary policy management applications using Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Access and (Oracle) SQL scripts.&lt;br&gt;Development of key output for our proprietary policy management applications using Seagate Crystal Reports, Microsoft Word and other desktop tools.&lt;br&gt;Write SQL scripts.&lt;br&gt;Trouble shoot incidents submitted by field users.&lt;br&gt;Execute testing and quality assurance plans.&lt;br&gt;Apply organization standards for product design and development to business solutions.&lt;br&gt;Make recommendations for standard changes and enhancements.&lt;br&gt;Provide regular project status reports to management and/or the client.&lt;br&gt;Perform other related duties as required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATIONS AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:&lt;br&gt;Post secondary degree / diploma in Computer Science.&lt;br&gt;Advanced knowledge of SQL scripting (2 &amp;#8211; 5 years of SQL experience required).&lt;br&gt;Advanced knowledge of Seagate Crystal Reports.&lt;br&gt;Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Access, Excel and Word (including Word merge functionality).&lt;br&gt;Advanced knowledge of Visual Basic.&lt;br&gt;Advanced knowledge of database design principles.&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of project management principles (MS Project referred).&lt;br&gt;Must be a service-oriented team player.&lt;br&gt;Comfortable with public speaking in small groups.&lt;br&gt;Superior analytical and problem solving skills.&lt;br&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills. &lt;br&gt;Ability to interact effectively with all levels of the organization.&lt;br&gt;French bilingual skills preferred.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you meet the criteria above, please forward your resume via email or fax. We thank all applicants for their interest in Aon Reed Stenhouse, however only those who meet the qualifications required will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For further information about Aon, please visit our website: www.aon.ca&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: MB/IT/LD&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;aon.careers@aon.ca&lt;br&gt;Aon Canada&lt;br&gt;20 Bay Street&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON M5J 2N9&lt;br&gt;Fax: 416 868 5502&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>76127C1A-0104-4447-AAEB-C7051A9E4A01</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-12T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Crystal Reports / SQL Lead Developer</title>
</post>
