<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Number: 4878805&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title: Web developer (Junior Web Developer) (NOC: 2175)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terms of Employment: Temporary, Part Time, Day&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: $17.00 Hourly for 30 hours per week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anticipated Start Date: As soon as possible&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario (1 vacancy)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skill Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education: Completion of university&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Not required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience: 2 years to less than 3 years&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Read English, Write English&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Setting: Government&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specific Skills: Prepare mock-ups and storyboards, Source, select and organize information for inclusion and design the appearance, layout and flow of the web site, Create and optimize content for web site using a variety of graphics, database, animation and other software&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Programming Languages: ASP, HTML, DHTML, Java, Java Script, CSS, PHP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Computer and Technology Knowledge: Windows, Programming software, HTML editing software, Web site creation and management software, Web service design, Programming languages&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applications: Adobe Acrobat Reader, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Flash&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Conditions and Physical Capabilities: Fast-paced environment, Work under pressure, Tight deadlines, Attention to detail, Sitting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: Reading text, Writing, Working with others, Problem solving, Critical thinking, Job task planning and organizing, Significant use of memory, Computer use&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other Information:For full job description, go to www.workink.com - Job Posting page.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employer: The Canadian Council on Rehabilitation and Work&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to Apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please apply for this job only in the manner specified by the employer. Failure to do so may result in your application not being properly considered for the position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By E-mail: info@ccrw.org&lt;br&gt;Online: http://www.ccrw.org&lt;br&gt;Business Profile: Providing employment opportunities to persons with disabilities..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Web Site: http://www.ccrw.org&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advertised until: 2010/03/08&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This job advertisement has been provided by an external employer. Service Canada is not responsible for the accuracy, authenticity or reliability of the content.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>799D739F-39B1-4128-950C-8A14C7969A9D</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web developer (Junior Web Developer) (NOC: 2175)</title>
</post>
