<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Information Security Advisor/Implementation &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your bank, your future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Bank of Montreal, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potentials. As one of North America's premier financial institutions, with more than 30 lines of business within our group of companies, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security Advisor&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The primary responsibilities in this position are to provide information security services and solutions in support of our Information Security Project Assessment Process and to participate in technology research and solution testing. The Advisor must possess a significant in-depth understanding of security classification, the security assessment process, system and application hardening, project management processes, documentation, audit, signoff and authorities processes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Specific Functions of this role:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conducting analysis for the security assessments.&lt;br&gt;Producing topic papers and white papers on emerging technologies.&lt;br&gt;Evaluating new threats and vulnerabilities to the Bank's systems.&lt;br&gt;Team leadership, as required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of different operating platforms.&lt;br&gt;Understanding of systems administration, the software development process, intrusion detection and vulnerability analysis.&lt;br&gt;Five to ten years of experience in information technology, with experience in major IT infrastructure projects, including at three years working on IT projects, and at least three years of information security experience.&lt;br&gt;Completion of a BSc in Computer Science or Engingeering, GIAC, CISA, CCIE, CCNE or other security certifications would be definite assets.&lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of Windows OS, Unix, HTML, PERL, C++/JAVA, CHECKPOINT, NMAP, Linux, email, browser technologies, CISCO, IOS, REALSECURE, NESSUS, NFR, Solaris, AIX, Oracle, Tivoli and CYBERCOP would be desirable.&lt;br&gt;Experience implementing information security policies and procedures is required, along with strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;br&gt;Advanced analysis skills are required.&lt;br&gt;High ethics and trust values.&lt;br&gt;Experience dealing directly with customers as a consultant or advisor is preferable.&lt;br&gt;An ability to balance the demands of several projects simultaneously is a requirement.&lt;br&gt;An understanding of project management, and the ability to lead people are also highly desirable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We value our employees. Join us, and Cultivate your skills through our life long learning initiatives&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strengthen your RRSP portfolio with our competitive Employee Share Ownership Plan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Choose your coverage with our flexible benefit plan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are committed to an equitable workplace and a diverse workforce.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: BGKJL00803&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Bank of Montreal&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>79E2D242-1FDA-454E-A7AD-D479902D95AF</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Information Security Advisor/Implementation</title>
</post>
