<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Deloitte Consulting Inc. is presently looking for ABAP consultants with 1 to 2 years SAP experience. Candidates should have experience with modifying ABAP reports, defining and coding data loads (Both BDC and Call transaction) under the direction of senior ABAP team members. Candidates should have experience applying OSS notes and following a structured testing methodology. Ideally, candidates should be able to work independently from functional specification. Experience with other programming languages, such as C, C++, Java would be beneficial.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deloitte Consulting Inc.&amp;#47977; technology infrastructure group (eTI) is looking for senior ABAP consultants with 3 or more years of intensive hands-on experience. Candidates should have expert knowledge (definition of specifications, testing and coding) of 3 or more of the following: ABAP reports; data loads; interfaces to and from non-SAP systems using RFC calls or batch data files; creating and modifying Sapscript layout sets; modifications to SAP transactions; creation of custom transactions; or dialog programming. Senior ABAP consultants will be able to define unit and integration tests for code modifications either made by themselves or the ABAP consultants which they mentor. Senior ABAP developers will be conversant in the way OSS is organized and will be able to research technical solutions in conjunction with functional team members. Senior ABAP consultants will be expected to be able to mentor and train more junior programmers. Experience with other programming languages such as C, C++, Java would be considered an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send you resume in word format, including salary expectations C/O Inga Rugole, Director of Regional Recruiting, jlupo@dc.com.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;jlupo@dc.com&lt;br&gt;Deloitte Consulting Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>79F4519F-1F52-4383-B3D4-25C5DFB6E544</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>ABAP Consultants</title>
</post>
