<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>K. Kwon</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Data Design Systems (DDS) (http://www.datadesign.com/) is a leading supplier of comprehensive software configuration management (SCM) solutions located in Mississauga. As an early SCM pioneer, DDS has ensured internal and external audit compliance for over 12 years. Our blue chip client list includes 13 of the top 25 banks in North America and large corporations in Europe and Asia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can be part of our Product Development Team and make a real impact on our success in the role of Software Developer. You will play an instrumental role in developing products critical to the company's success. You will work closely with product management, marketing and business development functions to ensure that product feature sets are appropriately delivered in new products. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must enjoy working with a strong team of peers in a fast-paced environment and enjoy the benefits and challenges of working in a small company.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You have likely had experience designing and developing software utilities and tools. The right candidate has excellent technical skills and experience, an aptitude for team-based technical software delivery and a genuine passion for software development. Innate analytical abilities and good communication skills are assumed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Data Design Systems, you will work with state-of-the art programming languages, environments, communication protocols and technologies. &lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;BS or MS in Computer Science or related field is mandatory. Experience in all phases of product development desired. Ability to work well with QA, Business Development and Marketing. &lt;br&gt;Technical Skills:&lt;br&gt;Environments: Windows XP/2000/NT, Unix, Linux, Solaris.&lt;br&gt;Database: SQL Server, MySQL&lt;br&gt;Languages: Java/Java Servlets, Perl, UML, XML, SQL, VB.&lt;br&gt;Protocols: SOAP, TCP/IP, HTTP, LDAP, SSL, FTP, NFS&lt;br&gt;We thank all candidates for applying but only those under consideration will be contacted. No phone calls, faxes or agencies please.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Submit your resume to: &lt;br&gt;careers@datadesign.com&lt;br&gt;Data Design Systems &lt;br&gt;5915 Airport Road, &lt;br&gt;Mississauga, ON &lt;br&gt;L4V 1T1 &lt;br&gt;Attention: Human Resources&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7A9A8920-562A-4F1A-8FFC-4392B2F644F5</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-10-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software Developer</title>
</post>
