<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>박경종</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>The positions below are currently available through Procom. If you meet the&lt;br&gt;qualifications and are interested in this opportunity please apply as per the&lt;br&gt;instructions below. Please note, this automated email has been sent to you as&lt;br&gt;the result of a successful keyword search on your resume within our database.&lt;br&gt;Please use discretion by only applying to positions that best suit your&lt;br&gt;qualifications. If you wish to remove yourself from future mailings, please&lt;br&gt;click the link supplied below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position:Vision Plus Programmer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: 3 days working from home and 2 in Oakville&lt;br&gt;Duration: 1 year&lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary:$55/hr if INC.&lt;br&gt;Start Date: October 2004&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;Large consulting company is looking for consultants with strong experience with&lt;br&gt;Vision Plus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;-Candidates must have previous Vision Plus programming experience&lt;br&gt;-Excellent coding,debbuging and troubleshooting skills&lt;br&gt;-Team Lead experience required&lt;br&gt;-Previous financial service industry experience would be preferred&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Business Analyst&lt;br&gt;*Experience with Vision Plus is a must*&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location:EUROPE&lt;br&gt;Duration:6 months +&lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary:$65-$75/hr if INC.&lt;br&gt;Start Date:October 2004&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;Our client within the financial services industry is looking for a Business&lt;br&gt;Analyst with strong Vision Plus knowledge.&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;-Strong Vision Plus knowledge&lt;br&gt;-Experience writing business requirements, business processes and documentation&lt;br&gt;-Technical background with good understanding of business would be considered&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROCOM SERVICES&lt;br&gt;A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES&lt;br&gt;currently have more than 1700 consultants on assignment. For over 25 years, we&lt;br&gt;have been finding high-quality jobs for our consultants. Our policies of&lt;br&gt;maintaining open communication with both clients and consultants consistently&lt;br&gt;make us the IT Firm of Choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions&lt;br&gt;will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please submit your most recent resume as a Word format to:&lt;br&gt;rossanap@procom.ca&lt;br&gt;No phone calls please&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7ACA8E4A-AA48-4C38-8384-5E6CEC0B2146</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-09-24T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Vision Plus Programmer</title>
</post>
