<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>CA-ON-Toronto/GTA-Hotel Applications Software Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Northwind is a leading global supplier of business applications to the Hospitality Industry (Hotels, Resorts). Northwind has developed business applications for over 20 years, and is experiencing continued growth through its Canadian Head Office and International network of distributors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We currently require 2 software developers/programmers to join our team to build new applications and enhance existing ones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS:&lt;br&gt;* 5+ years professional development experience&lt;br&gt;* Expertise in C or C++&lt;br&gt;* Proficiency with Windows and Unix operating systems&lt;br&gt;* Capable of writing clear and complete technical specifications&lt;br&gt;* Formal education in Computer Science or related experience/education&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DESIRED SKILLS:&lt;br&gt;* Knowledge of MS SQL Server and/or Oracle databases&lt;br&gt;* Experience in Java and Java Servlet programming&lt;br&gt;* Knowledge of Crystal Reports or similar report writer&lt;br&gt;* Knowledge of ODBC development&lt;br&gt;* Understanding of networking protocols and technologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PERSONALITY&lt;br&gt;* Must take initiative and ensure success for all responsibilities&lt;br&gt;* Must be able to work independantly within established&lt;br&gt;practices, and challenge those practices when you have a better idea&lt;br&gt;* Able to work within a group by cooperating on designs and implementations&lt;br&gt;* Able to focus on a task until completed&lt;br&gt;* Reliable and well organized&lt;br&gt;* Must be able to communicate well with team members, vendors, and clients&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with hotel systems is a major advantage to be selected as a successful candidate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank you for your interest, but only those qualified for interviews will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Salary: CAD 55,000.00 to CAD 80,000.00 per year &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;wdehan@north88.com&lt;br&gt;Northwind&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7B0ED93C-FAFA-4575-BD1D-F67FE3C6707C</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-14T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>CA-ON-Toronto/GTA-Hotel Applications Software Developer</title>
</post>
