<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Alpha Lab Inc. has been in the medical business for 30 years and has developed a number of medical information system during this time. Currently, we are in the process of developing an on-line distributed medical information system to be marketed as a product throughout North America. We are currently seeking 2 Client-Side Java Developers with the following qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SKILLS:&lt;br&gt;- Strong background in GUI design using Java/Swing/AWT&lt;br&gt;- Strong background in OO analysis and design&lt;br&gt;- Strong communication skills&lt;br&gt;- Strong interpersonal skills&lt;br&gt;- Demonstrated ability to work well under pressure with minimal supervision&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KNOWLEDGE AND EXPERIENCE&lt;br&gt;- Minimum 3 years of Java development&lt;br&gt;- Minimum 2 years of experience with Swing/AWT&lt;br&gt;- Minimum 2 years of OO modeling experience (UML/Rational Rose)&lt;br&gt;- Minimum 1 year of experience with J2EE&lt;br&gt;- Experience with server side Java programming using JMS, EJB, Servlet/JSP&lt;br&gt;- Good working knowledge of Design Pattern&lt;br&gt;- Experience with relational databases (Oracle, SQL Server)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDUCATION:&lt;br&gt;- University degree in Computer Science, Engineering or equivalent experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send resumes via email or fax to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Email: alpha@alphainc.org&lt;br&gt;FAX : 416-449-2543 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;alpha@alphainc.org&lt;br&gt;Alpha Lab Inc.&lt;br&gt;North York ON&lt;br&gt;Fax: 416 449 2543&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7B3D9A1A-E97C-4E41-8EF4-02DF39E69D9E</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Client-Side Java Developers</title>
</post>
