<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>We are currently looking for a Programmer (JAVA) - Level 2 resource for a&lt;br&gt;261business days contract position with our client located in GTA .&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please&lt;br&gt;have a look at the description, and call me at 416-646-2811 ext.244 or&lt;br&gt;e-mail me at ageanus@antandbee.com, if you are interested.The client is&lt;br&gt;looking for someone who is available on the 1st of A[ril, 2009 . Please&lt;br&gt;feel free to forward this job description to any of your colleagues that&lt;br&gt;might be interested.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIENT’S REQUIREMENTS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scope of Services and Deliverables - The Services and Deliverables to be&lt;br&gt;provided by the Vendor will include the following:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Design and implement the Configuration Management policies, procedures&lt;br&gt;and&lt;br&gt;standards and seek agreement and support for the new process through a well&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;designed communication and awareness program.&lt;br&gt;· Ensure that changes to the process methods and processes are properly&lt;br&gt;approved, communicated and managed through the Change Management process.&lt;br&gt;· Oversee implementation of new Configuration Management systems, after&lt;br&gt;proper&lt;br&gt;planning and communication.&lt;br&gt;· Ensure that the overall objectives of the process are agreed with the IT&lt;br&gt;Services Manager.&lt;br&gt;· Review the marketplace for systems and tools that will aide the process&lt;br&gt;to&lt;br&gt;perform better.&lt;br&gt;· Conduct reviews and evaluations of current process systems, designs and&lt;br&gt;implements improvements to current systems, monitoring and reporting&lt;br&gt;progress&lt;br&gt;being made.&lt;br&gt;· Create and provide the on-going management of the Configuration&lt;br&gt;Management&lt;br&gt;plan.&lt;br&gt;· Identify the Configuration Items that are to be captured and controlled&lt;br&gt;(e.g.&lt;br&gt;requirements, code, documentation, models, plans, hardware, software,&lt;br&gt;etc.).&lt;br&gt;· Design the way that Configuration Items information is collected and&lt;br&gt;recorded; the security levels associated with them and ensure that roles&lt;br&gt;and&lt;br&gt;responsibilities are clearly articulated.&lt;br&gt;· Establish naming styles and conventions for the Configuration Items that&lt;br&gt;are&lt;br&gt;to be managed and controlled.&lt;br&gt;· Design, implement and manage the Configuration Management Database&lt;br&gt;(CMDB),&lt;br&gt;Definitive Software Library (DSL) and Definitive Hardware Stores (DHS).&lt;br&gt;· Ensure that staffs are complying with the rules/standards established.&lt;br&gt;· Liaise with other process owners &amp; functional areas (e.g. Change&lt;br&gt;Management,&lt;br&gt;Release Management, etc.)&lt;br&gt;· Assist development team in establishing an automated build process which&lt;br&gt;includes the configuration items that are changed in the build.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical skills and experience required: (40 points)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consultant must have 5-9 years of experience in:&lt;br&gt;· Development of configuration management processes, policies, and&lt;br&gt;standards&lt;br&gt;(10 points)&lt;br&gt;· Working in a Java environment; i.e. J2EE, Wepsphere, Oracle, etc. (5&lt;br&gt;points)&lt;br&gt;· Automating the build processes (5 points)&lt;br&gt;· Release Management (5 points)&lt;br&gt;· Defect Management (5 points)&lt;br&gt;· Communications skills &amp;#8211; oral and written (10 points)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of methodologies, processes and tools: (40 points)&lt;br&gt;· Configuration management processes (10 points)&lt;br&gt;· Configuration management tools (10 points)&lt;br&gt;· Knowledge of build processes (5 points)&lt;br&gt;· Release management processes (5 points)&lt;br&gt;· Change management processes (5 points)&lt;br&gt;· Defect management processes (5 points)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pricing (20 points)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much for your consideration and have a wonderful day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ann-marie Geanus&lt;br&gt;Ant and Bee Corporation&lt;br&gt;416-646-2811 ext. 244&lt;br&gt;ageanus@antandbee.com&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7BF5C650-D48F-47CF-B840-A56091D3308F</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-04T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>a Programmer (JAVA)-Contract Position</title>
</post>
