<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior J2EE Architect &lt;br&gt;Toronto Area - Downtown, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;This is an exciting opportunity located at our offices in Downtown, Toronto. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will bring strong technical hands on skills to our consulting team and will assume a leadership role. You will be responsible for the development of technical architectures and integration strategies for all facets of systems integration and consulting. You will play an integral part in the architectural design of the project, provide support to the team and interact with senior level executives on both the project and client organization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ideal candidate will have 10+ years experience in the information technology industry and 3+ years of development and architecture experience on J2EE platform preferably with BEA Weblogic and Commerce Server exposure. You are experienced with E-Commerce Design and application design and have strong knowledge of systems architectural models, internet networking architectures. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ideal candidate will have hands on experience with Rational Unified Process (RUP). You must have experience with E-Commerce Design, Technical Project Management and application design. You will also bring an understanding of systems architectural models and Internet networking architectures and will be able to provide technical direction to developers, both during development and testing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join a winning team. CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration, and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start day one and includes a minimum of 3 weeks vacation, profit sharing and a stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RE)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;J2EE architecture&lt;br&gt;Experience managing the architectural design of large scale projects&lt;br&gt;E-Commerce Design, Project Management and Application Design&lt;br&gt;Rational Unified Process&lt;br&gt;Weblogic or Websphere&lt;br&gt;Nice to Have Skills&lt;br&gt;.NET&lt;br&gt;Tuxedo&lt;br&gt;DB2&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7D9F7476-0B8F-4B9E-AD7A-DE90A0347AF3</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior J2EE Architect</title>
</post>
