<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Heo, Hong</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Gartner research predicts :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By 2003, 75 percent of new IT application development projects will be based on Microsoft’s .NET and enterprise Java architectures (0.7 probability).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By 2003, 50 percent or more of new IT application development projects will be based on enterprise Java architectures (0.3 probability).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you see, Java is becoming a de facto platform for mainstream e-business solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To get through slim career market in IT industry, as well as to alive as a strong survivor, Java developer can be a good candidate for these goals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many special areas in computer-related jobs and many people wonder which one is comparably suitable to choose for me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are not certain for your specialty, check this first, or if you already have a specialty in java, please skip to next :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Web-oriented service(mandatory)&lt;br&gt;- Object-Oriented Programming(thorough understanding of OOD concept mandatory)&lt;br&gt;- SQL database programming(required)&lt;br&gt;- Oracle or RDBMS, Stored Procedure-PL/SQL(asset)&lt;br&gt;- Data modeling(optional)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you already know Java or experienced in some period :- Intermediate Level :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Servlet&lt;br&gt;- JSP(Java Server Page)&lt;br&gt;- Java Bean&lt;br&gt;- MVC(Model-View-Control) model(Jakarta Struts) on server-side&lt;br&gt;- JDBC programming&lt;br&gt;- EJB- Session Bean&lt;br&gt;- EJB- Entity Bean(CMP, BMP)&lt;br&gt;- XML&lt;br&gt;- Web session management - HttpSession, cookies, HTTP-rewrite&lt;br&gt;- IDE(Especially, JBuilder 4.0+)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is for Senior Java Developer :&lt;br&gt;- At least 3 years Java experience&lt;br&gt;- UML design and understaning skills are definetly asset&lt;br&gt;- Together ControlCenter(optional but asset)&lt;br&gt;- WebLogic or Websphere(practical experience)&lt;br&gt;- RMI&lt;br&gt;- JDBC connection pooling&lt;br&gt;- Multi-threaded programming&lt;br&gt;- Network programming(Java Mail, JNDI, Java Messaging)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last, to be a Java Architect :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- RUP(Rational Unified Process) methodology&lt;br&gt;- UML analysis and design(Rational Rose)&lt;br&gt;- Together ControlCentor 5.* (for Senior Java Architect)&lt;br&gt;- At least 5 years industry experience in IT&lt;br&gt;- Thorough understaning of J2EE&lt;br&gt;- Strong documentation skill in English&lt;br&gt;- Strong presentation skill in English&lt;br&gt;- Being able to consume political issues within team organization&lt;br&gt;- Master degree is asset &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I believe that most of interview questions are focused on those topics.&lt;br&gt;And please do not afraid of English sentences and try to be more familar with English environment. That's why I wrote it in English even though I'm not fluent. I always try to use and use until I've got accustomed to.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DH&lt;br&gt;Sr. Java Architect in BCE.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>806CC5E1-5956-4385-8212-61BC19200371</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-11-08T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>A tip to get a job for Java Developer</title>
</post>
