<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills:&lt;br&gt;Java, system, architecture, systems, Database, Oracle, IT, development, J2EE, Wireless, Network, Unix, CGI&lt;br&gt;Date:&lt;br&gt;4-4-2010&lt;br&gt;Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description Technical Java Lead&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This role is totechnically lead the design and implementation of a highly&lt;br&gt;scalable Java system in a multi-node architecture ( over 30 nodes). This&lt;br&gt;individual is expected to be hands on when required and have the aptitude to&lt;br&gt;pick up any technical issues quickly and have the leadership to analyse and&lt;br&gt;provide recommendations on solutions.&lt;br&gt;A strong background on how the overall systems work end to end from&lt;br&gt;Infrastructure (H/W &amp; OS) to Database (Oracle), to Java (JVM) and&lt;br&gt;webservers, to ensure high throughput is maintained is essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proven skills as a technical expert and team leader in an IT development&lt;br&gt;environment: Java, J2EE.&lt;br&gt;Experience in building large scale, high transaction volume systems.&lt;br&gt;Good understanding of Database design, and various vertical and horizontal&lt;br&gt;scaling of Java solutions.&lt;br&gt;Experience leading offshore resources an asset.&lt;br&gt;Exceptional Soft Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry Skills:&lt;br&gt;Good understanding of Wireless Network mediation would be nice to have.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Level of Education&lt;br&gt;Java certification&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Technical Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Java / J2EE expert 5+ yr&lt;br&gt;Large scale Java systems design expert 5+ yrs&lt;br&gt;Database/Oracle senior 3+&lt;br&gt;Unix senior 3+&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to Have Technical Skills:&lt;br&gt;Amazon EC2 configuration and deployment experience is highly desirable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At CGI, were a team of builders. We call our employees members because all&lt;br&gt;who join CGI are building their own company one that has grown to 25,000&lt;br&gt;professionals in 100+ offices worldwide. Founded in 1976, CGI is a leading&lt;br&gt;IT and business process services firm committed to helping clients win and&lt;br&gt;grow. We have the global resources, expertise, stability and dedicated&lt;br&gt;professionals needed to achieve results for our clients and for our members.&lt;br&gt;Come grow with us. Learn more at www.cgi.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join a winning team. CGI offers a competitive&lt;br&gt;compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional&lt;br&gt;development. Benefits for full-time, permanent members start on the first&lt;br&gt;day of employment and include a paid time-off program and profit&lt;br&gt;participation and stock purchase plans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying&lt;br&gt;for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be&lt;br&gt;contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WE ARE AN EQUAL OPPORTUNITY EMPLOYER.&lt;br&gt;_________________________________________________________________&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills&lt;br&gt;* J2EE&lt;br&gt;* Java&lt;br&gt;* Oracle&lt;br&gt;* UNIX&lt;br&gt;_________________________________________________________________&lt;br&gt;CGI&lt;br&gt;Web: http://www.cgi.com</content>
    <postId>815B4E14-2559-4267-B998-5037C303AA10</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Java Lead-CGI</title>
</post>
