<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이종규</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김규식</author>
            <date>2002-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>I could not find the job in the web site.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Systems Consultant &amp;#8211; 0200030&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description &lt;br&gt;The USI Systems Sales Compensation Team requires additional team members to support a series of initiatives significantly enhancing the existing Agency system. This position reports to the project manager of the Sales Compensation team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participate in the architecture, design, development and implementation of enhanced Agency business functionality. &lt;br&gt;Implement new functionality, enhance existing system functions, further develop the technical architecture, and provide solutions to complex technical and business problems. &lt;br&gt;Coach/mentor more junior System Analyst staff and provide leadership in the use of design principles and finding new ways to be more efficient.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Qualifications &lt;br&gt;Essential: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6-8 years of mainframe development experience in addition to architectural and design skills&lt;br&gt;Extensive experience with Agency systems, COBOL, CAP, DB2, CICS and JCL. Strong mainframe technical, analytical and design skills required&lt;br&gt;Understand and use design principles effectively &lt;br&gt;Strong interpersonal skills to work effectively with internal user community and Sales Compensation team members &lt;br&gt;Ability to understand the customers perspective, but also be able to influence decisions&lt;br&gt;Ability to mentor/coach staff &lt;br&gt;Ability to learn and apply new business and technical knowledge quickly and effectively &lt;br&gt;Good understanding of project management methodologies &lt;br&gt;Effective use of Manulife's Standard System Development Methodology &lt;br&gt;Ability to be flexible and adaptable when dealing with changes and work well under pressure &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Helpful: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of other systems which interact with the Agency systems &lt;br&gt;Insurance Industry experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Band: SM&lt;br&gt;Salary: $70,100.00 - $116,900.00&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note that if you wish to apply for this position, Human Resources hiring policies (found in the US and Canadian Employee Guides) apply. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Profile&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Position Title&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Information Technology&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Location&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; CA-ON-*Toronto-200 Bloor Street E&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Organization&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; US Individual&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Schedule&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Full Time&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Additional Information&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Opening&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; January 18, 2002&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Closing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; February 17, 2002&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Recruiter&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Emma deVries&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hiring Manager&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; John Coro&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employment Type:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Regular &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>81652E7E-44CF-47D9-8595-311F35AAC8A3</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-01-25T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>manulife에서 MainFrame 경력자를 구하네요...참조하세요</title>
</post>
