<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Software QA Test Lead: Web-Based Application&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have an immediate need for a highly skilled QA Test Lead to join our team in Toronto. In this challenging and rewarding role, you will be responsible for assisting our Fortune 50 client with the software quality assurance testing of a global B2B catalog management system. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The system you will be testing collects data (localization options, prices, product descriptions, discounts, etc.) from several different sources, uses this data to populate its own database, and then uses rules specified through the GUI to reassemble the data into catalogs that are fed to downstream systems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a successful candidate, you must have at least 5 years hands-on experience in the formal quality assurance testing of software including the knowledge of current testing tools and methodologies. To be considered for this position your detailed cover letter and resume must confirm that you possess all the necessary skills and experience as outlined below. Your cover letter must state the range of expected monthly remuneration. To be considered, you must currently be unemployed, and as such be available for immediate start. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This opportunity will call on your experience:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Analyzing business requirements and application specifications (technical/functional) &lt;br&gt;- Devising test strategies &lt;br&gt;- Identifying and writing test cases/scripts for manual software testing (functionality, GUI, usability, regression)&lt;br&gt;- Executing test cases using manual testing in a Client server environment &lt;br&gt;- Detecting, analyzing, rating and reporting defects&lt;br&gt;- Leading a formal software quality assurance testing effort&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**We’re looking for bright, proactive, and hard working minds to join our tech-savvy team.**&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Analyze the business requirements document, technical spec, and functional spec, and from these, understand what the application is intended to do and arrive at a test strategy and suitable set of tests that will validate that the application performs as it is intended to.&lt;br&gt;- Create clear, concise, detail oriented test plans and test cases/scripts for manual software testing (functionality, GUI, usability, regression)&lt;br&gt;- Perform both new functionality and regression tests; identify, rate and report defects for follow-up&lt;br&gt;- Perform tests and validation activities to ensure data integrity&lt;br&gt;- Liaise with development team, project management and business owners for testing and QA related functions via daily teleconferences and in-person meetings as required&lt;br&gt;- Interface with both client and internal testing resources to ensure deliverables are achieved in line with key project milestones&lt;br&gt;- Lead and coordinate internal team of QA testers&lt;br&gt;- Report to and interface with internal project management&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE (GENERAL):&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Must have high standards of professionalism&lt;br&gt;- At least 5 years experience in the field of formal software quality assurance testing with an excellent understanding of current testing methodologies and techniques&lt;br&gt;- Demonstrated experience leading a formal QA test effort&lt;br&gt;- Must be a demonstrated self-starter &amp;#8211; independently figure out what needs to be done and get it done&lt;br&gt;- Able to effectively lead a team of testers&lt;br&gt;- Able to estimate the test workload and lead all testing activities at the project level&lt;br&gt;- Able to design complex and custom test plans at the systems, regression, integration and acceptance levels&lt;br&gt;- Able to develop and revise testing procedures, standards and methods &lt;br&gt;- Able to evaluate and select testing tools and products&lt;br&gt;- Able to interface and report effectively to internal project management regarding testing QA/issues, timelines, etc.&lt;br&gt;- Experience in defect tracking management&lt;br&gt;- Impeccable written and oral communication skills &lt;br&gt;- Business-oriented; ability to interpret scope/requirements documentation and understand the technical implementation of same requirements set &lt;br&gt;- Proficient in MS Office &lt;br&gt;- High-energy personality&lt;br&gt;- Excellent presenter&lt;br&gt;- Highly analytical, thorough, logical, detail-oriented&lt;br&gt;- Amicable personality and positive attitude &amp;#8211; must be a people-person&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE (PROJECT SPECIFIC):&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Demonstrated data validation expertise; experience comparing and working with flat files (i.e. tab-delimited, XML, etc.)&lt;br&gt;- Experience and familiarity working with data structures&lt;br&gt;- Familiar with system-to-system transfer protocols&lt;br&gt;- Know how to analyze data collection, storage, manipulation and distribution flows&lt;br&gt;- Familiar with eBusiness and other Web-enabled systems (i.e. Web catalog management systems)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT APPLICATION REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To be considered for this position YOU MUST meet ALL of the following requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. You must be able to demonstrate that you have ALL of the qualifications outlined above&lt;br&gt;2. You must have at least 5 years hands on formal SQA testing experience as well as demonstrated experience leading a formal testing effort &lt;br&gt;3. In addition to your resume, to be considered you must submit a cover letter that confirms (1) your ability to start immediately, (2) your expected monthly rate, and (3) your acknowledgement that this is a contract position&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your profile matches the requirements outlined above, and you’re available to start immediately, then we’ve got the perfect job for you! Rush your detailed cover letter, resume, and monthly remuneration expectation to our recruiters at careers@mediaclay.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note this is a very competitive opportunity and the contract will be awarded on a point rated criteria where a candidate's experience will be judged against his or her monthly billing rate. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Temporary/Contract/Project&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers@mediaclay.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>81960ED7-CF22-4698-A822-91BBF3564E79</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software QA Test Lead: Web-Based Application</title>
</post>
