<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>허현옥</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>오늘 제가 메일받고 전화까지 받았는데요...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linux, Windows를 어느정도 하시고, 네트웍에 대해서 좀 아시면&lt;br&gt;이메일이나 전화를 해보세요.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;네트웍장비에 대한 Technical Supporter 같은데요. 주로 Support할 대상이&lt;br&gt;한국에서 오는 건 가보네요. Recruiter가 빨리 좀 구했으면 하네요..^^&lt;br&gt;아 처음에 교육도 해준다니까 관심있으신 분들은 연락해보시면 좋을 듯...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;이하는 메일 원문입니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hello Hyeonok Heo, I am a recruiter for Pivotal. I was viewing resumes on workopolis and I came across yours and I noticed that you had some skills that match a position we have available. I just have a few questions for you. On your resume it states that you are willing to relocate, this position is in Mississauga near Toronto , I am wondering if you would be interested in moving here to pursue a career. My second question revolves around your qualifications, this position is a Bilingual Korean/English position in which you would need a strong background in Linux, Windows and networking, at what level would you say your skills are in each of the skills I listed above? Lastly below I have listed all of the job specs below. Here is the link for the company for your perusal. www.sbs.siemens.ca&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Company Name: Siemens&lt;br&gt;Account: EMC&lt;br&gt;Role: Bilingual Technical Support &lt;br&gt;Status: 1 year contract to Full time- If performance standards are met FT is offered after 1 year&lt;br&gt;Shifts: 8hrs/day on a 24/7 schedule rotating every 2 weeks&lt;br&gt;Compensation: $20.00 per hour for duration of contract&lt;br&gt;Location: 6375 Shawson drive in Mississauga&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Let me know if you feel this is a good fit for you.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Shawn Daley&lt;br&gt;Resource Manager&lt;br&gt;PIVOTAL Integrated HR solutions&lt;br&gt;100 Milverton St Suite 801,L5R 4H1&lt;br&gt;Mississauga, Ontario&lt;br&gt;O- 905 890 4450&lt;br&gt;C- 905 510 5415&lt;br&gt;F- 905 507 9718&lt;br&gt;sdaley@pivotalsolutions.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>81AA6CE0-FF52-4BB0-8385-0192481672AC</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>영어/한국어 되시는 Technical Supporter를 찾네요.</title>
</post>
