<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Ruby on Rails Web Developer&lt;br&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;Mosaic Sales Solutions Canada is a Sales/Merchandising and Experiential Marketing agency that utilizes our considerable expertise, proven best practices and leading-edge technology to execute brand relevant selling, merchandising and event marketing programs across all retail channels and business-to-business.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mosaic Interactive, a department dedicated to creating high quality marketing websites for some of North America's leading brands, is currently recruiting for a full-time Ruby on Rails Web Developer to join the team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience in Ruby on Rails web development with production code (2-3 years) using PostgreSQL or MySQL Databases.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Working alongside a team of designers, web developers, project managers to deliver web applications. &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we're looking for:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Someone with attention to detail and quality orientated. Someone who is keen to learn, can take a task and solve it. You will be familiar with web development concepts and will have applied them in production for a number of years. Someone who takes pride in their work and can point to their achievements with enthusiasm.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While we would like 3 years experience in Ruby on Rails, we are not frightened if you just graduated! Come talk to us. Just demonstrate an understanding of web application development and show example(s) of working application(s) from start to end. &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The more things you can tick off in this statement, the more likely we are going to hire you. Most important to us is your ability to learn and your attention to details. These things will however make a difference..&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You understand web frameworks and why they are important.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You have developed and produced production code in Ruby on Rails for a number of years&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You will search in an open source library before trying to write something yourself&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You understand that indexes are good on database tables and have heard of the n+1 problem&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You understand what XSS is and how to avoid it&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You can edit an apache config file in order to get a vhost setup&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You understand the difference between unit testing and integration testing&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Unix command lines, well, you just have a thing for, or are in wondrous amazement how efficient those Unix sys admin's are..&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You are aware there is this browser known as IE6 that wreaks havoc in websites, and will test against it&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we offer:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A fun work environment and great team within a solid respected company. An amazing company culture that we believe is second to none. Our client list includes a who's who of big Brands across the spectrum, so within a year you will likely be able to point to be a big nationwide campaign website and say "I built that".&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;Please save yourself the time:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We are not looking for a "rock star" or a "ninja". These are terms often used for people to come in and "save the day" for a startup. That is not what we are looking for; there are plenty of startups out there that will offer you that.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This job is not for 'architects' as you may get bored in the position&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We are not looking to relocate people, nor are we able to offer telecommuting for this role.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum 2-5 years experience with Ruby on Rails Web Development &lt;br&gt;2-3 years using PostgreSQL or MySQL Databases &lt;br&gt;Example(s) of working application(s) from start to end (show us your portfolio) &lt;br&gt;Strong organizational skills &lt;br&gt;Comfortable working independently and in collaborative scenarios &lt;br&gt;Understanding of web frameworks and why they are important.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working within a team environment is extremely important to us and it will be to you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We love our workplace and we hope you will too.</content>
    <postId>831CBA5F-CE38-4E39-963B-51F61602D12C</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Ruby on Rails Web Developer</title>
</post>
