<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Java Developer&lt;br&gt;CPNI INC&lt;br&gt;Etobicoke, ON, CANADA; Mississauga, ON, CANADA; Toronto, ON, CANADA&lt;br&gt;Posted Mar 29, 2010&lt;br&gt;1 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAVA DEVELOPER&lt;br&gt;CPNI Inc. is a technology startup firm which provides application software and associated services to the financial industry, with a focus on Mobile Payments. Our technology is network-aware and has server and mobile phone components. Our flagship product facilitates money transfer services over the telephone, in a secured manner, and from anywhere in the world.&lt;br&gt;What We Need Most&lt;br&gt;Java professionals who simply love to create software. Our software development focuses on delivering wireless-based payment solutions using cutting-edge technologies. We'll give you some coding problems and you will blow us away with your brilliant solutions.&lt;br&gt;The Right Fit&lt;br&gt;Our formula for success starts with our people. We look for software experts by aptitude, and not mere training - in other words, serious techies who are proud of being techies. Our culture is based on the eXtreme Programming (agile) philosophy. If you are a programmer who is passionate about technology, loves collaborating with other keen minds, and possess tremendous skills with designing software and solving problems, let's talk.&lt;br&gt;The Challenges&lt;br&gt;The avant-garde Java pilot at CPNI has to be adaptive, learn a breadth of technologies, and be able to turn on a dime in this fast paced environment. Extraordinary is ordinary here. You'll be solving complex problems under pressure, mentoring other developers,and even parachuting into someone else's code. But you'll thrive.&lt;br&gt;Stuff our Hiring Managers Want to See&lt;br&gt;BS or MS in Computer Science or Engineering&lt;br&gt;Thorough understanding of the object-oriented paradigm&lt;br&gt;Well-developed and demonstrable coding and testing skills in Java&lt;br&gt;Nevertheless, experience with our current set of technologies will certainly help you thrive quicker&lt;br&gt;Java 5, Java 6&lt;br&gt;Java EE 5, Tomcat, Websphere, JBoss&lt;br&gt;MySQL, DB2, Oracle, Hibernate, JPA&lt;br&gt;J2ME, Objective-C, WAP, XHTML MP&lt;br&gt;Ruby, Buildr, FitNesse&lt;br&gt;Bottom Line&lt;br&gt;We are looking for software professionals who can really hit the high notes! You can make a difference and be part of a great story in Canadian high tech! For the right person, the opportunities are unlimited.&lt;br&gt;To Apply&lt;br&gt;Please send a cover letter telling us why you feel that you would qualify for this job along with your resume to: careers@cpni-inc.com .&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>8384AE87-AB02-43CF-8A40-FB5C859E598A</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-31T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer</title>
</post>
