<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Henry</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>제가 일하는 회사 notes담당자가 홍콩으로 돌아간답니다. 바로, 채용공고를 올리는군요. 아래 홈페이지를 참고하시고 직접 지원하세요.(저는 코업으로 일하고 있어서 도움이 못되드릴것 같습니다.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;www.socan.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br&gt;JOB POSTING&lt;br&gt;Information Technology&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;POSITION:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Lotus Notes Administrator&lt;br&gt;REPORTS TO:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Supervisor, PC/LAN Administration&lt;br&gt;LOCATION:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto&lt;br&gt;PAYBAND LEVEL:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;7&lt;br&gt;SALARY RANGE:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;$50,720 - $59,670&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Accountable for all aspects of the development, support and maintenance of Lotus Notes applications for all functional areas within SOCAN. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Solid understanding of general business practices, working with project managers, user groups, management and external clients to analyze, evaluate and determine user requirements for Lotus Notes applications.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Provide advanced level support and system maintenance of SOCAN’s Lotus Domino environment.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Oversee the support, upgrades, and enhancements of all of SOCAN’s Lotus Notes Environment. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Formulate and enforce Lotus Notes policies, guidelines, and procedures.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Provide second level support for user community's usage of Lotus Notes (mixture of Windows NT, Windows 2000, Windows XP and Citrix). &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Perform general administrative tasks, such as resolving replication problems, database rollouts, mail routing issues, file restores, audits of databases, routine preventative maintenance and troubleshooting.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Design Lotus Notes applications that will cater to the defined user needs and perform the system development and implementation of the systems.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Perform Microsoft Windows 2000 server administrative tasks, such as setting up servers, troubleshooting connectivity issues, and patch management. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Participate in planning, training and execution of rollouts of new versions of Lotus software for both clients and servers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REQUIREMENTS:&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Three or more years work experience with Lotus Notes R5 and R6 in a Lotus Notes Administrator/Designer role. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Proven experience in development of document management systems. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Strong knowledge of computer networks, client-server architecture, and microcomputer environment. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Strong knowledge of Microsoft Windows 2000 and various protocols. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working knowledge of some or all of the following: Windows NT, MS Windows 2000, MS Windows 2003, MS Windows XP, Crystal Report, MS Office, MS Access, MNotes and Visual Basic.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excellent analytical, verbal and written communication skills. &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Project management skills.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Strong interpersonal skills and the ability to perform and contribute in a team focused environment.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excellent technical knowledge and experience with a wide range of PC workstation hardware environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDUCATION:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Post secondary level in Computer Science Engineering or equivalent.&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Certified Lotus professional (CLP) System Administration or certification is in progress.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLICATION PROCEDURE:&lt;br&gt;If you are interested in and qualify for this position, please apply in writing to Human Resources and include a copy of your resume.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SELECTION:&lt;br&gt;Skills may be tested and selection will be based on factors such as past performance, previous related experience and alignment of personal skills and attributes to those required to perform the job.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Only qualified applicants will be contacted for an interview.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEADLINE:&lt;br&gt;The deadline for applications is October 6, 2004.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORKWEEK:&lt;br&gt;The successful applicant will have the option of working a 4 or 5-day workweek.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In this position, if you opt for a 4-day week your day off (either Monday or Friday), will be determined by your Manager in accordance with the department’s requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>84684401-2575-4403-A0A5-D820B55C3569</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Lotus Notes Administrator(Internal Job Posting)</title>
</post>
