<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;J2EE Web Developer &amp;#8211; 4 month contract&lt;br&gt;I was reviewing your resume and wanted to know if you are interested in a 4 month contract as a J2EE Web Developer.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Qualified candidates should forward their resume in WORD DOCUMENT FORMAT, with their name and the position they are applying for in the subject line of their email, to: abby.cheung@cryptologic.com. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In your reply you must indicate:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hourly rate&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Availability&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Review our website www.cryptologic.com to understand our industry and location&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You are able to complete a technical test&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Numbers of years and which company you have been responsible for OOAD and web-based programming using Java and J2EE to build large-scale applications in an enterprise environment &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Number of years and which company you worked in EJB, JSP, Servlets, STRUTS, Ant, JBuilder &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Number of years and which company you worked in UML &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Number of years and which company you worked in XML, SOAP&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SUN Certified accreditation is a definite asset&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience working with Internet based payment solutions an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;POSITION SUMMARY:&lt;br&gt;CryptoLogic Inc. is looking for an outstanding Web Developer who will play a major role in the development, maintenance, and deployment of the Company’s many exciting web-based solutions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Team Lead of Web Services, this demanding role requires strong Java and J2EE skills developing seamless web-based applications. The ideal candidate should have demonstrable project experience working with these technologies combined with exceptional oral and written communication skills. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Minimum of 5 years of OOAD and web-based programming experience using Java and J2EE to build large-scale applications in an enterprise environment. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Proven hands-on experience with J2EE, JSP, Struts, Jakarta Commons, Hibernate, Spring, and Web Services &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Solid understanding of SOA. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Good working knowledge of UML, object modeling, analysis and design patterns. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excellent written and verbal communication skills are required.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Strong focus on teamwork and achieving team goals.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Entrepreneurial, creative, resourceful, insightful, self-motivated and self-confident.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;abby.cheung@cryptologic.com&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>8547084B-C781-4996-88D2-F3DA3EFF36CF</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-11-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Web Developer</title>
</post>
