<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title: Java/J2EE Developer&lt;br&gt;Posted On: 3/30/2010 8:46:39 AM&lt;br&gt;Designation: Java/J2EE Developer&lt;br&gt;Number of Vacancies: 1&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: BS in Computer Science&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: &lt;br&gt;Java - 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Minimum Experience: 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Job Tenure: Full-time Only&lt;br&gt;Salary Offered: DOE&lt;br&gt;Job Location: Toronto, ON, Canada&lt;br&gt; Job Description &lt;br&gt;* We are seeking Java developers who are looking to take their experience to the next level. &lt;br&gt;* A minimum of 3+ years of professional Java development experience is required. &lt;br&gt;* The ideal candidates should have experience with Java, J2EE, Object Oriented Design, and Relational Databases. &lt;br&gt;* Pluses would include JUnit, JBoss, HTML and/or AJAX. A proven track record of working in a team environment, and experience with all phases of the software development life cycle is also required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;* Design, build, unit test and release software to analyze medical images and collect radiology assessments in support of clinical trials.&lt;br&gt;* Work with end users to understand requirements and troubleshoot system defects.&lt;br&gt;* Write design specifications, installation guides and other technical documentation in accordance with Synarc best practices.&lt;br&gt;* Work with other technical staff to support system installations, upgrades, and configurations of reading system software.&lt;br&gt;* Assist in training of users and creation of user manuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;The ideal candidates will be comfortable working in a Unix/Linux &lt;br&gt;environment and have experience using the following tools, or have the skills &lt;br&gt;and desire to quickly become proficient in:&lt;br&gt;- Java&lt;br&gt;- J2EE&lt;br&gt;- Object Oriented Design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Company Details&lt;br&gt;Name: Hays Information Technology&lt;br&gt;Type: Corporate Organization&lt;br&gt;Total Employees: 5000&lt;br&gt;Turnover: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Address: &lt;br&gt;606-700 West Pender Street,&lt;br&gt;Vancouver,&lt;br&gt;BC,&lt;br&gt;Canada&lt;br&gt;Profile: &lt;br&gt;Hays Specialist Recruitment Canada is a wholly owned subsidiary of Hays plc, which has been at the forefront of recruitment for over thirty-five years and which boasts annual revenues of over ￡1.3 billion. With the corporate head office located in the United Kingdom, Hays Specialist Recruitment is the largest specialist recruitment consultancy in the world. With 603 specialist business units and over 4600 employees, the company has over 300 offices worldwide. There are over 270 offices in the UK and Ireland alone. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other global locations include Australia, New Zealand, UAE, the Netherlands, Luxembourg, Germany, Spain, Portugal, France, Belgium, Sweden, Poland, Austria, the Czech Republic and of course Canada. Hays Specialist Recruitment enjoys leading positions in the vast majority of its markets. For organizations seeking to recruit globally, the network and presence in the world’s major markets give you the assurance of expert co-ordination of your world wide recruiting requirements</content>
    <postId>85BE09B9-7E34-4771-AAC3-1C33FA00D6EB</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java/J2EE Developer</title>
</post>
