<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Ranked on Profit Magazine's annual Hot list of Canada's top emerging growth companies for two years in a row, Workbrain builds innovative, web- based Workforce Management software that optimizes the deployment and management of large, complex workforces for maximum profitability. To learn more about the company and the solutions that are driving our success, visit www.workbrain.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working within the Schedule Optimization area in Research &amp; Development, the Optimization Developer will be responsible for enhancing the functionality and performance of Workbrain’s Labour Forecasting and Schedule Optimization software module. At the core of the module is a mixed integer/goal programming mathematical model. The problem is coded and solved using Dash. The ideal candidate will be expected to: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Extend the current mathematical model to handle new features and constraints &amp;#8226; Code new features and constraints into the MOSEL language from Dash Optimization &amp;#8226; Conduct performance analysis to determine if any improvements can be made with regards to the current model. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Investigate new techniques for solving labour scheduling problems &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Master’s degree in Systems Design, Industrial Engineering, Management Science or Mathematics (specializing in Applied Mathematics, Combinatorics and Optimization or Operations Research) &amp;#8226; Knowledge of mathematical programming software such as DASH, GAMS, Lindo, or ILOG &amp;#8226; An excellent command of English as you will need to work intimately with Product Mangers and other developers. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Programming: 1-2 years Java (J2EE), Back-end development. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent problem solving abilities &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vinh Quan, PhD., P.Eng. &lt;br&gt;President, CORS Toronto Section &lt;br&gt;Technical Implementation Architect, Workbrain Inc. &lt;br&gt;416-421-6700x2382, vquan@workbrain.com </content>
    <postId>85E2334D-F4DE-4B78-9F03-8C87B5312B7C</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-06-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Job opening at Workbrain</title>
</post>
