<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이상윤</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Dear All,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Thank you for your interest in Software Research Group(SRG). We, at SRG, so excited about your interest in us. You made us feel very happy. We are looking for many many employees for our company.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Depending upon your experience, we have already made some selections, almost 100 of you have already been selected to work with us. I am working on papers to make it possible to work in the USA. Some of you who have excellent experience and who are&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Permanent Residents or Landed immigrants, as we discussed, we may have to wait until we will apply for H1 rather than applying VISA which allows Canadian citizens to work in the USA immediately. We are interested, but we have to wait until April of 2006 to apply for H1. The H1 quota for this year has exhausted. I will 100% get back to you to talk in more detail. We hardly leave anybody out! SRG strongly believes in Training. We will train you if needed. We need everyone of you!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Starting from tomorrow, we are calling some of you who we did not have sufficient time to talk to. Please feel free to call me at 732-742-9127 if you have any questions. Please send me an email to canadajobs@srgroup.net.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;PLEASE TALK TO YOUR FRIENDS! SEND YOUR FRIENDS' RESUMES TO ME!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;Raghu Daripalli&lt;br&gt;President&lt;br&gt;Software Research Group, Inc.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Phone: 732-742-9127&lt;br&gt;Fax:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;732-636-1933&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;email: ragu@srgroup.net&lt;br&gt;Web: www.srgroup.net&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;485 US Highway 1 South&lt;br&gt;Building E, Suite 240&lt;br&gt;Iselin, NJ 08830&lt;br&gt;USA&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>85F77086-8223-4F77-9216-FEE9EE683F26</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Job Fair에 다녀온 후 받은 메일 입니다.</title>
</post>
