<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;INTERMEDIATE C/C++ DEVELOPER&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brief Job Description:&lt;br&gt;?Lead activity for projects to include: work direction to fellow engineers and to provide technical input based on knowledge and expertise.&lt;br&gt;?Participate as senior developer for projects.&lt;br&gt;?Resolve technical issues with project teams to ensure schedule is maintained and specifications are met.&lt;br&gt;?Interact with various functional areas to determine design feasibility and/or component selection and performance characteristics.&lt;br&gt;?With Engineering Management, develop planning activity for projects to include: schedule development, cost/time estimates, risk assessments, and resource requirements.&lt;br&gt;?Participate in the management of project budget by identifying resource requirements and by identifying tools and components required.&lt;br&gt;?Provide technology insight, direction and support to Management relative to business planning and decision making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Skills Required:&lt;br&gt;Experience with the following is considered a must: &lt;br&gt;?C/C++ programming proficiency&lt;br&gt;?Following coding standards / development procedures&lt;br&gt;?C/C++ programming in a multithreaded Microsoft Windows environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other Skills Required:&lt;br&gt;?Excellent communication skills, both written and verbal&lt;br&gt;?Proven leadership skills&lt;br&gt;?Ability to work well in a team environment as well as independently&lt;br&gt;?Excellent Time Management skills are a must in this role in addition to the need to multi-task&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education: BEng. (Comp Sci option) and/or BSc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Level: Intermediate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NO AGENCIES PLEASE!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Email: careers@mistwireless.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note in the subject line of your email the position you are applying for. Please include your resume as text in the body of the email and NOT as an attachment. Thank you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: MB-Int Dev.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers@mistwireless.com&lt;br&gt;703 Evans Ave., Suite 500&lt;br&gt;Etobicoke ON M9C 5E9&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>86F119D3-C732-418A-9E46-84A3060FED80</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-22T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>INTERMEDIATE C/C++ DEVELOPER</title>
</post>
