<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>PROGRAMMER ANALYST&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE JOB&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Programmer Analyst is responsible for back-end application development. Reporting to Manager, Technical Development, the successful candidate will work primarily within the Technical Development group and will be engaged in high priority software development initiatives. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidate responsibilities will include the following:&lt;br&gt;- Architecture, programming and support on consumer focused Java/J2EE projects. &lt;br&gt;- Full technical ownership of several key member retention tools.&lt;br&gt;- Working closely with client development and network group to ensure 24/7 support of applications.&lt;br&gt;- Provide basic administration, backup, recovery, installation and maintenance of existing production applications. &lt;br&gt;- Responsible to work with content development, project management and design teams.&lt;br&gt;- Responsible to work closely with both the US and International development teams. &lt;br&gt;- Assist in QA and creation of test plans.&lt;br&gt;- Development using a wide range of internet technologies along with AOL proprietary tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Proven technical background with considerable software engineering and development skills&lt;br&gt;-3+ years of application object-oriented design/development experience using Java- and J2EE/EJB-associated technologies (JSP, JDBC, JMS, JTS)&lt;br&gt;-7+ years of application object-oriented design/development experience with C/C++&lt;br&gt;-3+ years of experience with design/development of multi-tier net-centric architectures&lt;br&gt;-2+ years of experience with of servlet engines and application servers (e.g. iPlanet, WebLogic, WebSphere)&lt;br&gt;-Experience using XML/XSL/XSLT related standards&lt;br&gt;-Experience with Testing Methodologies&lt;br&gt;-3+ years of Microsoft Visual C++ development experience&lt;br&gt;-5+ years of client-server development experience including client, server, middleware, communications&lt;br&gt;-3+ years of Internet/Web development experience including scripting languages such as Perl&lt;br&gt;-Strong (5+ years) Windows and UNIX skills&lt;br&gt;-Strong (5+ years) SQL/RDBMS design experience (Sybase preferrable, Oracle optional)&lt;br&gt;-Strong written and verbal communications skills. Strong organizational skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Bachelor&amp;#47977; degree in a technical field (engineering, computer science) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REWARDS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOL Canada has a lively team environment and deploys state of the art technology . We offer a competitive compensation package and excellent benefits, along with an outstanding career opportunity. Apply your skills with a worldwide leader and experience the rewards we have to offer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send your resume with salary history in confidence to Human Resources Department, Recruiter, AOL Canada; e-mail llhawke@aol.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: lh 42&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;LLHAWKE@AOL.COM&lt;br&gt;55 St Clair Ave West&lt;br&gt;Toronto&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>879683AC-1373-46C7-92AD-72FB59788A6C</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-26T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>PROGRAMMER ANALYST</title>
</post>
