<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Application Support Specialist,&lt;br&gt;RUNNYMEDE HEALTHCARE CENTRE&lt;br&gt;Etobicoke, ON, CANADA; GTA, ON, CANADA; North York, ON, CANADA; Toronto, ON, CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;Posted Feb 12, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading the way in Complex Continuing Care&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Runnymede Healthcare Centre provides care for adults with neurological disorders, other chronic illnesses and palliative needs through collaboration and partnership. Runnymede Healthcare Centre's innovative, interprofessional approach improves the quality of life for each patient.&lt;br&gt;Construction of the new state-of-the art facility is now complete. For more information about Runnymede Healthcare Centre new facilities, please visit http://www.runnymedehc.ca/&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Application Support Specialist&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Application Support Specialist is responsible for the maintenance, support and security of all the applications required to support Hospital operations, including but not limited to databases and interfaces. The Application Support Specialist also provides expert application support for all internal users, employing high degree of customer service, technical expertise and timeliness. The incumbent may also be assigned to projects and provide business analysis support.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Responsibilities will include:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Provide end-user technical support applications, databases, reports and interfaces&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Plan and support application upgrades and enhancement in conjunction with sponsors, users and vendors:&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Install and assist with testing of new application releases, enhancement requests and bug fixes&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Obtain and test bug fixes outside of major upgrades&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Assist in the definition of application and interface specifications as required&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Manage service levels (fielding calls, requests, incidents, etc)&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Work closely with other teams to solve complex production and operational problems&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Create and maintain comprehensive support documentation as required to maintain Hospital applications&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Assume "on-call" responsibilities as per Hospital policy&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will possess the following qualifications/experience:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Diploma or post-secondary education in Computer Science&lt;br&gt;Desired certifications but not mandatory:&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; HL7 Certification&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Microsoft Certified Technology Specialist (MCTS), Microsoft Certified Database Administrator (MCDBA), Microsoft Certified IT Professional: Database Administrator (MSITPD)&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Oracle Database Administrator Certified Professional, Oracle Database Administrator Certified Associate&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Four to six years of experience in business application design, development, installation and modification in an online environment&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience in the healthcare industry or in a similar production/service environment&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of relevant technology, tools and middleware is critical, including development technologies and scripting languages (e.g. Java, J2EE, Tomcat, .Net, C#, VB, HTML/XML/XSLT, JavaScript, C/C++, Cobol, RPG,), OLE/MS Office, Windows, ODBC, GUIs and Various RDBMS&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of Crystal Reports is an asset&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working knowledge of desktop and server operating systems i.e. Windows 2000&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;For more information on this opportunity and our hospital, visit our website or contact:&lt;br&gt;Human Resources&lt;br&gt;Runnymede Healthcare Centre&lt;br&gt;625 Runnymede Road&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;M6S 3A3&lt;br&gt;Phone - (416) 762-7316&lt;br&gt;Fax - (416) 762-3836&lt;br&gt;e-mail -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;humanres@runnymedehc.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note that any offer of employment will be conditional upon a background check, including a criminal record check.</content>
    <postId>87C157C0-184E-4ECB-BE2D-9D825C1B7BA5</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>HL7 -Application Support Specialist, RUNNYMEDE HEALTHCARE CENTRE</title>
</post>
