<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;TECHNICAL SYSTEMS SUPPORT PROJECT MANAGER&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Careers that know no boundaries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOL Canada Inc. is a strategic alliance between America Online, Inc., the world&amp;#47977; leader in interactive services and Royal Bank, Canada&amp;#47977; premier global financial services group. Working in our dynamic, creative and stimulating environment you will have the opportunity to influence how the Internet impacts on the world. Check out the following opportunity that we have to offer and prepare for a career without limits. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECHNICAL SYSTEMS SUPPORT PROJECT MANAGER&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE JOB&lt;br&gt;Candidate will be responsible for providing 3rd and 4th level support to the AOL Canada Member Services organization. Responsible for taking full ownership of major issues and finding solutions. Candidate will work closely with client development and network group and become the primary technical liaison between client development team and member services. Person will track all issues and provide weekly updates to management. Candidate will be responsible for administering several War dialers, NT, UNIX and LINUX box&amp;#47977;. Provide basic Administration, backup, recovery, installation and maintenance. Candidate will be responsible for all technical issues as they relate to AOL Canada broadband hardware, software, and documentation and client connectivity. Candidate will be responsible for providing advanced training/presentations to member services high-speed team. Candidate will be responsible researching, evaluating, testing and reporting on all technical issues/projects assigned. Provide Technical Support to AOL Canada Management, IMD&amp;#47977; &amp; QA&amp;#47977;. Cross-trained with Network Analyst Position. Provide QA testing to Member Services and Client Development Team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;?-4 years direct experience in a technical support function. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#48610;inimum 2 years project management experience preferably in a web based development environment&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48613;C and software support experience required. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#48616;trong knowledge of networks and network protocols. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#48601;xcellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#48616;trong organizational and time management skills. Ability to establish and evaluate priorities with minimal supervision &lt;br&gt;&amp;#48601;xperience in all MS business applications, Windows, MAC, and UNIX a plus. Rational Visual Test a plus. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#48618;echnical Writing (Training Materials/ Installation Guides) useful.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REWARDS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOL Canada has a lively team environment and deploys state of the art technology . We offer a competitive compensation package and excellent benefits, along with an outstanding career opportunity. Apply your skills with a worldwide leader and experience the rewards we have to offer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send your resume with salary history in confidence to Human Resources Department, Recruiter, AOL Canada; e-mail llhawke@aol.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: lh 40&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;LLHAWKE@AOL.COM&lt;br&gt;AOL Canada&lt;br&gt;55 St. Clair Ave. West&lt;br&gt;Toronto&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>87E582AF-CAEB-4C78-8AE6-EAE694C79203</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-26T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>TECHNICAL SYSTEMS SUPPORT PROJECT MANAGER</title>
</post>
