<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Candidate Required:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Intermediate Java Developer&lt;br&gt;Opportunity Description:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Our Financial services Client is looking for an Intermediate Java Developer to join their team in a Permanent Capacity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their main responsibilities include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Providing team leadership in the technical design, development, testing and implementation of solutions and applications. &lt;br&gt;. Working closely with Application Architect to ensure that the application designs are carried onto the finished products&lt;br&gt;. Working closely with Application Development Manager and Application Architect to ensure that the development and application security guidelines are adhered to through code review&lt;br&gt;. Working with the project team in the preparation and tracking of the project schedule&lt;br&gt;. Providing technical leadership to assigned project staff throughout the application development cycle&lt;br&gt;. Coordinating assigned activities to project team&lt;br&gt;. Working closely with project team to ensure that project deliverables are met on time and on budget, as agreed upon in the project plan&lt;br&gt;. Investigating and resolving technical project issues and problems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Providing technical application development expertise to deliver clients' IT requirements and support websites and applications already in production by: &lt;br&gt;. Analyzing, coding, fixing and enhancing complex programming modules based on technical design and specifications, and in compliance with corporate IT development standards&lt;br&gt;. Developing and overseeing testing and implementation of systems and applications&lt;br&gt;. Recommending technical application development solutions which meet design specifications and client needs and promote overall corporate technology strategy&lt;br&gt;. Acting as a resource in the resolution of technical problems&lt;br&gt;. Establishing and maintaining tools, techniques, standards, documentation and performance criteria required for developing applications&lt;br&gt;. Coordinating development of all technical documentation such as technical specification and design document&lt;br&gt;. Working closely with the Architecture team in defining and implementing the technology infrastructure that meets the organizations strategic goals&lt;br&gt;. Provide application development expertise in completing research activities to establish technology approach/strategy/standards and best practices working with colleagues across the different technical teams&lt;br&gt;Specialization and Skills:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Software Development&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;AJAX&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;DHTML&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;J2EE&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Java&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;JavaScript&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;JSP&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;XML&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Content/Training/Design&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;HTML&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Additional Requirements:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Skill Name&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience&lt;br&gt;Experience with agile development methodologies and related tools and processes&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Experience with SQLServer, ORACLE or other relational databases and SQL&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Experience with web and application servers such as Websphere, Apache, Tomcat&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Experience with system deployment tools such as Maven and ANT&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Experience with operating systems Unix, Linux, Windows NT and their scripting language&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5 - 7 years&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of integrated development tools such as RAD and Eclipse, CVS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Capable&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Software Design Patterns, UML, SDLC&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Capable&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of network concepts&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Capable&lt;br&gt;Degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Mandatory</content>
    <postId>88228418-51B0-405E-8968-5E6CC2F7F0FC</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Intermediate Java Developer</title>
</post>
