<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>D Park</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Purpose&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The incumbent provides responsive systems level support for production critical systems, implementation support and user acceptance environment support on a global basis. This support consists of technical assistance to users, resolution and prevention of problems in a 7x24 production environment, systems capacity planning and recommendation of solutions to overcome resource constraints, systems level software installation and updates. This incumbent is also responsible for establishing and enforcing departmental logical access control guidelines and liaison with other departments for assistance with implementing new projects. m Support Specialist&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Complexity of Position&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;- strong knowledge of Windows 2000, Windows 2003 and Windows 2008 server&lt;br&gt;- strong knowledge of server hardware&lt;br&gt;- knowledge of windows scripting and VB scripts&lt;br&gt;- knowledge of IBM Director, MOM, SMS, etc.&lt;br&gt;- knowledge of Linux or Unix is s plus&lt;br&gt;- hands on experience on troubleshooting network related issues&lt;br&gt;- hands on experience on troubleshooting servers and desktop related issues&lt;br&gt;- knowledge of Citrix&lt;br&gt;- excellence oral and written communication skills&lt;br&gt;- good administrative and organization skills &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;1. Resolution and Prevention of Problems&lt;br&gt;Presented with system level and application problems on mission critical systems requiring immediate resolution, thus ensuring systems are operational according to agreed upon service level agreements and that they have a high degree of integrity and reliability. Often, resolution determination requires interaction with other teams, including service vendors. Considerable effort is placed into determining, developing and delivering procedures to protect production environment from unplanned outages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Provide Technical Assistance to Users&lt;br&gt;Establishes system scope and objectives. Develops practical manual or automated procedures to solve complex problems. Prepares detailed specifications for programs, analyse and revises existing system logic deficiencies, oversees all phases of the technical system design and will advice, check and direct systems programs onto the correct technical system design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Systems Administration and New Projects&lt;br&gt;Perform system administration tasks associated with environment of specialisation for the development, UAT and production environment as well supporting production code implementation. Provide training on specific environment to other departments as required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Control Access, Ensure Security and Contingency Planning&lt;br&gt;Ongoing customisation and maintenance of system access facilities to ensure and enforce strict security of financial environment. Plan, implement and test contingency plans for various hardware and software environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. System Monitoring and Updates&lt;br&gt;During the course of the year, applications are monitored and statistical information regarding resource usage is compiled. Recommendations are put forward to management for capacity planning and system upgrades where resource constraints are identified to ensure that a reliable production environment is maintained. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. User Group Involvement&lt;br&gt;Participate in user groups to gain information on other user?s project successes and/or failures. Required to keep up to date with technological breakthroughs and trends in field of specialization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job #: JOB0064129 &lt;br&gt;Hiring Officer:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Christopher Bieniek&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Manager, Staffing &amp; Recruitment&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Branch/Department:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Staffing &amp; Planning - Central Canada&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Mailing Address:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 56846 &lt;br&gt;44 King Street West&lt;br&gt;21st Floor&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Canada M5H1H1 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;E-Mail Address:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; chris.bieniek@scotiabank.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Phone:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 416-866-4586&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;Fax:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 416-866-3837&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>88676FB2-C519-4852-9516-B77AD5876D8E</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-12-24T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>BNS: Senior Systems Support Speciallist</title>
</post>
