<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Helen Park</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior System Support Analyst (MVS&lt;br&gt;internals/DB2/CICS/MQ/Websphere) &amp;#8211; MYWWL05618&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description&lt;br&gt;The incumbent of this position will be part of the HSSD Software Support Team that&lt;br&gt;provides round the clock on-site or on-call support to all mainframe systems and software.&lt;br&gt;The job functions include: service restoration, root cause analysis which may involve&lt;br&gt;collection and analysis of dump and trace data, vendor liaison, application of software fixes&lt;br&gt;or workarounds, proactive problem prevention and service improvements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt;This is a senior technical position. The candidate should have a computer science degree&lt;br&gt;or equivalent and at least 6 years of IT experience (programming or software support) in the&lt;br&gt;IBM mainframe environment. Must have applied skills in one or more of: programming&lt;br&gt;language, debugging techniques, system interface/monitoring tools, software maintenance&lt;br&gt;practices. Knowledge of MVS internals, DB2, CICS, MQ and Websphere is required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of BMO organization, applications and computing environment would be an&lt;br&gt;asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, the individual must have strong customer service orientation, problem solving&lt;br&gt;abilities and communications skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to work under pressure is essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please send cover letter quoting reference number and job title along&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; with a current resume to bmo.careers@exult.net or interoffice to Exult&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Recruiting BMTT, 6th Floor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>891CB80E-2831-429B-8496-7ED3A9A0D7DF</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>BMO, Senior  DB2/CICS/MQ/Websphere</title>
</post>
