<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>It is located in Princeton, NJ.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharepoint Architect&lt;br&gt;Princeton, NJ&lt;br&gt;3 Months&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;This position is open to US Citizen, Greencard or EAD and is w2 only.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Project Name: Sharepoint Architect&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Skill Requested: Infrastructure Architect Server Product Services-Microsoft &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Project description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The objectives of the project is to assist the client with the following activities in support of the SharePoint 2007 implementation: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; work with the Client’s Project Manager to create the project plan; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; manage and execute the project; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; validate the existing SharePoint lab and provide recommendations; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; review existing SharePoint design and architecture, make recommendations based on best practices and experience, obtain approval from Client &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; build production SharePoint 2007 environment; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; develop migration and implementation plan and obtain approval from Client &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; implement migration to SharePoint 2007; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; create SharePoint server recovery / build / restoration plan; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; review and revise SharePoint governance; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; create client branding &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; create community templates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required skills: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Leads the Software Development Life Cycle for the development teams &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Works with project managers for project planning, resource allocations, and estimating &amp;#8226; Identifies and manages project risks and issues to ensure successful project completion &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Acts as liaison between Quality Assurance teams and development teams to ensure the system developed meets customer needs &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Works with SharePoint Systems Administrator to assure proper mapping of application requirements to system configuration and topology. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to have skills: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 5+ years designing .NET/ASP.NET applications &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3+ years designing custom SharePoint applications &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 8+ years .NET/ASP.NET development&lt;br&gt;. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If you are qualified, available, interested, planning to make a change, or know of a friend who might have the required qualifications and interest, please email me a copy of your latest resume, even if we have spoken recently about a different position. If you do respond via e-mail please include a daytime phone number so I can reach you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In considering candidates, time is of the essence, so please respond ASAP.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Thank you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Sincerely yours,&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Christina LaShomb&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Axelon Services Corp.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Note: Please allow me to reiterate that I chose to contact you either because your resume had been posted to one of the internet job sites to which we subscribe, or you had previously submitted your resume to Axelon. I assumed that you are either looking for a new employment opportunity, or you are interested in investigating the current job market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are not currently seeking employment, or if you would prefer I contact you at some later date, please indicate your date of availability so that I may honor your request. In any event, I respectfully recommend you continue to avail yourself to the employment options and job market information we provide with our e-mail notices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christina&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Axelon Services Corporation&lt;br&gt;116 John Street&lt;br&gt;New York, NY 10038&lt;br&gt;christina.lashomb@axelon.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>8DC0155D-0A33-4DE6-AA14-88A6BA80CB25</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-10-05T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sharepoint Architect-Contract in NJ</title>
</post>
