<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강재형</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>source : www.workopolis.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Category: Other&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Industry: Technology&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Company URL: http://www.ati.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Year(s) of Experience: 4&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Date Posted: Jul 10, 2002&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Contact E-mail:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ati@rpc.webhire.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Consumer -&lt;br&gt;Application Engineer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Integrated Application Engineer will be responsible for facilitating ATI Set Top Box motherboard designs based on ATI integrated chipsets. Key customer deliverables are schematic and layout references, design guides and application notes, ODM/OEM design reviews and system bring-up. The right candidate will be required to work closely with customers as well as with multiple groups within Engineering, Marketing, FAE and the publications team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key responsibilities of the position include:&lt;br&gt;create reference schematics and layout guidelines for motherboard dest;ps based on ATI Set Top Box chipsets; conduct OEM/ODM design reviews at customer sites or through verbal and written communication; generate application notes and alert customers of any design changes and errata; actively participate in bring-up and debugging of customer motherboards and ATI reference designs; track and drive resolution of customer bugs, and communicate ATI hardware and software development status to remote offices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A B. Sc. In Electrical/Computer Engineering or equivalent and 4+ years of relevant experience is required as well specific knowledge in embedded systems, digital video, MPEG, high-speed digital and analog design; familiarity with PCB schematic/layout design and tools - PADS, Cadence etc.; debugging experience and comfort in using lab equipment - oscilloscopes, logic analyzers etc.; knowledge of semiconductor ASIC design, manufacturing and test.; some exposure to Assembly/C programming, and device drivers are considered an asset. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent communication skills required together with the ability to write technical application notes and design guides or customers. Mandarin or Korean or Japanese language skills will be a definite asset. Up to 35% of time might have to be spent at customer locations in an assigned geography. (China/Taiwan, Japan, Europe or Korea) &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLEASE REFER TO ATI-00000372 IN YOUR SUBMISSION&lt;br&gt;How to Apply for Positions in Toronto, Ontario.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please use one of the following methods to apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet : Online Application (Preferred Method)&lt;br&gt;Email : ati@rpc.webhire.com&lt;br&gt;(file formats accepted: Word 6&amp;7, WordPerfect, RTF, TXT, and HTML)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online Applicants submit your resume only once over the next 3 month period. Our resume tracking system will match your skills and experience to all open positions during the 3 month period. We thank all applicants in advance but advise only those under consideration will be contacted. No Agency solicitation or phone calls will be accepted. No Agency fees will be paid for any applicant resumes submitted without prior ATI authorization.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>8EE8F4ED-2A3E-4698-A1FB-70E7C3ED9284</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Application Engineer(need korean speakers)</title>
</post>
