<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>CA-ON-Toronto-Internet System Administrator &lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Description &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nexx Online is seeking an experienced System Administrator with strong Windows NT/2000, Internet Hosting, Security and firewall expertise. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful sysadmin must be able to design, install, and maintain systems using Windows 2000 Server technology for web hosting services in a 24/7 production environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Install, configure and security harden Windows NT and Win2K servers &lt;br&gt;- Manage IIS services in a high-density server environment &lt;br&gt;- Migration experience moving Windows NT/2000 servers locally and remotely &lt;br&gt;- Familiarity with Hosting Automation Tools &lt;br&gt;- Ability to develop programs and scripts to automate any repetitive system administration tasks &lt;br&gt;- Perform system backups, upgrades, and performance tuning &lt;br&gt;- Install, Configure and manage Firewalls, Switches &lt;br&gt;- Must understand &amp; be able to manipulate Active Directory, ADSI, Windows NT Registry, IIS Metabase &lt;br&gt;- Skilled in IIS, ASP, VB Scripting, TCP/IP &amp; Integration with Unix systems&lt;br&gt;- SQL 7/2000 Administration&lt;br&gt;- Solid understanding of Intel x86 based server hardware, including RAID configuration &lt;br&gt;- Experience limited to desktop or office network support is NOT adequate for this position &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- 2+ years of experience in management of Windows 2000/NT OS &lt;br&gt;- 2+ years UNIX/Linux Sys admin &amp; Network Admin Experience &lt;br&gt;- Strong Scripting and Programming skills &lt;br&gt;- Strong team player with excellent communications skills &lt;br&gt;- Previous experience at an ISP or web hosting company an asset&lt;br&gt;- Formal education in computer science / programming or related majors &lt;br&gt;- Microsoft certification is a plus &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nexx Online Inc. is an equal opportunity employer and offers excellent compensation and benefits. Please send your resume with a cover letter by e-mail to jobs@nexx.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mention on Subject Line: Ref Code: NT-SYSADM &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: NT-SYSADM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;jobs@nexx.com&lt;br&gt;Nexx Online Inc.&lt;br&gt;5255 Yonge St #800&lt;br&gt;Toronto Ontario M2N 6P4&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>8FFCD56D-E8D4-4C46-BF21-3AE78178C511</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-14T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>CA-ON-Toronto-Internet System Administrator</title>
</post>
