<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello,&lt;br&gt;Hope you are doing great!&lt;br&gt;Iam interested in reviewing your resume and having a conversation to see if we can potentially work together on the position that iam presently working on.I would appreciate if&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;you would send a word version of your resume and a number to reach by during the day&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Title: Java 3D Developer&lt;br&gt;Location: Tarrytown, NY&lt;br&gt;Length: 3+ Months&lt;br&gt;Rate: Open&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Job Description &lt;br&gt;Java 3D Developer, also&lt;br&gt;Seek consultants with for 1. Java 3D .&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;.Seek a Java Developer with Java 3D (mid to expert level) for on a consulting base with the following qualifications:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Experience in J2EE application development is a must. &lt;br&gt;Experience in Java 3D programming is a must. &lt;br&gt;Experience of programming against SQL RDBMS (Oracle or SQL Server) is a must &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of SQL programming is a plus &lt;br&gt;Experience in Oracle ADF is a plus&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Herein a brief of the first assignment; 3D Graph explorer with the following requirements:&lt;br&gt;Integrated with a J2EE Web application. &lt;br&gt;Display real 3D Charts (x-Dates, Z-$money, Y-PCT values% or ranks). &lt;br&gt;Navigation is a must including: Zoom in-out; Bird-eye navigation X, Y, Z; Rotate (arrows driven Goggle maps a like). &lt;br&gt;The ability to interactively select both point and zone in the graph and return the selected point/zone. &lt;br&gt;Assignment period: 3 Months with possibility to extend based on the candidate performance.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Assignment beginning time: ASAP.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;I look forward to hear from you!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Riaz Uddin | Riaz@catamerica.com&lt;br&gt;CAT Technology Inc. 377, Route 17 South,Hasbrouck Heights, NJ&lt;br&gt;Office:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(201) 696 9086&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ext : 221 | Fax: (201) 727 9296&lt;br&gt;www.catamerica.com | www.cattechnologies.com&lt;br&gt; </content>
    <postId>9095B595-3359-4A56-A2CC-9AC913FD0B74</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-09-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java 3D Developer / Tarrytown, NY / 3+ Months</title>
</post>
