<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Details &lt;br&gt;Title: Java/J2EE Software Developer&lt;br&gt;Posted On: 2/12/2010 12:22:02 PM&lt;br&gt;Designation: Java/J2EE Software Developer&lt;br&gt;Number of Vacancies: 2&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: Bachelor's degree&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Minimum Experience: 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Job Tenure: No Preference/Any&lt;br&gt;Salary Offered: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Job Location: TORONTO, ON, Canada&lt;br&gt; Job Description &lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client, a leading Canadian bank located in downtown Toronto is actively seeking an experienced Java/J2EE Software Developer to participate on a 6 month contract.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Company Details&lt;br&gt;Name: Nexstaf&lt;br&gt;Type: Consulting Organization&lt;br&gt;Total Employees: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Turnover: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Address: &lt;br&gt;116 Spadina Avenue,&lt;br&gt;Suite 300,&lt;br&gt;Toronto,&lt;br&gt;Ontario,&lt;br&gt;Canada&lt;br&gt;Profile: &lt;br&gt;Nexstaf was formed by the same ownership group that created one of Canada's largest and best known, IT recruiting companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rooted in ethics and professionalism, we aspire to earn the loyalty of all our stakeholders. Nexstaf works diligently to build relationships, not simply fill positions. While achieving this standard is more difficult, it ensures more satisfied employees, and ultimately, greater value to our clients.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you are an employer or a talented candidate, we understand that you have high expectations. For an overview of our business, please visit our fact sheet. We also invite you to learn more about what a professional IT staffing organization like Nexstaf can do for you.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>90A921D5-C8B5-4CD8-9BE2-C5A5CD289C73</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java/J2EE Software Developer</title>
</post>
