<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior Java/Vitria Developer - Toronto &lt;br&gt;Toronto Area - Downtown, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;Are you looking for a unique career opportunity? Join CGI's E-business team based at our 595 Bay Street office in downtown Toronto. This team delivers and supports E-Business solutions to our major client in the telecommunications sector. The E-Business team is currently looking for several Senior Consultants with extensive Java J2EE and Vitria Middleware experience. The projects incorporate custom and out-of-the-box connectors, automator models, event definitions, and Java code to provide the required functionality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a Senior Java/Vitria Developer you will be responsible for full life cycle of enhancements including analysis, design, coding and testing as well as preparing project and user documentation for the clients applications. The role also involves interacting with the end clients, other vendors, and development teams on a daily basis. Shift work and overtime are required during the deployment weekends and sometimes during the maintenance windows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ideal candidate will have a Bachelors Degree in Computer Science or a related discipline along with a minimum of 6 years of relevant IT experience. You are a customer focused professional with exceptional communication and relationship building skills. You have proven expertise in J2EE technologies including strong core Java, EJB, UML, HTML and XML programming abilities. Also, your experience includes 1-2 years of hands-on Vitria development experience with automators and connectors. Ideally you will have J2ME, Oracle, Unix and SQL experience. You should also possess the ability to analyze complex application problems and provide workable solutions, conduct system analysis and design based on system blueprints. You will be responsible for maintaining good customer relationships by directly interacting with the client and providing prompt problem solving services. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To succeed in this role you should be energetic, motivated, and achievement-oriented. You will have organizational awareness with the ability to balance service levels against quality of delivery. You are strong in character, confident, yet have the ability and will to \\&amp;quot;roll up your sleeves\\&amp;quot;. You are disciplined with a strong orientation towards detail. Motivated for future participation in the management team with astute business sense and superior communication skills. You are able to effectively present your ideas to senior management with a strong ability to think conceptually and strategically and to develop and/or leverage partnering relationships&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration, and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start day one and includes a minimum of 3 weeks vacation, profit sharing and a stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Code DM)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Core Java Development&lt;br&gt;J2EE technologies&lt;br&gt;Java Server Pages (JSP)&lt;br&gt;Vitria Businessware connectors/automators&lt;br&gt;Enterprise Java Beans (EJB)&lt;br&gt;XML, UML&lt;br&gt;Nice to Have Skills&lt;br&gt;Oracle&lt;br&gt;ASP&lt;br&gt;SQL&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>90F20772-74D6-458F-A991-30DA47173189</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Java/Vitria Developer - Toronto</title>
</post>
