<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Chilhoan, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently looking for a Sr. Java/J2EE Developer resource for a 4 month contract with the Government of Ontario, located in downtown Toronto. Please have a look at the description and call me at 416-646-2811 x223 or email me to cdiaz@antandbee.com to let me know if you are interested.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If so, please send me your updated resume in Word format, rate/hr and availability. The anticipated start date is 06/12/2006. If you are not available, feel free to forward this email to whom you consider a good fit for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Interact with the Architecture lead, Project Manager, Developers, Security &lt;br&gt;Lead and other concerned parties to understand and identify the system &lt;br&gt;requirements for OG phase 1 and 2, and;&lt;br&gt;· Develop the complete logical and physical system design artifacts that &lt;br&gt;conforms to EAPM guidelines in order to receive Corporate ACT/ARB checkpoint #2 &lt;br&gt;&amp; 3 approvals for Phases 1 and 2 of the Ontario Gateway project. The template &lt;br&gt;and the checkpoint process documentation is available and can be collected from &lt;br&gt;the GSDC office, and;&lt;br&gt;· Produce the required Corporate ACT/ARB presentation materials required to &lt;br&gt;pass the ACT/ARB checkpoint #2 and #3 reviews for both the phases of OG &lt;br&gt;project, and;&lt;br&gt;· Present the architecture and design artifacts to checkpoint review committee &lt;br&gt;and address to technical query / questions raised by the committee;&lt;br&gt;· Review, recommend and provide mapping of the OG objects with existing GO-CMS &lt;br&gt;system design. This will enable OG team to leverage on using existing GO-CMS &lt;br&gt;code modules to avoid duplication of efforts to save time and money;&lt;br&gt;· Update the artifacts to reflect any changes, modifications, or updates &lt;br&gt;requested as a result of the ACT/ARB review meetings, and;&lt;br&gt;· Understand and review newly developed BICEP application framework. If the &lt;br&gt;need arise, modify the framework components, documentation to suit the new &lt;br&gt;requirement and;&lt;br&gt;· Perform other project related activities as required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience and Skills required: Aside from experience in producing the specific &lt;br&gt;deliverables described in the deliverables section above, demonstrable expert &lt;br&gt;knowledge and experience of the following areas are required:&lt;br&gt;· Expertise in application design and development, latest design patterns, code &lt;br&gt;review&lt;br&gt;· Hands on J2EE development, deployment and troubleshooting experience &lt;br&gt;· Expert knowledge and understanding of key concepts of messaging &lt;br&gt;infrastructure systems and integration architectures;&lt;br&gt;· Excellent knowledge and understanding of the current trends of technology &lt;br&gt;directions and appropriate industry standards including, but not limited to, &lt;br&gt;application componentization that can be used in a Service-Oriented &lt;br&gt;Architecture (SOA) approach; &lt;br&gt;· Expert understanding of EJB, J2EE, XML, ebXML, data and object models using &lt;br&gt;UML notations (Class Diagrams, Sequence Diagrams, State Transition Diagrams, &lt;br&gt;Entity Relationship Diagrams, etc.); &lt;br&gt;· Strong understanding of WSDL, ebXML, WSIF, BPEL and BEPL engine would be &lt;br&gt;absolute plus&lt;br&gt;· Strong object-oriented systems analysis and design skills;&lt;br&gt;· Demonstrated experience, expert knowledge and successful track record in &lt;br&gt;application and technology architecture development in large and complex &lt;br&gt;projects;&lt;br&gt;· Working knowledge and understanding of Zachman Architecture Framework;&lt;br&gt;· Excellent analytical, problem solving and decision-making skills; verbal and &lt;br&gt;written communication skills, interpersonal and negotiation skills;&lt;br&gt;· Demonstrated experience as a good team player with a track record of working &lt;br&gt;in project teams of various sizes and strict deadlines and high pressure. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carolina Diaz&lt;br&gt;416-646-2811x223&lt;br&gt;cdiaz@antandbee.com </content>
    <postId>921FC841-D0F7-4964-87D6-F3E400BE10B6</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-06-06T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Contract - Ant &amp; Bee Corporation</title>
</post>
