<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>S. Suh Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Following opportunity is openning soon in my Dept. &lt;br&gt;If you are interested, send your resume to suh.lee@sympatico.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Competitive salary, excellent benefit and pension package, unionized work environment... &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;======================================&lt;br&gt;Job title: Shift Control Engineer/Officer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours of work: 40.00 &lt;br&gt;Shift work? Yes &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number required: More than 1 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Barrie &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group: NETWORKS &lt;br&gt;Business unit: Asset Management - Network Operating&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Accountabilities:&lt;br&gt;Perform, on a rotating shift basis, routine operation, triage, first level response, second-level response dispatch, and action tracking function for the Operating Facilities used for the operation of the Transmission and Distribution Systems. Perform routine maintenance/support of the Operating Facilities including database update, database backup, and other setup changes. The Operating Facilities include SCADA and Network Analysis functions, Outage Response Management System (ORMS), Information Storage and Retrieval System, Network Outage Management System, Training Simulator, Automated Logging and Reporting System, Integrated Voice Communication System, Special Protection Systems, Control Room Facilities, Computer Platforms, Class I, II, III and IV Electrical Supply System, Heating Ventilation and Air Conditioning (HVAC), Operating Telecommunication Network, hub site equipment, RTU's, and more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other accountabilities include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monitoring, Collection and Analysis of statistical information for availability, reliability and performance monitoring.&lt;br&gt;Inspection rounds.&lt;br&gt;Carry out routine tests and support emergency preparedness drills.&lt;br&gt;Planned Outage Co-ordination and verification before return to service.&lt;br&gt;Support commissioning and testing on new releases, new systems.&lt;br&gt;Support continuous improvement through procedural improvements and facility enhancements. &lt;br&gt;Help Desk function for Operating Centre Staff and external customers.&lt;br&gt;On-the-job training and mentoring of junior staff.&lt;br&gt;Training Simulator setup.&lt;br&gt;Set-up Incident Command Centre Facilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selection Criteria&lt;br&gt;Essential Competencies:&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated strong personal commitment to high quality work and customer satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated problem solving abilities to deduce and systematically eliminate possible causes of an observed symptom.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to assess, develop, recommend and implement integrated solutions.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to coordinate work with other staff.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated record of self-motivated behaviour and perseverance to accomplish objectives.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability in planning and maintaining control of quality and work performance.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated extensive hands-on experience with life cycle computer tool support.&lt;br&gt;Professional level of communication skills, both oral and written.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated capability to deal with external vendors.&lt;br&gt;Ability to work effectively as part of a large multi-disciplined team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential knowledge, Experience and Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;Requires an advanced knowledge of engineering and/or computer science subjects and disciplines in order to support large-scale real-time and mission critical computer systems, wide area telecommunications network and supporting infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;This knowledge is normally acquired through the completion of four years of University training or equivalent plus up to 4 years relevant experience.&lt;br&gt;Requires experience working in a disciplined, proceduralized manner. &lt;br&gt;Ability to work effectively as part of a large multi-disciplined team. &lt;br&gt;An understanding of power system concepts and processes used in transmission and distribution operation will be an asset.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>92EEA178-F19A-413D-A777-BB0E05FAE857</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-02-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Permanent Job Opportunity- HYDRO ONE</title>
</post>
