<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Empirical&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Intermediate Java Developer&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;We are seeking a Java Software Developer to join our team. While being involved in various parts of the business and new application development, your primary focus will be our core custom solution in-house. Common tasks include working with our team to define, refine and understand requirements, development of new features, unit testing features and ensuring timelines are met. Learning the system architecture, design of the current system and identifying areas that need to be refactored and documented will also be core tasks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Generating new ideas, dealing with constant change and effectively communicating information will be key to success in this role as you will also be developing progressive, leading edge social media applications in Facebook and other online community platforms. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this sounds interesting, and you'd like to join an exciting team working in the Toronto area, then we would love to hear from you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;Aid in the development of a proprietary, custom email, contesting and surveying application&lt;br&gt;Develop and maintain application code&lt;br&gt;Trouble-shoot software problems and identify/implement solutions&lt;br&gt;Contribute to brainstorming sessions for new refactoring ideas&lt;br&gt;Develop unit tests to ensure acceptable levels of unit testing&lt;br&gt;Assist in deployment of web applications, and development of deployment plans&lt;br&gt;Creation and maintenance of database structures&lt;br&gt;Ensure code and development practices confirm to company standards&lt;br&gt;Prepare technical documentation&lt;br&gt;Personal Skill Requirements: &lt;br&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills along with an ability to be self-motivated in meeting tight deadlines&lt;br&gt;Strong problem solving skills&lt;br&gt;Ability to work independently and provide appropriate status and updates to management&lt;br&gt;Self-starter with ability to learn quickly&lt;br&gt;Team player with positive attitude&lt;br&gt;Technical Skill Requirements: &lt;br&gt;2+ years experience in systems development with 2+ years in Internet environment&lt;br&gt;2+ years development experience working with Java and J2EE&lt;br&gt;2+ years experience working with Apache&lt;br&gt;Experience working with in Linux and exposure to Adobe JRun&lt;br&gt;Solid web skills (JavaScript, HTML, AJAX, XML, SAX/DOM/XSLT, etc)&lt;br&gt;Experience with web services&lt;br&gt;2+ years of relational database experience (comfortable with MS SQL 2003+)&lt;br&gt;Experience using database technologies (JDBC, Hibernate, etc)&lt;br&gt;Experience using Eclipse&lt;br&gt;Experience developing application for Mobile&lt;br&gt;Other Valuable Skills: &lt;br&gt;Experience with developing vector marketing and/or contest solution&lt;br&gt;Development experience using JQuery, PHP and .NET&lt;br&gt;Experience developing applications for Social Media platforms (Facebook, Twitter and others)&lt;br&gt;Struts 1+ years experience&lt;br&gt;Database experience using MySQL and Oracle&lt;br&gt;Experience using Axis and other Apache Java libraries&lt;br&gt;Experience using build technologies (ANT, Maven, etc)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Date:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;February 25, 2010&lt;br&gt;City/Town:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto&lt;br&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ON/Toronto/GTA&lt;br&gt;Wage/Salary:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;$70,000 - $75,000&lt;br&gt;Start:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Immediate&lt;br&gt;Duration:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full-time permanent&lt;br&gt;Type:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Full Time&lt;br&gt;How to apply:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Company:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Empirical&lt;br&gt;Contact:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Carreers at Empirical&lt;br&gt;Phone:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Fax:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Email:careers@empirical.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</content>
    <postId>93F5C129-ED77-4F29-AD31-00B1F9886531</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-01T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer-EMPIRICAL</title>
</post>
