<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>stevenkim</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is dificult to contact a right person to get the right information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, there was a similar inquiry and I would like to quote &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;an opinion of an agent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personally, no matter how good your skill sets are, the communication&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ability counts first.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So please concentrate on how to improve yourself on communication skill.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the quoted...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;As far as SAP is concerned - we are working with a few clients that have a &lt;br&gt;need for SAP people, however, the positions are team lead or project manager &lt;br&gt;positions so the communication skills have to be very good. Our clients are &lt;br&gt;not necessarily looking for only North American experience but some &lt;br&gt;experience in Canada or the US would be beneficial - even Europe is OK. &lt;br&gt;If you have a copy of this person's resume, I would like to take a look at &lt;br&gt;it - it would be more easier for me to determine his qualifications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope this helps in answering your question. \\&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope this is some help to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Thanks for the inquiry..&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I am in the process of collecting information..&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;I will post it as soon as it is ready.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Thanks.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;SK&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;안녕하십니까?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;본인은 이민을 진행중(대사관에 서류제출함) 입니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;본인은 현재 SAP R/3 FI Module 컨설턴트로 일하고 있습니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;또한 ABAP 개발도 합니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;캐나다에서의 직장 구하기가 하늘의 별따기 만큼 힘들다고 하는군요.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;캐나다의 현재 SAP R/3 시장상황과 향후 SAP R/3의 시장동향, 그리고 이민자가 SAP R/3관련 직장을 구하기 위한 준비사항, 현재 가장 인기있는 Module과 향후 인기가 있을만한 Module 등등.......&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;알고 계신 정보를 주시면 정말 고맙겠습니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9520420C-A570-4715-A07B-A35C1801A7DF</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] SAP R/3에 대해 의견과 정보를 원합니다.</title>
</post>
