<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>WATERFRONT INTERNATIONAL LTD.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON, CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;Posted Feb 22, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Waterfront International is a Toronto-based financial consulting firm, specializing in developing computer based statistical trading strategies. Waterfront¿s selective hiring process considers only highly talented individuals with a history of exceptional professional and academic achievement, and solid real-world experience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;Maintain existing real time data processing servers&lt;br&gt;Design, code and test new applications ensuring correctness&lt;br&gt;Work closely with analysts and other groups to provide software solutions&lt;br&gt;Monitor performance of programs after implementation&lt;br&gt;Troubleshoot and resolve application problems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Technologies:&lt;br&gt;UNIX, C/C++, Sybase, Tibco/Rv and other various third party solutions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements of the Candidate include:&lt;br&gt;3+ years of professional C/C++ programming experience&lt;br&gt;University education with background in computer science or related field&lt;br&gt;Proven analytical and creative ability in developing business applications&lt;br&gt;Excellent programming skills in fast paced production environment&lt;br&gt;Excellent analysis and problem solving skills&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to work independently under minimum supervision&lt;br&gt;Keen desire for continuous learning&lt;br&gt;Experience with multithreaded applications preferred but not required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates with limited to no experience can apply for the Jr C++/Unix Programmer position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waterfront International&lt;br&gt;Email: recruiting@wil.com</content>
    <postId>9657F685-C8FB-4A8E-8D49-88506B4464DF</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Junior - Senior C++ Programmer</title>
</post>
