<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly J Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>At least 3-5 years of professional web development experience, including at least one large-scale, successfully-launched project in a tech lead role. &lt;br&gt;Expert knowledge of PHP, including knowledge of object-oriented programming in PHP (and more importantly, having good judgement in knowing when OO should be used, and how much). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong experience with MYSQL/SQL and creating database schemas. &lt;br&gt;Experience using XML-RPC in PHP. &lt;br&gt;You should know your way around Unix. &lt;br&gt;Familiarity with http protocol and ability to use it for low-level troubleshooting as well as experience tweaking the configuration of Apache webservers. &lt;br&gt;Experience with HTML, CSS and JavaScript. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to work productively with minimal supervision. &lt;br&gt;Tolerance for the overhead of rapidly iterating toward greater usability. Insistence on complete/frozen specifications just won't work here. &lt;br&gt;A feel for good design -- both in terms of engineering and user experience. Along with the drive and ability to turn that feel into working products. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;some nice-to-haves:&lt;br&gt;Practical knowledge of relevant W3C standards (XHTML, DOM, CSS) and the de-facto standards (XHR, browser properties, etc) is a plus. &lt;br&gt;Contributions made to an open source project &lt;br&gt;CVS / SVN &lt;br&gt;Ant &lt;br&gt;Familiarity with Eclipse &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;VI / Emacs &lt;br&gt;Experience writing plug-ins (for any system) &lt;br&gt;Handy with regexes &lt;br&gt;Can build small tools in Python / Perl / PHP / Ruby &lt;br&gt;Shell scripting &lt;br&gt;=========================================================&lt;br&gt;You can work off-site from the comfort of one's home&lt;br&gt;The company is in California, no travel is necessary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: $60,000/year&lt;br&gt;the developer must demonstrate past work with proven experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;email your resume :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;jklee3@hotmail.com&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>97973459-DF4F-4936-99EA-04C8FE0704A2</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-08-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>PHP expert</title>
</post>
