<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Ottawa, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;This is an excellent opportunity to join the CGI Group in Ottawa in providing leading IS/IT services to our broad client base.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Role&lt;br&gt;Oracle DBA at the intermediate to senior level, ability to interface professionally with client, team player.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;-Coding/testing/optimization of SQL executable object (procedures, functions, packages, triggers, etc.) &lt;br&gt;-Installation, upgrades and daily maintenance of the database servers &lt;br&gt;-Change Management and Configuration Management/Version Control experience &lt;br&gt;-Reverse engineering and database documentation skills &lt;br&gt;-Maintain and monitor a set of standard database processes to ensure the regular database tasks are properly executed &lt;br&gt;-Carry out performance tuning &lt;br&gt;-Implement and monitor database security &lt;br&gt;-Perform database backup and recovery &lt;br&gt;-Participate or lead in the database capacity planning and the server upgrade process &lt;br&gt;-Work with database vendors to resolve database related issues&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate must possess a minimum of 3 to 5 years experience with hands on Oracle Database Administration and Development with 8.1.7 or higher background. Must be extremely motivated, well-organized, and resourceful.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong communication skills, high comfort level dealing with clients and understanding of the client/service provider relationship are important. Oracle Certification would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity to join a winning team. CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start on the date of hire and include minimum 3 weeks vacation, potential profit sharing and a stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of Oracle Database Administration and development (Oracle 8.1.7 or later).&lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of Oracle Database Administration in an Oracle / Java Code environment.&lt;br&gt;Nice to Have Skills&lt;br&gt;Data modeling knowledge.&lt;br&gt;Hands on working knowledge of Shell scripting.&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Power Builder, Power J and/or ASA database standard.&lt;br&gt;Government experience.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>97B3BCEB-82E5-4043-8F93-861E29CF4437</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-06T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Oracle DBA</title>
</post>
