<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>stevenkim</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Fetched from 'workopolis.com'&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Area Manager, Korea&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Full Time&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Category: Management&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Industry: Manufacturing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Company URL: http://www.husky.ca&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Date Posted: Jan 16, 2003&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; If you enjoy working in a fast-paced, challenging environment where excellence is expected and rewarded, Husky is the place to be. As the world's largest brand-name supplier of injection molding equipment, we're known for our exceptional technology, people and values. As a result, we continually look for individuals who share our spirit of integrity, proactive environmental responsibility and genuine care for those around us. In brief, people who go the extra mile because they are personally driven to do so. In return, we support a healthy lifestyle and offer exceptional opportunities for both personal and career growth, with the chance to share in our global success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Area Manager, Korea&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Reference Number: KOR-SAS-CUS-0001 &lt;br&gt;Location: Korea&lt;br&gt;Function: Sales and Service&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary: As a member of the Husky Team, your main responsibilities will be developing a sales territory, through market research, an established customer base and cold calls, using your entrepreneurial talents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work to keep your customers in the lead by introducing appropriate Husky products and services. &lt;br&gt;Identify and develop potential new customers. &lt;br&gt;Required to make presentations to and carry on technical discussions with all levels of management. &lt;br&gt;Need to be a relationship builder.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: The successful candidate will have completed a post secondary education in a related field (i.e. Electrical, Mechanical,.... Engineer or Technician). Must be self motivated and willing to take on exciting new challenges. You will also require strong written and oral communication skills and ability to interact professionally with employees and customers. English skills, written and spoken, are also mandatory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please fax or mail your r&amp;eacute;sum&amp;eacute; to: &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Husky Injection Molding Systems Asia Pacific Ltd.&lt;br&gt;Suite 1706-9, K. Wah Center&lt;br&gt;191 Java Road, North Point&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG&lt;br&gt;Fax: (852) 2157 0090&lt;br&gt;Attention: Human Resources (Vivien Poon)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>97D6BD6B-83E6-4943-8422-6312C10AD097</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Area Manager - Korea</title>
</post>
