<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Number: 4916503&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title: Web graphic designer (Graphic/Web Designer) (NOC: 5241)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terms of Employment: Permanent, Full Time, Day&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: To be negotiated, Medical Benefits, Dental Benefits, Life Insurance Benefits, Group Insurance Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anticipated Start Date: As soon as possible&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Scarborough, Ontario (1 vacancy)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skill Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education: Not applicable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Not applicable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience: No experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Read English, Write English&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Area of Design Specialization: General graphic design, Advertising, Publications, Books&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business Equipment and Computer Applications: Illustrator, Photoshop&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Setting: Corporation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Type of Technical Illustration: Technical, Software&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specific Skills: Prepare sketches, photographs or illustrations of subjects to be rendered, Prepare specifications for design, Produce final designs or illustrations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Samples: Design sample, Example of completed work&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Conditions and Physical Capabilites: Fast-paced environment, Attention to detail&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Site Environment: Non-smoking, Air conditioned&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transportation/Travel Information: Public transportation is available&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: Reading text, Numeracy, Oral communication, Decision making, Job task planning and organizing, Computer use&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other Information:Must have min of 2 years, knowledge of Rave7 and Excel an asset. Please include a pdf of some graphic work you have designed. Maintain our web site with videos and create we pages,flyers,lit.shts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employer: Southwest Binding Systems Limited&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to Apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please apply for this job only in the manner specified by the employer. Failure to do so may result in your application not being properly considered for the position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By E-mail: sarahc@southwestbindings.com&lt;br&gt;Business Profile: Manufacturers of presentation system. (binders, tabs, plastic bindings, lam film)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Web Site: http://www.southwestbindings.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advertised until: 2010/03/30&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This job advertisement has been provided by an external employer. Service Canada is not responsible for the accuracy, authenticity or reliability of the content.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>97D9CF03-A289-464D-8247-5930FE2A8792</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web graphic designer (Graphic/Web Designer) (NOC: 5241)</title>
</post>
