<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>POSITION TITLE:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Intermediate Software Developer&lt;br&gt;LOCATION:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Downtown Toronto &lt;br&gt;DURATION:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;6 Month Contract&lt;br&gt;RATE:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; $40 - $45 / hr POSITION OVERVIEW: This position is aimed at an intermediate level developer who will be able to work independently and in a team to efficiently achieve the functionality desired in a short period of time.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The successful applicant will have experience working with database driven web applications using popular open source frameworks and libraries. QUALIFICATIONS: * Bachelors Degree in Computer Science, and/or equivalent experience&lt;br&gt;* 3+ years developing Java based applications in a professional setting&lt;br&gt;* Experience with JSF, JSP, JavaScript, CSS.&lt;br&gt;* Experience developing J2EE based web applications&lt;br&gt;* Experience with Struts 1.x, Spring 1.x/2.0, Hibernate, JPA, JTA&lt;br&gt;* Experience with XML and related technologies in a JAVA environment&lt;br&gt;* Experience with MySQL and writing optimized SQL.&lt;br&gt;* Experience with testing frameworks and methodologies&lt;br&gt;* Ability to develop in a Linux based environment&lt;br&gt;* Comfortable working in a fast passed, agile, team based work environment&lt;br&gt;* Interpersonal and communication skills (oral and written), presentation skills, analytical and problem-solving abilities are an absolute must. You can view a full description of this position J2EE Developer (XML, Hibernate, Spring) - ID# 1011454 at our online career centre http://www.aresstaffing.com/hotjobs.html&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;To apply to this position please apply through our web portal or forward your resume directly to this job's email at 1011454.ares@hiredesk.net Regards,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AReS Staffing Corporation &lt;br&gt;1835 Yonge Street, Suite 603&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;M4S 1X8&lt;br&gt;416.480.2700 &lt;br&gt;Fax 416.480.2886&lt;br&gt;www.aresstaffing.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9815E46C-92DC-4B29-A7B8-31BA7093919C</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-11-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2EE Developer (XML, Hibernate) - CONTRACT, Toronto</title>
</post>
