<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>K. Kwon</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>If you are interested in it, please send your resume to david.mandar@cgi.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fred, &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Thank you for your time this morning, and congratulations on the new&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;job. As discussed, here is the job description for the position we&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;talked about. Let your friends know about it.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Thank you again,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;David Mandar&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Java/Vitria Developer - Toronto&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Are you looking for a unique career opportunity? If so, join CGI's&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;network management and planning team based at our 595 Bay Street office&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;in downtown Toronto. This team delivers and supports Network Management&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and Planning solutions to our major clients in the telecommunications&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;sector. The projects involve the implementation of Vitria middleware&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;solutions including the design and development of Order Management&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Systems. The solution incorporates custom and out-of-the-box &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;connectors,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;automator models, event definitions, Java code and Oracle databases to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;provide the required functionality.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;As a Vitria Developer you will be responsible for full life cycle of&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;enhancements including analysis, design, coding and testing as well as&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;preparing project and user documentation for the client's applications.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The role also involves interacting with the end clients, other vendors,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and development teams, as well as managing the Trouble Ticket queues on&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a daily basis. Shift work and overtime are required during the&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;deployment weekends and sometimes during the maintenance windows.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Our ideal candidate will have a Bachelors Degree in Computer Science or&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a related discipline with a minimum of 8 years of relevant IT&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;experience. You are a customer focused professional with exceptional&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;communication and relationship building skills. You have proven&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;expertise in J2EE technologies including strong core Java, EJB, UML,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;HTML and XML programming abilities. You also must have hands-on&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;experience with Vitria Middleware including connectors and automators.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Any experience with J2ME, Oracle, Unix and SQL will be an asset. You&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;should also possess the ability to analyze complex application problems&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and provide workable solutions, conduct system analysis and design &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;based&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;on system blueprints. You will be responsible for maintaining good&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;customer relationships by directly interacting with the client and&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;providing prompt problem solving services.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;To succeed in this role you should be energetic, motivated, and&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;achievement-oriented. You will have organizational awareness with the&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ability to balance service levels against quality of delivery. You are&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;strong in character, confident, yet have the ability and will to "roll&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;up your sleeves". You are disciplined with a strong orientation towards&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;detail. Motivated for future participation in the management team with&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;astute business sense and superior communication skills. You are able &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;effectively present your ideas to senior management with a strong&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;ability to think conceptually and strategically and to develop and/or&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;leverage partnering relationships &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration, and &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;management of business and IT functions. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;day one and includes a minimum of 3 weeks vacation, profit sharing and &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;a&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;interviews will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;(Code DM)&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>98FD81EF-A74F-43B6-A051-B090EC99A146</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-11-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] Java/Vitria Developer - Toronto</title>
</post>
