<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김동원</author>
            <date>2010-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>감사합니다. 참조하겠습니다.</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>김동원</author>
            <date>2010-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>The interviewer told using cookies is for the client, but his question is about three ways</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>김동원</author>
            <date>2010-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>in server side. He said session is one way for server.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Friday Morning, Key people do not drop by my office to ask something that is really unusual.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;One of my colleagues told me that “ Life should taste as good as Swiss Chalet “.as he passed by. All of sudden, I changed my mind to write the answer of the following question as I have such a mysterious mind about the life idiom.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Web applications:&lt;br&gt;1. What are the benefits of MVC application model for web applications?&lt;br&gt;From IBM site.&lt;br&gt;The application of the model-view-controller division to the development of J2EE Web applications has several benefits:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;You can distribute development effort to some extent, so that implementation changes in one part of the Web application do not require changes to another. The developers responsible for writing the business logic can work independently of the developers responsible for the flow of control, and Web-page designers can work independently of the developers. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;You can more easily prototype your work. You might do as follows, for example: &lt;br&gt;1Create a prototype Web application that accesses several workstation-based programs. &lt;br&gt;2Change the application in response to user feedback. &lt;br&gt;3Implement the production-level programs on the same or other platforms. &lt;br&gt;Outside of the work you do on the programs themselves, your only adjustments are to configuration files or name-server content, not to other source code.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;You can more easily migrate legacy programs, because the view is separate from the model and the control and can be tailored to platform and user category. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;You can maintain an environment that comprises different technologies across different locations. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;The MVC design has an organizational structure that better supports scalability (building bigger applications) and ease of modification and maintenance (due to the cleaner separation of tasks). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. What are three methods for maintain state in a web application?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The process of managing the state of a web-based client is through the use of session IDs&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Session ID information embedded in the URL, which is received by the application through HTTP GET requests when the client clicks on links embedded with a page. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Session ID information stored within the fields of a form and submitted to the application. Typically the session ID information would be embedded within the form as a hidden field and submitted with the HTTP POST command. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Through the use of cookies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mainly, once we as developers say "State in a web application", it points to "Session". To deliver and keep the state value on every navigation page flow, we use different ways based on security. As mentione above, URL based parameter passing , hidden post filed form based (GET or POST method) or Cookie are three candidates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. What are three potential bottle necks in web application performance?&lt;br&gt;Bottlenecks are elements of your system that impede the normal flow of traffic&lt;br&gt;Bugs, Web server configuration, DB table relation and more factors related System can cause any matter of traffic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Name at least 5 web application frameworks.&lt;br&gt;For Java Application, Apache Struts, Hibernate, Spring, Eclipse and JSF&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Outline 4 pros and 4 cons for using a web application framework.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; There are a few factors such as Cost, maintenance, usability and availability to choose a web application framework.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; With one of factor, there is con or pro.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Provide three general hurdles encountered in scaling out a web application.&lt;br&gt;Additional users, less capacity of system and network infrastructure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9B1093E8-CC35-47AB-91BD-134B6921C3A1</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Life should taste as good as Swiss Chalet !!!??</title>
</post>
