<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Greetings. If you are interested in the position described below, please reply with a copy of your resume as soon as possible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reference #&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;06-114&lt;br&gt;Job Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Senior Developer&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Permanent&lt;br&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Salary:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Open&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Start Date:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ASAP&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Client Description:&lt;br&gt;With over 10 years of experience, our client is a premier provider of web hosting solutions and technology to successful small and medium-sized businesses, home-office, entrepreneurs and individuals worldwide. Currently they support over 1.2 million websites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;The client is looking for an experienced senior programmer to participate in designing, developing, enhancing, and maintaining all new and existing applications. The successful candidate will have prior experience in the web application development life cycle in order to meet the demands of a large-scale customer base. This is an exciting opportunity with excellent compensation, bonus and benefits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;- Participate in design and development.&lt;br&gt;- Convert system designs and technical specifications into program code.&lt;br&gt;- Perform quality assurance testing to ensure business requirements, system designs, and technical specifications are met.&lt;br&gt;- Maintain and document code.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills:&lt;br&gt;- Minimum 5 years of web applications/services development experience in Unix environments&lt;br&gt;- Experienced in developing n-tier business applications&lt;br&gt;- In-depth knowledge of Perl, PHP, and SQL&lt;br&gt;- Extensive knowledge of HTTP, SOAP, XML, and XSLT&lt;br&gt;- Version control system experience (preferably CVS)&lt;br&gt;- Excellent working knowledge of RDBMS systems (PostgreSQL etc.)&lt;br&gt;- Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;br&gt;- Experience with reporting software (Cognos etc.)&lt;br&gt;- Ability to operate among conflicting requests and priorities&lt;br&gt;- University degree in Computer Science or related area&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Message from:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;JIM HEELS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Recruiter - RJS Associates&lt;br&gt;"HR Solutions... SIMPLIFIED"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;jim@rjscanada.com&lt;br&gt;416-291-7212&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9B38514D-6CE1-400A-BA91-1684568E68D9</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-09-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Developer (06-114)</title>
</post>
