<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>정재용</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>안녕하세요..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;저는 Coska멤버인 Andrew Jung 이라고 합니다.&lt;br&gt;다름이 아니라 저희 회사에서 Intermediate Unix Administrator를 뽑기에 여기 coska에 올립니다. 제가 같은 position으로 일하고 있는데여..&lt;br&gt;정말 일하기 좋은환경과 급여및보너도 좋구여.. 안정적이라 나이에상관없이 retire하기전까지 일할수 있습니다. 아래의 기술은 가지신분은 저에게 멜을 보내주세여 물론 영어루 의사소통이 자유로우서야 되구여.. 기술두 겸비하세야 합니다. 소개하는 저의 입장을 생각해주시면요..&lt;br&gt;저의 멜은 jyblues@hotmail.com이구여 일루 10월 13일 전까지 Resume를 보내주시면 됩니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;POSITION:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Intermediate Unix Administrator (Ref. #237)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REPORTING TO: &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Manager, IT Infrastructure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a member of the Information Technology Group, your primary focus will be to provide technical support and administration for corporate systems and servers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Identification of key skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·A solid Unix background with 3+ years of Unix administration in a Sun&lt;br&gt;Solaris and Red Hat Linux environment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Windows NT Server Knowledge isrequired.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·Thorough understanding of storage technologies, SAN and NAS devices, file systems and volume management, including RAID, Fiber channel, etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·History of automating of day-to-day processing. Techniques should include implementation of 3rd party solutions, shell scripting and associated documentation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·Understanding of DNS, NIS and overall network troubleshooting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;.Education And Skill Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Computer Science degree with 5 yrs of Unix related experience.&lt;br&gt;· Administration experience with directory services, send mail and &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;calendar servers.&lt;br&gt;· Experience with backup software, specifically Legato and Veritas &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;products.&lt;br&gt;· Project management and experience using MS Project required.&lt;br&gt;· Knowledge of Unix and TCP/IP security.&lt;br&gt;· Excellent problem solving skills and strong communication skills are&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;required.&lt;br&gt;· Experience with MS Office products.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9C867BFB-0BC5-442F-AA1A-979331C2E68E</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-10-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Intermediate Unix Administrator !!</title>
</post>
