<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>IP System Administrator,&lt;br&gt;CARTEL INC.&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON, CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;Posted Mar 5, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With over 33 years of experience, Cartel is considered one of Toronto's leading employment agencies servicing the legal community. Our clients are among the most distinguished law firms and our success lies in our applicants and their desire for the perfect career match. There is no fee to register with Cartel for any employment opportunity. We listen. We're honest. Just ask your friends. They'll tell you. Cartel. Give us a call; we really do make the difference. Sincerely, Marsha Meyers President &lt;br&gt;IP System Administrator &lt;br&gt;Salary: Open&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client is a leading Canadian law firm with over four decades of experience.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;They are currently seeking to hire a candidate with at least 3 - 5 years of experience to develop and maintain the firm's IP management system.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Candidates must have exceptional technical skills and be customer driven.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of Patricia file management system would be an asset.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working knowledge of logical database design, SQL and Excel are required.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Proficiency with PC/Windows platform, MAC/Firefox Browser, Java Plug-Ins, Infomaker, and Adobe are also required.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Previous exposure working in an IP environment is preferred and would be an asset.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you would like to find out more information or apply for this great opportunity, please forward your resume immediately to be considered. &lt;br&gt;(Job ID# 286)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Please Contact:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Vanessa Meli&lt;br&gt;Email:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Vanessa@cartelinc.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;CARTEL INC&lt;br&gt;First Canadian Place, Suite 2550, 100 King Street West&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Toronto's Most Trusted Authority in Legal Personnel&lt;br&gt; </content>
    <postId>9E4B3176-1DD3-4A8E-9D2D-3722B8BFB47A</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>IP System Administrator, CARTEL INC.</title>
</post>
