<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김유나</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>회사정보 &lt;br&gt;회사명 The Ministry of Attorney General &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;주소 Canada Ontario&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;720 Bay St., 2nd Fl., Toronto, ON M5G 2K1 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;홈페이지&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;회사소개 Canada Ontario Government. &lt;br&gt;Court Services Division, Corporate Planning Branch, Ministry of the Attorney General &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;채용정보 &lt;br&gt;직종 전산직&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;직무 IT ANALYSTS &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;고용형태&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;모집기간&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Apply by Jan 24, 2003 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;급여 $1,030 - $1,253 / week &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;근무지 Canada&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ontario Toronto&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;지원자격 &lt;br&gt;학력&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;자격증&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;경력&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;필요한기술 Qualifications: experience in/knowledge of IT hardware including mainframes, micros, local/wide area networking, information architecture, structured programming, Internet technology; experience designing, developing, implementing information-management systems; project-management skills; knowledge of various platforms, standard software, databases; experience evaluating systems, creating technical solutions, developing business cases/service-level agreements. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;기타 The Ministry of the Attorney General's court services division seeks experienced individuals to lead and co-ordinate the development and implementation of technical solutions including related activities in support of operations and the rollout of large, complex corporate systems. You will: co-ordinate feasibility studies; participate in developing/implementing IT initiatives; manage infrastructure changes; develop related policies/business cases; participate on working committees; help develop service-level agreements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Reference Number : File AG/CRT-4898 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;지원방법 &lt;br&gt;지원방법 By Fax&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;담당자 David Scott &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;전화 -- -- -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;팩스번호 416- 326- 1869&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9EE9A77F-6D68-439C-85FC-0584927F3DFA</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>IT ANALYSTS</title>
</post>
