<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>SR. WEB SOFTWARE DEVELOPER&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location: Etobicoke, ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Category: Computers-Internet, Computers-Software&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Industry: Information Technology&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Company URL: http://www.globalrecruit.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Year(s) of Experience:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Date Posted: Mar 1, 2002&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Contact E-mail:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2362wks65281@globalrecruit.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Reference: #2362 [Please quote this 薩綬er on all correspondence] &lt;br&gt;Position: SR. WEB SOFTWARE DEVELOPER&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Type: PERMANENT &lt;br&gt;Salary: NEGOTIABLE&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location: ETOBICOKE&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Description: Position:Senior Web Software Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Client develops software targeted at the Retail &lt;br&gt;marketplace. &lt;br&gt;They are currently looking for a Senior Software &lt;br&gt;Developer.&lt;br&gt;Design and implement Intranet solutions to drive &lt;br&gt;business productivity within the corporate office using &lt;br&gt;Web and Database Technologies&lt;br&gt;Design and implement Extranet solutions to drive &lt;br&gt;business productivity among the corporate office, our &lt;br&gt;clients and partners using Web and Database Technologies&lt;br&gt;Liaise with internal department managers and &lt;br&gt;stakeholders in efforts to Web-Enable core business &lt;br&gt;systems.&lt;br&gt;Technical Skills Required:&lt;br&gt;Minimum 4 years of Web development experience using Web &lt;br&gt;and Database Technologies&lt;br&gt;Web Server maintenance, and configuration experience&lt;br&gt;Understanding of Web Security requirements.&lt;br&gt;Technical knowledge in: HTML, ASP, Perl, CGI, SQL, and &lt;br&gt;related languages.&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Microsoft Web Services (XML, SOAP, UDDI) &lt;br&gt;with practical experience&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Microsoft technical environment&lt;br&gt;Current technical knowledge in LAN and WAN technologies, &lt;br&gt;TCP/IP, FTP, DNS, Telnet, etc.&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Windows NT/2000, Unix environments&lt;br&gt;Other Skills Required:&lt;br&gt;Excellent communication skills, both written and verbal&lt;br&gt;Self starter who can work independently with little &lt;br&gt;supervision under demanding time constraints&lt;br&gt;Strong troubleshooting, debugging, analytical and &lt;br&gt;testing skills&lt;br&gt;Ability to work in a team environment&lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full-Time&lt;br&gt;Location: Etobicoke area, near 427&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please email your resume to: 2362wks65281@globalrecruit.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9EEB23A1-AB8E-40D1-A640-2EF9BCB17F65</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>SR. WEB SOFTWARE DEVELOPER</title>
</post>
