<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior C/C++, Visual Basic Consultant - Toronto &lt;br&gt;Toronto Area - Downtown, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;Are you looking for a unique career opportunity? Join CGI's E-business team based at our downtown Toronto office. This team delivers and supports E-Business solutions to our major client in the telecommunications sector. CGI is currently looking for a Senior C/C++, Visual Basic Consultant to join their development and integration team. The Senior Consultant will be a key team member dedicated to the support and development of mission critical applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ideal candidate will have a Bachelors Degree in Computer Science or a related discipline along with a minimum of 5 years in developing or coding business applications. You will work closely with CGI Project Managers and clients to identify structured solutions for new systems or the migration of existing systems. You will be responsible for the support and development of the clients mission critical Sales and Product applications. You will be proficient in using C, C++, Visual Basic, Com, ASP, MTS, VBScript, SQL, HTML and IIS. You should also possess the ability to analyze complex application problems and provide workable solutions, conduct system analysis and design based on system blueprints. You will be responsible for maintaining good customer relationships by directly interacting with the client and providing prompt problem solving services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI is the fourth largest independent information technology services firm in North America providing end-to-end IT services and business solutions to more than 3,000 clients worldwide. CGI provides a full range of IT services, including consulting, systems integration, and the management of business and IT functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CGI offers a competitive compensation package with opportunities for growth and professional development. Benefits for this position start day one and includes a minimum of 3 weeks vacation, profit sharing and a stock purchase plan. We are an equal opportunity employer. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We wish to thank all applicants for their interest and effort in applying for this position; however, only candidates selected for interviews will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No unsolicited agency referrals please. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Code DM) &lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;C Programming&lt;br&gt;C++ Programming&lt;br&gt;Visual Basic Programming&lt;br&gt;COM&lt;br&gt;SQL&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A1132D3C-2D1D-4E27-996C-B40368D1AF3D</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior C/C++, Visual Basic Consultant - Toronto</title>
</post>
