<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>sonia</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>We have an opportunity that may be of interest to you. If you are interested and qualified for this opportunity, please apply online (link below). This submits your application for priority consideration on this opportunity. If this position is not a fit or if you are not currently available, perhaps you can refer a friend who could be a fit (link below).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opportunity ID : 28799&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply Online : http://www.sisystems.com////index.cfm?mg=cpo.details&amp;uv=%25%26%20%3BX1%2C4%20%0A&lt;br&gt;Refer a Friend : http://www.sisystems.com////index.cfm?mg=cpcanr.referral&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note that we do *not* accept applications over the phone or by reply email.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sourcing Office : Vancouver&lt;br&gt;Title : Systems Administrator&lt;br&gt;Project Description : Our client is in need of a dynamic and experienced Systems Administrator who can start immediately and hit the ground running on all cylinders. This is a contract position for a minimum of 3 months which may lead to full time.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Systems Administrator role will be working with Windows/Mac/Linux server and Windows/Mac desktop environment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The client's server environment consists of 21 Windows/Linux/Mac servers and utilizing to a small extent Microsoft and VMWare virtualization.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This role is primarily responsible for day-to-day hardware, software, network support and managed services requirements within the client's corporate office based in Burnaby.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specialization and Skills :&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Network and Infrastructure&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Systems Administrator&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; (2 - 4 years)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Requirements :&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Experienced with Linux/Unix Server administration, installation, maintenance (2 - 4 years)&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Mac OSX experience (&amp;lt; 2 years)&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Excellent verbal and written communication skills. (Mandatory)&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Please summarize your experience in the following mandatory areas: Active Directory administration, Windows 2003 Server administration; Windows 2000/XP/7 desktop installation and administration; Microsoft Office installation and support; Microsoft Exchange 2003 administration; VMWare ESX administration; SuSE Linux administration; PCI DSS experience; VoIP systems administration; Sonicwall VPN; MS Virtual server and VMware vSphere; Backup Exec administration; Network setup and troubleshooting; and Network patch panel management (Mandatory)&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Any skills in the following areas are considered assets, but are not mandatory.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please highlight any experience in: ERP Systems experience; Tripwire Enterprise experience; Nagios Monitoring knowledge; Linux patch management; Unix shell scripting; MS Visio, MS Project; OSX Server knowledge; Drupal CMS (Capable)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start Date : May 19, 2010&lt;br&gt;End Date : Aug 27, 2010&lt;br&gt;Rate : Hourly&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;$ 32&lt;br&gt;Work Environment : Reporting to the Director of IT, this role will be working in the corporate office in Burnaby.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This role will work with a small team in a fast paced, and fun environment where your opinions matter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you for your time and consideration Sonia!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best Regards,&lt;br&gt;Michael Watson,&lt;br&gt;S.i. Systems - Vancouver&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;P.S. We are always looking for good people! Refer your friends to us and you could receive our $500 referral bonus!&lt;br&gt;Click here for more information: http://www.sisystems.com////index.cfm?mg=cpcanr.referral&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are receiving this email because you have selected to be notified about opportunities in this branch.&lt;br&gt;If you do not want to receive similar notifications, please login to your profile at http://www.sisystems.com/// and change your email notification preferences.&lt;br&gt;If you do not have your login and password, please go to 'Forgot Password' at&lt;br&gt;http://www.sisystems.com////index.cfm?mg=cpcans.candidate_login and your login information will be sent to you at this email address.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A123C19F-E2F1-440D-A346-C4408E12ADD6</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>System Administrator Position - Vancouver</title>
</post>
