<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Rate: $46 per hour &lt;br&gt;Duration: 6 months to begin, this is a long term contract&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will be responsible for overall technical leadership of medium to large scale projects. &lt;br&gt;~ Working with project managers, architects business analysts to complete and document technical analysis and design. &lt;br&gt;~ Ensuring that solutions adhere to development best practices and Architectural principles and meets business requirements. &lt;br&gt;~ Provide detailed development estimates to Project Manager for web development effort as well as weekly status reporting &amp; budget forecasting &lt;br&gt;~ Familiarity with the principles of SDLC and ability to come up to speed with SDLC methodology. &lt;br&gt;~ Apply analytical skills to resolve problems and deliver viable solutions. Anticipate obstacles and execute proactive approaches to issues. &lt;br&gt;~ Configuration Management for the sub projects within the release &lt;br&gt;~ Responsible for coding, packaging, deployment and support of builds as code is promoted from Development, System, Acceptance &amp; Production environments &lt;br&gt;~ Providing leadership, including code and unit test reviews, to a team of 3-6 developers. &lt;br&gt;~ Working closely with environment team to ensure that environments are fully functional and that builds are properly deployed &lt;br&gt;~ Support to Business and testing team &lt;br&gt;~ Defect triage and resolution &lt;br&gt;~ Data set up and environment shake down &lt;br&gt;~ Documentation of design options &amp; solutions &lt;br&gt;~ Working with 3rd party Vendors to ensure project success &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATOINS: &lt;br&gt;~ 5+ years of working experience with JAVA, JSP, Websphere, and web services is an absolute must. &lt;br&gt;~ Prior experience of leadership in code review and design is required &lt;br&gt;~ Previous experience with Object Grid &amp; IBM's CMOD platform is a definite plus &lt;br&gt;~ Excellent communication skills with an ability to translate highly technical concepts to our Business partners &lt;br&gt;~ First preference is for this candidate to be based out of our Creekside location however for the right candidate - we will also accept them being located at our London, ON office. &lt;br&gt;~ Proven track record with code deployments &lt;br&gt;~ Experienced in the use of SDLC methodologies &lt;br&gt;~ Ability to work effectively with others; self motivated &amp; a team player &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;***Please note: while this contract is initially listed for a 6 month duration - it is very likely that the business need will continue through July '10, 2010.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;JAVA * 5+ Yrs. &lt;br&gt;JSP (Java Server Page) * 5+ Yrs. &lt;br&gt;Leadership * 5+ Yrs. &lt;br&gt;SDLC (System Development Life Cycle) * 5+ Yrs. &lt;br&gt;WebSphere * 5+ Yrs. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;If you know of someone who would be interested in this role, feel free to forward the job description and my contact information &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Best Regards,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Arshiya Gopalani&lt;br&gt;Recruitment Consultant&lt;br&gt;+ arshiya@nexstaf.com &lt;br&gt;i www.nexstaf.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A14B168E-142B-4304-A43D-D0747E8F60D5</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-07-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer</title>
</post>
