<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At BMO Financial Group, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potential. As one of North America's highly diversified financial services providers, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Writes high-quality and well documented code using PL1, CICS, COBOL, DB2, C/C++, Java languange following the department's coding and standards. Maintains application for CBDS. Writes and executes unit test cases, assists with integration and user acceptance testing. Designs components and writes functional and design specifications. Provides application support to production. Demonstrates strong interpersonal skills and a team player. A self-starter who display strong self initiatives, can work with minimal supervision and is flexible and a fast learner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Has over 7 years of hands-on experience with the PL1, CICS, DB2, VSAM, COBOL, MVS, TSO, ISPF, JCL system development, significant development experience with C/C++, Visual Age for Java, WebSphere; and strong knowledge of Unix a definite asset. Possesses depth knowledge of design and analysis methodology and application development processes (proven experience in complete systems development lifecycle is beneficial). Has ability to manage multiple task in a fast-paced work environment. Has strong interpersonal and communication skills. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group thanks all applicants. We advise that only those who qualify for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At BMO Financial Group, we are committed to diversity and equitable opportunity for all individuals. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://bmo.recruitsoft.com/servlets/CareerSection?art_ip_action=FlowDispatcher&amp;ctx=1&amp;flowTypeNo=13&amp;pageSeq=2&amp;art_servlet_language=en&amp;jobOfferNo=27626&amp;csNo=2"&gt;&lt;font color=blue&gt;Apply online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: DSBAH00977&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group - BMO Groupe Financier&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A316744D-FF73-43C0-8A73-65B5413BFCB5</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Mainframe &amp; C/S Developer</title>
</post>
