<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-Junior, Intermediate &amp; Senior IT Professionals &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We have a need for top-notch technical talent in our Toronto, Ontario Application Solutions Center. If you are an IT Professional with more than one year Application Development experience we want to talk to you. The following are the technical skills that are of interest to us:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;· Cobol, JCL, DB2, Visual Basic, SQL Server, MS. Access, Java.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are interested in one these exciting opportunities, please submit your resume quoting reference #W-DEV-TOR to apply@oaot.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAO Technology Solutions (NASDAQ: OAOT) is a global provider of information technology services that address the enterprise-wide challenges of Fortune 1000 companies, mid-market organizations, health benefit organizations, and the public sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our most important competitive advantage is that we have the flexibility, responsiveness and cost-effectiveness of a smaller firm, while offering the benefits that a large integrator can provide. OAOT adds further value by giving customers one source of accountability for a full-range of IT services that span the full spectrum required to plan, build, staff and manage IT solutions. Our customers choose the mix of services they need, and we deliver superior services at lower costs than they could achieve themselves.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Headquartered in the Washington, DC area, OAOT has offices in the United States, Canada, Italy, France and the United Kingdom. OAOT employs over 2,400 professionals who promote a culture of customer satisfaction. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;apply@oaot.com&lt;br&gt;OAO Technology Solutions (Canada) Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A3CA7D21-B8E7-45D2-8A6F-1C1C21BC1379</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-12T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-Junior, Intermediate &amp; Senior IT Professionals</title>
</post>
