<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>예준호</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>IBM to spend $35M to create services centres for small and mid-sized businesses&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Canadian Press &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thursday, September 02, 2004&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADVERTISEMENT &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;TORONTO (CP) - IBM Canada Ltd. plans a $35 million expansion to create regional centres across Canada to sell technology services to small and mid-sized companies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move by the Toronto-area computer giant is part of a broader strategy to expand its penetration of the small and mid-sized corporate market in Canada for technology services, business the company says is worth up to $5.6 billion a year. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Small to mid-sized companies in Canada spend about 60 per cent of their IT budgets on services," Shannon O'Connor, a senior executive in IBM's global services division, said in a release Thursday. "These businesses place a high priority on price and on having one key local provider to meet their IT services needs." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The companies IBM Canada is targeting are those with worforces of between 100 and 1,000 people. The Markham, Ont.-based subsidiary of global computer giant IBM Corp. does much of its current business with larger companies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new technology centres will be developed in London, Ont., Calgary, and Toronto, with another planned for the Montreal area later this year and others in 2005. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The centres will help IBM Canada employees co-ordinate with the numerous regional business partners - such as technology infrastructure providers, consultants and software firms - the computer services company has around the country. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current employees will be reassigned to the centres, but the company will add new jobs if needed. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IBM Canada recently announced it is adding 1,200 new jobs to its workforce of about 20,000 people as the company expands its business. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A436428D-1D73-45E8-99A2-9D813BFC2FD4</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-09-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>IBM Canada recently announced it is adding 1,200 new jobs to its workforce of about 20,000 people as the company expands its business.</title>
</post>
