<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Web Developer&lt;br&gt;CTV Inc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Category:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Marketing&lt;br&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Being part of the Globe &amp; Mail team, Canada’s #1 National newspaper requires a passion for excellence and an unwavering commitment to customer service in a fast-paced and dynamic organization. Demonstrating these values in the workplace everyday is what makes our people the foundation of our success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We support a culture in which employees can live their ideals, develop their abilities, creatively contribute to the success of the organization and be recognized, appreciated and rewarded for doing so. We are currently looking to engage a full-time Web Developer. If you are the best in your field, we'd like to hear from you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are a fast-paced, dynamic media organization in search of a Web Developer to join our web development team. The Web Developer will focus on implementing and maintaining efficient, user friendly, interactive, high performance web applications specializing in front end technologies. The successful incumbent for this role will have the opportunity to directly impact how people consume news and information in our changing media landscape so must have a drive to deliver the best product possible. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must possess an undergraduate degree in a Computer Science or Software Engineering or similar discipline or equivalent (5-7 years) experience in a web or software development role&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Skills:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3+ years hands-on web development experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript (including jQuery); awareness of cross-browser compatibility issues and proven ability in solving such issues&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience programming in JSTL and JSP including the ability to write simple JSP tags&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with svn/git or another version control system&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with SQL and relational databases such as Oracle and MySQL&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with agile development methodologies and processes&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Personable team player with excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Strong attention to detail and proven ability to consider the user-experience in creating successful web applications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Asset to Have:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with PHP/Python/Ruby/Java/Groovy or another object-oriented programming language&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience working with Unix/Linux and Oracle &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Knowledge of CSS3 and HTML5, microformats and API design&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience working with third party APIs (both server and client side implementations)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with usability testing and analysis&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with column stores&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Knowledge and familiarity with Globe and Mail online products&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; </content>
    <postId>A4E28147-F500-443A-89AD-5A9CC366F877</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Developer CTV Inc.(Globe n mail)</title>
</post>
