<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-HTML Layout Assistant &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Self-Motivated individual needed to work in a creative GAY &lt;br&gt;POSITIVE environment building template driven websites. This is a &lt;br&gt;perfect entry-level position for those looking to get their feet wet in &lt;br&gt;the world of web design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Knowledge of human computer interactions and Internet design &lt;br&gt;standards&lt;br&gt;- Working knowledge of HTML and ability to hand code required&lt;br&gt;- JavaScript an asset&lt;br&gt;- Solid knowledge of Web/Internet based design and Website &lt;br&gt;Management&lt;br&gt;- Knowledge of Photoshop/Image Ready, Homesite Dreamweaver &lt;br&gt;required&lt;br&gt;- Knowledge of Xara X and ThumbsPlus and asset&lt;br&gt;- Results Driven Individual that can take direction and work &lt;br&gt;independently or as part of a team&lt;br&gt;- Organizational skills, multi-tasking and problem solving abilities &lt;br&gt;are a MUST&lt;br&gt;- Ability to work under pressure with tight deadlines a MUST&lt;br&gt;- Able to take initiative and self-manage workload&lt;br&gt;- Strong communicator with superior written communication skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Produce template driven websites through specific methodology&lt;br&gt;- Properly document action items and deliverables&lt;br&gt;- Maintain and update the visual quality standards of the company&lt;br&gt;- Take part in brainstorming team meetings as necessary for &lt;br&gt;specific projects&lt;br&gt;- Occasionally design web based graphics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applicants should respond by email and include a cover letter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;karl edwards&lt;br&gt;jobs@blathermatter.com&lt;br&gt;blathermatter inc&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A83E555D-86A9-4B8F-A6BA-03E17CB97A2D</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-15T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-HTML Layout Assistant -Entry Level</title>
</post>
