<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Number: 4967219&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title: Illustrator and graphic designer (NOC: 5241)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terms of Employment: Permanent, Part Time, Weekend, Day&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: To be negotiated, Bonus, Other Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anticipated Start Date: As soon as possible&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Etobicoke, Ontario (1 vacancy)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skill Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education: Completion of high school, Some college/CEGEP/vocational or technical training, Completion of college/CEGEP/vocational or technical training, Some university&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Not required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience: 3 years to less than 5 years&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Read English, Write English&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Area of Design Specialization: General graphic design, Technical illustration, Advertising, Books, Multimedia, Forms&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business Equipment and Computer Applications: MacIntosh, QuarkXpress, Illustrator, Photoshop, PageMaker, Corel Draw&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Setting: Corporation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specific Skills: Prepare sketches, photographs or illustrations of subjects to be rendered, Produce final designs or illustrations&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: Reading text, Oral communication, Job task planning and organizing, Computer use&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other Information:must be a WEB DESIGNER ALSO***&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employer: RAPID ROOTER&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to Apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please apply for this job only in the manner specified by the employer. Failure to do so may result in your application not being properly considered for the position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Phone: between 9:00 and 17:00: (416) 208-3138&lt;br&gt;Advertised until: 2010/04/28&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This job advertisement has been provided by an external employer. Service Canada is not responsible for the accuracy, authenticity or reliability of the content.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A96F30B4-FCB9-47B2-A417-3CE6B2755D2E</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Illustrator and graphic designer (NOC: 5241)</title>
</post>
