<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title: Mobile Developers &amp;#8211; Needed ASAP (IITJ)&lt;br&gt;Posted On: 3/3/2010 6:20:46 PM&lt;br&gt;Designation: Mobile Developer&lt;br&gt;Number of Vacancies: 1&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Minimum Experience: 0 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Job Tenure: Contract - Corp-to-Corp&lt;br&gt;Salary Offered: $50 - $60/hour&lt;br&gt;Job Location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada&lt;br&gt; Job Description &lt;br&gt;Position: Mobile Developers - Needed ASAP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Skills: Must have experience with Android OR Brew OR Adobe Air&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Type: Contract &amp;#8211; 3 to 6 months&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Downtown &amp;#8211; Dot.com environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working for an exciting mobile software development firm. Work on the latest applications that deliver fast and flexible mobile content!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills and Experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong background with software engineering with at least 2 years focused on developing\\\\architecting software for Mobile Devices &amp;#8211; IPhone, Blackberry, Palm, etc&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For this role you must have development experience with ONE of the following&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Android &amp;#8211; 2 contractors required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Brew &amp;#8211; 2 contractors required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Adode Air &amp;#8211; 1 contractor required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As well as project experience with most of the following technologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- J2Me, Windows Mobile 6.1 and/or 6.5, Blackberry development,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- iPhone SDK, or Palm SDK,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- development using IDEs, Netbeans, Visual Studio&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- WebServices, SOAP, XML,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Wireless Connectivity technologies would be a plus&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Mobile platform development and porting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Project scope\\\\Requirements discussions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Tech spec development&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Source code development&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Unit testing your own code.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Post-release support for product.=&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If do have these skills; e-mail a current version of your resume along with a few bullets that quickly describe your suitability for the role and this will push your application to the top.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you don't have these skills but would like to be entered in our database to be matched with available opportunities please e-mail your resume with "Available Opportunities" in the subject line. This will ensure your resume is directed for immediate data entry in our system and we will be in touch as soon as you are matched to one of our positions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plaese only apply to this ad if you are qualified!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joanne Webb&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Recruiter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;joanne@options9.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Company Details&lt;br&gt;Name: Options9&lt;br&gt;Type: Consulting Organization&lt;br&gt;Total Employees: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Turnover: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Address: &lt;br&gt;151 Richmond St,&lt;br&gt;Richmond Hill,&lt;br&gt;ON,&lt;br&gt;Canada&lt;br&gt;Profile: &lt;br&gt;Options9 combines a pool of over 10,000 screened and qualified candidates with an extensive network of some of Ontario's most successful public and private sector clients, including:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Financial&lt;br&gt;* Telecom&lt;br&gt;* Wireless&lt;br&gt;* Manufacturing&lt;br&gt;* Software Development&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the Principals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Options9's principals have more than 20 years' experience providing value to clients and candidates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joanne Webb has a background in the high-technology and financial sectors. Since 1995 she has leveraged her insights to provide human resources that meet both the technical and business requirements of Toronto and the GTA's top firms.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>AA26B7C5-E921-462F-99A4-B16E3093A62F</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mobile Developers &amp;#8211; Needed ASAP (IITJ)</title>
</post>
