<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Snapshot&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;Other Pay: To be negotiated&lt;br&gt;Employee Type: Full-Time Employee&lt;br&gt;Manages Others: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Design&lt;br&gt;Experience: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Post Date: 19/03/2010 Contact Information&lt;br&gt;Ref ID: lindam82-0&lt;br&gt;Description&lt;br&gt;We are looking for a Junior XSLT site designer to add to our team. This is an entry level position; we are ready to meet with fresh, enthusiastic graduates with less experience, but strong design / HTML skills and a keen desire to learn. THIS IS A FULL TIME, PERMANENT POSITION. We are NOT looking for any freelancers. Ideally, you should have a full understanding or training in: - Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Flash (Animation &amp; Basic Actionscript) - HTML, XML, CSS, XSLT - Basic graphic design principles &amp; web usability guidelines -Knowledge of WordPress and Joomla would be an assetYour responsibilities will include: - Talking to clients and transforming their ideas into design. - Designing new logos &amp; branding schemes for e-commerce businesses. - Designing e-commerce and eBay templates in Adobe Illustrator / Photoshop and converting template designs into HTML. - Executing small design changes in our clients' e-commerce sites - Working with our development team to ensure e-commerce website designs are cleanly implemented into working sites. Your responsibilities will NOT include: - back-end database development - developing e-commerce website functionality - grunt jobs like fetching coffee or filing paperwork Please include BOTH a resume in Word format and a website link to your portfolio or some samples of your work.</content>
    <postId>AAA1B794-D818-4913-9F39-2F1DEA8759FD</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Entry Level -XSLT site designer Kyozou-Joomla</title>
</post>
