<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Description&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Introduce new interactivity and technology into the sites, including Flash and multimedia components&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Add new sections and features to the site as needed&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Create and implement template-based forums and blogs&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Build and maintain contests and polls&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Manage small web projects&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; New tool development&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Manage and/or administer changes to 3rd party applications, and work with 3rd parties to optimize use of new features and functionality&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Monitor site and troubleshoot technical problems to ensure prompt resolution and minimal disruption&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Work with technical team and other members to efficiently resolve issues and address new requests&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; An interest in crowd sourcing, web 2.0 and social media&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Post-secondary degree or diploma in multi-media or graphic arts, or related experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3-5 years of web production experience, preferably in a publishing or media environment&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with Adobe PhotoShop, HTML, CSS, and Flash is required&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Knowledge of JavaScript, PHP, MySQL is an asset&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Working knowledge of Wordpress is an asset&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience managing small projects independently&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Ability to work independently within tight deadlines&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Ability to work in a highly matrixed environment&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to effectively manage multiple tasks and/or projects at once and possess the ability to keep up with changing task prioritization without sacrificing quality&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Strong time management skills and interpersonal&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent communication skills&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Rogers is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The future is exciting and Rogers is leading the way.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Canadians count on Rogers to keep them in touch with those who matter most to them - whether at their desk, on the couch, or on the go. As Canada's telecommunications leader, we keep everyone informed, connected and entertained, with our exciting array of products and services. Our drive to provide the latest and most innovative products ensures that our customers enjoy unmatched convenience, reliability, and flexibility. Rogers continues to set the pace by investing in our networks, platforms, products and people. Are you ready for a high-energy career that feeds your enthusiasm? Join us now.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Job Posting Feb 23, 2010&lt;br&gt;Job Digital&lt;br&gt;Primary LocationCA-ON-Toronto&lt;br&gt;Schedule Full-time&lt;br&gt;Employee Status Regular&lt;br&gt;Travel No&lt;br&gt;Target Start Date Mar 8, 2010</content>
    <postId>AB5C8F8A-CFC1-4482-A0DF-8F187EC81269</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-27T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Producer-17300</title>
</post>
