<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Wooseog Choi</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>제가 일하고 있는 회사에서 직원을 채용하고 있습니다.&lt;br&gt;관심이 있으시거나 궁금하신게 있으시면 저에게 직접 Resume를 보내시거나 메일을 주세요. 제가 담당 매니저에게 직접 전해 주겠습니다.&lt;br&gt;저의 e-mail은 gosuchoi@gmail.com입니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PACKETEER, INC.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Software QA Engineer&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Full Time&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location: Kelowna, BC, CANADA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Category: Computers-Software, Engineering-Computer&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Industry: Computer Software &amp; Processing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Company URL: http://www.packeteer.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Year(s) of Experience: 5&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Number Of Positions: 1&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Packeteer (NASDAQ: PKTR), founded in 1996 and headquartered in Cupertino, California, is the pioneer and global leader in WAN Application Traffic Management. Packeteer solutions combine a family of scalable appliances with patented software capabilities to deliver unmatched visibility, control, acceleration, and management of application traffic across WAN and Internet links. These solutions help align network and application resources with the priorities of the business, optimizing performance and reducing operational costs in the process. Packeteer solutions are sold through a global network of VARs, distributors, and system integrators, and are backed a 24X7 global service and support organization. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Quality Assurance Engineer will test, verify, and ship innovative bandwidth management inter-networking products.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;He or she will be chiefly responsible for investigating the behavior of various network client applications under bandwidth management and high traffic stress. Additionally, the candidate will be responsible for feature integration and User Interface testing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The position calls for someone with strong practical network experience, who is interested in extending their knowledge of the deeper technical details of TCP/IP networking. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Design, implement and maintain automated and manual tests for testing networking devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Write and maintain test-designs, test suites and test plans based on customer and market requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Setup and conduct performance benchmark evaluation of software prototypes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Develop test harness, scripts and internal tools for benchmarking&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Report and document software faults and verify fixes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Collaborate with engineering to ensure testability of new and existing features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Install and support internal computer systems for testing and for development operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Create, maintain and support for test automation infrastructure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidate is expected to be working under minimum supervision, must be able to meet tight deadlines.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It is expected that the candidate will carry on his/her duties as both a QA Analyst and a QA automation specialist.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills and Experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Candidate must hold a Bachelor s or Master s degree in one of the following: Electrical Engineering, Electronic Engineering, Computer Science, Computer Engineering, , CSc-Mathematics, CSc-Physics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Minimum two years formal SQA (Software Quality Assurance) experience including test design, test automation and bug tracking and escalation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Expertise in all levels of testing (functional, installation, acceptance, load, stress)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Knowledge of Software Development Life Cycle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Practical experience with configuring Window and/or Linux/Unix clients&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Strong skills in at least one or more of Perl, Python, C, SilkTest, CVS, Ethereal, Etherpeek&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Shell scripting abilities (specially in Linux environment)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desired Skills and Experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Protocol-level knowledge of TCP/IP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Hands-on experience setting up complex test labs that included routers and switches&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; XML&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience configuring Cisco routers, Linux/Unix clients,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Knowledge of&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Software Test and Quality Assurance Methodologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A good understanding of Linux or other UNIX-style operating systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience in testing networking hardware and protocols&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience working with hubs, bridges, switches and routers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience in creating test tools, test automation tools, test plans, test cases and automation of test cases and procedures&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Be able to understand product requirements and create test plans and test procedures accordingly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Setting up of Firewall and VLAN environments is an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Excellent problem-solving and troubleshooting abilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Superb oral and written communication skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ability to work on problems of diverse scope where analysis of data requires evaluation of identifiable factors&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>AB776D97-18B1-42FD-B80A-7C5AEFA7D405</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-08-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>open position in QA</title>
</post>
