<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Web Application Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;CryptoLogic, Inc. is an Internet software development and licensing company with proprietary commerce-enabling technology that permits secure, reliable, efficient and rapid financial transactions over the Internet. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our products permit the processing of online transactions, with a current focus on e-commerce software. Our software is used by individuals registered in 240 nations and territories worldwide. We have processed more than 380 million individual transactions and in excess of US$ 4 billion in secure electronic deposits, from more than 580,000 clients. Common shares of the Company are listed on the Toronto Stock Exchange and on the Nasdaq National Market. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Located at the Yonge/Davisville subway area of Toronto, we are currently looking to expand our team with a &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Web Application Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Develop and maintain core back-end technologies, primarily mod_perl development&lt;br&gt;As part of development group, you will work closely with the development team and the templating/HTML programming group. This is newly created position. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- 3+ years experience &lt;br&gt;- mod_perl expertise&lt;br&gt;- HTML &amp; JavaScript&lt;br&gt;- Apache Web Server (configuration and tuning)&lt;br&gt;- strong Unix background (BSD preferred) &lt;br&gt;- OO Perl experience &lt;br&gt;- RDBMS experience (MySQL and SQL) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of C would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you would like to be considered for this role, please forward your resume to jobs@cryptologic.com, quoting your name and the position you are applying for in the subject line of the email.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interviews will begin immediately, however due to the volume of replies, we are sorry, but only those chosen for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>AC03450C-BCA0-4475-96A2-1B4D02EBE33E</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Application Developer</title>
</post>
