<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Business Systems Specialist &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Arbor Memorial Services Inc., through its subsidiaries, is a significant player in the cemetery and funeral business from coast to coast. We are currently recruiting a results-driven, customer focused Business Systems Specialist.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROLE OVERVIEW:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position reports to the Manager, Business Systems - Information Services and involves:&lt;br&gt;?designing, overseeing and/or performing functional testing &lt;br&gt;?business analysis&lt;br&gt;?designing and executing the training of I.S. customers on systems use&lt;br&gt;?supporting training on business procedures&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will work with all levels and areas within the company to identify, develop and implement projects that meet business needs and I.S. customer expectations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position contributes to the improvement of company performance by participating in the development of strategies and plans for the business systems group, facilitating I.S. customer participation, ensuring I.S. projects deliver products that meet business needs and by fostering excellent I.S. customer relations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A minimum of 2-3 years proven experience testing, and a demonstrated ability to apply testing methodologies and techniques are required. Previous experience with testing tools, particularly QA Run, is a definite asset. Strong change management and facilitation skills and excellent customer service orientation are required. Superior verbal and written communication skills round out your qualifications and excellent planning, coordinating and business analysis skills are essential to success in this position. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested applicants are requested to submit their resumes to hrdept@arbormemorial.com, quoting Business Systems Specialist in the subject line of the email.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants in advance and advise that only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;hrdept@arbormemorial.com&lt;br&gt;Arbor Memorial Services Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>AD6384BC-4E5D-4585-9569-DCCE611AAEE0</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Business Systems Specialist</title>
</post>
