<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강재형</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Some one who are interested in working for World Vision Canada can directly send a resume and cover letters to&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;volunteer@worldvision.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This positiska.s absolutely volunteer position(no paying job), main jobs are translation(English to Korean &amp; Korean to English), fundraising(phone call to koreans), MS-office(word,excel), copying, enveloping etc... their main environment is Win 2K, lotus notes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That is good for someone who need to be exposed to office tasks and get some work references. You are required to work just 8 or 9 hrs twice a week. Their location is near hwy 401 and Hurontario rd.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I've worked there since last July, but they need more korean volunteers.&lt;br&gt;Please read attached mail and Good Luck!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Currently, they don't have any IT related Volunteer position and full time position. but in the future, woh konws? If they open, this experiences would be great assets to apply for..)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;=================================================================&lt;br&gt;Hi Jay,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you SO much for doing that translation so quickly!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;And I really&lt;br&gt;appreciate your willingness to continue to check the Korean messages.&lt;br&gt;Please let me know if there is a message that needs my attention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am sorry to hear about the awful commute and hope that things will&lt;br&gt;improve as you settle into your new job.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you again for all of your help to date.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I agree with you, we&lt;br&gt;certainly need more Korean volunteers.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please feel free to recruit on my&lt;br&gt;behalf - if you could direct them to email volunteer@worldvision.ca and to&lt;br&gt;call the Korean phone number that would be best.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please let me know the&lt;br&gt;websites where you have posted so I can add them to our list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a great weekend!&lt;br&gt;_______________________________________________________&lt;br&gt;Kristina Huddy&lt;br&gt;World Vision Canada&lt;br&gt;Manager, Ethnic &amp; Volunteer Relations&lt;br&gt;phone: 905-565-6200 x2144&lt;br&gt;fax: 905-696-2161&lt;br&gt;email: xxxxxx@worldvision.ca&lt;br&gt;_______________________________________________________&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This message and any files attached hereto are intended only for the&lt;br&gt;addressee. They may contain privileged or confidential information. Any&lt;br&gt;unauthorized disclosure is strictly prohibited. If you have received this&lt;br&gt;message and any attachments in error please notify me as soon as possible.&lt;br&gt;Please delete the originals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;jay kang\\&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;lt;jay_kang84@hotm&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;To:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;xxxxx@worldvision.ca&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;cc:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;Subject: Re: translation help?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;09/27/2002 12:02&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;AM&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hello, Kristina;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sorry for late response. oh God, it took more than 2.5 hrs to get home from Markham yesterday... lots of traffic jam, I do not understand why they block the two lanes in hwy 401 at rush hours for rebulid.. Anyway..Yes, I can check the voice message with my home phone and even my cell phone. well, there is no message so far. I'll do check it every day. And, please check attached word format. My wife did the proof-reading twice,so it must be O.K.(?)...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am really concerned about my volunteer job in World Vision. I'll do my&lt;br&gt;best if you still need my participation. But I think you might need more&lt;br&gt;korean volunteers who can do the job well than you are expecting. If you&lt;br&gt;don't mind I'm gonna put your name and e-mail address on the internet for koreans who are interesting in volunteering.&lt;br&gt;Just think about it please and let me know.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>AFD656EA-DD4E-4C25-AF89-9C6A7F5B82D9</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Volunteer Position in World Vision Canada</title>
</post>
