<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Web Designer / Drupal (CMS) Designer &lt;br&gt;Post Date: 03/23/2010 &lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto , ON &lt;br&gt;Assignment: Full Time &lt;br&gt;Pay Rate: $60,000 to $70,000 per year &lt;br&gt;Start Date: 01/11/2010 &lt;br&gt;Industry: Printing/Publishing &lt;br&gt;Job Order Number: 512-017797 &lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;As a strong candidate for the role of Web Designer, you bring the following experience and proven skill sets: *Created at least 1 large CMS site preferably utilizing Drupal however equal Joomla skills will be acceptable. *3+ years of CMS (Content Management system) experience. *3+ years of Search Engine Optimization experience. *5+ years experience with HTML, CSS, PHP, and MY SQL. *3+ years of Administration experience with Free BSD Systems. *3+ years experience working with Apache Web Server is required. *Exposure to CARP, BSD Jails and Squid proxy server is an asset. *Experience working for and internet service provider is an asset. For more information and to request immediate confidential consideration, email your resume today to Sean Simon at sean.simon@rht.com, quoting the job reference &amp;#8211; Web Designer (#512-017797) &amp;#8211; in the subject line.&lt;br&gt;Description: &lt;br&gt;Our client, a large advertising and marketing company, requires a Drupal (CMS) Developer. Experience for consideration must include Systems Administration work within a Free BSD environment. This is a full-time career opportunity reporting directly into the Manager of I.T. and will involve 75% development with PHP and 25 % Systems Administration of the Free BSD operating system. Specific key responsibilities and focus will involve: *Creating (CMS) Content Management Systems, designed to ease the process of adding and modifying new content to the internal webpage; the pages content is stored in the database as opposed to in the file server and is created in Drupal 6. *Demonstrated aptitude improving the volume and quality of traffic for the SEO (Search Engine Optimization) of multiple web pages. *Primarily utilizing PHP, HTML, and MY SQL for development of the required modules and application within the CMS. *Administration of Free BSD Systems with the environment. *Exposure to protocols such as CARP (Common Address Redundancy Protocol). *Knowledge of FreeBSD jail (operating system-level virtualization for open source systems). *Knowledge of Proxy Servers such as Squid.&lt;br&gt;With more than 100 locations in North America, Europe, and Australia, Robert Half Technology is a leading provider of IT professionals on a project and full-time basis for IT initiatives ranging from Internet development and multiplatform systems integration to network engineering and technical support. Robert Half Technology offers online job search services at www.roberthalftechnology.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Half Technology is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply for this job now or contact our branch office for additional information: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Half Technology Markham &lt;br&gt;175 Commerce Valley Drive West &lt;br&gt;Suite 300 &lt;br&gt;Thornhill,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; L3T 7P6 &lt;br&gt;Phone :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 905 - 763 - 2851 &lt;br&gt;Fax :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 905 - 709 - 3664 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;markham@roberthalftechnology.com</content>
    <postId>B1A77459-2550-4F6B-BA05-82CB06C543A5</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-31T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Designer / Drupal (CMS) Designer </title>
</post>
