<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title: Java Developer&lt;br&gt;Posted On: 2/9/2010 10:37:12 AM&lt;br&gt;Designation: Java Developer&lt;br&gt;Number of Vacancies: 3&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: Degree in Computer field&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: &lt;br&gt;Solaris - 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Java/J2EE - 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Struts - 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;HTML / CSS/XML - 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Minimum Experience: 3 yrs.&lt;br&gt;Job Tenure: Full-time Only&lt;br&gt;Salary Offered: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Job Location: Toronto, ON, Canada&lt;br&gt; Job Description &lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES: &lt;br&gt;--Develop, implement and test server-side and front-end Java-based applications and relevant system components in a Solaris environment running WebLogic.&lt;br&gt;--Develop creative, innovative and practical solutions based on best practices.&lt;br&gt;--Work with business users to develop and clarify requirements.&lt;br&gt;--Work with senior team members to enhance personal and technical capabilities.&lt;br&gt;--Provide supporting documentation and training for operations.&lt;br&gt;--The ideal candidate should have demonstrable project development life cycle experience working with these technologies -combined with exceptional oral and written communication skills. &lt;br&gt;--Adherence to branding, usability and web development standards and tenets&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;br&gt;--Bachelor's Degree in one of: Engineering, Computer Science, or Mathematics.&lt;br&gt;3 - 5 years of OOAD using Java and J2EE to build large-scale applications in an enterprise environment on both server-side --and front-end applications&lt;br&gt;--Proven hands-on experience with HTML, J2EE, Struts, JSP, and XML. &lt;br&gt;--Good working knowledge of UML, object modeling, analysis and design patterns. &lt;br&gt;--Excellent written and verbal communication skills are required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Technical Skills:&lt;br&gt;--Java/J2EE, EJB, Struts, XML/XSLT&lt;br&gt;--Deployment tool Ant &lt;br&gt;--Solaris Unix &lt;br&gt;--SUN Certified accreditation is a definite asset&lt;br&gt;--Working knowledge of Weblogic and SOA would be an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you or your friends meet the above skill sets, please apply online.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Company Details&lt;br&gt;Name: International Business Search&lt;br&gt;Type: Consulting Organization&lt;br&gt;Total Employees: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Turnover: Not specified&lt;br&gt;Address: &lt;br&gt;150 Consumers Rd.,&lt;br&gt;Suite 306,&lt;br&gt;Toronto,&lt;br&gt;Ontario,&lt;br&gt;Canada&lt;br&gt;Profile: &lt;br&gt;International Business Search Inc. is one of Canada’s foremost recruitment and placement firms celebrating its 10th year. Although our primary focus has been Information Technology and Computer Professionals, we also specialize in the areas of Engineering, Finance &amp; Administration, Human Resources and Sales, both permanent and contract personnel. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;International Business Search Inc.’s commitment to providing comprehensive and integrated services has made us one of Canada’s most innovative and involved organizations in the field. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We believe that enabling an organization to achieve its full potential means working in partnership to define leadership positions and long term goals, and locating the most effective means towards achieving optimal ends &amp;#8211; whether by placing individuals or introducing and executing strategic alliances.</content>
    <postId>B2836245-5C47-4FBB-88FD-47E9693817E8</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer-Solaris</title>
</post>
