<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>Pearl Park</author>
            <date>2008-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>Is this still opening?</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>권칠환</author>
            <date>2008-12-19T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>Call or email him!!!</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;I have a client whose looking to fill a vacant role with a similar skill set as yours, if the job description below interests you, please forward a Word version of your resume with a synopsis of your skill set.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client is well known in the Educational Media sector located Downtown Toronto .&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Their IT department is looking to hire a Linux/Oracle Systems Administrator/Database Administrator on a full time basis.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The role is a combination of 40% Systems Administration and 60% Database Administration.&lt;br&gt;Start date: immediate&lt;br&gt;Salary:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;pays up to $70,000&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Downtown Toronto&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The role:&lt;br&gt;The Administrator’s role is to ensure the stability and integrity of the client’s Linux Systems, Oracle and other database technologies. These activities are achieved through planning, designing, and advancing the respective environments. The Administrator will specify, install, monitor, maintain, support, integrate, and optimize the server and database infrastructures.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Administrator will be expected to analyze and resolve problems in a timely and accurate fashion, and provide training and mentoring as required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Design and deploy the client’s standard Database and Intel Server infrastructures;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Execute Database and Server trend and performance analysis;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Perform and test backup and recovery situations across the entire system and database application infrastructure;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Configure Databases and Systems to ensure smooth and reliable operation and integration for fulfilling business objectives and processes;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ensure the associated hardware resources allocated to the Databases and Systems are appropriate to ensure high availability;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Collaborate with management and department leaders to assess near- and long-term Database and System needs;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Create and maintain documentation as it relates to Database and System configuration, mapping, processes, and service records;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Develop, implement and maintain policies, procedures, and associated training plans for Database and System administration, usage, and disaster recovery;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Conduct research on products, services, protocols, and standards to remain abreast of developments in the Database and System industries;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Practice asset management, including maintenance of component inventory and related documentation and technical specifications information;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Provide and receive cross training on client infrastructure technologies, such as server installation and general Sys Admin duties;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Mentor co-workers on Linux System Administration and Database Administration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Position Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;University degree in computer science and/or 5 years equivalent work experience;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven Oracle Database Administration experience, to include 9i, 10g, RAC, OEM;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Practical experience with other database systems, such as mySQL and MS SQL;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven Red Hat Linux System Administration experience;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven experience with Red Hat Linux and Windows Servers;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven experience with application servers such as WebSphere and Tomcat;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven and expert experience with scripting languages PHP and Java;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Working technical knowledge of shell scripting languages: bash, python, perl;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience with capacity planning, security principles, and general technology management best practices;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience with application monitors , hardware specific element managers, enterprise management tools such as Nagios, Cacti, HP OpenView; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Excellent knowledge of industry leading Technology vendors and their products;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Working technical knowledge of current network hardware, protocols, and Internet standards, including: tcp/ip, http, https, dns, dhcp, snmp, smtp, etc;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Competence with testing tools and procedures; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Knowledge of applicable data privacy practices and laws; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ability to be on an On-Call rotation;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ability to occasionally work nights or weekends; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Strong interpersonal, written, and oral communication skills;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Highly self motivated and directed, with keen attention to detail;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven analytical and problem-solving abilities;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Strong customer service orientation;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience working in a team-oriented, collaborative environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you know of someone who would be interested in this role, feel free to forward the job description and my contact information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you using LinkedIN - click on this link and connect with me! http://www.linkedin.com/pub/6/9b5/243 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best Regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Barry&lt;br&gt;Account Manager&lt;br&gt;+ bbarry@nexstaf.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;i www.nexstaf.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;http://www.linkedin.com/pub/6/9b5/243&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B288651E-9925-4A51-8123-53B2F691D391</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-10-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Nexstaf - Linux/Oracle System Admin/DBA</title>
</post>
