<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Software Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;CryptoLogic, Inc. is an Internet software development and licensing company with proprietary commerce-enabling technology that permits secure, reliable, efficient and rapid financial transactions over the Internet. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our products permit the processing of online transactions, with a current focus on e-commerce software. Our software is used by individuals registered in 240 nations and territories worldwide. We have processed more than 380 million individual transactions and in excess of US$ 4 billion in secure electronic deposits, from more than 580,000 clients. Common shares of the Company are listed on the Toronto Stock Exchange and on the Nasdaq National Market. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently searching for an individual to expand our team in the role of:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software Engineer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates should have a broad range of skills, with emphasis on:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;?C++ (3 years minimum)Windows or Unix&lt;br&gt;?SQL Windows (4 years minimum)&lt;br&gt;?experience in the design of communication interfaces (C++ gateways or HTTP interfaces)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you would like to be considered for this position, please email your resume, stating salary expectations, with your name and position you are applying for in the subject line of the email to: jobs@cryptologic.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interviews are targeted to start the week of Aug 5,2002 and while we thank everyone who submits a resume, due to time constraints, we will only be able to contact those chosen for an interview.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Marilyn Shabot, Director - Human Resources&lt;br&gt;marilyn.shabot@cryptologic.com&lt;br&gt;Cryptologic Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B2F0FC00-CEEB-4C29-8929-D30B58ABEF29</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-28T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software Developer</title>
</post>
