<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Business Intelligence Consultant &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At BMO Financial Group, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potential. As one of North America's highly diversified financial services providers, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business Intelligence Consultant&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a Business Intelligence Consultant, you will be responsible for working with business clients, understanding their requirements, and producing functional specification documents. Working closely with the Transformation Programmers, QA Analysts and business clients, you will resolve any and all requirement and specification issues as they arise. Business Intelligence Consultants are dedicated to working with business and data requirements and analysis, developing extensive documentation on the requirements and functional specifications for the Data Warehouse developers, and supporting the Data Warehouse development team in terms of understanding requirements. Front and back end programming is not a requirement, but as a Business Intelligence Consultant, you may be required to assist with data analysis and testing, so strong SQL skills are therefore required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have a university degree or college diploma, along with three to five years of experience as a business systems analyst in a business or information technology environment. You have a solid understanding of the data warehousing end-to-end development lifecycle. Your strong SQL programming skills and solid understanding of relational databases and data architecture is combined with knowledge of at least one procedural language. Some Unix experience, with OLAP technologies, is required. You have some background in project management or team leadership, although this is not a project management position. You are a self-motivated individual who takes pride in delivering high quality work and working as an integral part of a team. You thrive in a fast-paced, results oriented environment, and have worked within the structure of a large organization. Financial industry experience would be beneficial. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group thanks all applicants. We advise that only those who qualify for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At BMO Financial Group, we are committed to diversity and equitable opportunity for all individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: BGKTM00941&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group - BMO Groupe Financier&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B36205F5-A457-456A-AB51-88CD9EF36468</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-28T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Business Intelligence Consultant</title>
</post>
