<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Intermediate Software Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Domain Knowledge Inc. (DKI) is a global provider of Business Process Management solutions. DKI solutions enable organizations to design and capture processes, integrate them with existing technology systems, and then deploy the processes throughout the organization. We are looking for innovative, enthusiastic team players who embrace leading-edge technologies and the exciting changes occurring in today's marketplace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills/Experience/Education&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6-8 years of progressive experience in a professional, product-oriented development environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Substantial design and implementation experience producing Enterprise applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very acronym friendly including COM/DCOM/ADO/XML/XSLT using Visual C++ and the Microsoft development tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong understanding of OO principles. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience designing and coding distributed processing applications using leading RDBMS' (like Oracle and SQLServer). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Familiarity with MS .NET, Sun J2EE platforms or consortia initiatives like BizTalk, UDDI etc is a definite advantage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to lead by example, review, analyze and improve on the designs of others within the team. Must act as a resource to the team and to the VP of R&amp;D. Experience in a formal development process. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Engineering or related technical field &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking for someone whose personal qualities include curiosity, a good sense of humour, complete professional honesty and an absolute commitment to product quality. A person who takes pride in a job very well-done and has fun doing it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No phone enquiries please.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;hr@domainknowledge.com&lt;br&gt;Domain Knowledge Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B47B5794-C66D-45F8-81C1-9F6CB0087290</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-29T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Intermediate Software Developer</title>
</post>
