<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-Systems Development Manager &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;br&gt;If you aren't a match for this role, but are looking for work, we invite you to visit our site - www.gsigroup.com - click on Staffing Services, then on the Search button. This shows a list of our Job Orders which can be applied for online. Please don&amp;#47978; respond to this Monster posting by sending your CV \\&amp;quot;on spec\\&amp;quot; (these CVs are set aside to be reviewed later, which can take many weeks). We regret that, as a placement agency, we are unable to assist candidates in obtaining Canadian Work Permits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client has an immediate requirement for a Systems Development Manager (NOT a Project Manager).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;Manage the development of information technology systems &amp; procedures. Direct the provision of system support. Budget, hire/fire, other related duties. Responsible for team of 14.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills:&lt;br&gt;-- Min 10 yrs corporate experience&lt;br&gt;-- Min 5 yrs as manager of a team, department or division&lt;br&gt;-- Advanced knowledge of methodologies&lt;br&gt;-- Technically adept with PowerBuilder, Oracle, PL/SQL, C&lt;br&gt;-- Must be able to mentor staff.&lt;br&gt;-- Excellent people management skills&lt;br&gt;-- These items are nice to have: J2EE, WebSphere, Aix, Thin client&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Salary: CAD 80,000.00 to CAD 85,000.00 per year&lt;br&gt;Bonus could bring package up to 90K. &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: B9B-3J-ATB&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Gillian Eley&lt;br&gt;geley@gsigroup.com&lt;br&gt;GSI International Consulting Group&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B5DFC590-CD75-4959-BF0E-62EB003CA99E</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-27T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-Systems Development Manager</title>
</post>
