<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>S. Suh Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Following Job just opened in my department. If you are interested, please send your resume and covering letter to me at suh.l@sympatico.ca.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;===================================================================== &lt;br&gt;Job Title: Engineer/Officer - System Software Development and Support&lt;br&gt;Hours of work: 35.00 &lt;br&gt;Location: 49 Sargeant Drive, Barrie &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Accountabilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Full life cycle support of software for the Integrated Operating Facilities used in the real-time monitoring and control of the Transmission system.&lt;br&gt;Design, develop, and implement software modules using established procedures and practices.&lt;br&gt;Analyze performance of integrated systems and their components.&lt;br&gt;Provide technical support for software developers and end users.&lt;br&gt;Investigate and resolve failures at the software and operating system level.&lt;br&gt;Develop procedures and standards required for the secure operation and management of Transmission/Distribution information systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selection Criteria&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Competencies:&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated strong personal commitment to high quality work and customer satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to develop and deploy complex real-time tools required for transmission operations.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to work in a project environment, under tight deadlines, interfacing with other project staff, as well as users and project leader.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to assess, develop, recommend and implement integrated solutions.&lt;br&gt;Ability to work effectively as part of a large multi-disciplined team. &lt;br&gt;Demonstrated record of self-motivated behaviour and perseverance to accomplish objectives.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability in planning and maintaining control of quality and work performance.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated extensive hands-on experience with life cycle computer tool support.&lt;br&gt;Professional level of communication skills, both oral and written.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated capability to deal with external vendors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential knowledge, Experience and Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated experience in successful design and implementation of robust software. &lt;br&gt;Experience in a real-time control system environment would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated proficiency in one or more programming languages, including: C/C++, Java, and/or Visual Basic.&lt;br&gt;Experience in developing multi-threaded high performance software.&lt;br&gt;An understanding of multitasking operating systems and TCP/IP networks.&lt;br&gt;Requires an advanced knowledge of electrical engineering/computer science subjects and disciplines in order to design, develop and support large-scale real-time and mission critical computer systems. This knowledge is normally acquired through the completion of four years of University training. &lt;br&gt;A period of up to 8 years experience in software lifecycle management is required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notes:&lt;br&gt;Applicants with lesser qualifications will also be considered at the lower salary level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B661F028-11A4-4631-B369-197ABC0839C8</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-06-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Internal Job Posting 1 - Hydro One</title>
</post>
