<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최종구</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>[copied from workopolis.com] &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to gain Canadian experience&lt;br&gt;The lack of Canadian experience is a major obstacle for newcomers looking for work. Among the many ways of overcoming this are: writing a resum?according to Canadian standards, doing any kind of volunteer, part-time or contract work at the beginning, networking, and using the services of community organizations that can assist you in your job search. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carolyn Poulter - &lt;br&gt;October 3, 2003&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the many problems facing new immigrants is the penchant of Canadian employers to insist that job applicants can show Canadian experience on their resum&amp;eacute;s. But how can you get Canadian experience if you can't get a job until you have Canadian experience? Good question. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With no simple or easy answer. However, there are a few things you can do immediately to help with this issue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Make sure your resum&amp;eacute; is brief, concise and well written. Highlight your skills in point form. If English or French is not your first language have the resum&amp;eacute; proofread to avoid spelling and/or grammar mistakes. Canadian resum&amp;eacute;s contain considerably less personal and family information than is often the norm in other countries. See our Resum&amp;eacute; writing section for many tips, hint and articles on this subject. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get some kind of Canadian experience on the resum&amp;eacute;. Anything at all will help. It does not even have to be in your field, though obviously that is preferable. Consider taking a part-time job, contract work, agency work. Offer to volunteer your skills to local organisations. If you are an accountant see if your church or temple or local social club needs assistance. If you are in social work offer to be a volunteer visitor at your local hospital. This is especially useful if you speak languages other than English or French. Include all of this experience on your resum&amp;eacute;, right at the top so that the first thing the employer sees is the Canadian experience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Network, network, network. Print business cards with your name, address, telephone number and field of work. You can do this easily on most computers or have it done at any print shop or office supply store. Even though you are not in business as such you are marketing yourself. You have to be sensible about this, if you are invited to a wedding it is probably not a good idea to hand out the cards following the bride up the aisle. But in social situations most people do ask you what you do for a living, how you are liking Canada, have you settled in ok, etc. There is no harm in explaining that you are still looking for a job and if they hear of anyone who needs someone in your field to keep you in mind and hand them a card.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Try not to panic. The reason the Canadian Government insists that you have quite substantial landing funds is because it simply is quite difficult to get into that first 'real' job. Some new immigrants, the very lucky few, do land on their feet and get a job within days of landing which is great. But many more do not. You are not alone. There are many organisations that provide help for newcomers, don't be afraid to ask for help. There is no shame in feeling a bit adrift after making such a major life change.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B68260CA-D295-4417-9D07-A801A7FBB712</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-04-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>How to gain Canadian experience</title>
</post>
