<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My name is Diane Browne and I work for Keane Canada, an IT Consulting firm (www.Keane.com). We are currently looking for a strong Application Support Analyst. Our records show that you are a possible match for this requirement. If you are available, interested or planning to make a change, please send me an email. Thank you very much.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diane Browne&lt;br&gt;Sr. Technical Recruiter&lt;br&gt;Keane, Inc&lt;br&gt;Diane_E_Browne@keane.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KEANE IS HIRING&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keane is hiring for our Advanced Development Ctr. in Markham, Ontario.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Level 2 Application Support &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To work in supporting financial applications in a Enterprize environment. This position calls for very strong SQL, TSQL, Perl and basic Unix skills as well as Very Strong Database management experience on Sybase or SQL. The engineer will be responsible for DB performance management for all Sybase production databases. Should have thorough understanding of database design and should be able to interpret stored procedures and transact SQL programming.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Must have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MS-SQL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TSQL&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RDBMS (any)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perl &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shell Scripting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic Unix&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent written and verbal skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong Analytical skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong understanding of web server technologies (IIS 6.0). Would be nice to have experience in setting up application websites including deploying code on IIS servers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong TCP/IP troubleshooting skills . Basic networking knowledge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good understanding of MQ. Basic administration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Understanding of SOAP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic .net c#&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic Unix administration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic Windows 2000 administration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic understanding of the following :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FTP, HTTP, HTTPS,TCP/IP, SSH, Unix shell: Korne, NFS, NAS, NIS &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desired/transferable:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Help Desk Experience, Operations Support; Informatica; Autosys; Basic VCS clustering knowledge&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shift Information&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shift 1 - 8am to 5pm&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shift 2 - 4pm to 1am&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shift 3 - 12am to 9am&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours (different than regular?): ___N _X__ Y Specify: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, The hours will be consistent but will be assigned to shift work. Also, project coverage is 7 days per week. While each resource is only scheduled 5 days per week, this individual would likely be regularly assigned 1 weekend day. This is a US based client which operates 365 days per year. The team is required to provide on site coverage on all holidays (including Christmas day) and this individual could be assigned on any or all of those days, with another day off.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being a member of the Keane team will give you the ability to work from Markham, Ontario on projects for International Fortune 500 companies. Enjoy a top-notch benefits package, active Social Club, on-going company-paid training and more! Come be a part of Keane's continued growth and success in the Canadian IT marketplace!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you do not want to receive future announcements of career opportunities with Keane, just let me know by replying to this e-mail. I will remove you from our mailing list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you would like to unsubscribe, please click here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lookup Candidate</content>
    <postId>B7F08B15-EF8E-42C9-A952-7897E7BF299E</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-08-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Application Support for Keane Canada in Markham, Ontario</title>
</post>
