<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>http://www.recruitingsite.com/csbsites/aecl/en/JobDescription.asp?JobNumber=161273&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Datacentre Administrator&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Posted Date:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;18-07-2006&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Mississauga, Ontario, Canada&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Description:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Atomic Energy of Canada Limited is an integrated nuclear technology company providing services to nuclear utilities worldwide. Our 4,000 employees are focused on delivering R&amp;D support, nuclear services, design and engineering, construction management, specialist technology, and waste management and decommissioning in support of CANDU reactor products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atomic Energy of Canada Ltd is looking for a Data Centre Operations Administrator. The successful applicant, located at the Sheridan Park location and reporting directly to the Section Head, Data Centre Operations, will efficiently provide support for the Data Centre Operations Section by performing the following duties:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Install, upgrade, configure and maintain Windows and UNIX server systems including maintenance of existing hardware, software and utilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Install, upgrade, configure and maintain disk storage systems, backup devices and other interfaces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Monitor and troubleshoot problems related to Data Centre server systems, disk usage, CPU utilization and availability, power resources and operating condition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Maintain high server systems availability (potentially 7 days-a-week x 24 hours/day)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Provide systems support during normal hours and off-hours as required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Remain technically current, particularly in HP Hardware, operating systems and Data Centre technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ensure system integrity and maintain system security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Recommend changes for improvements.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Assist with projects aimed at reducing costs, increasing productivity and improving service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Carry out assigned projects and duties as requested&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Participate in the change control management process&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Windows 2003 operating system software and Intel-based hardware is required&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Knowledge of Unix Operating System (HP-UX &amp; Red Hat Linux) would be highly desirable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Knowledge of network concepts would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ability to work with minimal supervision is required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate must have good interpersonal skills to work well with customers and fellow team members.&lt;br&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills are required .&lt;br&gt;Patience, good judgement, diplomacy, and grace under pressure are essential attributes.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3 year university or technical college diploma in Computer Science or Computer Systems Technology or related discipline. Candidates having equivalent training and experience in the support of computer systems in a corporate network environment will be considered.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AECL has an Employment Equity Program and encourages applications from women, Aboriginal Peoples, visible minorities and persons with disabilities. AECL provides a smoke-free workplace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B83C930F-5B59-4741-9DF4-5CE228C8008D</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-07-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Datacentre Administrator</title>
</post>
