<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>안병욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>저희 회사는 아닙니다.&lt;br&gt;다만, 혹시 코스카 회원 여러분에게 도움이 될까해서 올립니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Luck 입니다. :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Junior UNIX Administrator - Toronto, Ontario &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University Health Network (UHN) is one of Canada's largest acute-care teaching hospital organizations, comprised of four healthcare organizations located in downtown Toronto: Toronto General Hospital, Toronto Western Hospital, Princess Margaret Hospital and Toronto Medical Laboratories. UHN has a long-standing tradition of patient care, education and research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate should have hands-on experience with multi-platform environments (Unix, Windows, Mac OS) and the services that provide for heterogeneous integration. Candidates should be team oriented and be able to work unsupervised.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Installation/administration/maintenance of back-end servers and client workstations&lt;br&gt;- Troubleshooting client machine/software problems&lt;br&gt;- Configuration and compilation of various research/bio-medical software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;REQUIRED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- 2 to 3 years experience in a multi-platform Unix Administration role&lt;br&gt;- Strong system administration knowledge of Unix operating systems: Solaris, IRIX, Linux&lt;br&gt;- Good understanding of network services: NIS, sendmail, NFS, DNS, Samba&lt;br&gt;- Excellent troubleshooting and communication skills&lt;br&gt;- University Degree in Computer Science/Information Technology or equivalent diploma&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PREFFERED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Programming/scripting experience&lt;br&gt;- Understanding of Windows, Mac OS.&lt;br&gt;- Working experience within educational/research/health care facilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position is a temporary full time position with reassessment at 8 months for permanent full time employment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University Health Network thanks all applicants however, only individuals selected for interviews will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please email resumes with the position in the Subject field to:&lt;br&gt;ris-jobs@uhnres.utoronto.ca&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B8982013-499D-4B26-B426-F0DCE4710A29</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Junior UNIX Administrator - Toronto, Ontario</title>
</post>
