<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior Information Systems Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;[Dev-2003-04-08-102] &lt;br&gt;Senior Information Systems Developer &lt;br&gt;- Toronto, Ontario &lt;br&gt;Posted on: 2003-04-08 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position reports to Corporate Manager, Database &amp; Information Systems &lt;br&gt;Salary range: Commensurate with experience &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Main purpose &lt;br&gt;To be responsible for analysis, design, hands on development and maintenance of all existing and new Information Systems applications while working with a team of Developers and DBAs. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key responsibilities &lt;br&gt;1.Design, develop and maintain Tucows internally developed ERP and CRM Information Systems applications and data sources. &lt;br&gt;2.Work cross functionally with various departments to understand there needs and deliver Information services. &lt;br&gt;3.Actively participate in the analysis and hands on development of all major/minor Information Systems projects. &lt;br&gt;4.Work with a small team of Analysts, Developers and DBAs as a senior team member. &lt;br&gt;5.Mentor junior staff with development projects. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ideal Candidate Profile &lt;br&gt;Related experience / Unique skill set &lt;br&gt;1.Around 5 to 7 years of practical experience in Information Systems Analysis and development. &lt;br&gt;2.Expert level hands on experience in designing and developing analytic reporting including Financial and Distribution systems. &lt;br&gt;3.Excellent development experience in web development using Perl, PHP, HTML, Java Script running under APACHE. &lt;br&gt;4.Proven expert background in Oracle development tools such as SQL *Plus, PL/SQL, and SQL *Loader. &lt;br&gt;5.Strong concepts about data warehousing and practical experience working with Microsoft OLAP tools and MS SQL Server. &lt;br&gt;6.Excellent working knowledge about RDBMS systems and Oracle8i in particular. &lt;br&gt;7.Excellent practical experience using Linux, Solaris or other Unix flavors. &lt;br&gt;8.Version control system experience (preferably CVS). &lt;br&gt;9.Experience in mentoring small teams of analysts and developers. &lt;br&gt;10.Experience in working with multiple teams in a cross-functional setup. &lt;br&gt;11.Experience in object oriented programming languages such as Java and C++ is a plus. &lt;br&gt;12.Willing to work long and sometime odd hours whenever needed &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bachelor Degree in Information Science/Computer Science or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interpersonal skills &lt;br&gt;1.Self motivated with tons of creative as well as productive energy. &lt;br&gt;2.Excellent time management skills to meet demanding timelines. &lt;br&gt;3.Excellent planning and documentation skills. &lt;br&gt;4.Ability to effectively communicate with users of all type and technical levels. &lt;br&gt;5.Strong sense of ownership and urgency to deliver services in a timely fashion. &lt;br&gt;6.Ability to comprehend Company's broader business objectives. &lt;br&gt;7.Ability to understand and manage dynamically shifting priorities. &lt;br&gt;8.Natural ability to work under pressure. &lt;br&gt;9.Good conflict management and resolution skills. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supervisory experience &lt;br&gt;N/A&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other &lt;br&gt;1.Expect to work long and sometimes odd hours whenever needed. &lt;br&gt;2.Expect to be on call 24/7 as a part of high availability support cycle. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please e-mail your resume and cover letter to hrdept@tucows.com and refer to &lt;br&gt;[Dev-2003-04-08-102] Senior Information Systems Developer in the subject line. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are applying for any other opportunitites with Tucows, please submit your resume to hrdept@tucows.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;hrdept@tucows.com&lt;br&gt;Tucows&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B9E8DF03-B643-4818-AAEB-D48AD7B38D8D</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-04-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Information Systems Developer  from Monster</title>
</post>
