<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience opportunity with a team that's growing and going strong&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAO Technology Solutions, Inc. is looking for their newest, world-class Developer!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position:&lt;br&gt;Our developers work with top-notch teams to build on long-term customer relationships. Primary responsibilities for this position will be to analyze requirements and develop computer programs. From the moment you join our team, our shared focus is your success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5 - 7 years in UNIX, shell scripting&lt;br&gt;5 - 7 years in C, ProC, PL/SQL, Oracle,Oracle forms, Java, and UML&lt;br&gt;5 - 7 years as a Systems Analyst or &lt;br&gt;5 - 7 years experience in documentation like. design documents and testing plans&lt;br&gt;Project management and team leader ship experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good to Excellent command of the English language &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong analytical skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to produce quality work in a team environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please forward your resume in confidence to apply@oaot.com, quoting reference number MON - Sr. DEV -TOR.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAO Technology Solutions (OAOT) is a provider of IT and e-Business solutions servicing some of the world’s largest businesses, communications and automotive companies. Our progressive work culture is centered on building careers while fueling the expertise that drives success in today’s marketplace. In this way we outpace the competition in an industry that rewards technical savvy and inspiration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAO Technology Solutions is a provider of employee equality and diversity.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: MON - Sr.Dev - TOR&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;apply@oaot.com&lt;br&gt;OAO Technology Solutions (Canada) Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>BBDFB380-88A9-4547-8D61-93F6D9924969</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Developer -OAOT</title>
</post>
