<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Dear Chilhoan, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I came across your professional profile on the Internet. Currently my company has immediate need to fill a position of:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CA-ON-Markham-Java Application Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.fivestarjobs.com/posting.asp?redir=-30k-34kMqVdP6VjMKtfE7ZVO6xjBa_V&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Markham, Warden/HWY7 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With your background I thought there may be a potential fit for you. Please follow the link to review the job description. If the position is of interest to you please send your current resume and a cover letter in word format along with your salary/rate expectations. If you have no interest in this position and you can think of someone who would be better suited for the position please feel free to forward the information to them and have them contact me via e-mail or the web site.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much,&lt;br&gt;Gennadi Nestertchouk&lt;br&gt;FiveStarJobs&lt;br&gt;gennadi@fivestarjobs.com&lt;br&gt;http://www.fivestarjobs.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is the purpose of this email? With this email we are letting you know that we have a job that may be a fit for your skills. If it is of interest, please apply for the position through our web site. If it is not of interest, please disregard. If you can think of someone who would be better suited for the position please feel free to forward the information to them.&lt;br&gt;Why did you get this? Keywords in your resume met a search string used in searching for qualified resumes in our database and(or) resume databases of popular job boards. And you provided your e-mail address in your resume to contact you.&lt;br&gt;You don't want any more of these emails? Please reply to this email and put word "Remove" in the subject line. If you find that this doesn't work, contact support@fivestarjobs.com or submit a feedback through our web site at http://www.fivestarjobs.com/feedback.asp Please allow 1-2 days for processing.&lt;br&gt;You'd like to see all the jobs we currently have and know more about FiveStarJobs? Please check out http://www.fivestarjobs.com/currentpostings.asp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br&gt;This e-mail message (including attachments, if any) is intended for the use of the individual or entity to which it is addressed and may contain information that is privileged, proprietary, and confidential and exempt from disclosure. If you are not the intended recipient, you are notified that any dissemination, distribution or copying of this communication is strictly prohibited. If you have received this communication in error, please notify the sender and erase this e-mail message immediately. &lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br&gt;Le present message electronique (y compris les pieces qui y sont annexees, le cas echeant) s'adresse au destinataire indique et peut contenir des renseignements de caractere prive ou confidentiel. Si vous n'etes pas le destinataire de ce document, nous vous signalons qu'il est strictement interdit de le diffuser, de le distribuer ou de le reproduire. Si ce message vous a ete transmis par erreur, veuillez en informer l'expediteur et le supprimer immediatement. &lt;br&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gennadi Nestertchouk&lt;br&gt;gennadi@fivestarjobs.com&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>BC650091-3B7A-4AA5-8A86-5DB315A17118</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-12-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>CA-ON-Markham-Java Application Developer</title>
</post>
