<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Company background:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IPDEVCO provides comprehensive solutions for the on-line gaming industry and Internet based electronic cash management. The company has developed an integrated suite of applications consisting of solutions for the player and back office operations based on JAVA and C++ technology. Its client base consists of domestic and international clients.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business initiative:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IPDevco continually develops new client functionality for its application suite. IPDevco requires additional Full-Time C++ Developer to join the team. The incumbent will be responsible for developing new C++ components and re-engineering new components from existing code that can be used by application developers. This is a senior position that requires extensive knowledge of multi-threaded applications, event handling, and component development. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5 ?8 years experience in C++ using Visual C++ 6.0, MFC&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience in building Object Oriented components in C++, Active X, COM&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft Visual Studio with C++, SourceSafe, InstallShield&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Windows 32 Bit platforms: 95/98/NT/2000/ME &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Effective communication skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent team player&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice to have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of 2D/3D graphics animation and sound support&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Game Development experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Java exposure&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Re-factoring experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank you for your interest but must advice that only candidates to be interviewed will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: IPD-Game&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Sonia Dhoofar&lt;br&gt;jobs@ipdevco.com&lt;br&gt;IP Marketing / IP Devco&lt;br&gt;67 Mowat Ave Suite # 440&lt;br&gt;Toronto&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C182684F-F733-4E3B-8B3A-25CE886DD954</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>C++ Game Engine Developer</title>
</post>
