<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Number: 4914197&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title: Web developer (NOC: 2175)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terms of Employment: Temporary, Full Time, Day&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: $20.00 to $30.00 Hourly for 40 hours per week&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anticipated Start Date: 2010/03/26&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario (1 vacancy)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skill Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education: Some high school, Some college/CEGEP/vocational or technical training, Some university, Not applicable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Not required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience: 1 year to less than 2 years&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Read English, Write English&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Setting: Research and development institution , Computer systems unit&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specific Skills: Consult with clients to develop and document web site requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Programming Languages: HTML, XML, CSS, Object-Oriented programming languages, PHP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Computer and Technology Knowledge: Windows, Database software, Programming languages&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applications: Adobe Photoshop&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Conditions and Physical Capabilities: Tight deadlines, Attention to detail&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transportation/Travel Information: Own transportation, Public transportation is available&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Skills: Problem solving, Job task planning and organizing, Computer use&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employer: Ontario Federation of Indian Friendship Centres&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to Apply:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please apply for this job only in the manner specified by the employer. Failure to do so may result in your application not being properly considered for the position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By E-mail: njamieson@ofifc.org&lt;br&gt;Business Profile: A Non-Profit organization, for the betterment of Urban Aboriginals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advertised until: 2010/03/21&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This job advertisement has been provided by an external employer. Service Canada is not responsible for the accuracy, authenticity or reliability of the content.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C2456551-08D2-4D2C-902E-FED0C131F390</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web developer (NOC: 2175) </title>
</post>
