<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>관심 있으신 분은 레주메를 보내주세요&lt;br&gt;seasign@gmail.com&lt;br&gt;회사 www.opensolutions.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Programmer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job ID # 764653 &lt;br&gt;Location Canada-Ontario-Oakville &lt;br&gt;Job Stream Information Technology &lt;br&gt;Job Type Permanent, Full-Time &lt;br&gt;Salary/Rate Open &lt;br&gt;Number of Positions Open 1 &lt;br&gt;Start Date of Employment ASAP &lt;br&gt;Posting Date 21-Nov-2006 &lt;br&gt;Travel Required Occasionally &lt;br&gt;Educational Requirements College Diploma &lt;br&gt;Languages Required English &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description &lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Manger Development Services, the Programmer is responsible for writing, testing, analysis, implementation, and support of reports/applications for the Product Development and Support family of products. &lt;br&gt;Specific responsibilities in this role include: &lt;br&gt;Develop and support systems using current technologies as required according to specifications. &lt;br&gt;The incumbent will develop new reports/programs, according to department standards and architecture, as described in project definition documents or business requirements documents. &lt;br&gt;Responsible for assigned development items as per Incident Reports within predefined response and delivery times. &lt;br&gt;Will perform functional, unit, and systems integration testing prior to hand-over to the Quality Assurance group. &lt;br&gt;Will assist in the design of new products and systems, under the guidance of more senior Programmer Analysts and/or the Chief Developer. &lt;br&gt;Will analyze existing systems for functional gaps and enhancements with the objective of providing recommendations to more senior Programmer Analysts and/or the Chief Developer. &lt;br&gt;Will input as requested to project definition documents and business requirements documents for the analysis and design of systems. &lt;br&gt;May be responsible for internal and external installation and training duties as required. &lt;br&gt;May be required to travel to customer sites. &lt;br&gt;May be called upon for 7/24 functions. &lt;br&gt;Will respond to, investigate, and resolve production problems. &lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate will possess the following education, skills and traits: &lt;br&gt;Community College or higher, specializing in Computer Science related studies, with at least four years of work experience. &lt;br&gt;An excellent understanding of Crystal Reports, and relational databases including DB2, SQL, and Oracle. &lt;br&gt;Good analytical, problem solving, and fault isolation skills. &lt;br&gt;Possesses effective written and oral communication skills. &lt;br&gt;An understanding of the payments industry and self-service financial products, switching, monitoring, transaction processing, and settlement and reconciliation would be beneficial. &lt;br&gt;Experience following development processes and methodologies, and familiarity with all phases of the software development life cycle. &lt;br&gt;Must be able to communicate ideas and concepts to all parties. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C357B053-4F76-4429-B82F-B152F43B3346</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-11-30T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Crystal Reports, RDB/SQL, Banking</title>
</post>
