<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Software Support Consultant &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ADC is The Broadband Company(tm). ADC's fiber optics, network equipment, software and integration services make broadband communications a reality worldwide by enabling communications service providers to deliver high-speed Internet, data, video and voice services to consumers and businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently looking for a Software Support Consultant for our Billing and Customer Management application group in Toronto, Ontario.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mission of the R&amp;D Support Team is to generate customer satisfaction by providing timely and effective solutions to support requests (mainly problem reports and questions) reported against the Singl.eView suite of products as released by R&amp;D. The team provides 3rd level Singl.eview application support to internal customers (GCS implementation teams, GCS Production Support teams, Sales ACs, trainers) in line with R&amp;D SLAs. As both our product portfolio and our customer base continue to expand, we are looking to augment the team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key areas of responsibility/activity are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take ownership of allocated support requests through to successful resolution.&lt;br&gt;Liaise closely and collaboratively with the internal customer and, where necessary, the Development Team to facilitate timely resolution. &lt;br&gt;Apply analytical skills to identify and solve problems.&lt;br&gt;Provide solutions, work-arounds and advice to internal customers in response to support requests.&lt;br&gt;Keep supervisor informed of progress and delays in resolution of support requests.&lt;br&gt;Become a subject matter expert on one product/aspect of a product within the suite, with a working knowledge of the broader suite of products. &lt;br&gt;Work collaboratively with other Support team members to ensure top priorities are being addressed and that absences are covered.&lt;br&gt;Follow procedures and provide concise, accurate information at all times.&lt;br&gt;Opportunities for short-term travel may arise on occasion. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Degree Qualified or relevant experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 2 years previous experience in a Support, Maintenance or Development role.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 1 years experience with Unix environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requires a working knowledge of Unix commands and concepts including environment variables, file permissions, login/out procedures, shell scripting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A working knowledge of SQL and at least one programming language. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of at least one of C/C++/Java/Perl is highly desirable. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Oracle and Tuxedo is desirable. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Highly-developed analytical problem solving skills to aid in swift problem diagnosis and identification of obscure problems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An aptitude for grasping problems and solutions in a business as well as a technical sense. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The role requires technical knowledge but with a business focus. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commitment to solving customers' problems with a strong customer focus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clear and professional communication skills (oral and written) and inter-personal skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to work cooperatively with internal customers, the Support Centre, Support team and rest of R&amp;D. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attention to detail and quality, ability to work under pressure, sometimes with a sense of urgency, ability to work on a number of problems at the same time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability and willingness to relocate overseas on short-term assignment on a rotation basis is desirable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relevant industry experience is highly desirable, in particular Billing Operations experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Training will be provided on the relevant Singl.eview products. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: 01002&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;ADC - The Broadband Company&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C4CE45E0-CAC0-4A43-A4E5-4E999BC58788</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-10-30T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software Support Consultant</title>
</post>
