<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Mainframe Environment Analyst &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At BMO Financial Group, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potential. As one of North America's highly diversified financial services providers, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mainframe Environment Analyst&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is an exciting opportunity for the right person. The individual will be responsible for working with the Infrastructure Analyst and QA Coordinator in the Finance/InSight line of business to establish processes and methodologies for the environments within the department. The incumbent must be able to work independently, be assertive in terms of promoting their ideas, and to multi-task.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have strong proven technical skills gained from your experience in a large corporate environment. You have ideally supported multiple technologies and applications, including PeopleSoft, mainframe, client/server, desktop and web. Preference will be given to those with a strong mainframe background. Exposure to other technologies is also a benefit. You have experience with TSO, JCL, tools and utilities, system management (including network hardware), networking concepts and system administration. Applications and tools include Focus and WebFocus, DB2 and SQL. Hardware includes the RS/6000 platform and Intel. You have the ability to work under pressure, manage expectations and to prioritize. You have a strong customer focus, and are willing to work extra hours or weekends to meet project demands. PeopleSoft and client/server experience are definite assets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group thanks all applicants. We advise that only those who qualify for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At BMO Financial Group, we are committed to diversity and equitable opportunity for all individuals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: BGKJF00926&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;BMO Financial Group - BMO Groupe Financier&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C53CAFDA-AF22-4729-BB1D-02197F13B124</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mainframe Environment Analyst</title>
</post>
