<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Number - J0403-0729 - Full Time&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Title Consultant Systems Developer &lt;br&gt;Category Information Technology &lt;br&gt;City Toronto, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;Job Location Toronto &lt;br&gt;Posting Date (dd/mm/yyyy) 12/06/2003 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Job Description/Accountabilities Business Unit Description:&lt;br&gt;The World Markets, Wealth Management and Treasury Balance/Risk Technology holds an abundant wealth of expertise in application and experience in infrastructure development. You will be a part of a team that believes in providing &amp;#48214;orld class?service and support in a collaborative global framework. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our offices expand worldwide and our primary services include: infrastructure support and services, technology strategy, architecture development, vendor management, application development/support and implementation of technology solutions. Our leadership and dedication to excellence will contribute to our exceptional global Infrastructure support and service organization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities / Activities:&lt;br&gt;Canadian Securities Operations Technology has the mandate to provide technology solutions for our client team Canadian Securities Operations. We are searching for two senior team members to help us to deliver on this mandate. Our technology base is varied with mainframe, client server and web applications in our inventory. &lt;br&gt;Our mandate includes the support and enrichment of the existing application base as well as delivery of new projects. &lt;br&gt;Your mandate will be to provide leadership, technical direction, quality assurance within a team environment for day-to-day support, ongoing enhancements and project work. &lt;br&gt;Relationship building with client areas and technical staff are strong focuses for this position. Your responsibilities will include working with clients and team on the prioritization of client requests, developing requirements, planning deliveries, providing technical consultation and problem solving on solutions and designs, mentoring and developing the technical staff. &lt;br&gt;Support and direction for the 'programmer on call? &lt;br&gt;Active participation in projects including developing business cases and budgets. Leadership and support for internally driven mandates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;Solid technical experience:- &lt;br&gt;5 years- SQL, Cognos-Powerplay, Impromptu, WEB&lt;br&gt;5 years of application experience&lt;br&gt;5 years- Unix&lt;br&gt;5 years -Financial Services / Brokerage / Operations experience&lt;br&gt;Network and Communication experience is desirable&lt;br&gt;5 years or equivalent of SQL Server and/or Oracle (preferred )experience&lt;br&gt;Experience with QA testing, load testing is an asset&lt;br&gt;5 years of strong technical design skills&lt;br&gt;A minimum of 5 years experience with System Development Lifecycle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attributes:&lt;br&gt;Service Orientation&lt;br&gt;Results Orientation&lt;br&gt;Agile/Adaptable&lt;br&gt;Relationship Building&lt;br&gt;Leading Others&lt;br&gt;Analytic/Systematic Thinking&lt;br&gt;Accountability&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special conditions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIBC is an equal opportunity employer. It is the Company's policy to recruit and select applicants for employment solely on the basis of their qualifications, with emphasis on selecting the best qualified person for the job. CIBC does not discriminate against applicants based on race, color, religion, sex, national origin, or disability or any other status or condition protected by applicable federal, state or local law.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Skills Brokerage&lt;br&gt;Quality Assurance&lt;br&gt;Design&lt;br&gt;Financial&lt;br&gt;Client Server&lt;br&gt;Operations&lt;br&gt;Impromptu&lt;br&gt;Testing&lt;br&gt;Oracle&lt;br&gt;PowerPlay&lt;br&gt;SQL&lt;br&gt;SQL Server&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;https://cibc.njoyn.com/cibc/xweb/XWeb.asp?tbtoken=Z1tbRBsvCG0FEHVwRFVXCFU9BBFEcCMudEhYWl4EE2AqWkYeWTFoLiUuQC4kXhMBLiUuQC4kXgk%3D&amp;chk=dFlbQBNQ&amp;Page=JobDetails&amp;Jobid=J0403-0729&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C5AEA697-A0D4-455F-967B-CDDD1EC3A2DD</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Consultant Systems Developer-CIBC</title>
</post>
