<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>K. Kwon</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Anticipating an economic turnaround, CIOs are&lt;br&gt;starting to snap up the best IT talent out &lt;br&gt;there while it's still a buyer's market. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So what are you waiting for?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BY ALICE DRAGOON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the economy improves, as inevitably it will, the pent-up demand &lt;br&gt;for IT&lt;br&gt;will incite a scramble for talent that will leave the unprepared&lt;br&gt;organization in the dust. A CIO study shows this rush has already &lt;br&gt;begun,&lt;br&gt;with 19 percent of respondents already ramping up IT staff, and 27 &lt;br&gt;percent&lt;br&gt;planning to hire in the third and fourth quarter of 2002. To avoid &lt;br&gt;getting&lt;br&gt;caught unprepared, CIOs must first identify what IT work must happen to&lt;br&gt;support their company's post-recovery goals, and what IT skills and&lt;br&gt;competencies will be needed to provide that support. Also, identify the&lt;br&gt;specific business indicators that will signal an imminent spike in the&lt;br&gt;business's demand for IT services. CitiStreet CIO Barry Strasnick, for&lt;br&gt;example, will watch for when the S&amp;P 500 reaches 1200. Then negotiate &lt;br&gt;now&lt;br&gt;with executive management to remove budgetary and hiring restrictions &lt;br&gt;before&lt;br&gt;the current buyer's market evaporates. In other words, companies need &lt;br&gt;to&lt;br&gt;manage for recovery, not constraint. Bank One, Northwestern Mutual and &lt;br&gt;UPS&lt;br&gt;are among those embarking on a recovery hiring strategy. Bank One, &lt;br&gt;which at&lt;br&gt;press time has filled 745 of the 996 IT positions it plans to add, has &lt;br&gt;been&lt;br&gt;able to lure employees from top technology companies-workers who two &lt;br&gt;years&lt;br&gt;ago would not have returned the bank's phone calls. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C5F34867-726C-4440-A989-B8CB5A95A2AD</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>What the CIOs are being told....</title>
</post>
