<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>ob Snapshot&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;Employee Type: Full-Time Employee&lt;br&gt;Manages Others: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Information Technology&lt;br&gt;Experience: 7 to 10 years&lt;br&gt;Post Date: 18/02/2010 Contact Information&lt;br&gt;Ref ID: 4190--1246916&lt;br&gt;Description&lt;br&gt;Requisition #4190--1246916 &lt;br&gt;Job Location: Canada-Ontario-Toronto &lt;br&gt;Job Stream: Information Technology &lt;br&gt;Job Type: Contract, Full-Time Contract Duration1,012&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hours &lt;br&gt;Number of Positions Open: 1 &lt;br&gt;Start Date of Employment: ASAP &lt;br&gt;Posting Date: 17-Feb-2010 &lt;br&gt;Travel Required: Not Required &lt;br&gt;Educational Requirements: N/A &lt;br&gt;Languages Required: N/A &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department Overview: We are looking for an IT Specialist to join the Specialized Support Group (SSG) within Infrastructure Technology Solutions. SSG is responsible for the infrastructure for a number of applications which support both the Wholesale Bank and Treasury &amp; Balance Sheet Management (TBSM) within TD Bank. The focus of this position is to support TBSM and the Novell OES Linux environment. This will be a challenging position, with involvement in many projects in a dynamic fast paced environment Job Description/Accountabilities: The candidate will be responsible for the day to day support for the Novell OES infrastructure in TBSM. The role will be based in the downtown Toronto location with occasional visits to other sites in the GTA as project needs arise. The individual’s primary responsibility will be to acquire the technical expertise and balance it with business knowledge to support the subsequent applications and provide full end to end support of the product. They will have to: - Provide end to end support from dev all the way to production environments, including after hour on-call duties. - Incident escalation point for both Level 1 application and infrastructure support teams. Primary responsibility for incident resolution - Implement application and infrastructure changes - Capacity and security management - Work with other members of the SSG team and other key areas in the TD Enterprise The candidate must hold a range of broad knowledge of Linux skills and be eager to learn how to support the business and understanding business requirements. Engineering and support skills for the following products are required, Must have skills: - Linux: SUSE / Redhat (7-10 years) - Novell OES (7-10 years) - Hardware: Intel/AMD HP and IBM (7+ years) - High availability clustering technologies (7+ years) - Scripting: Perl, Python, Shell Scripting (7+ years) -Strong background in project related tasks Nice to have: - Working knowledge of monitoring tools such as Tivoli &amp; nagios (3+ years) - Experience supporting servers in a SAN environment (3+ years) - Supporting middleware tiers such as Apache Tomcat (3+ years) In addition, the candidate is expected to have the following support skills: - Balanced knowledge of business, application, server, and network technologies -Broad application, protocol, server, network diagnosis skills -Fluent with transaction &amp; data flow through the system Specific Educational Requirements/Accreditations: - College / University with emphasis on computer science and business or equivalent work experience. - IT Industry accreditions not required, but will be considered along with experience Other Qualifications/Skills/Experience: - Financial Services IT experience - Broad experience with IP networking concepts - routers, firewalls, etc - Teamwork - strong relationships with developers and business analysts, architecture &amp; operations - Excellent communication and presentation abilities - Effective time management skills and ability to work under deadlines and operational pressures&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; </content>
    <postId>C5FDC19E-1D55-4FA0-B336-C7FDD3600C7E</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>IT Specialist to join the Specialized Support Group (SSG) within Infrastructure </title>
</post>
