<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Dear Chil-Hoan:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope everything is going well with you. I would be happy to hear &lt;br&gt;about your current status and career goals. If this message found you in &lt;br&gt;error please accept my apologies, but feel free to send me your updated &lt;br&gt;resume. This will enable me to look for suitable and challenging &lt;br&gt;positions for you. Urgently, we are looking for an Oracle Developer. Following &lt;br&gt;you will find the job description.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you already obtained a position through VTRAC, please disregard this &lt;br&gt;message and kindly forward this message to your friends. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please let me know if you are interested or you know anyone who might &lt;br&gt;be interested in this position. Also, I would appreciate it if you could &lt;br&gt;pass our company's name and our Website www.vtrac.com to your friends &lt;br&gt;who have strong expertise in Developing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you and best regards, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rod Power&lt;br&gt;VTRAC Corporation&lt;br&gt;366 Bay Street, Suite 500&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON, M5H 4B2, Canada&lt;br&gt;Phone: (416) 366-2600 ext. 220&lt;br&gt;Fax: (416) 366-5550&lt;br&gt;e-mail: rodp@vtrac.com &lt;br&gt;www.vtrac.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;VTRAC Consultants Corporation&lt;br&gt;"Solutions for Growth" &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;POSITION: Database Developer&lt;br&gt;STATUS: Permanent&lt;br&gt;LOCATION: Toronto&lt;br&gt;JOB #: 11145&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please e-mail your resume as Ms-Word attached document with reference &lt;br&gt;to Oracle Developer in confidence to rodp@vtrac.com or call: (416) &lt;br&gt;366-2600 x 220&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities / Activities:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Oracle PL/SQL developer to enhance on an internally developed PL/SQL &lt;br&gt;project. This project involves developing code to load, scrub, and &lt;br&gt;summarize hundreds of millions of rows daily, with summarized data being &lt;br&gt;transferred to reporting repositories. The successful candidate will &lt;br&gt;continue PL/SQL development of the existing system, while investigating, &lt;br&gt;designing, developing, and implementing improved strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major Activities:&lt;br&gt;* Participate in design, engineering, configuration, testing and &lt;br&gt;performance tuning of Oracle data database environment. Provide technical &lt;br&gt;leadership in evaluating the design and coordinating the initiatives with &lt;br&gt;application development teams.&lt;br&gt;* Support production environments, configuration, testing, and &lt;br&gt;performance tuning of all Oracle database environments.&lt;br&gt;* Managing problem/project tickets queue and maintaining communication &lt;br&gt;with business team members.&lt;br&gt;* Actively provide leadership and technical expertise to ongoing &lt;br&gt;problem identification/resolution and root cause analysis process.&lt;br&gt;* Participate as a team member in evaluating system resource &lt;br&gt;utilization and storage usage/capacity, and makes recommendations to increase &lt;br&gt;application performance to meet business and financial requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;* Architectural experience developing &lt;br&gt;* Knowledge of techniques for transferring data between databases &lt;br&gt;* 3 years experience in PL/SQL development &lt;br&gt;* Application performance tuning experience &lt;br&gt;* Experience with Oracle database (10g experience an asset) &lt;br&gt;* DBA experience considered an asset &lt;br&gt;* Familiarity with JDBC an asset&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Technologies:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Support, administer, and maintain Oracle 8i,9i &amp; 10g environments &lt;br&gt;under UNIX.&lt;br&gt;* Oracle High Availability architectures (RAC, DATA GUARD)&lt;br&gt;* Oracle Enterprise Manager Diagnostic Pack, Tuning Pack&lt;br&gt;* Oracle Enterprise Edition Option Packs (OLAP, Data Mining)&lt;br&gt;* Sun Solaris 2.6, 2.8, &amp; 2.9, Win2k &amp; Win3K &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all the candidates in advance. Only those candidates that are &lt;br&gt;selected for interview will be contacted. For other exciting &lt;br&gt;opportunities, please visit us at www.vtrac.com.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C699BF8D-B1F6-44A0-843B-2ED5E5A95B25</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-05-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Database Developer</title>
</post>
