<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title: Network Analyst, Data Network Services &lt;br&gt;Req Number: NA112202 &lt;br&gt;Location(s): Toronto ON&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;COMPANY INFORMATION &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AIM Funds Management Inc. offers investors many ways to reach a diversified range of funds distinguished by asset class, geography, sector and management style AIM makes it easy to find the right mix of funds for any portfolio. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All AIM funds are managed according to the rigid criteria of their investment discipline, meaning investors know exactly how their money is being managed. Each discipline has been developed over AIM's lengthy history to bring the best opportunities to each portfolio and long-term growth to each investor. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the AMVESCAP group of companies, AIM and its sister company, INVESCO, manage assets of over C$600 billion (as at September 30, 2000), making AMVESCAP one of the largest independent money management firms in the world. As a truly global company with roots stretching back to the 19th century, AIM relies on the expertise of its world wide network of investment professionals working out of our 40 offices located in 20 countries on 5 continents to bring you the world's premier investment opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The position will be responsible for tactical planning, development, implementation, and support of new/existing data network services to maintain optimal functionality and ensure operational effectiveness. Work with internal client departments, network carriers, and external suppliers to address new requirements and pursue enhancements/improvements to existing data networks including Internet/Intranet services. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department Summary/Mandate: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Telecom &amp; Data Network team's role, as part of the IT/Technology Management Department, is to deliver and support high quality, innovative telecommunications, voice processing, data communications, and Internet/Intranet services that address AIM's business goals. Plan and maintain an efficient and cost-effective voice and data network infrastructure that can accommodate the future growth of existing/new business services, sharing knowledge to provide expertise and direction on the use of existing/new telecommunications, contact center technologies and services. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Responsibilities: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Evaluate, plan and coordinate networking systems hardware/software and network upgrades to ensure the reliability and availability of key data network services &lt;br&gt;-Research, develop, evaluate, and implement best practices to improve customer service, efficiency and reduce costs &lt;br&gt;-Work with internal clients to assess and understand their data network requirements &lt;br&gt;-Initiate, schedule, and coordinate work activities with internal and external parties &lt;br&gt;-Plan, schedule, test, and implement network changes &lt;br&gt;-Work with carriers and suppliers to ensure reliability and operational effectiveness of data networking systems &lt;br&gt;-Develop, monitor and maintain service measurements and capacity of data network systems and services &lt;br&gt;-Provide timely support for service requests &lt;br&gt;-Provide hands-on approach to the resolution of complex networking issues &lt;br&gt;-Develop, maintain configuration documentation and operational procedures for network services &lt;br&gt;-Train and provide technical assistance and support to the Help Desk and other Network staff &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Requirements: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Minimum of five (5) years data networking and Internet work experience required &lt;br&gt;-Post-secondary education majoring in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science, and/or Telecommunications &lt;br&gt;-Completion of Cisco certified training courses (CCNA, CCNE designations) preferred &lt;br&gt;-Possess strong customer orientation and sense of urgency &lt;br&gt;-Excellent problem solving and analytical skills &lt;br&gt;-Strong communication (written/verbal) skills &lt;br&gt;-Ability to work under pressure and keep composure in a fast-paced work environment &lt;br&gt;-Strong work ethic and maturity &lt;br&gt;-Flexible work schedule requiring some overtime and weekends &lt;br&gt;-Able to provide 24/7 primary on-call support on a rotational basis &lt;br&gt;-Ability to travel between offices within the Greater Toronto Area and occasionally within Canada &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Skill Requirements: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-CISCO Routers (15540 optical, 6509, 7200 series), Switches (3600 series), IOS, ACLS, TACACS/Radius, AS5300 RAS technology, VLANS &lt;br&gt;-DNS, BIND, DHCP &lt;br&gt;-File Transfer services and secure FTP &lt;br&gt;-Network services including T1, Fractional T1, ATM, ISDN (PRI/BRI) &lt;br&gt;-Internet/Intranet/Extranet networks, BGP, SSL, HTTPS &lt;br&gt;-Nokia Firewall / Checkpoint NG management &lt;br&gt;-VPN, Nortel Contivity, Entrust PKI &lt;br&gt;-Network and routing protocols including TCP/IP, EIGRP, VRRP &lt;br&gt;-Ethernet, FastEthernet, GigaEthernet &lt;br&gt;-HP OpenView, Packeteer Packetshaper &lt;br&gt;-Cat 5E/Cat 3 Structured Cabling, SMF &amp; MMF Fibre &lt;br&gt;-UNIX Solaris and Windows XP/NT experience is preferred &lt;br&gt;-Broad knowledge of PC hardware and software &lt;br&gt;-Some Telecom background or exposure (voice networking, VoIP, Avaya PBX) &lt;br&gt;-Radware WSD an asset &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C8A7292E-18A1-4A28-868B-0BB11AA28427</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-28T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Title: Network Analyst, Data Network Services</title>
</post>
