<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>IT Technician,&lt;br&gt;EHVERT ENGINEERING&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON, CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1 Position(s)&lt;br&gt;Posted Feb 18, 2010&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT Consultant- Full-time - Toronto&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Ehvert Engineering provides IT consulting, Communications, Electrical and Mechanical engineering to large organizations in a multi-vendor environment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Our services include network &amp; systems integration, wireless network engineering, systems management, security planning and audits, technical support, fibre/cable plant design, providing outsourced IT services and technology relocation.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are continuing to grow and are looking for an IT Consultant to join our team.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Your role would be the following:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Perform the role of Ehvert's technical team lead during Ehvert's larger migration projects for both desktop and server migrations working closely with both Ehvert's clients and Ehvert project manager&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Provide primary onsite support for Ehvert's small and medium client base (The technology deployed at small and medium clients typically consist of Windows 2000 / XP servers and workstations, Exchange&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2000, 2003 and XP, small routers and firewalls)&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Participate and be the primary consultant in the development of the recommendations and fee proposals for the small and medium clients&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Implement and managed technical solutions for Ehvert's small and medium clients&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Primary systems architect for Ehvert's Internal network and systems&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Assist in supporting Ehvert's internal day to day IT requirements&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Provide rotational pager support required for Ehvert's network&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Actively participate in the architectural design and implementation of Ehvert's network&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;We are looking for a candidate with a strong technical knowledge, good attention to details, and the ability to work on multi concurrent project while delivering the highest quality of work. The successful candidate will have a minimum of 5 years hand-on technical experience in the IT field as well as experience with the core suite of Microsoft products including Microsoft Exchange. Previous project type experience is an asset but not a requirement.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will be a confident self-starter who has excellent organizational and communication skills and is very detail oriented.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are looking for candidates who are willing to take the initiative, are knowledgeable about technology and can work in a self managed environment.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;For more information about Ehvert Engineering, please visit our website at www.ehvert.com.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you are interested in applying, please send your resume to careers@ehvert.com.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Due to the volume of resumes we receive, we regret that only qualified candidates will be contacted.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Thank you for your interest in Ehvert Engineering, we look forward to receiving your resume!</content>
    <postId>C9EEF91F-10AE-4667-9B67-72118EAF8AD2</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>IT Technician, EHVERT ENGINEERING</title>
</post>
