<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>K. Kwon</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;Date: Wed, 02 Oct 2002 18:02:27 -0400 &lt;br&gt;From: \\&amp;quot;Consulpro\\&amp;quot; &amp;lt;ed@consulpro.com&amp;gt; | This is Spam | Add to Address Book &lt;br&gt;Subject: job opportunity &lt;br&gt;To: kwon96@yahoo.com &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best regards,SENIOR DESIGNER, WEB INFRASTRUCTURE PERFORMANCE MANAGEMENT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1049&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senior designer brings significant application domain&lt;br&gt;expertise in performance management to the R&amp;D team. He/she is&lt;br&gt;responsible for establishing the product&amp;#47977; technical vision,&lt;br&gt;accelerating development of product features and capability,&lt;br&gt;mentoring a skillful team of software engineers, creating&lt;br&gt;functional specifications, leading and documenting the&lt;br&gt;architecture and design activities. The incumbent will also&lt;br&gt;contribute to coding critical modules and functionality, as well&lt;br&gt;as performing unit test activities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements engineering:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- be a principal participant in the product definition process&lt;br&gt;- contribute to the feature roadmap for the product&lt;br&gt;- participate in the feature and requirement prioritization&lt;br&gt;process&lt;br&gt;- leverage expertise in performance management to develop&lt;br&gt;solutions for various application requirements&lt;br&gt;- create functional specifications and conceptual design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;System Architecture &amp; Software Design:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- lead the system architecture evolution&lt;br&gt;- lead technology architecture and evaluation for related areas&lt;br&gt;in the development of the product&lt;br&gt;- lead technical discussions and meetings&lt;br&gt;- coordinate the design of product subsystems and documentation&lt;br&gt;- actually design critical and risky software subsystems&lt;br&gt;- design the integration strategies of 3rd party tools and&lt;br&gt;systems into the product&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Implementation:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- coordinate the code review process within the project team&lt;br&gt;- write and maintain the code for key system components&lt;br&gt;- provide 3rd level technical support for product related issues&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Validation:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- participate in the pre-production and staging validation&lt;br&gt;process as needed, at the functional and system testing levels&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deployment &amp; Support:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- assist as necessary in the deployment of code releases&lt;br&gt;- provide 3rd level technical support for product related issues&lt;br&gt;- provide technical expertise to other departments within the&lt;br&gt;company when required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- university degree in Computer Science, Engineering or related&lt;br&gt;fields&lt;br&gt;- 8+ years of industrial experience developing and maintaining&lt;br&gt;complex software systems&lt;br&gt;- 3 years experience in Java programming&lt;br&gt;- expert knowledge of TCP/IP and the HTTP protocol&lt;br&gt;- a minimum of 3 years experience in a key design role in&lt;br&gt;implementing performance management solutions involving one or&lt;br&gt;more of the following fields: web log analysis, web application&lt;br&gt;infrastructure monitoring, Network and Event Management Systems&lt;br&gt;(BMC, OpenView), trend analysis, root cause analysis&lt;br&gt;- extensive experience with the Linux platform or Unix variants&lt;br&gt;- excellent knowledge of web based applications and technologies&lt;br&gt;(Java, J2EE, XML)&lt;br&gt;- excellent knowledge of several Java application servers&lt;br&gt;(WebLogic, WebSphere, Tomcat, Resin etc)&lt;br&gt;- excellent knowledge of web client technologies (browsers, HTML,&lt;br&gt;Java, JavaScript)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Kaluzny, MBA&lt;br&gt;Consulpro&lt;br&gt;Tel.: 514-932-9523&lt;br&gt;mailto:ed@consulpro.com&lt;br&gt;http://www.consulpro.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>CA08AC73-6DA7-4C82-BA3D-60952CE1C88F</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-10-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SENIOR DESIGNER, WEB INFRASTRUCTURE PERFORMANCE MANAGEMENT</title>
</post>
