<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>BROADVISION - TECHNICAL LEAD and ADMINISTRATOR :. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Status:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Salary:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;CAD 75,000.00 to CAD 90,000.00 per year&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Client is one of the world’s Leading Service Providers &amp;#8211; Empowering Fortune 500 businesses to MAXIMIZE! IT Infrastructure Management, Application Hosting, E- Services, and M-Commerce. A BroadVision Technical Lead is required to be the “technical go to for resolution of high level issues”. Mentor a team of BroadVision Professionals in high-level implementations, monitoring, and support of web technologies and databases. High profile client base - providing support to 25 different regions &amp;#8211; implement new customer applications, act as the focal point of web related software, and establish new support procedures. Ideal candidates must have demonstrated expertise in a high availability support environment with an emphasis on BroadVision &amp;#8211; current environment consists of iPlanet, LDAP, WebLogic, Websphere, UNIX, NT and Oracle. Excellent client interface skills and leadership skills a must &amp;#8211; An exciting, challenging and invigorating environment. Tons of growth potential! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank you for your response, however; only those candidates being considered for an interview will be contacted. Suitable resumes will be data based for future career opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;....................................................................................................................................................................&lt;br&gt; Contact Information :.&lt;br&gt;info@kcicareers.com&lt;br&gt;KCI Careers Inc.&lt;br&gt;#850 36 Toronto St&lt;br&gt;Toronto M5C 2C5&lt;br&gt;Ph: 416 366 9166&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>CA0C4C27-68BC-4B61-B5A8-D705507A6D94</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>BROADVISION - TECHNICAL LEAD and ADMINISTRATOR</title>
</post>
