<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Maternity leave replacement of one year.&lt;br&gt;The position is located within the following governmental organization(s): Parks Canada.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALARY: $ 45,181 to $ 54,968 per annum.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANGUAGE: English essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL LANGUAGES: USEFUL INFORMATION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO CAN APPLY: Employees of Parks Canada Agency occupying positions in Canada and/or persons who work or reside within 500 kilometres from the work location : Tobermory. Candidates should clearly indicate their home or work address.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORK ENVIRONMENT: &lt;br&gt;Parks Canada is committed to the principles of diversity and employment equity under the Employment Equity Act, and strives to ensure that our workforce reflects the diverse nature of Canadian society. We encourage women, Aboriginal peoples, persons with disabilities and visible minorities to self-identify on the application form.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Parks Canada Agency is established as a separate employer in the Federal Public Service under the Public Service Staff Relations Act. Persons appointed to the Agency continue to be part of the Public Service. The Parks Canada Agency operates under its own human resources framework outside of the Public Service Employment Act and in line with values of fairness, competence and respect, and its operating principles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In accordance with paragraph 8(2)(a) of the Privacy Act, information or material, whether provided directly by the candidate or otherwise obtained by the selection board, used during the selection process for the purpose of assessing a candidate may be used as part of the selection review and recourse processes. Such relevant information may be provided to third parties, such as other candidates or their representatives, who have a legitimate reason to be aware of that information. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHALLENGE: &lt;br&gt;The position is based in Tobermory and will operate in the following area: Southwestern Ontario Field Unit, Bruce Peninsula National Park and Fathom Five National Marine Park.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this position, you will be responsible for the development and maintenance of a Geographic Information System (GIS), associated databases and traditional paper-based resource library in support of the ecosystem-based management program at Bruce Peninsula National Park and Fathom Five National Marine Park and the greater park ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDUCATION: &lt;br&gt;A university or college degree in one of the natural sciences or computer sciences with significant emphasis on the application of Geographic Information Systems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPERIENCE: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designing, developing and managing a large digitized natural resource database(s) for application in ecosystem-based management; &lt;br&gt;Using spatial technologies including GPS and satellite imagery for GIS applications; &lt;br&gt;In quantitative analysis of natural resource data using GIS and database management technology; &lt;br&gt;Managing projects related to GIS and/or database management; &lt;br&gt;Preference may be given to candidates who have experience in the operation of SPANS/ARCVIEW GIS software and/or a graduate degree. &lt;br&gt;ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS / COMMENTS: &lt;br&gt;Candidates will be screened against the education and the experience factors listed above. &lt;br&gt;Candidates must clearly demonstrate to what degree they meet the experience criteria, giving examples of EACH element. &lt;br&gt;Quote the reference number and your Personal Record Identifier (PRI#), if you have one ; &lt;br&gt;Proof of Education must be submitted with your application, if you submit your application electronically, you must confirm that you have the credentials and forward the proof of education by mail or fax to the address provided below. &lt;br&gt;Please provide 2 references with your application (one being your supervisor and one other work-related reference). &lt;br&gt;Reliability/Security:Enhanced Reliability. &lt;br&gt;Possession of a valid Ontario Class G driver’s license or equivalent. &lt;br&gt;Requirement to wear Parks Canada uniform. &lt;br&gt;Similar positions in Ontario may be staffed as a result of this competitive process. &lt;br&gt;REFERENCE NUMBER: 2002-12-BFF-T-OC-OO9&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLOSING DATE: January 15, 2003&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates who meet the above criteria will also be assessed against the Statement of Qualifications for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;If you apply online, DO NOT send a duplicate by fax or regular mail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note: If you are applying by fax or by regular mail, we would ask that you fill out form PSC 3391, \\&amp;quot;Application for Employment\\&amp;quot;. If you are unable to obtain a copy of this form, you must clearly indicate your citizenship as well as the title and reference number of the position for which you are applying. Your resume must demonstrate that you meet all of the above mentioned requirements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates with foreign educational credentials are required to provide proof of Canadian equivalency. You may consult The Canadian Information Centre for International Credentials at http://www.cicic.ca/indexe.stm for further information. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please clearly indicate your citizenship. Preference will be given to Canadian citizens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all those who apply. Only those selected for further consideration will be contacted. As the Public Service of Canada promotes Employment Equity, we also encourage candidates to voluntarily self-identify if they are an Aboriginal person, a member of a visible minority group or a person with a disability. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are interested and meet the above requirements, please apply on line or send your resume to Marilyn Handley, fax (519) 596-2298 or mail to: Bruce Peninsula National Park/Fathom Five National Marine Park, Human Resources, 20 Centennial Drive, Hwy # 6, Tobermory, Ontario N0H 2R0. If you require further information, you may contact Frank Burrows, Resource Management Specialist, 519-596-2444 ext. 310.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please quote reference number: 2002-12-BFF-T-O/C-009&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are committed to employment equity. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>CA8DF37C-8BD2-451C-8EDA-262815BE0A5D</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-12-31T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>DATABASE MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST, Tobermory, ON</title>
</post>
