<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Full time term position more than 12 months.&lt;br&gt;The position is located within the following governmental organization(s): Department of the Environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALARY: $50,663 (under review).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANGUAGE: English essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL LANGUAGES: USEFUL INFORMATION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO CAN APPLY: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Persons working or residing in an area where the postal code begins with L, M, N or P.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHALLENGE: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FPA (Forecast Production Assistant) is a software system designed for improving productivity in a weather office. It allows forecasters to visualize and interact with computer graphic representations of the latest weather data. The FPA is somewhat comparable to a geographic information system (GIS), except for us the time dimension is much more prominent. This state of the art system has been licensed to two large international companies. Your task is to gain technical expertise in the FPA, participate in plans to move the product forward, and play a key role in communicating with our clients.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're looking for someone with an excellent grasp of software design, but also a keen interest in science and commercial activity. You will work in a research environment with many diverse activities including software development, testing, documentation, web site design, and marketing. You will have a wide array of tools at your disposal, and a friendly atmosphere in which to contribute your ideas. You will meet people from other countries with an interest in your work. This is truly a unique opportunity for a motivated and team oriented individual to work on interesting projects and make a difference.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDUCATION: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graduation with an acceptable Bachelors degree (BSc.) from a recognized university in Computer Science, Systems Design Engineering, Geography, Meteorology or a related branch of earth or environmental science.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPERIENCE: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience in the configuration or processing of geomatic or remote sensing data, or in the computer enhanced visualization of scientific data; Minimum one year recent industry experience in software design, computer programming, software documentation, web site design; Minimum 1 year recent industry experience in programming languages such as C, C++, Perl, FORTRAN, Javascript; Experience with operating systems such as HP-UX, SUN Solaris, Linux, UNIX.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS / COMMENTS: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enhanced security clearance will be required prior to appointment. &lt;br&gt;As Environment Canada is striving to achieve a truly diversified and representative workforce, Environment Canada will make every reasonable effort to accommodate the needs of its employees and candidates. &lt;br&gt;Work will be conducted primarily at the King Radar (near King City, Ontario), and occasionally at Meteorological Service of Canada (MSC) headquarters in Downsview. There is no public transit or food service available at King Radar. &lt;br&gt;Those candidates called for a written test are requested to provide references, proof of citizenship, and proof of education at such time. Tests and final interviews will be conducted at King Radar. &lt;br&gt;All costs related to travel and/or relocation for the purposes of the selection process may be the responsibility of the candidate. &lt;br&gt;The eligibility list established for this position may be used to staff similar vacancies. &lt;br&gt;REFERENCE NUMBER: DOE13768GZ05&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLOSING DATE: December 6, 2002&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates who meet the above criteria will also be assessed against the Statement of Qualifications for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you apply online, DO NOT send a duplicate by fax or regular mail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note: If you are applying by fax or by regular mail, we would ask that you fill out form PSC 3391, \\&amp;quot;Application for Employment\\&amp;quot;. If you are unable to obtain a copy of this form, you must clearly indicate your citizenship as well as the title and reference number of the position for which you are applying. Your resume must demonstrate that you meet all of the above mentioned requirements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates with foreign educational credentials are required to provide proof of Canadian equivalency. You may consult The Canadian Information Centre for International Credentials at http://www.cicic.ca/indexe.stm for further information. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please clearly indicate your citizenship. Preference will be given to Canadian citizens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all those who apply. Only those selected for further consideration will be contacted. As the Public Service of Canada promotes Employment Equity, we also encourage candidates to voluntarily self-identify if they are an Aboriginal person, a member of a visible minority group or a person with a disability. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public Service Commission of Canada&lt;br&gt;1 Front Street West,&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;M5J 2X5&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAX: (416) 973-1883&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>CAB1C023-E08B-499E-A030-CE3ABD78539D</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-15T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>SCIENTIFIC PROGRAMMER AND TECHNICAL LIAISON</title>
</post>
