<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content> I have a client whose looking to fill a vacant role with a similar skill set as yours; if the job description below interests you please feel free to forward a Word version of your resume with a synopsis of your skill set &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Rate: Please provide your best rate &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Project Start Date: November 10, 2009 (approximate) &lt;br&gt;Project End Date: March 31, 2010 &lt;br&gt;Project Duration: 100 Business Days for each Programmer/Analyst &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The Client is seeking two (2) Programmer/Analysts&lt;br&gt;The Programmer/Analysts will have at least 8 years of development experience of which at least 6 years will be working experience in Java / J2EE technologies. Demonstrated experience in one or more of the following areas is also required: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory requirements &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience in Java/J2EE code reviews. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with different presentation and server side frameworks (i.e., Struts, Spring etc.); &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with the development of common utility components; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience in contributing to large, complex, IT system development and implementation projects; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience in the development of distributed applications; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with Java Message Service (JMS), Java EE Connector Architecture, and transaction management; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Web development experience, including HTML, Javascript, AJAX; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Demonstrated experience with a wide range of Open Source Java Libraries (Jasper Reports, iText etc,); &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with object oriented analysis and design; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with Oracle SQL and PL/SQL; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Familiarity with additional Java technologies such as Velocity, Quartz, Jakarta Commons, log4j, Java mail API, XMLBeans, PMD, etc; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Demonstrated experience with encryption/crypto APIs; &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent analytical, problem solving and decision making skills; excellent English language verbal and written communication skills; excellent interpersonal and negotiation skills; and &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; A team player with a track record for meeting deadlines. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Desirable attributes: &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience within the OPS in projects of a similar nature; and &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with Web Services, SOAP, MQ-Series, XML, XSL/XLST, Schemas is a plus. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;If you know of someone who would be interested in this role, feel free to forward the job description and my contact information &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Best Regards,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Arshiya Gopalani&lt;br&gt;Recruitment Consultant&lt;br&gt;+ arshiya@nexstaf.com &lt;br&gt;i www.nexstaf.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;Aring; 416-849-1238 fax 416-849-3517 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;______________________________ &lt;br&gt;Nexstaf &lt;br&gt;5025 Orbitor Drive&lt;br&gt;Building 2, Suite 400&lt;br&gt;Mississauga ,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ontario ,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;L4W 4Y5 &lt;br&gt;Setting the Standard f or IT Staffing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>CC84C3D8-5215-4D0F-885A-4572B3DCDA9C</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer- Contract- Downtown </title>
</post>
