<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>POSITION&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Database Administrator&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;REPORTS TO&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Manager, Technical Services&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;DEPARTMENT&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Technical Services&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;JOB STATUS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full-Time&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;COMPANY&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Rogers Communications Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;DIVISION&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Rogers Shared Services&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;LOCATION&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ontario&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;LOCATION DETAILS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Markham&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;JOB TYPE&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Information Technology&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;JOB REFERENCE #&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;RILP050&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perform application and database optimization by working with developers, customers and system support personnel. &lt;br&gt;Investigate and provide methodology, processes and procedures to exploit new features and directions of IMS. &lt;br&gt;Provide optimization recommendations through historical analysis. &lt;br&gt;Physical design of application database and file structures. &lt;br&gt;Increase database reliability and availability through process improvement. &lt;br&gt;Evaluate, provide and maintain software tools to assist internal and external customers. &lt;br&gt;Aid in problem determination and resolution. &lt;br&gt;Provide database and related system support. &lt;br&gt;Provide on-call assistance for database related problems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;University degree in computer science or equivalent with substantial directly related work experience. &lt;br&gt;Minimum 5 years Database Administrator experience &lt;br&gt;Excellent working knowledge of Oracle, Unix, and Scripting &lt;br&gt;Excellent ability of RDBM database problem determination and resolution &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of AIX, HP and SUN, NT, Progress and SYBASE would be an asset &lt;br&gt;Strong organizational, interpersonal, motivational &amp; Analytical skills &lt;br&gt;Effective written &amp; verbal Communication skills &lt;br&gt;Availability for on-call support of database related activities &lt;br&gt;Ability to work effectively on multiple simultaneous tasks within fast paced, “high tech” customer service oriented environments &lt;br&gt;Ability to complete project tasks in a timely manner &lt;br&gt;Outstanding customer service skills &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply for this opportunity using the on-line resume.&lt;br&gt;Learn of other ways to apply for this opportunity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested Applicants please forward resumes to rsscareers@rci.rogers.com quoting job code number RILP050 in subject line</content>
    <postId>CCB1580D-4E99-4678-B124-EA6D5D3A9AE9</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Database Administrator</title>
</post>
