<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>ississauga, Ontario&lt;br&gt;Employee Type: Full-Time Employee&lt;br&gt;Manages Others: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Information Technology&lt;br&gt;Restaurant - Food Service&lt;br&gt;Experience: 5 to 7 years&lt;br&gt;Post Date: 22/02/2010 Contact Information&lt;br&gt;Ref ID: 1236622&lt;br&gt;Description&lt;br&gt;Requisition #1236622 &lt;br&gt;Job Location: Canada-Ontario-Mississauga &lt;br&gt;Job Stream: Information Technology &lt;br&gt;Job Type: Permanent, Full-Time &lt;br&gt;Number of Positions Open: 1 &lt;br&gt;Start Date of Employment: ASAP &lt;br&gt;Posting Date: 21-Jan-2010 &lt;br&gt;Travel Required: Not Required &lt;br&gt;Educational Requirements: N/A &lt;br&gt;Languages Required: N/A &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client in the retail technology space in Mississauga has an immediate opening for a Database Administrator (Production). The preferred candidate will have experience working with SQL Servers v2000 and 2005, and Analysis Server 2000 and 2005 (MS OLAP). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Full understanding of all database interactions with application in our production environment&lt;br&gt;Daily maintenance and review of system related items for all database server&lt;br&gt;Investigation and resolution to database system related performance issues&lt;br&gt;Install, upgrade and maintain all production and office database systems&lt;br&gt;Support all business units from a database perspective&lt;br&gt;Administer, monitoring of all database related processes. This includes but not limited to proper maintenance and backup routines&lt;br&gt;Support systems database environment for all daily, monthly operations. On call availability to respond to priority one incidents. 24x7 may be require&lt;br&gt;Database production issues to be investigated and root cause analysis discovery&lt;br&gt;Maintenance of databases environments by staying on top of, reviewing anticipated performance and capacity volumes. Subsequently providing input for improvement and tuning&lt;br&gt;10. Proactive monitoring&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;11. Provide consultation on database technology for any cross functional changes i.e. application design, systems design, new products&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;12. Champion Database environment disaster recovery plan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;13. Co-manage and determine project plans for database related projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology focused degree (computer science, software engineer, etc.)&lt;br&gt;MS SQL related to OLTP and DS databases (stored procedures, functions, tables, views, indexes, triggers, etc.)&lt;br&gt;SSIS, ETL, Job management&lt;br&gt;MS OLAP (AS2000 and AS2005)&lt;br&gt;5-7 years working experience&lt;br&gt;Experience working in a .net environment&lt;br&gt;Excellent English language skills&lt;br&gt;A highly organized, detail oriented attitude</content>
    <postId>CDAE8FC7-7628-46B4-9F9A-28520A6DA9A6</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>MS-SQL (agency)</title>
</post>
