<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Length: To be defined&lt;br&gt;Respond By: April 19, 2010&lt;br&gt;Deliverables:&lt;br&gt;`````````````&lt;br&gt;* Deliverables required all of the stated mandatory experience; &lt;br&gt;* Fuller details will be published when available. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills Required:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory:&lt;br&gt;``````````&lt;br&gt;* Functional expertise in implementing Oracle ERP Financials and I-Expense, HRMS, OLM, and Payroll modules; &lt;br&gt;* Minimum 6 years Oracle ERP 11i; &lt;br&gt;* Minimum 1 year Version R12; &lt;br&gt;* Experience in Migrating ERP11i to Release 12i; &lt;br&gt;* Familiarity with Human Resources, Finance and Payroll general policies and procedures in an unionized environment. &lt;br&gt;Other:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How To Respond:&lt;br&gt;````````````````&lt;br&gt;A). Email reponse directly to hr@tlwenterprise.com;&lt;br&gt;B). Provide your resume in Word (It will only be presented with your permission);&lt;br&gt;C). Quote "Re: Oracle Application Specialist, Contract, Toronto, ON, Posting # 1" on the Subject Line; &lt;br&gt;D). Provide three work references with contact info for submission to the client; &lt;br&gt;E). Please help us to know your work experience better by answering the following questions in your reply:&lt;br&gt;1. Please specify the number of years of experience for the following:&lt;br&gt;a) IT environment (including b below)?&lt;br&gt;b) Oracle Application Specialist?&lt;br&gt;c) When were the most recent month and year you worked as an Oracle Application Specialist?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and as an Oracle Application Specialist with:&lt;br&gt;(Please specify both "years of experience" &amp; "when was the last used")&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;d) Functional expertise in implementing Oracle ERP Financials and I-Expense, HRMS, OLM, and Payroll modules?&lt;br&gt;e) ERP 11i?&lt;br&gt;f) Version R12?&lt;br&gt;g) Migrating ERP11i to Release 12i?&lt;br&gt;h) Human Resources, Finance and Payroll general policies and procedures in an unionized environment?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. When are you available to start?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Are you incorporated, registered partnership, sole proprietorship or individual?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. What is your expected hourly rate?&lt;br&gt;------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Selected candidates will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Type:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contract &lt;br&gt;Position URL:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.tlwenterprise.com</content>
    <postId>CDC00685-7D0A-48C8-A5F4-70D0BB624959</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Oracle Application Specialist</title>
</post>
