<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Visual FoxPro Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Position Description&lt;br&gt;The Developer develops, designs, maintains and documents modules related to a Financial application. Designs, codes, tests and/or provides ongoing support of an application.. Provide suggestions to management regarding design improvements as they relate to assigned work units. Adhere to the project programming standards. Identify inconsistencies and errors present in design documents and communicate them to the proper parties for resolution. Assist testing specialists and less experienced co-workers as required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Duties&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Assist in the development of large client/server based application using Visual FoxPro 6/7 and Visual Basic/ADO. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 5 years experience with Visual FoxPro&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3 years experience with VB/ADO/DAO&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be an organized and meticulous individual that works and integrates well with a team &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must be able to work independently with little supervision and be able to lead others where necessary&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Object Orientated programming experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 2+ years of design and implementation on large Client Server based applications.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Able to produce clear technical design documentation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Skills&lt;br&gt;Platform: Windows 2000/NT and Win 95&lt;br&gt;Object Orientated Development: Java or C++ preferably.&lt;br&gt;Programming Languages: Visual Basic, Visual FoxPro&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Salary: CAD 75,000.00 to CAD 95,000.00 per year &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Contract&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Bal Bains&lt;br&gt;hr@webbglue.com&lt;br&gt;Webbglue Consulting&lt;br&gt;127 Pinemont Place NE&lt;br&gt;Calgary AB T1Y 1V9&lt;br&gt;Ph: (403)809-7945&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>CF162902-3B5E-4855-AFF7-EBD8C354C928</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Visual FoxPro Developer</title>
</post>
