<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>One of the TEKsystems media production clients is actively searching for a full-time Flash developer. In this newly created full time position, the successful candidate will work directly with the Technical Lead on the Interactive team. You will be a wizard in Flash, experienced at game and site programming, and have the ability to take an idea from concept to bug-free delivery, all with appropriate documentation. You will be an independent thinker and worker, with the ability to work with other people to create leading-edge content. You will be current in technology standards, continuously evaluating emerging opportunities and trends. Some of your major responsibilities include:&lt;br&gt;¿Integrate/implement projects in coordination with requirements, teams, stakeholders, schedule and budget. &lt;br&gt;¿Contribute to project ideas and utilize standard technology best practices. &lt;br&gt;¿Work intensively with Flash to implement design and functionality. &lt;br&gt;¿Work with video/audio (basic edits/conversion/integration/ interface.) &lt;br&gt;¿Produce and maintain clear documentation and file integrity. &lt;br&gt;¿Ensure each project is created and functions at a superior technical level, and that it meets or exceeds each project requirements. &lt;br&gt;¿Thorough testing of all projects, ability to prioritize work. &lt;br&gt;¿Work closely with the team on critical path for projects. &lt;br&gt;¿Participate in brainstorm and post-mortem sessions, aiming to improve performance and processes&lt;br&gt;Minimum Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;¿Expert understanding of ActionScript 3.0 and the Flash IDE. &lt;br&gt;¿Excellent understanding of XHTML / CSS / JavaScript. &lt;br&gt;¿Must have the ability to work in a collaborative, open environment. &lt;br&gt;¿Ability to lead technical strategies for complex projects. &lt;br&gt;Join TEKsystemsⓒ and get your career on the fast track. As one of North America's premiere technology staffing and services companies, we are passionate about deploying high-caliber IT and communications expertise. To satisfy our constant need for expertise, we actively seek talented technical professionals with all levels of information technology and communications skills. Because of our industry-specific focus, expertise, and connections, we can find you highly desirable positions you might not otherwise know about. From customized training and flexible hiring options to dedicated teams of recruiters working to find you the right opportunity, TEKsystems offers all the tools you need achieve to your long-term career goals.&lt;br&gt;Make your next career move with TEKsystems!&lt;br&gt;We respect your right to privacy. Your personal information is only collected, used and disclosed by TEksystems Canada Inc. in accordance with our Privacy Policy . Your personal information is never sold or leased to any external company.&lt;br&gt;TEKsystems Canada Inc. is an Allegis Group, Inc. company.&lt;br&gt;Contact: Arjun Asokakumar&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Fax: 416-342-5070&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D02D491D-C0E2-41F0-91F8-E0EAC9380478</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Flash Game Developer - TEKsystems</title>
</post>
