<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-IT Systems Administrator/Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;About Body Blue &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Body Blue is a contract manufacturer of personal care products such as shampoos, creams, and deodorants in Mississauga, Ontario. Body Blue is licensed to manufacture pharmaceuticals by Health Canada and specializes in OTC drug products in the personal care realm such as antiperspirants, topical analgesics and antibacterial products. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Body Blue is a rapidly growing and very entrepreneurial company. Body Blue operates out of 150,000 square feet in three facilities and we employ over 250 people. We are one of the leading contract manufacturers for deodorant and antiperspirant sticks and other health &amp; beauty aids for the major brands and retail organizations in North America and Internationally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently looking for an IT Systems Administrator/Developer to join our team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;- Daily administration of servers (file, print, email, database)&lt;br&gt;- Daily administration of network and PCs&lt;br&gt;- Maintenance of user accounts, passwords and security&lt;br&gt;- Purchase, installation, and support of all IT infrastructure&lt;br&gt;- Daily support of users on OS (Windows 95, 98, 2000, XP) and Office applications&lt;br&gt;- Establishment of written procedures and policies for IT administration (backups, disaster recovery)&lt;br&gt;- Preparation of technical documentation&lt;br&gt;- Planning, scheduling, and coordinating IT projects, including: Migration to SQLServer 2000 and Access 2002, Complete IT infrastructure for new building, Selection of server-based fax solution, Wireless networking&lt;br&gt;- Programming skills: Database programming (Access and/or SQLServer 2000), Visual Basic (VB) or Visual Basic for Applications (VBA)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills Required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Highly motivated and determined to succeed;&lt;br&gt;- Integrity: honest, ethical, trustworthy, reliable, responsible;&lt;br&gt;- Excellence: intelligent, good problem solver, intuitive, entrepreneurial, good communicator, enjoys a challenge, quick; can work with a minimum of supervision and direction.&lt;br&gt;- Experience: Strong background (3+ years) in IT Systems Administration&lt;br&gt;- Education: College diploma or university degree in related field&lt;br&gt;- Certification: Microsoft Certification an asset&lt;br&gt;- Servers: Windows NT 4.0, 2000; Exchange 5.5; IIS 5.0; SQLServer 2000&lt;br&gt;- Server Applications: Backup tools, Norton Anti-Virus&lt;br&gt;- Clients: Windows 95, 98, 2000, XP&lt;br&gt;- Client Applications: Office 97 and up&lt;br&gt;- Networks: TCP/IP, Ethernet&lt;br&gt;- Hardware: Dell Servers PCs, RAID controllers, tape backup devices, printers, hubs, switches, routers&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Career Opportunities&lt;br&gt;The IT Systems Administrator position is an excellent training opportunity to learn about the personal care products industry. Opportunities will exist for advancement into many areas of the company. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Human Resources&lt;br&gt;hr@bodyblue.com&lt;br&gt;Body Blue Inc&lt;br&gt;2280 Drew Road&lt;br&gt;Mississauga L5S 1B8&lt;br&gt;Fax: (905) 677-0311&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D13137FD-2CD8-43D2-94CA-16B84C0564D4</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-28T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-IT Systems Administrator/Developer</title>
</post>
