<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>John Ko</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I just forward my mail that I received today...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt; Hi,&lt;br&gt; Can I ask for your help?&lt;br&gt; I Found your info in Workopolis, and wondered if you&lt;br&gt; were looking for new opportunities in Embedded&lt;br&gt; Development...&lt;br&gt; If not, please keep my contact info for the future,&lt;br&gt; and pass this email on to a friend.&lt;br&gt; As thanks, please see the reference links at the&lt;br&gt; bottom of this email....&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 1. Three Software Designers: 05-5134&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Contract to&lt;br&gt; April 2006 (6+mo)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Montreal&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &amp;#8226; Tools to configure the network elements of&lt;br&gt; cellular and two way radio infrastructure &lt;br&gt; &amp;#8226; Software applications for public safety that&lt;br&gt; utilize the wireless communications networks. &lt;br&gt; &amp;#8226; Test and load tools for various network elements&lt;br&gt; (cellular and two way radio) &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Software projects are executed by teams ranging in&lt;br&gt; size from 2 to 30 engineers led by a Project&lt;br&gt; Manager. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Needed:&lt;br&gt; RTOS Software development (eg VxWorks, pSoS, Linux&lt;br&gt; derivatives)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Exposure to the use of low level troubleshooting&lt;br&gt; tools such as logic analyzers, oscilloscopes,&lt;br&gt; Labview etc.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Exposure to working on platforms such as RISC H/W&lt;br&gt; platform (PowerPC QUICC) and MPC 860. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 2. CDMA Software Designer: 05-4510&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Abstract: We have an immediate 6+ month contract&lt;br&gt; requirement with a telecommunications client in&lt;br&gt; Calgary for a CDMA Software Designer. Minimum&lt;br&gt; Competencies Required: 5+ years of software&lt;br&gt; development experience with 3+ years of C and C++ in&lt;br&gt; an embedded real-time OS. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 3. Kitchener Perm Job - Embedded Developer&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(up to&lt;br&gt; 80K)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Computer Science, Engineering, or similar &lt;br&gt; 5 years real experience in object oriented software&lt;br&gt; design using C++ &lt;br&gt; Excellent communication skills &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Desired Experience: &lt;br&gt; Java programming experience &lt;br&gt; Enterprise software experience, XML, SOAP, RMI, etc.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Image Processing/Machine Vision experience &lt;br&gt; Experience with Matrox Imaging Library &lt;br&gt; High-level experience with computer hardware &lt;br&gt; ---------------&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Please send a resume, or contact me for further&lt;br&gt; info.&lt;br&gt; I will reply to all submissions. Thanks for your&lt;br&gt; interest in this!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Thanks,&lt;br&gt; Chris Richmond&lt;br&gt; BScH, MCSE, MCDBA IT Recruiter&lt;br&gt; Ian Martin Ltd.&lt;br&gt; 905-815-1600 x 2276&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Reference site:&lt;br&gt; www.pc104.ca&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Jobs:&lt;br&gt; See More details for my current Embedded Job&lt;br&gt; Postings that I'm working on...&lt;br&gt; http://www.pc104.ca/oem/industrial-computer.asp&lt;br&gt; This is an RSS feed you can subscribe to!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Free Training:&lt;br&gt;www.brainbench.com/xml/bb/common/testcenter/freetests.xml&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D139B20F-DB41-4B63-A564-5B2874C51957</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-09-28T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Jobs for Embeded Software Developers</title>
</post>
