<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Directory Services Professional, GTA &lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Deloitte &amp; Touche is one of Canada's leading professional services firms, providing a full range of assurance and advisory, tax, and management consulting services through 6,600 people in more than 46 locations across the country.Our firm's professionals have been developing effective business solutions for Canadian and international companies for more than 150 years. We are dedicated to helping our clients and our people excel, and have been recognized as one of the Top 50 Companies to Work For in Canada by the Globe and Mail's Report on Business magazine. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deloitte &amp; Touche is part of Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu, a global leader in professional services with more than 95,000 people in over 140 countries. For more information, please visit our web site at www.deloitte.ca. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Enterprise Risk Services (ERS) practice is a global leader in helping clients manage risk from the boardroom to the Network. We provide a broad array of services that allow clients around the world to better measure and manage risk and control, and to enhance the reliability of systems and processes, throughout the enterprise. As the largest risk management consulting practice of its kind, we have thousands of dedicated ERS professionals across the globe whose core competencies provide the basis for a broad array of integrated services. Our ERS professionals help clients understand exposures, stabilize control processes, mitigate risks, clarify control responsibilities and maximize the benefits of technology, from implementation through post-production.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With over 130 professionals in Canada, located in our offices in Vancouver, Calgary, Edmonton, Winnipeg, Toronto, Ottawa and Montreal, our Security Services Group offers an extensive portfolio of e-Business strategies and applications, secure networking, infrastructure solutions, privacy services, website assurance and software implementation project support. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our iMAAP (Identity Management, Authentication, Authorization, Protection) service offering is focused on delivering enterprise security answers to our clients including architecting and implementing access management, provisioning and enterprise directory solutions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities: An iMAAP practitioner would be responsible for working on implementation project teams to help transform our clients?enterprise security environments. This would include architecting, designing and implementing market leading technologies and integrating them within the clients?existing security environment. This requires a solid grounding in security concepts/principles, fundamentals of IT (o/s, networking, etc), product knowledge, project execution/management experience and strong consulting skills. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A candidate should be able to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply information security principles, techniques and standards for network operating systems&lt;br&gt;Perform basic UNIX, NT, Novell and network (TCP/IP) programming &lt;br&gt;Provide technical guidance and manage all aspects of information protection architecture projects&lt;br&gt;Identify and resolve complex issues and develop innovative solutions for clients&lt;br&gt;Provide technical assistance relating to the design and implementation of security and controls of clients' networks&lt;br&gt;Develop good client relationships&lt;br&gt;Evaluate, counsel, mentor and provide feedback on the performance of others&lt;br&gt;Develop security policies and procedures &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bachelor's degree in a related field&lt;br&gt;CISSP, CISA, CFE, Microsoft Certification, CISCO Certification, or related IT certifications and/or courses&lt;br&gt;2-8 years of experience with directory services &lt;br&gt;Experience working as a part of a culturally diverse team&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expertise with programming languages including HTML, JAVA, C++, XML&lt;br&gt;Experience with .net or Websphere operating systems&lt;br&gt;Experience with Plumtree, Broadvision or other portal products and their integration with security&lt;br&gt;Directory Services experience, particularly with the administration of LDAP implementations&lt;br&gt;DCE installation administration or middleware experience&lt;br&gt;Object oriented application development experience&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of security products and processes for the middleware environment&lt;br&gt;Ability to present recommendations to technical and non-technical audiences&lt;br&gt;IT Project Management experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Experience:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Directory Products: Novell, Sun One, iPlanet, Active Directory&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access Management: Tivoli, Netegrity, Sun One, iPlanet&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Programming Development: .net, Websphere&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provisioning: BMC, Access 360&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Consulting Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills including both technical and business writing, documentation and presentation skills&lt;br&gt;Previous consulting firm experience is an asset&lt;br&gt;Travel required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We request that interested individuals engage in our online application process. Applications and/or resumes external to this process will not be accepted or acknowledged. No phone calls please.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: APJ2106&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D32C0C0D-B71D-4AEA-95B5-733C2D866424</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Directory Services Professional, GTA</title>
</post>
