<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Software Engineer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Opportunity:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Z-Tech (Canada) Inc. is growing and we are seeking a talented and motivated software engineer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About Us:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Z-Tech is focused on the development and marketing of innovative methods of detecting breast cancer. Z-Tech&amp;#47977; core group of engineers, software developers, physicians, financial and marketing personnel have long standing expertise and experience in the field of electromedical devices. Z-Tech has developed a revolutionary screening technology for the detection of breast cancer. Large scale clinical trials in the U.S., Canada and overseas will begin January 2003.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our temporary head office is located on Pape north of Danforth. Relocation is possible but our head office will remain in south-central Toronto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Design and develop a user interface and embedded software in Visual Basic, Access, and C, to be used in a next generation breast cancer detection device. &lt;br&gt;- Design Windows device drivers using the Windows XP DDK.&lt;br&gt;- Interface with hardware designers to design hardware/software interfaces.&lt;br&gt;- Design test programs and procedures for finished systems and components.&lt;br&gt;- Verify and validate existing designs and prototypes. &lt;br&gt;- Use MatLab and Excel to perform data-analysis and mathematical modeling. &lt;br&gt;- Develop and maintain an internal web-server and web-server applications.&lt;br&gt;- Administer configuration and change control activities using PVCS or a similar tool.&lt;br&gt;- Author user manuals, procedures, and other technical documentation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- B.Sc. Electrical/Computer Engineering&lt;br&gt;- Minimum of 2 years of experience&lt;br&gt;- Excellent spoken and written English&lt;br&gt;- Ability to solve problems independently and work with minimal supervision&lt;br&gt;- Understanding of software engineering principles (models, cycles, responsibilities) &lt;br&gt;- Working knowledge of: C, VB, VBA, Access. &lt;br&gt;- The following knowledge would an asset: TI 54x DSP, MatLab, Perl, Java, Apache Server, Linux, Digital and Analog Circuit Design. &lt;br&gt;- Knowledge of statistical and analytical methods, including finite-element-modeling and signal processing theory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's in it for you?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Competitive salary and benefits&lt;br&gt;- Contribute to a growing company doing important, exciting work&lt;br&gt;- Opportunity to work in a small fast-paced development environment in which your individual contribution will be recognized.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants in advance for their interest, however only qualified candidates will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Zoran Pavlovic&lt;br&gt;jobs@z-techinc.com&lt;br&gt;Z-Tech Inc.&lt;br&gt;983 Pape Avenue&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON M4K 3V6&lt;br&gt;Fax: 416 421-8180&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D33E77DA-08FE-45EE-9D24-D102C6467CB0</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software Engineer</title>
</post>
