<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>저에게 날아온 이메일입니다.&lt;br&gt;참조하시고 응모?&lt;br&gt;직장을 찾는 모든분...아자!!! &lt;br&gt;(아빠, 힘내세요!..우리가 있잔아요~~~)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Mainframe and Unix Operator &lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills: Mainframe &amp; Unix &lt;br&gt;Nice-to-Have Skills: &lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto &lt;br&gt;Duration: 6 month &lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary: Negotiable &lt;br&gt;Start Date: ASAP &lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;PRIMARY DUTIES: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. A) Starts up computer systems and schedules batch or on-line &lt;br&gt;applications according to defined standards and procedures. &lt;br&gt;B) Sets up job controls, input files, back-up files and output &lt;br&gt;files for jobs to be executed. &lt;br&gt;C) Monitors operation of on-line communications network and &lt;br&gt;initiates corrective action as required. &lt;br&gt;D) Monitors operation of all software packages and initiates &lt;br&gt;corrective action as required. &lt;br&gt;2. Executes jobs as per computer schedule and on request, as &lt;br&gt;determined by the Operations Manager. &lt;br&gt;3. Monitors jobs during execution and takes corrective action as &lt;br&gt;required for successful job completion as defined in Operating &lt;br&gt;Instructions. Escalates problem situations to appropriate &lt;br&gt;levels as required. &lt;br&gt;4. Records controls in respective logs. &lt;br&gt;5. Prints, bursts and decollates output as required. &lt;br&gt;6. Separates, identifies and puts output in I/O distribution area. &lt;br&gt;7. Performs housekeeping maintenance on all peripheral devices. &lt;br&gt;8. Records system activity with special reporting for system &lt;br&gt;problem/failures. &lt;br&gt;9. Calls Customer Support in the event of hardware failure, and &lt;br&gt;escalates to appropriate levels as required. &lt;br&gt;10. Maintains a neat and orderly equipment area as defined in &lt;br&gt;Operations Standards. &lt;br&gt;11. Maintains an orderly tape library. &lt;br&gt;12. Makes minor job control changes as required from time-to-time to &lt;br&gt;recover from production interruptions. &lt;br&gt;13. Receives computer forms and stocks same in storage area. &lt;br&gt;14. Maintains orderly files of Systems Department file copy of job &lt;br&gt;output. &lt;br&gt;15. Assists Applications Development staff in making minor JCL &lt;br&gt;changes or corrections from time-to-time in the absence of the &lt;br&gt;Operations Analyst, and assists with the processing of development Staff's testing. &lt;br&gt;16. Records and documents incidents in a detailed fashion to &lt;br&gt;support process and escalation. &lt;br&gt;17. Acts as service desk (3707) during off hours and weekends. &lt;br&gt;18. Other duties as requested or required. &lt;br&gt;II MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS: &lt;br&gt;1. University degree/College Diploma in related discipline. &lt;br&gt;2. Specialized training in computer operations. &lt;br&gt;3. Four years' work related experience. &lt;br&gt;4. Ability to work under minimum supervision. &lt;br&gt;5. Good oral and written communication skills. &lt;br&gt;6. Self-starter. &lt;br&gt;The environment is basically as follows: &lt;br&gt;1. IBM Mainframe Machine Type 2066 running Z/OS (300 MIPS) with multiple LPARS &lt;br&gt;2. IBM 3494 Tape Silo (RMM) &lt;br&gt;3. IBM 2105 DASD Storage Shark &lt;br&gt;4. 130 Servers (Rack Mounted) comprising of High Availability Clustered &lt;br&gt;Environments using both Unix Sun Solaris 7.0 and 8.0, Windows &lt;br&gt;2000 and Windows NT &lt;br&gt;5. Veritas Netbackup 5.0 for Server backups &lt;br&gt;6. TWS -OPC Job scheduler &lt;br&gt;7. DB2 &amp; CICS &lt;br&gt;8. INFOPAC &lt;br&gt;We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further. &lt;br&gt;Please submit your most recent resume to: Jean-Francois Bourgeois &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;jfb@procom.ca &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D433C13F-A030-473A-98A9-29941F8C2B09</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-06-28T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mainframe and Unix Operator</title>
</post>
