<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임 정숙</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>안녕하세요.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;제가 우연히 관련 사이트 리서치하다가 찾은 구인광고입니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;회사 사이트는 www.cyberplex.com이고&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;자세한 내용은 밑에 첨부했습니다.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;저랑 관련없는 회사이니 제게 reply 하지마시고 밑에있는 연락처(HR@Cyberplex.com)로 resume보내세요. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;그럼&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Luck ;-)&lt;br&gt;*************************************************&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to be a part of an environment characterized by diversity, entrepreneurial spirit and fun, we'd love for you to experience Cyberplex from the inside.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Send your resume to HR@Cyberplex.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software Architect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;The Software Architect is accountable for:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Ensuring that the technology architecture of the solutions designed within the project meets CX standards of excellence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Software Architect assumes a leadership role on a project basis working with the Development Manager/Team Lead and the Project Manager to meet client expectations and to deliver quality solutions to the client.&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Extensive experience in building business solutions often focused on a specific skill area such as software architecture, Java or Microsoft expertise, etc. It is also possible that the architect has broader but less specific skill depth and contributes to projects across a spectrum of technical specialties. &lt;br&gt;- Good understanding of Object Oriented Programming theory, techniques, application and modeling design tools (i.e. Rational Rose). &lt;br&gt;- Ability to translate business requirements into technical specifications &lt;br&gt;- Extensive knowledge of software development life cycle &lt;br&gt;- Strong knowledge of enterprise level performance and scalability issues at the software, database, network, security, and hardware levels &lt;br&gt;- Ability to contribute to the evaluation of performance of other team members &lt;br&gt;- Ability to translate strategy into action plans &lt;br&gt;- Able to coach, mentor and motivate team members often in partnership with the development team lead &lt;br&gt;- Able to contribute to resource allocation discussions &lt;br&gt;- Ability to assess performance of team members &lt;br&gt;- Ability to participate in the recruitment processing by interviewing potential candidates &lt;br&gt;- Ability to communicate with clients in both technical and non-technical interactions. &lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Certifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Degree in Computer Science/Engineering or equivalent experience.&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Experience:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;several years of software development experience</content>
    <postId>D6171C00-D268-46BC-BF6B-046A108B6571</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Job Postings for Software Architect</title>
</post>
