<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>CLIENT ACCOUNTS COORDINATOR (for Web Projects)&lt;br&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Client Accounts Coordinator (for Web&lt;br&gt;Projects)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Description&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To start, this junior position will be responsible for coordinating&lt;br&gt;projects for all areas of the Web Services Department: Web Design, SEO/Online&lt;br&gt;Marketing, Website Migrations, and Web Maintenance. This role will act as the&lt;br&gt;gatekeeper for all web projects to ensure the full life cycle of the project is&lt;br&gt;managed properly, from billing, provisioning/order fulfillment, to ongoing&lt;br&gt;account management. The individual occupying this role MUST have superior&lt;br&gt;documentation and organizational skills backed up expert Microsoft Excel&lt;br&gt;and Word skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Career Path: As the Web Services Department grows further, this position&lt;br&gt;will have the opportunity to branch out into either a Web Designer role or a&lt;br&gt;Web Accounts Management role.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Type:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full-time, permanent, salary +bonus, benefits. Some occasional extra&lt;br&gt;hours will be expected for time sensitive projects and deadlines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a&lt;br&gt;client facing role but will also require daily internal communications and&lt;br&gt;coordination as well:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coordinate and track all web projects,&lt;br&gt;contracts, and orders in CRM system and/or Excel spreadsheets&lt;br&gt;Work with Billing Team to ensure all orders&lt;br&gt;are billed accurately and on time&lt;br&gt;Work with the Technical Provisioning/Order&lt;br&gt;Fulfillment Team to ensure service is delivered according to contracts&lt;br&gt;Facilitate the provisioning of project work by&lt;br&gt;following up with customers on outstanding items that may be impacting the&lt;br&gt;delivery of their service&lt;br&gt;Manage customer accounts through daily&lt;br&gt;email/phone communications to the clients to provide status updates&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications, Skills and&lt;br&gt;Experience Required&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUST&lt;br&gt;HAVE:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Web knowledge: must have a&lt;br&gt;very strong understanding of web concepts and web technologies: web&lt;br&gt;design, online marketing, search engine optimization, domain&lt;br&gt;registrations, etc.)&lt;br&gt;Account Management skills:&lt;br&gt;previous client account management experience&lt;br&gt;Administrative skills:&lt;br&gt;previous role as a Provisioning Coordinator would be preferred&lt;br&gt;Documentation skills: must&lt;br&gt;be able to document client information, project information, ticketing&lt;br&gt;information, invoice numbers, and dollar values with 100% accuracy&lt;br&gt;Communications skills: must&lt;br&gt;be able to communicate technical information comfortably and clearly&lt;br&gt;between multiple parties to effectively&lt;br&gt;coordinate technical detail to ensure projects are delivered as expected&lt;br&gt;and within scope&lt;br&gt;Must be extremely organized&lt;br&gt;Overall technical understanding of website&lt;br&gt;design and development&lt;br&gt;Must be able to work under tight deadlines and&lt;br&gt;competing priorities&lt;br&gt;Multi-tasking skills along with high&lt;br&gt;efficiency and high productivity output a MUST&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICE TO HAVE (Having these skills will make&lt;br&gt;this role easier but is not necessary to perform the role):&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graphic design skills (ie.&lt;br&gt;Photoshop)&lt;br&gt;Technical familiarity with&lt;br&gt;other Open Source CMS applications, Flash design skills, Photoshop&lt;br&gt;(graphic design skills)&lt;br&gt;Previous experience working with a variety of&lt;br&gt;web sites and setting up email accounts&lt;br&gt;Technical expertise supporting websites&lt;br&gt;developed with any or all of the following: HTML, PHP, Perl, MySQL,&lt;br&gt;.htaccess, ASP, ASP.NET, MSSQL, web form configurations, etc.&lt;br&gt;Technical expertise with domain setup and&lt;br&gt;administration: registrations, transfers, DNS records, etc along with&lt;br&gt;familiarity with a variety of Control Panels an asset.&lt;br&gt;Technical familiarity with setting up and&lt;br&gt;configuring Open source CMS applications (ie. Joomla, Wordpress,&lt;br&gt;osCommerce, Zencart, phpBB, etc.)&lt;br&gt;Some code debugging skills along with advanced&lt;br&gt;web skills including cron and SSL an asset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our ideal candidate will be a dependable, self-motivated, efficient top&lt;br&gt;performer that brings in their "A" game EVERY DAY and never settles&lt;br&gt;for second best. You are customer focused and driven to exceed expectations for&lt;br&gt;every task you perform. You are more than willing and able to put in extra&lt;br&gt;hours and extra efforts to get the job done right and on time. If you believe&lt;br&gt;you are this candidate, send us your updated resume demonstrating your recent&lt;br&gt;accomplishments along with some ideas on how you think you may be able&lt;br&gt;contribute to our Team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT: When&lt;br&gt;applying, please state your minimum base salary requirements. We thank&lt;br&gt;all interested candidates but only qualified candidates will be contacted. A&lt;br&gt;COVER LETTER MUST BE INCLUDED.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D6297D18-D88F-4E2B-B598-03A3DD768582</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-31T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Joomla Junior</title>
</post>
