<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Applications Developer 2&lt;br&gt;Location&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;000Z Steeles Tor&lt;br&gt;Organization Name&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SB20 - Oracle On Demand - Development&lt;br&gt;Department Description&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Oracle CRM On Demand is a hosted CRM product from Oracle Corporation.Oracle On Demand applications offer industry-leading hosting, award-winning security, and the power and scalability of Oracle Database solutions. Oracle CRM On Demand is a comprehensive, strategic CRM solution that goes far beyond any other software as a service offering to help customers bring clarity to to their sales processes; build loyal, long-term customer relationships; accelerate productivity; boost call center efficiency; and derive comprehensive, real-time customer intelligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brief Description&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Oracle Corporation Canada is looking for a highly motivated Applications Developer to actively expand our development teams in the Toronto, Canada. The Oracle On Demand team develops high performance, scalable, web and database server components used by the Oracle CRM OnDemand Product (www.crmondemand.com). Typical areas of focus include Web UI framework using Oracle Application Server, J2EE, C++ Business Objects and Oracle Siebel Tools. Teamwork and solid written and verbal communication skills are of utmost importance, as this group works closely with Product Marketing and other software development teams in the USA, Canada, Ireland, and India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work with the Product Marketing group to identify product specifications&lt;br&gt;Design product features, create high-level and detailed design documents, and conduct design reviews&lt;br&gt;Participate in development projects and provide technical guidance to other software developers&lt;br&gt;Implement new product features using C++, Java, JavaScript , HTML and Oracle Siebel Tools in a Windows environment&lt;br&gt;Work with various development teams to ensure various components are well integrated and meet performance and scalability specifications&lt;br&gt;Enhance and maintain existing product capabilities&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 to 3 years of work experience in enterprise software product development&lt;br&gt;Bachelors or Masters degree in Computer Science or Engineering is also required&lt;br&gt;Experience in C++ or Java is required&lt;br&gt;Experience in SQL is required&lt;br&gt;Experience in OOP/OOD and Data Modeling is required&lt;br&gt;Experience in Internet/Web-based application development is required&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of D/HTML, JavaScript, Java, Servlet, J2EE and XML is highly desirable&lt;br&gt;Knowledge and experience in J2EE deployment and best practices is desirable&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of one of the following RDBMS is highly desirable: DB2, Oracle, MS SQL Server&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Oracle Siebel Tools is desirable&lt;br&gt;Proven application of sound software development practices during all phases of the development cycle: specification, design, implementation, test/debug, documentation, rollout, maintenance&lt;br&gt;Strong track record in delivering complex, high quality software to production users in a timely fashion&lt;br&gt;Must demonstrate the ability to work independently and in a team environment&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detailed Description&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;As a member of the software development division, you will perform detailed design based on provided high level design specifications. Assist in system planning, scheduling and implementation. Build enhancements (including new product features) and resolve bugs. Build and execute unit test and unit test plans. Review integration and regression test plans created by QA. Interact with QA and porting analysts about problems in the code.&lt;br&gt;Job Requirements&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Duties and tasks are standard with some variation; displays understanding of roles, processes and procedures. Performs moderately complex problem solving with assistance and guidance in understanding and applying company policies and processes. Preferred Qualifications: BS degree or equivalent experience relevant to functional area. 1 year of software development or related experience.&lt;br&gt;Additional Details&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Location&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toronto,CA&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D85FC247-6234-4372-979E-4E35C1E51BE3</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Oracle Applications Developer </title>
</post>
