<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Snapshot&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario (Map it! ) &lt;br&gt;Employee Type: Full-Time Employee&lt;br&gt;Manages Others: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Job Type: Information Technology&lt;br&gt;Experience: Not Specified&lt;br&gt;Post Date: 04/03/2010 Contact Information&lt;br&gt;Contact: Ramy Morsy&lt;br&gt;Ref ID: 2229941&lt;br&gt;Description&lt;br&gt;ARE YOU PASSIONATE ABOUT FLASH DEVELOPMENT?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now is your chance to join the Ganz team that has brought you such products as Webkinz and Webkinz Jr. You can be a part of developing new adventures !&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now is your chance to join the creative team that has brought these vibrant worlds to life. Ganz is seeking talented and motivated people with a proven love of online entertainment for these positions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLASH DEVELOPERS (Intermediate/Senior)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designing, developing, and unit testing of Flash based Internet applications and games, utilizing Object Oriented ActionScript.&lt;br&gt;Ensuring that best-practices are followed and that code is optimized in order to ensure that applications are operating as efficiently as possible on a high traffic websites.&lt;br&gt;Participating in the software development process from design to release.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience in developing Flash or ActionScript and/or Flash based games.&lt;br&gt;Development experience with Flash, CSS and XML.&lt;br&gt;Experience with use of relational databases (MYSQL, Oracle, SQL Server).&lt;br&gt;Experience with source control (eg SVN) software is an asset.&lt;br&gt;Experience with multi-use environments and high traffic websites.&lt;br&gt;Strong understanding of software development life cycle.&lt;br&gt;Strong analytical and problem solving skills.&lt;br&gt;Excellent written and verbal communications skills.&lt;br&gt;Detail-oriented, well organized, quick learner with very strong technical aptitude and the ability to work concurrently on multiple projects.&lt;br&gt;Interested candidates are invited to forward resumes by email to (see below).&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D873F088-A586-470B-850F-93548F314B68</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-05T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Flash Developer -GANZ</title>
</post>
