<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>D Park</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>D Park</author>
            <date>2008-12-12T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>If you need more information about this position, please call Dave at 416-607-4661</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>- The incumbent must have an excellent working knowledge in the following operating systems and technologies: Sun Solaris, Sun hardware, NIS, DNS, LDAP, NFS, Weblogic,Websphere application server, Websphere MQ, Tomcat, Sun One Web server, Web proxy, Citrix on Unix and Veritas products (Volume Manager, File System, Netbackup, Clustering),monitoring tools, shell scripting, and Tidal Job Scheduler would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;- Working knowledge of the following databases is an asset: Oracle, Sybase.&lt;br&gt;- Working knowledge of LAN/WAN environments and protocols.&lt;br&gt;- Requires a minimum of 5 years job related experience and possesses analytical and proactive problem solving skills. Expert understanding in area of specialty.&lt;br&gt;- Ability to work with non-technical users.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Skills&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Requires post-secondary education with focus on Computer Science, Math or Engineering disciplines.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Resolution and Prevention of Problems&lt;br&gt;- Presented with system level and application problems on mission critical systems requiring immediate resolution, thus ensuring systems are operational according to agreed upon service level agreements and that they have a high degree of integrity and reliability. Often, resolution determination requires interaction with service vendors. Considerable effort is placed into determining, developing and delivering procedures to protect production environment from unplanned outages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide Technical Assistance to Users&lt;br&gt;- Establishes system scope and objectives. Develops practical manual or automated procedures to solve complex problems. Prepares detailed specifications for programs, analyses and revises existing system logic deficiencies, oversees all phases of the technical system design and will advice, check and direct systems programs onto the correct technical system design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Systems Administration and New Projects&lt;br&gt;- Perform system administration tasks associated with environment of specialization for the development, UAT and production environments as well supporting production code implementation. Provide training on specific environment to Operations, Network and Development Departments as required. New projects could include applications such as central back up for applications and database application monitoring tools or high-speed restoration software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Control Access, Ensure Security and Contingency Planning&lt;br&gt;- Ongoing customization and maintenance of system access facilities to ensure and enforce strict security of financial environment. Plan, implement and test contingency plans for various hardware and software environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;System Monitoring and Updates&lt;br&gt;- During the course of the year, applications are monitored and statistical information regarding resource usage is compiled. Recommendations are put forward to management for capacity planning and system upgrades where resource constraints are identified to ensure that a reliable production environment is maintained.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Group Involvement&lt;br&gt;- Participate in user groups to gain information on other user's project successes and/or failures. Required to keep up to date with technological breakthroughs and trends in field of specialization.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Christopher Bieniek&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Manager, Staffing &amp; Recruitment&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Branch/Department:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Staffing &amp; Planning - Central Canada&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Mailing Address:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 56846 &lt;br&gt;44 King Street West&lt;br&gt;21st Floor&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;Canada M5H1H1 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;E-Mail Address:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; chris.bieniek@scotiabank.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Phone:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 416-866-4586&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;Fax:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 416-866-3837&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D9036A67-FD02-4BE7-8F55-FE4751398448</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>BNS: Systems Support Specialist (Unix)</title>
</post>
