<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>alexna2003@yahoo.com &amp;lt;-- 이쪽으로 이력서 보내주세요. &lt;br&gt;직장에서 체용되면 저에게 소개비 준다고 합니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;============================================= &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Solutions Architect - SAP/PeopleSoft/Oracle eBusiness &lt;br&gt;Location: Waterloo, ON &lt;br&gt;Job Code: 07TBH136 &lt;br&gt;# of openings: 1 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description &lt;br&gt;Application Lifecycle Management in an SAP World &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This role presents is a unique opportunity within the MKS R&amp;D organization. We are looking for someone that has considerable experience working in the trenches of packaged application design, development and deployment, struggling with the challenges of coordinating the activities of large teams of developers. If you have thought to yourself that there has to be a better and more efficient way of managing the development and deployment of those solutions, this is your chance to be at the center of that revolution. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This role is well suited to a senior developer who has experience in many phases of development, from requirements to design to implementation. Hands on experience working within an SAP development environment is essential. First hand experience with project management, assess project risks and an ability to communicate with project stakeholders all form part of the portfolio of skills required for this job. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what we need on the technical side: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Senior software developer/architect &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; SAP,Oracle eBusiness or PeopleSoft solution development and deployment &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience with other packaged applications (e.g. PeopleSoft, Oracle eBusiness) &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Java and other OO languages &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Database design and development &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Solutions design and modeling &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s what we’re looking for in soft skills: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Creative and entrepreneurial nature &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Desire to find a better solution to a presented problem &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Project leadership, team leadership &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Project management &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Likes to switch between high level strategic view and down and dirty coding &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Comments </content>
    <postId>DA2CB76D-7CBA-45CB-8E32-6CE21B3377BA</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Solutions Architect - SAP/PeopleSoft/Oracle eBusiness</title>
</post>
