<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Genesys Conferencing is the world's leading conferencing specialist with over 17,000 customers in 18 countries throughout the world. We are seeking a Quality Assurance Team Lead and a Quality Assurance Analyst to continue our expansion of our Toronto Network Operations Center.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidates will work independently in a small group to develop, implement and refine quality assurance processes and procedures for the Genesys Meeting Center system (GenMC). This is a new group and its responsibility relates to system testing, integration testing and deployment signoff of GenMC and associated systems prior to deployment into production IDCs. The group will also be responsible for the monitoring of the overall quality of the GenMC production systems. The candidates are expected to accommodate the deployment release schedule (which will involve weekends and evenings).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Tasks:&lt;br&gt;- Coordinate with various internal departments to capture their requirements with respect to quality assurance testing parameters and scope&lt;br&gt;- Develop a set of quality assurance testing procedures and processes&lt;br&gt;- Ensure appropriate standards are adhered to&lt;br&gt;- Test and report results through established systems&lt;br&gt;- Analyze daily production performance results&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills and Qualifications (must have):&lt;br&gt;- A degree or diploma in computer technology&lt;br&gt;- At least 3 years eperience in the field (the Team Lead must have at least 1 year experience with direct reports)&lt;br&gt;- Strong analytical and reporting skills&lt;br&gt;- Excellent interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br&gt;- Excellent hands-on system administration and user skills on Windows 95/98, NT, and Windows 2000&lt;br&gt;- Positive attitude and willingness to learn&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skills and qualifications (nice to have):&lt;br&gt;- MCSE designation&lt;br&gt;- Experience with C/C++, HTML and Java&lt;br&gt;- Microsoft SQL experience&lt;br&gt;- Experience with load balancing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Darlene Cook&lt;br&gt;darlene.cook@genesys.com&lt;br&gt;Genesys Conferencing&lt;br&gt;304 The East Mall, Suite 800&lt;br&gt;Toronto Ontario M9B 6E2&lt;br&gt;Ph: (416) 207-0605&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>DBBD4284-56DB-4678-8194-4C506D40BEE4</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Quality Assurance Team Lead/Analyst</title>
</post>
