<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>하수용</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>지역은 몬트리올입니다 지원해주시기 바랍니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOBILE CLIENT SOFTWARE DEVELOPER &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FirstIn Wireless Technology is expanding and we are seeking highly motivated and enthusiastic candidates who are client focused, performance driven, and deliver timely quality work, in return for our high expectations, we offer an open and respectful atmosphere, competitive salary and benefits, as well are rewarding career opportunities &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mobile Client Software Developer will join the OUR Development Team to design software for the FirstIn Wireless Technology projects. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Responsabilities : &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software development for mobile devices &lt;br&gt;Analyze requirements &lt;br&gt;Interface with device vendors, carriers, and portals to integrate technology &lt;br&gt;Involvement in conception, implementation, and product launch &lt;br&gt;Unit testing, Bug fixing, Documentation &lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minimum of 5 years experience of software development using Java (preferably J2ME), C/C++ &lt;br&gt;Experience with data communications, protocols, and embedded environments &lt;br&gt;Experience using mobile environments such as MIDP, BREW, Symbian, Smart Phone, Pocket PC, win32 programming &lt;br&gt;Experience with mobile technologies such as SMS, MMS, GPRS, GSM CDMA, etc &lt;br&gt;Software design experience with products for telecommunications operators &lt;br&gt;We would like to thank all applicants who apply, however, only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FirstIn Wireless Technology is an equal opportunity employer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Submit your resume to: groundwalker@firstinwireless.com or career@firstinwireless.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>DBEEB39D-9F87-438A-9DC9-8328537E3305</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Mobile Client Software Developer</title>
</post>
