<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Brendan</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello Brendan,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was nice speaking with you. I have reviewed your CV. I have a good PERMANENT position that might closely match your skills. It is for a very large company with a great working environment. They are looking for someone with great J2EE skills and good communications skills. I will look out for contract positions for you since you are looking for contracts only.&lt;br&gt;Here's the job description. Please forward it liberally to your Java/J2EE associates and JAVA community that might be interested in the position. They can contact me directly if they like. I have many other positions. Thank you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have enclosed details for you below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Programmer/Analyst/Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills: J2EE (5 years); WEBSPHERE (3 years); DB2 (3 years); WSAD (3 years); UML (3 years); JMS (3 years); Nice-to-Have Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Scarborough (Ontario, Canada)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duration: Permanent&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: Around $75,000 per year&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start Date: ASAP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Conduct initial analysis of user requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Design codes and test programmes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; provide guidance and direction to several project team members&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATIONS / SKILLS:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Degree in computer sciences&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 4 years minimum experience in J2EE design and development&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 5 years experience in Java development including JSP, Servlet and EJB&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 5 years experience n web-based application design and development (HTTP,HTTPS,HTML/DHTML, Javascript etc.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3 years experience in WebSphere v.5 Network deployment model including configuration and deployment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3 years of WSAD 5+ experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3 years’ experience with JMS MQ series including MQ manager set-up and configuration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 5 years’ experience with JDBS and standard SQL, 4 years’ DB2 experience (including DB2 connector, Command Centre, Command Line Processor)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 4 years’ experience implementing MVC model using Apache’s Struts framework&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3 years’ experience with Unit test framework, and software Build and deployment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3 years’ software configuration experience (Source Code Control, including CVS etc.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 5 years’ experience in Application Integration (e.g. Single Sign On, cross platform communication) &amp;#8226; 3 years’ UML experience (Diagrams and Tools e.g. Rational Rose/Together)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3 years’ experience in test cycle (test case design, stress/load testing, regression testing) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Experience in Mainframe, Lotus Notes and Content Management Systems, specifically Vignette, are definite assets &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Ability to manage 2-3 projects concurrently and shift priorities as required &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Ability to provide guidance and direction to 2-4 team members and vendors &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Experience in all phases of project lifecycle and documentation of same &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Good communication skills and ability to interact effectively with users and ISD management &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Ability to manage requirements against deliverables in terms of quality and tight timelines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kind regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodney Yap&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Recruiter&lt;br&gt;Direct Line: 647-288-2545&lt;br&gt;Toll Free: 1-800-461-4878 x 324&lt;br&gt;Fax: 416-483-8102&lt;br&gt;rodneyy@procom.ca</content>
    <postId>DE0B61C5-A12F-4C6F-BCBE-4CD7197D8C6A</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. J2EE developer, Perm, Scarborough</title>
</post>
