<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>K&amp;C Tech</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>joseph@knctech.com / 604-629-0799 로 연락주세요...&lt;br&gt;친구분 추천해 주실분 있으시면 이메일로 Resume를 보내주세요...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;===========================================================&lt;br&gt;K&amp;C Tech. is rapidly growing importing and marketing company located in Vancouver, British Columbia. We deal with importing computer accessories and peripherals from the Pacific Rim and market them across North America. Over the past year while most companies have seen a decline in sales and have been down sizing; K&amp;C Tech. has seen exponential growth. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: &lt;br&gt;Customer Service &amp; Product Sourcing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description: &lt;br&gt;We are looking for a Korean/English Bilingual who can handle customer service as well as product sourcing relating to computer products. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;(1) Must be Fluent in both English and Korean.&lt;br&gt;(2) A strong background in consumer service or tech support. &lt;br&gt;(3) Experience in computer related product sourcing would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;(4) Excellent oral and written communication skills. &lt;br&gt;(5) Strong computer skills (pc and windows operating systems)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The work environment at K&amp;C Tech. is stimulating, emphasizing collaboration and personal growth. For more information about our company or our niche product called the 'Universal Smart Drive', please visit our websites: &lt;br&gt;www.knctech.com, www.universalsmartdrive.net and www.itave.com . &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are interested in pursuing this opportunity, send us your Resume to joseph@knctech.com or fax to (604) 629-0805. We thank all candidates who choose to apply, however, only those selected for an interview will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>DEBF0A71-68BD-451E-B01D-C92387894507</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-12-19T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Korean/English Bilingual Product Sourcing (computer)</title>
</post>
