<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Intermediate Database Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are headquartered in Toronto, Canada, and are ranked the #1 Internet Services Business in the World, and the 4th fastest growing franchise Worldwide. We have established ourselves as the world’s leading Internet Services Franchise whose systems are used by over 700 franchisees in 87 countries around the world. We deliver thousands of e-business solutions to small and medium sized businesses annually.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications include:&lt;br&gt;- Year(s) of Experience: Minimum of 4-6 years&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Tasks and Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Supervisor of Development, the successful candidate will be responsible for:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; The ideal candidate will join a team of analysts/developers in designing, creating, and maintaining the Company’s e-Business Internet-based systems. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; The position requires the candidate to be part of team of analysts/developers to design and build a variety of database objects for the Company’s various e-Business, transactional, web-based systems. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; We are looking for an Intermediate Database/Web Developer with a strong emphasis on Microsoft technologies. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Proven achievements in web architecture, design and development for both external and intranet sites&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Proven track record of design, development and deployment of transactional, Internet solutions for the MS platform. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Knowledge of Database Development Concepts is critical including:&lt;br&gt;o Must have strong RDBMS skills with MS SQL2000&lt;br&gt;o Solid experience in logical and physical database design. &lt;br&gt;o Strong knowledge of SQL coding. &lt;br&gt;o Mastery of Stored Procedure design and development (SQL and Transact SQL).&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Must have strong ASP, VB Script, .Net, and IIS skills.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Knowledge of OO programming concepts is required.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent communication skills.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent analytical skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Compensation: $50K-65K/year plus benefits with room for advancement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please email your resume and cover letter as Word attachments to: career11@torontohomeoffice.com&lt;br&gt;Only applicants residing within driving distance of the Greater Toronto Area with be considered.&lt;br&gt;Only those qualified candidates will be contacted for interviews.&lt;br&gt;Please serious enquiries only.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>DF146D4C-DA78-46C8-96B9-62C67267EF26</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Intermediate Database Developer</title>
</post>
