<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior Software Developer/Team Lead :. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Status:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Software Developer/Team Leader&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gavel and Gown Software is a private Canadian company engaged in the development of the world leading practice management software for lawyers. We are currently looking for a dynamic, energetic and resourceful individual with excellent problem solving and planning. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting to the Development Manager, the successful candidate must be an excellent technical expert and a natural leader. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Analyze product specifications and develop and document technical designs that meet requirements&lt;br&gt;-Implement high quality code following general specifications&lt;br&gt;-Provide technical guidance and assistance to team members&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;-Computer Science or related field degree.&lt;br&gt;-Minimum two years supervising a team of senior and intermediate software developers&lt;br&gt;-Minimum 10 years of Software Development experience&lt;br&gt;-Proven database-driven and client-server application development experience &lt;br&gt;-Strong application development experience using Visual Basic&lt;br&gt;-Web development expertise &amp;#8211; ASP, Scripting languages, HTML/DHTML, XML &lt;br&gt;-Ability to prioritize and handle multiple tasks at the same time&lt;br&gt;-Familiar with the software development cycle&lt;br&gt;-Ability to work within and meet deadlines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please apply on-line. Fax submissions will NOT be accepted.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;....................................................................................................................................................................&lt;br&gt; Contact Information :.&lt;br&gt;Gavel &amp; Gown Software Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E02660BA-51AD-46C2-9E69-F5BCE8C5F9A8</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Software Developer/Team Lead :.</title>
</post>
