<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Senior Software Developer&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overview&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OpenCola, Inc. requires senior software developers for P2P community based discovery software, written in C++ and running on Win32 and Linux platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our office is informal, dynamic and diverse. The workday starts with our company song, Brick House by the Commodores. Not everyone sings well. We also have unlimited java for employees who are caffeine dependent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Experience/Knowledge&lt;br&gt;= A minimum of five years of professional development experience &lt;br&gt;= Expertise in C++&lt;br&gt;= Expert in object oriented design methodologies &lt;br&gt;= Good understanding of software engineering processes &lt;br&gt;= Capable of writing clear and complete technical specifications &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Desirable Experience/Knowledge&lt;br&gt;= Experience building production level commercial software &lt;br&gt;= Familiarity with P2P architectures &lt;br&gt;= Understanding of networking protocols and technologies &lt;br&gt;= Working knowledge of XML, XSLT&lt;br&gt;= Special consideration for anyone who plays the violin &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personality&lt;br&gt;= Must take initiative and ensure success for all responsibilities &lt;br&gt;= Must be willing to shower and use soap on a regular basis &lt;br&gt;= Must be able to work within established practices, but challenge them when they don't make sense, especially any movement to bring back Atari &lt;br&gt;= Able to work within a group by cooperating on designs and implementations &lt;br&gt;= Able to focus on a task until completed &lt;br&gt;= Reliable and well organized &lt;br&gt;= Must be able to communicate well and understand the value of communication, in a known language &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Send resume to: jobs@opencola.com&lt;br&gt;NO calls please!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E213B251-0A1A-465F-A9BD-8F4AAFA85183</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>CA-ON-Markham-Senior Software Developer</title>
</post>
