<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Java Software Developer&lt;br&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;The Applications group of Alcatel-Lucent develops innovative solutions for both service providers and enterprises. Service providers use the Group’s solutions to create innovative and profitable products for consumers, such as digital home management and rich media applications that span mobile and connected devices. Through service providers as well as through direct channels, the Group enables enterprises to deploy applications to transform their customer service capabilities across multiple channels including internet, e-mail, phone and mobile.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The common focus is developing software that enriches the personal communications experience for people. Currently, there is an opportunity for a Java Software Developer to to join the Applications Platform team.&lt;br&gt;You will be a key developer in the team responsible for developing the next generation of Alcatel-Lucent's telco-grade platforms/Framework. You will work with a global team to develop software. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your responsibilities will cover all aspects of software development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excellent knowledge of Object Orientated concepts and design&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Expert level knowledge of Java&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excellent communication skills, both verbal and written&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Superior problem solving skills&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Familiarity with Linux or other UNIX flavors&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Strong team player&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Passion for delivering high quality software, on time&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience working with high performance, complex, multi-threaded Java applications&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering, Computer Science, or related discipline with a top notch academic record&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excellent verbal and written English communication skills&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Desired:&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience with Eclipse, JAIN, JSLEE, J2EE&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Understanding of distributed reliable computing&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience with XML and related technologies&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Understanding of databases and related concepts: SQL, Object-Relational Mapping, Oracle&lt;br&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Unit testing, Code inspection and other development best practices&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Please note that applicants who have been selected will be asked to write a short aptitude test prior to interviewing.&lt;br&gt;Please apply online&lt;br&gt;http://www.alcatel-lucent.com/wps/portal/careers , Search under Canada jobs and job number APPL-100603-01R</content>
    <postId>E2A9C603-BF28-4733-B7D2-4AADFA671C17</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Software Developer</title>
</post>
