<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Programmer / Analyst :. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Status:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Salary:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;CAD 50,000.00 to CAD 70,000.00 per year&lt;br&gt;plus profit sharing and benefits&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Reference Code:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Venture Programmer&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Job Location: Etobicoke&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venture Steel is the fastest growing steel service center in Canada. The company's commitment to utilizing advanced integrated technology in its manufacturing operations and ongoing I.T. development is a key component to the organization's success. The company has recently installed (Jan 2002) a new ERP system, custom developed for the steel industry. The company is committed to investing in the resources required to continuously enhance this system to meet the company's evolving business model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venture Steel needs a strong programmer/analyst to join the IT department to further enhance this system. This individual will be required to play a key role in a dynamic and innovative I.T. environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key skills required:&lt;br&gt;- a minimum of 5 years programming experience&lt;br&gt;- a good knowledge of all Microsoft technologies&lt;br&gt;- experience with Visual Basic 6.0 and ASP on multi-tiered platform based on COM+&lt;br&gt;- extensive experience with SQL Server 2000&lt;br&gt;- Crystal Reports and MS Office as reporting tools&lt;br&gt;- an ability to work both independantly and as part of a team occasionally under pressure&lt;br&gt;- good communication skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preference will be given to candidates with manufacturing and ERP systems experience.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;....................................................................................................................................................................&lt;br&gt; Contact Information :.&lt;br&gt;Venture Steel Inc.&lt;br&gt;60 Disco Rd&lt;br&gt;Etobicoke ON M9W 1L8&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E37EC06E-888F-41CA-A4DC-FD350293135A</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Programmer / Analyst :. from monster.ca</title>
</post>
