<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Java Web Programmer (Contract)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position requires you to create the necessary programmatic code to achieve the features and functions of a website based on requirements given to you by the project lead. You will be expected to create reliable and readable code that is complete, bug free and measures up to our quality standards. In addition, you will be required to interact with other team members to provide status, communicate capabilities and limitations, and acquire additional information necessary to complete your project. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position is part of the Technical Development Group, and you would be reporting to the Technical Lead for the project. The Technical Development Group is responsible for the architecture, logic, testing, and deployment aspects of all applications created. You would also interact with the Graphic and Project Management groups as they work on the particular project. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills: &lt;br&gt;?Proven ability to communicate effectively about technical issues, both written and orally &lt;br&gt;?2 years application programming experience in Java &lt;br&gt;?4 years programming experience &lt;br&gt;?2 years working with web site projects &lt;br&gt;?1 year experience interacting with a SQL based database &lt;br&gt;?Able to solve coding problems independently and innovatively &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With your resume you must supply source code to fulfill the following request. You will not be considered for the position without supplying this additional item along with your resume:&lt;br&gt;Making use of JSP create an interface that would allow a user to create, edit, and then display a set of nested tags without the use of HTML in the forms. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snap Media Corp. is a web application and creative development boutique providing solutions for media, entertainment and consumer products industries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If interested in this 8 to 12 week contract position that starts July 1st, please send resume and JSP source to: tech-jobs@snapmedia.com and reference job #TD-140. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank you for your interest in Snap Media, but only those candidates selected for an interview will be contacted. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Contract&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;tech-jobs@snapmedia.com&lt;br&gt;Snap Media Corp.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E4245B24-BC7E-4AA0-BEE2-506FBF4EDA36</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Web Programmer (Contract)</title>
</post>
