<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Liberty Registry Management Services manages the infrastructure tools and systems required to operate a leading edge global domain registry services. But it is our people that are key to Liberty's success in doing what we do. It' s the ideas, creativity and knowledge of our people that is the mainstay of Liberty's infrastructure. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're looking for people to work with the Liberty Team, who want more than just a job. We're looking for people who willingly want to learn and to apply their knowledge and creativity with the kind of energy and spirit that makes up a winning team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are in current need of a Senior Developer as described below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title: Senior Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Reports to: Team Leader ?Development&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary: Commensurate with experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Main Purpose of Position: To design and develop various tools and applications for the Liberty, RMS registry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major Activities of Position: &lt;br&gt;-design, code, test, document and make modifications to program or simple to medium complexity according to specifications&lt;br&gt;-maintain and provide ideas for enhancements to existing code&lt;br&gt;-prepare test data, conduct test verification and document test cases&lt;br&gt;-provide pager support on a rotational basis&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge and Skill Requirements:&lt;br&gt;-5 or more years of application programming and development experience in Java, SQL, and Unix shell scripting.&lt;br&gt;-must be knowledgeable with any of the following Unix systems; Linux, Solaris, AIX, FreeBSD&lt;br&gt;-must have knowledge of relational databases such as PostgreSQL, Informix, Oracle, Sybase, MySQL. &lt;br&gt;-must have significant experience in at least one of:&lt;br&gt;-socket programming&lt;br&gt;-application layer protocol implementation&lt;br&gt;-JSP web development&lt;br&gt;-CGI web development&lt;br&gt;-XML parsing and publishing &lt;br&gt;-experience with Perl, C++ and/or C would be considered an asset &lt;br&gt;-experience in full development lifecycle&lt;br&gt;-experience in software design and implementation skills&lt;br&gt;-degree or diploma in Computer Science or equivalent&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interpersonal Skills:&lt;br&gt;-good problem solving, analytical and communication skills&lt;br&gt;-ability to learn new technologies quickly and readily adapt to changing requirements&lt;br&gt;-demonstrated ability to work effectively in a team based environment&lt;br&gt;-exceptionally efficient and thorough &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please forward your resume and cover letter to careers@libertyrms.info &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers@libertyrms.info&lt;br&gt;Liberty Registry Management Services&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E4B3130C-4177-40AC-A4F2-230B4E633978</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-10-30T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Developer</title>
</post>
