<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Microsoft CMS User Interface Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Company:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Navantis is a rapidly growing Web development company catering to a stable complement of Fortune 500 companies. In the past year we have been voted the Up and Coming Company of the Year (Branham Awards), one of Canada's 10 Most Innovative companies (IDC), and awarded Microsoft's Solution of the Year honours. Our dedication to excellent customer service and superior product development has allowed us to thrive even during this tough economic climate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Navantis offers:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; An exciting and fast-paced work environment &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; The opportunity to work on cutting-edge projects for top clients&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; An excellent work environment&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; The opportunity to continuously improve your skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; A competitive compensation package&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Navantis there are no limits to your career development opportunities!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Position: Microsoft CMS User Interface Designer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using the Microsoft Content Management Server the User Interface Designer builds websites from conception to completion taking a multi-disciplinary approach which includes graphic design, information architecture, usability and coding. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate has solid HTML, MSCMS and Photoshop skills, preferable with at least two years experience working in a production environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience using MSCMS is a prerequisite. Strong visual design skills and a proven track record of building solid websites are also a must. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being able to code ASP is definitely an asset, along with knowledge of advanced API functionality is MSCMS. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skill Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;HTML, XHTML&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Microsoft Content Management Server&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Adobe Photoshop&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested candidates should submit a resume and portfolio by email to userinterface@navantis.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;www.navantis.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;userinterface@navantis.com&lt;br&gt;Navantis Inc.&lt;br&gt;21 Randolph Ave., 3rd Floor&lt;br&gt;Toronto ON M6P 4G4&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E4CD09F1-ECEF-40C7-9522-690A2AD5B881</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-27T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Microsoft CMS User Interface Developer</title>
</post>
