<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Term position full time for more than 12 months.&lt;br&gt;The position is located within the following governmental organization(s): Department of the Environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALARY: $30,021- $49,947 per annum.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANGUAGE: English essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIAL LANGUAGES: USEFUL INFORMATION&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO CAN APPLY: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open to persons working or residing in an area where the postal code begins with L, M or N.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHALLENGE: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designs custom software for LIDAR (Laser Radar) data acquisition and analysis including training and technical support. Participates in field tests and research projects involving the use of one or more LIDAR installations (e.g. aircraft-based and ground-based). Archives and performs analysis of LIDAR data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDUCATION: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graduation with a degree from a recognized university in computer science or an associated discipline, OR, completion of a technical institution/college computer science program, OR, an acceptable combination of education, training and experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPERIENCE: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience in developing, documenting and maintaining software for scientific applications; Experience in developing and maintaining object-oriented programs in C++; Experience in computer programming and management in a Windows environment; Experience in developing visualization software and Graphical User Interfaces (GUIs); Experience in hardware/software interfacing with data acquisition cards and servo motion controllers; Experience analyzing and interpreting LIDAR (Laser Radar) data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS / COMMENTS: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates must clearly indicate in a covering letter how they meet the above-noted qualifications; &lt;br&gt;Eligibility list may be used to staff similar positions; &lt;br&gt;A written test may be administered; &lt;br&gt;Reference checks will be conducted; &lt;br&gt;Enhanced security clearance will be required prior to appointment; &lt;br&gt;All costs related to travel and/or relocation for the purposes of the selection process may be the responsibility of the candidate; &lt;br&gt;As Environment Canada is striving to achieve a truly diversified and representative workforce, Environment Canada will make every reasonable effort to accommodate the needs of its employees and candidates. &lt;br&gt;REFERENCE NUMBER: DOE13788GZ05&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLOSING DATE: November 28, 2002&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates who meet the above criteria will also be assessed against the Statement of Qualifications for this position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you apply online, DO NOT send a duplicate by fax or regular mail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please note: If you are applying by fax or by regular mail, we would ask that you fill out form PSC 3391, \\&amp;quot;Application for Employment\\&amp;quot;. If you are unable to obtain a copy of this form, you must clearly indicate your citizenship as well as the title and reference number of the position for which you are applying. Your resume must demonstrate that you meet all of the above mentioned requirements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates with foreign educational credentials are required to provide proof of Canadian equivalency. You may consult The Canadian Information Centre for International Credentials at http://www.cicic.ca/indexe.stm for further information. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please clearly indicate your citizenship. Preference will be given to Canadian citizens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all those who apply. Only those selected for further consideration will be contacted. As the Public Service of Canada promotes Employment Equity, we also encourage candidates to voluntarily self-identify if they are an Aboriginal person, a member of a visible minority group or a person with a disability. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public Service Commission of Canada&lt;br&gt;1 Front Street West,&lt;br&gt;Toronto, Ontario&lt;br&gt;M5J 2X5&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAX: (416) 973-1883&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are committed to employment equity. &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E8F17A77-5CCA-438B-9F83-4FF91F53CEEA</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/DATA ANALYST</title>
</post>
