<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Profile &lt;br&gt; Advertisement number: 240634 &lt;br&gt; Title: Local area network (lan) technician (Wireless LAN Technician) (NOC: 2281)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Terms of Employment: Permanent, Full Time &lt;br&gt; Salary: To be negotiated &lt;br&gt; Anticipated Start Date: As soon as possible&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Location: Toronto Centre, Ontario (2 vacancies) &lt;br&gt; Skill Requirements:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Education: Completion of high school, Completion of college/CEGEP/vocational or technical training &lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Other: CWNA; WLAN cert. from Cisco or other vendors will be considered. &lt;br&gt;Experience: 1 - 2 years, Other: Experience conducting Site Surveys, installing Access Points, etc &lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Read English, Write English &lt;br&gt;Operating Systems: MS Windows 95/98/NT/2000, MS Windows CE &lt;br&gt;Hardware Environment: IBM PC and compatibles &lt;br&gt;Other Information: No phone calls or faxes will be accepted.Candidates must currently hold the Certified Wireless Network Administrator (CWNA) certification. Wireless LAN certifications from Cisco, or other vendors will also be considered. Previous applicants need not apply unless your information has changed.We thank you for your interest in Wave2 Wireless, but only those applicants selected for an interview will be contacted. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Employer: Wave2 Wireless Inc.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; How to Apply:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;By E-mail: resumes@wave2wireless.ca &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Business Profile: Wave2 Wireless Inc. is Canada's premier provider of Wireless LAN training solutions. We are the only authorized Certified Wireless Education Center located in Canada. &lt;br&gt; Web Site: www.wave2wireless.ca &lt;br&gt; Advertised until: 2003/02/28 &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E9B1A98F-13AE-4DFB-9E74-FA4F24B81354</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Local area network (lan) technician (Wireless LAN Technician)</title>
</post>
