<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job Profile &lt;br&gt; Advertisement number: 235422 &lt;br&gt; Title: Web programmer (Search Engine Optimizer) (NOC: 2174)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Terms of Employment: Permanent, Full Time, Day &lt;br&gt; Salary: To be negotiated &lt;br&gt; Anticipated Start Date: As soon as possible&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; Location: Toronto North, Ontario (1 vacancy) &lt;br&gt; Skill Requirements:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Education: Completion of university, Other: experience in optimizing websites for search engine positioning. &lt;br&gt;Credentials (certificates, licences, memberships, courses, etc.): Other: Must have a degree/diploma in field of computers &lt;br&gt;Experience: 3 - 5 years, Other: Must have experience with marketing web sites online &lt;br&gt;Languages: Speak English, Read English, Write English &lt;br&gt;Work Setting Experience: Software developer &lt;br&gt;Operating Systems: DOS, Linux, Unix &lt;br&gt;Hardware Environment: IBM PC and compatibles &lt;br&gt;Programming Languages: ASP, HTML, DHTML, XML, Java, Java Script, Perl, PHP, Visual Basic, VB Script &lt;br&gt;Applications: Adobe Photoshop, MS Excel, MS FrontPage, MS Office, MS Word &lt;br&gt;Communication Protocols: TCP/IP &lt;br&gt;Generic Skills: Computer use (ex., use software packages; knowledge of hardware; work with computer-operated machinery), Reading skills (ex., follow written directions; interpret documents like charts, maps; acquire specialized knowledge), Working with others (ex., work with individual or team; build consensus), Planning and organizing skills (ex., manage priorities; order tasks efficiently), Problem-solving skills (ex., identify problem causes; determine steps to resolve; assess solution), Speaking and listening skills (ex., communicate clearly and effectively; follow directions; mediate disputes) &lt;br&gt;Other Information: Experience in search engine optimization ONLY need apply. Website Optimizer needed to increase traffic to company web site. Full-time person needed to work under Senior Search Engine Optimizer and be able to take instructions and work independently.Your responsibilities will be to increase listing positions on the major search engines on the Internet. We are not looking for a designer or a programmer with no experience but a search engine optimizer/marketer. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Employer: Confidential &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; How to Apply:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Contact Name: Clear Text Solutions Inc. &lt;br&gt; By E-mail: cleartextsolutions@hotmail.com &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Advertised until: 2003/02/22 &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>E9CE701F-662F-4DDC-AA7B-68BB43985D22</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-09T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web programmer</title>
</post>
