<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Quality Assurance Strategy Specialist &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Mastech Emplifi - A New Era in Advanced Technology!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently looking for a highly skilled Quality Assurance Strategy Specialist to join our team in Toronto. In this challenging and rewarding role, you will be responsible for developing testing strategy and plans, including system integration testing and user acceptance testing. You will be responsible for identification of resource requirements and making recommendations on appropriate testing tools. You will help define and implement new testing processes, and you will be responsible for coordinating the implementation of the testing strategy and plans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* 5 or more years of experience with QA Methodologies and testing. &lt;br&gt;* Knowledge of automated test tools and version control systems would be required.&lt;br&gt;* Experience leading a test team, Planning, Organizing, and implementing processes would be an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mastech Emplifi is one of the most respected and successful IT consulting firms in North America. We pair excellence in technology with a firm dedication to the development and potential of our people. We are proudly ISO 9001 certified in our Toronto, Ottawa and Montreal branches. Mastech Canada services telecommunications, manufacturing, insurance, financial, and government clients. For more information about our company, please visit our web site: www.mastechemplifi.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are interested in pursuing this opportunity, please contact us by sending us your resume in Rich Text Format (. RTF) or ASCII Format (. txt)!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Contract &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: GTA - 5856&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Robert Fenwick&lt;br&gt;recruit_mbef@mastech.ca&lt;br&gt;Mastech Emplifi&lt;br&gt;5800 Explorer Drive, Fifth Floor&lt;br&gt;Mississauga ON L4W 5L4&lt;br&gt;Ph: 905-602-7000&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>EA4B43FD-28BF-4D0E-981E-B32877619C5E</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-10-30T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Quality Assurance Strategy Specialist</title>
</post>
