<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>한영호</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>AMD에서 일하실 Senior Application Engineer로 일할 한국말 가능한 분을 찾네요...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;혹시 가능하시면 메일 주세요~ 포워딩 해드릴께요~&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;young_ho_han@hotmail.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Applications Engineer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATI Is Now Part of the New AMD.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMD and ATI have joined forces, combining AMD's technology leadership in microprocessors with ATI's strengths in graphics, chipsets, and consumer electronics. The new AMD is a processing powerhouse that will reinvent our industry through a smarter strategy that empowers growth, innovation, and choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATI Business Units are now called: AMD Graphics and Media Processors (formerly ATI).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are currently looking for a Senior Applications Engineer to join our Handheld team to be responsible for key customer deliverables such as chip specifications, application notes, board tuning to achieve optimum performance, reference designs, recommended layouts as well as being responsible for customer demonstrations. The Senior Applications Engineer will be required to work closely with multiple groups including the Hardware and Software design teams, and the Technical Publications team to ensure that all communication with the customers is accurate and delivered as committed. As well, the Senior Applications Engineer will also work with customers at their location to expedite the bring-up of customer platforms. As a Senior Applications Engineer, you will be a role model to other Application Engineers and help them with difficult customer situations. You will also participate in the creation of the technical publications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirement:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;- University degree in Electrical or Computer Engineering&lt;br&gt;- 5+ years of direct customer engineering support, in multiple geographies&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;- Advanced knowledge of the ASIC and software development process&lt;br&gt;- 3+ years electrical engineering experience &lt;br&gt;- Proven track record on managing several projects and coordinating multiple, changing deadlines&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;- Strong interpersonal, written and verbal communication skills&lt;br&gt;- Strong relationship-building, negotiation and problem solving skills&lt;br&gt;- (optional but preferred) Fluency in the Mandarin Chinese, Japanese and/or Korean language(s)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This team is essential to the success of AMD as a growing company. It is a very exciting environment where you will be working with the very best in our technology, while working on some of the most exciting projects the industry has to offer.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>EADEFB38-AAFD-4F25-80D5-30E18AB9D3BE</postId>
    <pubDate>2007-11-07T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Application Engineer</title>
</post>
