<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김태희</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Mainframe Programmer Job Posting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Mainframe Programmer&lt;br&gt;Company:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Infotech Solutions&lt;br&gt;Position Type:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Contract to Hire&lt;br&gt;Pay Rate:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 40&lt;br&gt;Date Posted:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Feb-16-10&lt;br&gt;Browse Similar Postings &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By employer... &lt;br&gt;- Jobs from Infotech Solutions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By location... &lt;br&gt;- Tech jobs in Toronto, ON &lt;br&gt;- Tech jobs in Ontario &lt;br&gt;- Mainframe jobs in Ontario &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By category... &lt;br&gt;- Mainframe Programmer jobs &lt;br&gt;- Mainframe jobs &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ShareThis&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client is looking for a intermediate mainframe programmer.&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Provides maintenance and support for the student loan application&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Translates business requirements into a technical document&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Constructs simple to moderately complex application programs according to specifications &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Tests application changes using internal testing standards to ensure the application meets all business and system requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Assists Quality Assurance in the user acceptance testing phase of new or modified applications to ensure system integrity&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Implements application programs using version control tools to ensure the integrity of the application systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Provides on-call support for the Mainframe applications both batch and on-line 7 x 24 as required to ensure system service level agreements are met&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;§ Completes documentation and knowledge transfer for completed projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Competencies:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Formal computer science training (university or college diploma) &lt;br&gt;Sound practical experience using COBOL/ COBOL II in an IBM mainframe environment with MVS/ CICS/ VSAM/TSO, essential. &lt;br&gt;Effective analytical and problem solving skills, required. &lt;br&gt;Effective communication (oral and written) skills, required. &lt;br&gt;Ability to work effectively in a team under minimal supervision, within an environment of constant change and tight deadlines, required. &lt;br&gt;Sound knowledge of Windows environment preferred. &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Easytrieve Plus, Endevor and File-AID an asset &lt;br&gt;Working knowledge of WORD, ACCESS and EXCEL, an asset &lt;br&gt;Previous experience within financial industry, an asset &lt;br&gt;Willingness to learn and be challenged required. &lt;br&gt;Send us resumes to mainframe.placements@gmail.com&lt;br&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Canada-ON-Toronto&lt;br&gt;Telecommute:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; No (Onsite Position)&lt;br&gt;Contact Name:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;James&lt;br&gt;Contact Phone:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Contact Email:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;mainframe.placements@gmail.com&lt;br&gt;Contact Comments: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please mention Dev Bistro when contacting us.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>EDEA1C61-F8E5-43E1-A42C-DC203FCD6343</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>웬????  Mainframe Programmer</title>
</post>
