<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>-.NET Developer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Marketrend Systems Inc. is a premier, full service automotive marketing company with over 160 employees world wide. Marketrend has over 20 years of marketing experience in the automotive field and personal working knowledge of dealerships. Our company produces a wide variety of traditional and web-based marketing tools for automotive manufacturers and dealers in North America and the Caribbean. Our office in North York is seeking a full-time .NET Developer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br&gt;As a member of the development team, you will leverage your knowledge, together with your technical skill-set to design, develop and implement web based software products and infrastructure using the .NET framework and Visual Studio.NET application development suite, with special emphasis on the C# programming language. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUALIFICATIONS:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Degree or diploma in Computer Science&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; 3-5 years of related experience developing, customizing and implementing enterprise-level software solutions using the Microsoft Solutions Framework &lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Component-based programming experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Application development experience&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Internet development (HTML, Javascript, ASP.NET,VB.NET, .NET Framework, XML web services, IIS)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Data access (ADO, ADO.NET, SQL Server, Transact SQL)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Microsoft Certification preferred&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Ability to work well under pressure with multiple deadlines.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Devoted to producing high quality products.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Strong organizational skills and attention to detail.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Excellent oral and written communication skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#61607; Proven team player&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers@marketrend.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>EE766A68-D72F-47A1-A633-ED1B8FE70143</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-03-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>-.NET Developer</title>
</post>
