<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>asheen</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;Opportunity: Sr Java Developer &lt;br /&gt;Date Posted: January 12, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;Location: Toronto (Downtown) &lt;br /&gt;Type: Full Time $80-85k&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About The Opportunity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our client provides business-to-government (B2G) and business-to-business (B2B) eservice solutions that enable organizations to greatly enhance the services they provide to their customers. With a unique combination of capabilities and state-of the-art systems, our client is at the forefront of delivering service potential in the land, legal and financial services industries as well as enabling electronic government service delivery.&amp;nbsp; Looking for a Sr. Java Developer to design, develop, and implement software applications on a 24X7 web based client facing application.&amp;nbsp; Work in a fast paced agile software development environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;?Develop detailed program specifications &lt;br /&gt;?Unit test code. &lt;br /&gt;?Develop and maintain application code &lt;br /&gt;?Participate in integration and regression testing &lt;br /&gt;?Prepare technical documentation. &lt;br /&gt;?Implement security policies as set out by client&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interpersonal and Technical Skills:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;?Must have excellent verbal and written communication skills. &lt;br /&gt;?Must be a good team player with positive attitude. &lt;br /&gt;?Self-starter with the ability to learn quickly, has good problem-solving skills and &lt;br /&gt;?Can meet tight deadlines&lt;br /&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;?Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in computer science, engineering, or a related discipline &lt;br /&gt;?At least 8 years of experience in systems development with 5+ years in Internet environment. &lt;br /&gt;?Excellent front end and backend development skills. &lt;br /&gt;?Experience developing client facing, W3C standards compliant, web applications supporting multiple browsers and operating systems. &lt;br /&gt;?Strong knowledge of concepts, practices and procedures of systems development life cycle. Relies on experience and judgment to plan and accomplish goals. &lt;br /&gt;?Familiarity with Agile development and Scrum. &lt;br /&gt;?Excellent technical skills and experience with the environments and tools identified below.&lt;br /&gt;Systems Environment:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;?Multi-tier web based solutions, wide variety of hardware and operating systems (Linux, AIX, Windows, etc), Oracle, and MS SQL, Agile and RUP (development methodology), Rational suite of products to manage development life cycle, Replication Server Technology, Remedy, Spectrum, Patrol, Networking fundamentals, PKI, Intrusion Detection, X.500 Directory&lt;br /&gt;Development Environment and Tools:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;?Java, J2EE, Spring, hibernate, JDBC, SOA, XSLT, FLEX, JSON, CSS, XML, HTML, Debugging tools, application servers(Weblogic, JBOSS), Apache, Linux, scripting tools and languages, Oracle, Eclipse, ClearCase , ClearQuest, UML, Knowledge of modeling tools. &lt;br /&gt;?Hailstorm for vulnerability testing and Fortify for code security scanning.&lt;br /&gt;Roy Andrade&lt;br /&gt;Alliance Search Group Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:roy@alliancesearch.net"&gt;roy@alliancesearch.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alliancesearch.net"&gt;www.alliancesearch.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Direct line: 416-265-9688&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <postId>EF9B03C1-C5E1-43CC-A821-546F16439791</postId>
    <pubDate>2012-01-18T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java developer</title>
</post>
