<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강재형</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Check this one out!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;source : http://www.flipdog.com/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software Developers - Markham, Ontario&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;We have an immediate opportunity for 5 full-time Software Developers reporting to either the Director, Application Development or the Manager, Application Development in our Marketing and XRM Products Division at the Markham location. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incumbents in this role will be accountable for developing and maintaining code, unit integration and regression testing. Software development activities will include assisting our customer support and professional services teams in identifying and resolving problems with InSystems products or integrations while following InSystems current system of development methodology. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will possess a BSc in Computer Science or equivalent plus 3-5 years experience in software development. They will also possess proven problem solving communication skills. The ability to work as an integral part of a team, meet and exceed deadlines and adapt to new paradigms and languages is critical to success in this role. Some travel may be required with these roles. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Summary: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(1) Main duties and responsibilities: Develop eXterity prototypes for our marketing team (2 positions). Techical qualifications include, Programming: C++, Java, other object oriented languages, object oriented analysis and design (OOAD), Com, Com+, MFC. Platforms: Windows, NT, Unix (an asset). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(2) Main duties and responsibilities: Developer for eXterity Group Service Application (1 position). Technical qualification include programming languages as listed in (1) above and two plus years of J2EE experience (using Jbuidler), IBM Websphere, MQ Series, AIX Administration and Oracle database experience will be considered an asset. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(3) Main duties and responsibilities: Applications support for eXterity group service (2 positions). Technical qualification as listed in (1) and (2) above. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested applicants are invited to submit a resume to Human Resources quoting this title and reference number in the subject line: Software Developer (#101 M&amp;E). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We regret that due to the volume of resumes received, only those applicants selected for an interview will be contacted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No agencies please. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Contact: Human Resources&lt;br&gt;E-mail: hrdept@insystems.com&lt;br&gt;Fax: (905) 513-1419 &lt;br&gt;Mailing Address:&lt;br&gt;InSystems Technologies Inc.&lt;br&gt;Attn: Human Resources&lt;br&gt;19 Allstate Parkway, Suite 400&lt;br&gt;Markham, Ontario, Canada&lt;br&gt;L3R 5A4 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>EFF363C4-794D-44FA-9342-2510D12BBFE7</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>5 Software Developer needed!--Markham</title>
</post>
