<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>정연국</author>
            <date>2009-08-13T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Hi, How can I contact you</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>권칠환</author>
            <date>2009-08-14T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Call Glenn for the job opportunity!!! There is the TEL number.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>THIS PERSON MUST HAVE EXPERIENCE WORKING IN A BANKING ENVIRONMENT, please see job description:&lt;br&gt;Functional and Educational Competencies: &lt;br&gt;1- Clear and effective written and oral communication. &lt;br&gt;2- Relevant University or post-secondary degree with an aptitude for research and learning. &lt;br&gt;3- At least 8 years experience developing in a Unix Environment (preferably Solaris) &lt;br&gt;4- Strong knowledge with Oracle/Sybase SQL, Java, and general J2EE technology &lt;br&gt;5- Very Strong database design and development skills with ability to conduct Data analysis and ETL development. &lt;br&gt;6- Familiarity with concepts of Network, LAN, shared Enterprise wide IT Infrastructure (e.g. SAN, NFS, SFTP), Change Control and IT Security practice. &lt;br&gt;7- Systems Integration and Vendors interaction experience is a definite asset &lt;br&gt;8- Familiarity with Web technology such as HTML, XML and CGI is a definite asset &lt;br&gt;9- Knowledge and experience with Securities Finance applications (like securities lending and Repo) or completion of Canadian Security Certification is an asset. &lt;br&gt;10- Disciplined in software development methodology, tools and concepts &lt;br&gt;11- Strong troubleshooting, analytical and problem solving skills &lt;br&gt;12- Must be flexible to adapt to a dynamic and fast pace environment &lt;br&gt;Job Summary: &lt;br&gt;This position belongs to an application development and support team for the companys applications mainly in Global Equity Finance and securities data handling. The incumbent will be responsible to develop and support medium to fairly complex applications and must be able to interact with various teams like Business Analysts, Users, vendors, and Production Support Teams. He/She must possess the skills and desire to understand business requirements and translate them to underlying systems design and database schemas. It is essential that the incumbent to be proactive, eager to learn, and to have a 'Can Do' attitude. &lt;br&gt;Key Accountabilities: &lt;br&gt;1) Develop or integrate cost effective applications and provide technical specs and designs. &lt;br&gt;2) Provide technical support to applications in Production and User Acceptance Testing &lt;br&gt;3) Implement application changes by handling vendor patches installs, building own internal code, reviewing other developers' code, planning and documenting the change. &lt;br&gt;4) Troubleshoot and investigate reported issues and provide a timely response and logical explanations of the resolution and potential root causes, with pro-active recommendations on what can be done to address the issues for short and long term considerations. &lt;br&gt;5) Provide technical guidance to other team members as required &lt;br&gt;Thank you in Advance for any consideration that you may have in this matter, and Please contact me ASAP, if you know anyone who might be interested it&lt;br&gt;Take care and have a great day!&lt;br&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;Glenn&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glenn H. Steinberg, President&lt;br&gt;H.B.Sc., M.Sc.Phm., Ph.D.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glenn Partners Staffing Solution Inc.&lt;br&gt;4950 Yonge St., Suite 2200&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON&lt;br&gt;M2N 6K1&lt;br&gt;Office: 416 218 5557 ext. 2198 &lt;br&gt;Alt.: 416 512 1179 &lt;br&gt;www.glennpartners.com&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F07382BC-A660-4E7A-9B86-9F0A02D9F828</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-08-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java/J2ee Contract</title>
</post>
