<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>POSITION&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Senior Unix Administrator&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;REPORTS TO&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Senior Manager, Technical Services&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;DEPARTMENT&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Technical Services&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;JOB STATUS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Full-Time&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;COMPANY&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Rogers Communications Inc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;DIVISION&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Rogers Shared Services&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;LOCATION&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ontario&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;LOCATION DETAILS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Markham&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;JOB TYPE&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Information Technology&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;JOB REFERENCE #&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;RILP61&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Unix Administrator will be responsible for performance, tuning and capacity of all production Midrange Unix platforms. &lt;br&gt;They willthino be responsible for assisting and guiding development teams in system application design to ensure a high level of performance, functionality and availability is maintained. &lt;br&gt;The Unix Administrator will also be required to assist in related software evaluation and upgrades. &lt;br&gt;Perform system optimization by working with developers, customers and system support personnel. &lt;br&gt;Investigate and provide methodology, processes and procedures to exploit new features and directions of IMS. &lt;br&gt;Provide optimization recommendations through historical analysis. &lt;br&gt;Perform required configuration, maintenance &amp; tuning of all system related components including system software. &lt;br&gt;Evaluate, provide and maintain software tools to assist internal and external customers. &lt;br&gt;Aid in problem determination and resolution. &lt;br&gt;Provide Unix and related system support. &lt;br&gt;Provide on-call assistance for database related problems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;University degree in computer science or equivalent with substantial, directly related work experience &lt;br&gt;5+ years HP-UX systems administration and EMC experience are a MUST &lt;br&gt;Excellent understanding of NFS, DNS and basic routing concepts for problem determination and resolution &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of NT, Oracle, Sun and AIX systems would be an asset &lt;br&gt;Strong organizational, interpersonal, motivational &amp; analytical skills &lt;br&gt;Effective written &amp; verbal communication skills &lt;br&gt;Availability for on-call support of Unix system related activities &lt;br&gt;Ability to work effectively on multiple simultaneous tasks within fast paced, “high tech” customer service oriented environments &lt;br&gt;Ability to complete project tasks in a timely manner &lt;br&gt;Outstanding customer service skills &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply for this opportunity using the on-line resume.&lt;br&gt;Learn of other ways to apply for this opportunity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interested Applicants please forward resumes quoting job code RILP61 to rsscareers@rci.rogers.com</content>
    <postId>F2672FF7-5FA6-4811-B3BB-4F33728957CB</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Unix Administrator</title>
</post>
