<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Heo, Daniel</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi all,&lt;br&gt;I found a good architect/developer position in my company. I decided to help out our Korean immigrants. Please check this information if you are qualified.&lt;br&gt;This position is only available within short period time, so please hurry if you think you are qualified.&lt;br&gt;Strong English speaking/writing skills are required because this is architect position.&lt;br&gt;You can contect me if you need some more detail information and guideline, or you can post your resume directly via online application form through the bellow URL. Make sure you cannot post two times with same resume.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BCE Emergis is a heart of BCE(Bell Canada Enterprise). This company is a unique vendor for eCommenerce solution accross Canada as a Bell Canada family.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1) Job Opening URL :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://www.emergis.com/careers/job_offer.asp?JobPostID=391&amp;LANG=en&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-------------- pasted from original -------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2) Positions Available :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security Architect/Developer&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Req. # : emer-00000677&lt;br&gt;Mississauga, Ontario, Canada&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BCE Emergis is seeking technical architects to analyze, design and lead the development of software products that operate in a real-time claims processing environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities will include the design and build of security architecture for an eCommerce B2B/B2C application. This will include the design and of a user authentication and authorization component, and assessing whether or not to buy a packaged software versus build. Responsibilities will also include integrating this solution with the application architecture (as appropriate) and developing and executing test scripts for the entire security architecture.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;University degree in a computer science or related discipline, or an equivalent combination of education and experience&lt;br&gt;Experience with gathering and analyzing security requirements&lt;br&gt;Experience with the design, build, test, and deployment of a security architecture for a large eCommerce B2B/B2C application.&lt;br&gt;Experience with web access control implementations and LDAP.&lt;br&gt;Experience with implementing network security access control.&lt;br&gt;Intermediate application development skills - Java&lt;br&gt;Minimum 3 years experience as an application and network security architect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should you feel that you qualify for this position, please submit your curriculum vitae via our online job application form. Please ensure that you indicate the appropriate Req.# for the position you are applying for in the space provided in the online form.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You need only submit your resume once to be eligible for all openings. Our resume tracking system will match your skills and experience to all open positions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------- end of paste ----------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F4097243-8D28-43BA-9806-3CAC714417BB</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-11-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Job Info : Security Architect/Developer for B2B/B2C</title>
</post>
