<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>As a platinum sponsor to Toronto .Net User Group, Navantis has the opportunity to communicate to the user group about important company announcements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Located in Toronto, Ontario, Navantis is a rapidly growing professional services firm specializing in software development using Microsoft technologies and server products. We currently have immediate openings for Senior .NET Developers and Software Project Managers. We believe that our employees are the key to our success. We employ and seek the best of the best - people who are passionate about delivering excellent software solutions and a superior customer experience. If you are looking for a rewarding and challenging environment then Navantis is the place for you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior .NET Developers with Architecture Ability (Permanent or Contract)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking to hire several senior .NET developers with strong ASP.NET, C#.NET, VB.NET, SQL Server, XML/XSLT, ADO.NET, and SQL Reporting Services experience. Your knowledge of SharePoint Portal Server 2003, Commerce Server 2002, Content Management Server 2002 or BizTalk Server 2004 would be a recommendation. Your ability to lead a development team of junior and intermediate developers as well as your written and verbal communication skills are essential to this position. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply online at www.navantis.com/english/about/careers/job_dotnet.htm or send your current resume in Microsoft Word format to Jason Cheng at jasonc@navantis.com. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software Project Managers (Permanent or Contract)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are looking to hire several senior software development project managers with a strong focus on methodology (iterative development/RUP/Agile) and solid core knowledge of the Microsoft .NET platform. Your ability to remain focused under pressure, your excellent written and verbal communication skills and your deep understanding of risk management in the software project lifecycle will be an asset. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply online at www.navantis.com/english/about/careers/job_pm.htm or send your current resume in Microsoft Word format to Jason Cheng at jasonc@navantis.com. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Navantis Inc. | 21 Randolph Ave. Toronto, Ontario M6P 4G4 | 416.532.5554 | www.navantis.com&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</content>
    <postId>F49EA082-DD8D-4361-9274-75F41E6F26FF</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-06-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior .NET Developers at Navantis</title>
</post>
