<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>If you are interested in this position, please send me your very detailed resume in word format as an attachment, write your number of years of experience beside each of the Work Experience and Technical Requirements section below (feel free to expand on each item if you wish as this will be used as your introduction profile to the client), give me your current salary and your salary expectations and a tel # where you can be reached during the day. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;Our client, a dynamic marketing company, requires one Intermediate-Senior Web programmer to join their growing team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Summary:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Web Programmer is responsible for developing custom applications, functions, enhancements and resources for the organization’s intranet in order to support their business.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This individual will also conduct extensive user-analysis in order to ensure that the organization’s technical resources support their business processes and internal workflow.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work Experience and Technical Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Minimum of 5 to 10 years experience in developing Web Applications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Expert level development skills using ASP.Net&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Strong background developing with Classic ASP &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Experience using Php and C# is strongly preferred&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Experience in dealing with internal users and business groups, providing technical consultation and process improvements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Strong familiarity developing applications on a Windows Platform&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Strong familiarity interacting with MS SQL Databases in a High Volume Environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Extensive experience creating reporting tools and/or custom output reports&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Experience with Crystal Reports and/or other reporting services is preferred&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Ability to adhere to established documentation processes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Ability to provide complex solutions to internal workflow challenges&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Core Competencies:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Excellent communication skills &amp;#8211; Verbal and Written &amp;#8211; to conduct business/workflow analysis&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Proven ability to prioritize a diverse workload&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Excellent time management skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Strong user-analysis capabilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Ability to thrive in a fast-paced environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Focus on efficiency, function and cost&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-University Degree or College Diploma in a relevant field&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position/Environment:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Reporting to the Director of IT&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Communicative management style, team-based approach to problem solving&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-The company services high-profile organizations in the non-profit sector&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-IT Department is a great team environment and always progressing forward&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Stable organization &amp;#8211; continuous growth over the past 5 years&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Fairly laid back environment &amp;#8211; not overly formal&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Criminal check will be conducted&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deliverables/Technical Focus/Requirements:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Soft Skills are Crucial: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Excellent communication, conscientiousness is a major focus, constantly looking to improve the existing applications/workflow, mindful of the overall business strategy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Memory usage is a concern &amp;#8211; experience in a high volume environment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Patience is important for internal user analysis &amp;#8211; experience conducting needs assessment with Non-IT professionals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Will be providing technical Solutions to internal business/workflow requirements &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Emphasis is on developing functional applications which is not always attractive to a lot of developers &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Business Conscious &amp;#8211; Mindful of budget, time management, return on investment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Constantly developing add-ons, enhancements and upgrades to intranet-based applications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Focus on developing User-Friendly applications, functions and resources&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salary is $60 - $85k&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Best regards,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julie Cox&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sr. IT Recruiter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CareerDriven/J. Cox Consulting Inc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;905-737-4721&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;www.careerdriven.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F4B88812-AC17-4F64-B741-B6BC14958D8F</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-01-02T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Programmer position available - perm - Yonge/Sheppard area</title>
</post>
