<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>저에게 날라든 직장 입니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi there, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let me start by apologizing for the mass email. I have an extremely urgent and time sensitive opportunity and the IBM Hiring Manager is looking for people NOW. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As is the norm with IBM, we are somewhat constrained by rate. The most I can offer is $38/hour if you are incorporated. If you are not incorporated, the rate is $36.50/hour. I know that is low for some of you so please ignore this email in that case. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please let me know if you’re interested. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: 3600 Steeles &amp;#8211; IBM H.O. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Length: 1 yr with extension up to 3 years (already budget approved) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start: ASAP &amp;#8211; next week if possible &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pay: $50 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There may be occasional pager support required &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent team of 6, and once ramped up &amp;#8211; work 4 days a week from home &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is Support and Admin &amp;#8211; no build, no new programming &amp;#8211; all support, the Hiring Manager has asked that we ensure candidates are aware of this. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An average work day would be maintenance of steady state, troubleshooting, health checks, backup and restore, fine-tuning. This is for an Intermediate resource &amp;#8211; the Hiring Manager would rather have someone with all the skills than someone with much depth in just one or two of the skills. So we are looking for someone with at least 3-6 yrs experience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUST HAVES &amp;#8211; THE HIRING MANAGER CANNOT CONSIDER ANYONE WHO DOES NOT HAVE THE FOLLOWING: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please tell me in your Present how the candidate matches these “must have” requirements: (please tell me the number of years experience) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MS Sql server DB 2005 in a cluster environment (key here is in a multi server environment) &lt;br&gt;Oracle 8i &amp; 9i &lt;br&gt;DB2 &lt;br&gt;Maintenance of an enterprise environment &lt;br&gt;Troubleshooting &lt;br&gt;Health checks &lt;br&gt;Backup/restore &lt;br&gt;Comms must be a min of 8/10 (multi client facing) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Collins &lt;br&gt;National Resource Manager &lt;br&gt;chrisc@peopletogo.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cell - 416.564.5959 &lt;br&gt;Office - 905.940.9292 ext 2362 &lt;br&gt;Fax - 905.513.9995 &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F5462456-AD4A-4C63-BD45-8173E9553FEC</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-06-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>날라든 이메일</title>
</post>
