<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;J.D. Edwards, headquartered in Colorado, provides worldwide enterprise software solutions. Throughout our 25-year history, we’ve created a unique work environment that has led to our being named by Fortune Magazine as one of the best companies to work for in America. The combination of our corporate culture and technology has propelled J.D. Edwards to the forefront of the enterprise software industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When J.D. Edwards hires new employees, we look for three basic qualities&amp;#8212;integrity, industry, and intelligence. We are unique in our ability to take management’s new ideas and put them into action quickly, while providing a harmonious work environment where everyone can work to their utmost potential. Our employees must be willing to preserve our corporate culture, while maintaining company growth at a sustainable rate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Develop APS modules for release in the area of Production Distrubution and Planning. To design and develop modules in the APS product line.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Team player. Self-motivated. Excellent communication skills (written and oral) are desired. C++ User Interface and/or database programming experience are required. Scripting for Unix and NT environments. Strong Design experience with complex systems, implementation, unit testing, and full life cycle development. University degree with 5+ years experience in software development is necessary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our main goal is to provide creative solutions to our clients in an efficient manner, which leads to continuous customer satisfaction. We work hard to achieve this, and we are continuously looking for innovative team players to help us. EOE.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLICANTS PLEASE NOTE:&lt;br&gt;Find out more about us at www.jdedwards.com. An email response is encouraged for best results. Please state the reference code# DEV4416MB in the email subject line and attach your resume in Windows Word (.doc) or generic text (.txt) format and mail to Canada_recruiting@jdedwards.com When applying for multiple positions please submit only one resume. Include all codes in subject line. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: DEV4416MB&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;Canada_recruiting@jdedwards.com&lt;br&gt;J.D. Edwards&lt;br&gt;655 Bay Street Suite 1200&lt;br&gt;Toronto&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F58569D2-19DB-4AAD-9B9B-4DCD29824F72</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-05-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Software Developer</title>
</post>
