<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이상훈</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Application &amp; Technical Support Specialist 1&lt;br&gt;File Reference #: X9CSB17188 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the direction of the Supervisor, Process Control Systems and in cooperation with Toronto Water Integrated Technology Support staff, the incumbent provides technical support of the application software and hardware components of the computerized systems in the plant, including the Process Control System (PCS) a PCS Historian, and the related Local Area Networks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities include the following:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schedules workload and sets priorities&lt;br&gt;Leads team in identification and resolution of issues and problems&lt;br&gt;Provides expertise in assessment, analysis, evaluation of alternatives and resolution of issues and problems&lt;br&gt;Liaises and coordinates with internal and external groups on resolution of problems&lt;br&gt;Recommends preventative solutions to mitigate recurrence of similar problems&lt;br&gt;Develops and recommends improvements to current environment, policies and processes&lt;br&gt;Acquires and disposes of hardware and software&lt;br&gt;Configures computer, PLC (Programmable Logic Controllers) SLC (Single Loop Controllers) network and server-related hardware and software&lt;br&gt;Monitors and maintains access and security of data and infrastructure&lt;br&gt;Configuration of server hardware and software&lt;br&gt;Provides technical support in the maintenance and service in the following applications: Performance and Operations Management System (POMS), a Work Management Systems (WMS), a Laboratory Information Management System (LIMS), an Industrial Waste Management Systems (IWMS), a PCS Historian&lt;br&gt;Advises desktop configuration management teams on hardware and software technologies and deployment alternatives&lt;br&gt;Advises network management teams on hardware and software technologies, connectivity and backup and recovery alternatives&lt;br&gt;Advises security management and control teams on security-related technologies and access control alternatives&lt;br&gt;Performs capacity planning&lt;br&gt;Reviews work of staff and provide training to them&lt;br&gt;Prepares, directs, and recommends for approval training material and documentation for use by clients and staff&lt;br&gt;Provides training to clients in use of technology&lt;br&gt;Prepares statistics and drafts summary reports&lt;br&gt;Supports the centralized management of access control&lt;br&gt;Installs/rolls out application, hardware and/or software and takes inventory of such assets&lt;br&gt;Designs and creates databases&lt;br&gt;Attends meetings&lt;br&gt;Travels to off-site locations&lt;br&gt;Key Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your application must describe your qualifications as they relate to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical support experience in the maintenance and service in at least one of the following applications: Performance and Operations Management System (POMS), a Work Management Systems (WMS), a Laboratory Information Management System (LIMS), an Industrial Waste Management Systems (IWMS), a PCS Historian.&lt;br&gt;Working experience in a CITRIX/THIM client environment.&lt;br&gt;Technical Support experience in a large diverse computing environment.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated experience in LAN administration in a Windows 2000/ 2003 environment. &lt;br&gt;Excellent technical skills to configure workstations and servers; install software and provide troubleshooting and problem resolution services for a diverse client group. &lt;br&gt;Proven systems management skills, specifically with technical issues at the desktop and the Local Area Network level, including problem determination and resolution and desktop/server configuration and installation. &lt;br&gt;A diploma or certificate in computer studies from a recognized community college or equivalent combination of education and experience.&lt;br&gt;Possession of valid Ontario Class “G” Driver’s License and access to a motor vehicle.&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of and experience utilizing electrical, electronic and industrial instrumentation principles related to systems maintenance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must also have:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fundamental knowledge of industry standards, protocols, system architectures and operating systems. &lt;br&gt;Strong conceptual, analytical and problem solving skills. &lt;br&gt;Willingness and ability to acquire or update knowledge of business applications, control systems and communication network technologies.&lt;br&gt;The ability to work days, afternoon and night shifts, including weekends and statutory holidays.&lt;br&gt;Travel within the City of Toronto required. &lt;br&gt;Excellent interpersonal, oral and written communication skills to provide troubleshooting support, prepare technical documentation and reports on problems and to deal effectively with all levels of management and staff.&lt;br&gt;Proven commitment to delivering superior customer service, performance quality and continuous improvement.&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated ability to work effectively within a dynamic team environment as well as project team setting as required.&lt;br&gt;Proven working knowledge of PLC and SCADA. &lt;br&gt;Knowledge or Water and Wastewater plant operations will be an asset.&lt;br&gt;Practical working knowledge of one of the following: Performance and Operations Management System (POMS), a Work Management Systems (WMS), a Laboratory Information Management System (LIMS), an Industrial Waste Management Systems (IWMS), a PCS Historian or Document management.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To apply for this position, please send us a resume and cover letter, quoting File #X9CSB17188, using one of the following methods: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online: Click on the Apply for this position button at the bottom of this posting, or &lt;br&gt;FAX: 416-397-9818, or &lt;br&gt;Mail to: Human Resources, City of Toronto, Metro Hall, 55 John Street, 5th Floor, Toronto, Ontario, M5V 3C6.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please do not send duplicates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applications must be received b February 10, 2009.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Salary: $36.95 - $40.50 per hour &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Committed to employment equity, the City of Toronto encourages applications from Aboriginal people, people with disabilities, members of visible minority groups and women.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accommodation will be provided in all parts of the hiring process as required under the City’s Employment Accommodation policy. Applicants need to make their needs known in advance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We thank all applicants and advise that only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;http://wx.toronto.ca/inter/hr/jobs.nsf/73d8f37fbff29b7385256fe0003ff434/1169f15fc21538788525753d0059a72b?OpenDocument</content>
    <postId>F63E17EB-0FCE-4AD0-8BCE-B76758D1ECAA</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-01-29T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Application &amp; Technical Support Specialist 1</title>
</post>
