<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi,&lt;br&gt;Please discard this mail if it has come to you in error or you are not interested in the permanent position at Mississauga given below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location: Mississauga&lt;br&gt;Type: Full time:&lt;br&gt;Salary: 55 to 65K.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;Our client is seeking an analyst/developer with mainframe and distributed J2EE technology experience to join their delivery team. The successful candidate will work on various development initiatives under the direction of a technical lead.&lt;br&gt;The delivery team is responsible for enterprise customer data utilized by our key banking systems. The application is the primary vehicle for delivering customer centric data and services to their technology clients and business partners. Today, this team is host-based utilizing IMS and DB2 technology, however they are actively in the process of extending and evolving their services over to the distributed platform using WebSphere, J2EE and Web Services technologies.&lt;br&gt;* Perform analysis, design, program/system development, unit testing, and walkthroughs following SDLC methodology while adhering to bank technology standards &lt;br&gt;* Create test plans, test and debug, using available/appropriate tools and participate in reviews &lt;br&gt;* Utilize the system development life cycle (SDLC) and project management methodology (PMLC) by participating in creating, reviewing and completing - PMLC and SDLC documentation as required. &lt;br&gt;* Contribute to team success by meeting key project milestones and overall project deliverables on time and within budget, while adhering to development and quality standards. &lt;br&gt;* Coach, lead, and mentor other team members.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Participate in knowledge transfer with the team and business units.&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;* Minimum 6 years development experience with mainframe COBOL, IMS (DB/DC), DB2, JCL, SAS, Endevor, TSO, CA7, ACF2 &lt;br&gt;* Proven workplace development skills using Java, J2EE, EJB, OO and related technologies&lt;br&gt;* Experience with IBM WebSphere Application Developer and WAS 5.1&lt;br&gt;* Experience with Spring Framework, MQ Series, SuSE Linux&lt;br&gt;* Strong analytical and problem solving skills&lt;br&gt;* Excellent communication and documentation skills&lt;br&gt;* Ability to multi-task and work with minimal supervision&lt;br&gt;* Ability to work effectively in a team setting and fast pace environment&lt;br&gt;* Experience with Financial Institution systems&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In case you fit the role and are interested, please send me your updated resume. Also please feel free to ask anyone you know who would be interested to mail me too.&lt;br&gt;Thank you&lt;br&gt;Ninad Chaubal&lt;br&gt;Account Manager&lt;br&gt;Nexstaf IT Recruitment&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F67A320A-CDE2-4B1A-AF26-FD03D331DCED</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-08-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>IT Solutions Developer</title>
</post>
