<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A leading Internet social portal requires an experienced Project Manager for its downtown Toronto, Canada office.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Description: &lt;br&gt;This position manages R&amp;D teams responsible for the development of the social portal's product line. A combination of technical product management, development project management and team management is required for this role. We are looking for the individual who combines leadership and management skills with a strong sense of technology. The ideal candidate will be familiar with Java and Oracle technologies. Direct reports include software developers, QA staff, and technical writers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primary Responsibilities include:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Overall management of site development teams, including hiring as required, performance management, resource allocation, and salary reviews.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Work with CTO and Marketing Product department to define release objectives.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Project planning and tracking.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Software Development risk assessment.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Responsible for driving, refining, and supporting the development of best practices within the managed team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 5+ years of software development experience &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; 3+ years of management/team lead experience. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Excellent written and oral communication skills. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Strong Java, UNIX (including Solaris) and Oracle database experience.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Significant scheduling and project management experience. &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience managing the development of significant software targeted to external customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mind-set: &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Understands people issues&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Process-oriented&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Planner and organizer &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Good communicator (written and verbal) &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Balances long term requirements and short term urgencies &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Considerations:&lt;br&gt;This position reports to the CTO.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F69EDFCF-2100-4B00-9425-7F61AAE472AE</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Project Manager - Java</title>
</post>
