<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Brendan</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Brendan,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you for taking the time to talk with me this morning regarding the permanent Java development role we are working on. Here is the brief description. Let me know if you are interested in pursuing this opportunity or know of anyone who is.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position: Java Developer&lt;br&gt;Mandatory Skills:&lt;br&gt;Nice-to-Have Skills:&lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto (Ontario, Canada)&lt;br&gt;Duration: Permanent&lt;br&gt;Rate/Salary: Negotiable&lt;br&gt;Start Date: ASAP&lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Procom Toronto is currently looking for a permanent employee to come in and work for a company currently offering IP address management and DNS securitization services. The company is located in North York. Our clients main stream of business focuses on creating DNS security solutions via hardware appliances.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This company is urgently looking for Intermediate and Senior Java developers to join their team. This developer will be working on an application that is running on the Linux platform. The candidate should have the following skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·Exposure to network principals and solutions like Firewalls, Routing, VLAN&lt;br&gt;·2+ years Perl scripting, Bash scripting&lt;br&gt;·Exposure (preferably experience) to TCP/IP or DNS&lt;br&gt;·Software development background&lt;br&gt;·1+ year C/C++ experience&lt;br&gt;·1+ year of developing on the Linux platform (will consider Unix)&lt;br&gt;·5+ years of experience with Java and J2EE&lt;br&gt;·Experience with J2SE nice to have&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our client’s environment is extremely demanding and they are looking for developers who are up to that challenge and are comfortable working with little or no supervision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROCOM SERVICES&lt;br&gt;A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 2700 consultants on assignment and place hundreds of people in permanent positions annually. For over 28 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our candidates. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and candidates consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheers,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desmond Hope&lt;br&gt;Technical Recruiter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Procom Consultants Group Ltd.&lt;br&gt;Direct: (416) 545-5251&lt;br&gt;Toll Free: (800) 461-4878 x371&lt;br&gt;Fax: (416) 483-8102&lt;br&gt;eMail: desmondh@procom.ca</content>
    <postId>F6AF1BEF-1B5D-4D88-85B0-876F5D2D5E9E</postId>
    <pubDate>2007-01-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer - Network, PERM</title>
</post>
