<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Position Title&lt;br&gt;Software Developer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Position Summary&lt;br&gt;Participate in the development, maintenance, support and documentation of all internally developed software applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department Summary/Mandate:&lt;br&gt;The Software Development Department within Information Technology is responsible for the development, maintenance and support of all internally developed software used by AIM Canada users, and the corresponding documentation. The department is also responsible for assisting in the planning and implementation of new software/computerization requirements by working closely with colleagues both within Information Technology and other AIM Canada business units. Additionally, Software Development also assists in preparations for system/software upgrades and in evaluating third party software, which may be used by the company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Competencies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to effectively manage a diverse workload and meet deadlines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detailed orientated with a thorough and systematic approach to problem solving.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A good communicator with strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-motivated and with an open mind.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to pick up new technology independently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ability to work independently and / or as part of a team.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Responsibilities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Develop application software in an n-tier environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maintain and enhance existing Software Applications developed for AIM Canada users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participate in the whole Software Development Life Cycle including: analyze functional and system specifications, write and test software codes, write documentation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provide production support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements/Education&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post Secondary Degree in Computer Science / Software Engineering or Post Secondary Diploma in computer related discipline with 1+ year(s) of Software Development work experience in Oracle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical Abilities and/or other Specialized Skills &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with Oracle database (preferable 8i or above) and related database development languages such as: SQL, PL/SQL and Pro*C is required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience in UNIX Shell Programming, Perl, C and Visual Basic (VB5 or above) is required.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good knowledge of UNIX and NT Operating Systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Multi-tier and Event Driven Programming concept is essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of Transaction Monitor (preferably TUXEDO) a definite advantage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Browser based application development experience a plus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of reporting tools such as Postscript, DOC1, and Crystal Report an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detail oriented with a logical mind-set and commitment / ability to deliver bug free software with fast response time a must.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working Conditions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Require to work on weekends and statutory holidays as needed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Require overtime work as needed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Require being on-call during off-hours with company provided cell phone and laptop.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Environment/Opportunities&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Career Advancement &amp;#8211; Next Level: Senior Software Developer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;cindy_jones@aimfunds.ca&lt;br&gt;AIM Trimark Investments&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F7D3CCD8-8282-425D-ADC3-5F97FF01F72A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-28T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Software Developer</title>
</post>
