<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This is an email message from an employer who viewed your confidential &lt;br&gt;resume on the Brainhunter CareerSite CareerSite.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You can reply directly to the &lt;br&gt;employer by clicking the "reply" button on your email. # 2779 Middleware Architect position available &amp;#8211; 2 year contract&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Client: large IT Consulting firm&lt;br&gt;Location: downtown Toronto&lt;br&gt;Rate per hour: $55&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The position will involve a variety of technical consulting, solution architecture/design, delivery/implementation, and deep level support activities. Successful candidate will work on a team of senior middleware high availability experts who are responsible for the delivery and deep level support of the middleware web and application server infrastructure technologies. The incumbent will also be expected to work on several customer projects concurrently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can provide deep level technical support for various middleware technologies, work with the development/deployment group to implement new customer applications, provide functionality testing for new releases, act as the focal point and custodian of web related software, establish new support procedures, receive and act on software alerts, manage release to production of software source file code, prepare and maintain software support procedures, implement day to day software changes and provide 7/24 escalation support. Will stay abreast of market trends, build our credibility, and retain client loyalty by providing the best service experience in the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Need broad knowledge of corporate policies, products, markets and processes, as well as understanding of business management principles and practices. Typically require state-of-the-art technical, functional or business knowledge.&lt;br&gt;Need skills in management, planning, problem solving, innovation, analysis, communication and negotiation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technical skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Demonstrate expert level of expertise with middleware &amp; a wide range of other technologies (SunOne, WebLogic, WebSphere, etc.)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Design architectures at global and enterprise level &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Design plans for accessibility, scalability, and availability &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Identify and address technical risk &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Troubleshoot problems and support client&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Functional skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Assess business impact of multiple technologies/strategies &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Play key role in preparing proposals and bids &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Contribute to client long-term IT strategy &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Conduct enterprise-wide needs analysis &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Develop technically feasible strategies to implement plans &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Define practice processes, standards, and policies &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Ensure technical solution meets business needs &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Evaluate effect of external factors on solution &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Provide input on enterprise architectures &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Provide status reporting &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Solicit project input from stakeholders &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professional/consulting skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Act as corporate and client advocate &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Align technical orientation to audience level &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Build and maintain relationships &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Build and maintain strategic partnerships &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Build rapport and trust with client &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Consult on IT market, strategies, and trends &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Consult on emerging technologies &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Collaborate with management &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Maintain business/technology/industry expertise &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Represent yourself as a middleware solution architect &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Sponsor information exchanges &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General business/project management skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Act as delivery architect for enterprise-wide projects &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Direct regional and global technical activities &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Provide review/input on project activities &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Use systems and tools to perform functions of job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;General skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Build rapport and trust with client &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Develop and apply listening skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Demonstrate multitasking skills &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Manage and resolve conflict &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Mediate opposing viewpoints &lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226; Negotiate equitable solutions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please forward your resume as a Word attachment, stating your availability to: greg@pegsoft.com&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F9B268CD-B44E-4FF2-A1C3-09EBCC4961E6</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-10-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Confidential Employer Message from the Brainhunter CareerSite</title>
</post>
