<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>배길상</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Contact to: Gavin Chand&lt;br&gt;Email: gavin@gurulink.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Job Title: Software Developer &lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada &lt;br&gt;Starting: ASAP &lt;br&gt;Type: Permanent &lt;br&gt;Travel: N/A &lt;br&gt;Dress Code: business casual &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Job Description:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Create design document based on requirements\\\\specification documents&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Design, develop, test and deploy IVR applications using 3rd party IVR tools&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Design, develop, test and deploy database applications using MS-SQL, Oracle and other databases&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Works with team leader and clients to determine system requirements&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Attend meeting with the internal team and the customer&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Create new or modify existing user documentation(e.g., job preparation instructions, run dependencies, recovery procedures)&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Maintain and manage customer applications and systems&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Provide 2nd level support to customers regarding issues with IVR applications or internal products&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Install and configure customer system using IVR tools and 3rd party components.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Must Have Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with programming with Java, AS400 and .NET &lt;br&gt;ASP.NET, C#, VB, C++, &lt;br&gt;Experience in working with databases i.e. - SQL Server, Oracle&lt;br&gt;Proficient in pl/sql procedural language, particularly coding related to stored procedures, functions and triggers.&lt;br&gt;Understanding of or experience with dynamic web technologies.&lt;br&gt;Self-directed and collaborative work experience. Capability to excel in a team-oriented environment. Must possess strong interpersonal, oral and written communications skills&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Nice to Have Skills:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Working knowledge on any IVR systems and telephony technology is an asset&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Experience in design and development of VXML based IVR applications are an asset&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;Working Knowledge and experience in speech engines, Java, XML, J2EE environment is a plus &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;Refer a Guru To apply for this job you must first either login or register &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>FB32C6EE-59CE-4322-8872-F444F3D438C4</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>.Net Software Developer</title>
</post>
