<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GTA-Senior Programmer - PeopleSoft &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Accenture is the world's leading provider of management and technology consulting services and solutions. Here you'll have the opportunity to develop a rewarding career, working in a collaborative, energetic and diverse environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Senior Programmer will design and code medium to high complexity software objects and repair applications to keep them performing in accordance with technical and functional specifications. In addition, a Senior Programmer will execute and document tests necessary to ensure that an application or technical environment meets performance requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Senior Programmer will document and assist in defining the functional and technical requirements of the application and support configuration changes to packaged software applications to meet business process requirements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1 year of PeopleSoft application programm마의and development experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience with PeopleCode, Application Engine&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Significant experience with 3GL programming (SQR)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong testing, configuration and deployment experience&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong oral and written communication skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong teamwork skills&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Location&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto (Mississauga), ON&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are committed to employment equity. We encourage all people, including women, visible minorities, persons with disabilities and persons of aboriginal descent to apply.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apply DIRECTLY to our website referencing job code 02I-MONP76:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent &lt;br&gt;Ref Code: 02I-MONP76&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>FC6CC1D4-0216-46EE-A743-BA3A3FB294A6</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>GTA-Senior Programmer - PeopleSoft</title>
</post>
