<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Sr. Quality Assurance Analyst/Team Lead&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position is located at our head office in Milton, ON, Canada.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About the company:&lt;br&gt;SXC has built its business by offering a comprehensive&lt;br&gt;suite of software applications to the pharmaceutical&lt;br&gt;supply chain industry. SXC's products manage the&lt;br&gt;exchange of information at various stages in the&lt;br&gt;process of prescription filing, including: billing,&lt;br&gt;processing and payment of benefit claims between&lt;br&gt;healthcare providers and payers; retail and mail order&lt;br&gt;pharmacy drug dispensing and work-flow systems;&lt;br&gt;real-time switching of claims between pharmacies and&lt;br&gt;payers; contra-indication verifications between the&lt;br&gt;pharmacist and the patient; and valuable data mining&lt;br&gt;for payers, employers, and drug manufacturers. SXC's&lt;br&gt;software raises the efficacy and lowers the cost for&lt;br&gt;all participants in the supply-chain, with a focused&lt;br&gt;effort on raising the level of patient safety and&lt;br&gt;care.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary:&lt;br&gt;This position is responsible for the oversight of quality for all deliverables from the Open Systems development team. This includes Web, PC and UNIX based products. This position is responsible for defining and administering the QA process, from design reviews to software release. The person in this position must have excellent analysis skills, excellent knowledge of QA standards, procedures and implementation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educational Requirements: &lt;br&gt;Degree in Business Administration, Computer Science, or equivalent experience &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Core Responsibilities:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53618;nsuring that QA activities are directed toward process improvement and cost effectiveness of processes&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53618;nforcement and communication of established quality policies, procedures and standards,&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;efinition and execution of Software Testing Strategies across all development projects&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53614;uthorizing the final release of all software, documentation and other products to customers.&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53630;roject management and staffing of QA testing projects&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53630;erform functional and regression testing to meet the project quality objectives,&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53618;nsure that team and individual responsibilities are understood, performance objectives are clear and measured,&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53614;ssess, prepare and deliver staff performance reviews on a timely basis,&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53626;aintain test and production-like environments for all supported customers&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53616;ompile regular quality measurement reports to management,&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53630;erform usability and documentation testing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Required Skills:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53633;trong background in quality assurance testing&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53626;inimum of 5 years experience in quality assurance&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;esire to learn new technologies&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53633;trong leadership, motivational, development and management skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53617;emonstrates peer coaching and mentoring&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53615;alances risks against costs, while remaining sensitive to the broader issues of project success&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53614;bility to work well under pressure and changing demands&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53633;trong organizational, planning, coordination and scheduling skills&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53633;elf-motivated team player with initiative, skills, and perseverance&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53614;bility to work independently&lt;br&gt;&amp;#53614;bility to multi-task&lt;br&gt;.Ability to work overtime as required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assets:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Experience with automated testing tools&lt;br&gt;-Healthcare, insurance or PBM industry experience is an asset.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Employee&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;careers.canada@sxc.com&lt;br&gt;SXC&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>FE505629-DAC7-4C03-BCA6-76B8CDD71A90</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Quality Assurance Analyst/Team Lead</title>
</post>
