<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Minotaur Software Ltd. requires an additional programmer, to write ERP (accounting, inventory, E-Commerce) applications, and do system programming. Experience with C programming is required. Other areas where experience or interest would be desirable: C++, Java, XML, EDI, ERP Applications, Database programming, Pervasive SQL, MS-SQL. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The primary responsibility of the programmer will be to write application programs from specifications to be part of our large ERP system. Applications would be reports, user input and posting functions, maintenance functions, etc. This programming is done in C, sometimes also using XML or SQL. There could also be work adding to system capabilities, including working with a Java XML client and C++ server. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excellent English communication skills are required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minotaur Software has 15 employees and has been in the same business for 15 years. It is a very stable, conservatively run company. The position is not well suited to someone who is looking for lots of excitement or constant change. We are highly customer focused, and not so concerned about being on the cutting edge of technology. Our customers are manufacturers and distributors with sales up to $250 Million. We are looking for someone who might like to work somewhere for a long time, not someone who likes to change jobs frequently. Full benefits, good working conditions, opportunity for advancement and training, competitive salary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional Information &lt;br&gt;Position Type: Full Time, Permanent&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact Information &lt;br&gt;info@minotaursoftware.com&lt;br&gt;Minotaur Software Ltd.&lt;br&gt;12 Automatic Road Suite 203&lt;br&gt;Brampton ON L6S 5N3&lt;br&gt;Fax: 905-458-5585&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>FFB2ABFE-B50F-40A6-B9FB-328E3AFDCB6F</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>C/C++/Java Application Programmer</title>
</post>
