<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;By: Robert Farkaly&lt;br&gt;June 17, 2005 01:00 PM&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relieving the Pain&lt;br&gt;=================&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As any IT manager will tell you, ensuring the reliable backup and recovery of centralized data is difficult enough. Add the myriad challenges associated with backing up data from multiple remote locations and the complexity increases exponentially. That's why remote data backup and recovery has become the bane of many an IT manager's existence. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The problem of protecting remote site data is significant. Today's remote offices tend to have increasing amounts of critical data residing locally, whether it's customer databases, e-mail, applications, or financial information. In fact, according to a study done in 2004 by Strategic Research Corporation, 60% of the data resides outside the data center and as much as 75% of this data is unprotected and unmanaged by any IT staff. What's worse, Strategic Research Corporation also reports that up to 50% of remote backups fail. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because there's more unprotected critical data residing outside the data center, companies are searching for solutions for backing up, recovering, consolidating, and managing distributed data. These solutions range from the traditional approach of using backup servers and tape drives at each location to new software-driven solutions that automate the process of backing up and consolidating remote data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Traditional Approach&lt;br&gt;========================&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Historically businesses that have attempted to protect their remote site data deployed backup servers, backup software, and tape drives or autoloaders at each location. On a daily or weekly basis, remote personnel changed the tapes and sent them to the data center or disaster recovery site. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clearly this "good enough" approach has a number of drawbacks - oft times tapes are rotated, changed, and mailed to a central site by poorly trained non-technical staff for whom backup is an afterthought at best. As a result, backup policies may not be followed properly, tapes may not be rotated or handled correctly, and failed backups may not be noticed. In addition, tapes may be lost, misplaced, or damaged during shipment to the data center. Local recoveries are equally difficult, generally requiring the assistance of central IT staff. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The traditional approach also requires IT staff to periodically travel to each remote site for system maintenance, upgrades, and troubleshooting. This quickly becomes an expensive proposition for companies with dozens or hundreds of remote locations - and represents a significant drain on costly IT resources. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Good Enough Isn't&lt;br&gt;Until recently many organizations managed to make do with the traditional approach to protecting remote data despite its many drawbacks. However, today's fast-changing business climate now dictates that businesses find a better, more reliable way to back up and recover remote data. In particular, many organizations must now comply with a host of new regulations for protecting mission-critical data. These regulations, such as Sarbanes-Oxley, govern a number of data protection factors, including how long data must be stored, how quickly it must be recovered, and how many miles apart a central and mirror site must be for effective disaster recovery. These regulations also require that businesses have full audit accountability for IT systems and processes for data protection and availability. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a result, businesses with distributed data are now examining their backup and recovery practices to identify areas that are potentially non-compliant. These internal audits often uncover significant gaps in their data protection strategies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For example, a large meat packing company in Canada has a backup server and tape drive at each of its 150 locations. Every night an employee at each location leaves the processing line, removes his gloves and smock, changes the tape, packages up the used tape for shipment, and returns to the line to complete the shift. As one might imagine, this manual process proved highly unreliable. Employees often followed improper tape rotation procedures or forgot to change the tapes altogether; tapes were prone to dirt and contamination; and shipments were lost or damaged. As a result of these factors, the company's auditors now require that it implement a more reliable backup and recovery solution for its distributed data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Besides the new regulations, other issues in remote site backup and recovery include meeting internal service-level agreements, protecting current investment in IT assets, resources and improving ROI, and providing greater control over distributed information. Together these factors are driving change in how organizations protect, consolidate, and manage their remote site data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Replication Software: Right Technology, Wrong Problem?&lt;br&gt;======================================================&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of their quest to improve remote site backup and recovery, many organizations are evaluating replication technology. Replication enables a second storage unit to duplicate the data on the original storage unit. Originally designed for duplicating storage in the data center, replication has recently gained momentum as a means of duplicating remote site data, given the relative affordability of the high-bandwidth connections that replication solutions require. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remote site data replication entails two separate steps - duplicating data from the remote site to the central site, then consolidating and backing up the entire data set centrally. While this approach improves the reliability of backing up branch office data, it introduces a number of additional challenges that businesses must consider before implementing a replication-based solution. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Replication solutions require companies to buy, install, administer, and maintain replication servers and software licenses for each remote location. This not only represents a significant hard cost, particularly for companies with a large number of remote sites, but also necessitates considerable IT expertise to deploy and manage the solution. In addition, customers with heterogeneous environments at their remote locations may face major management or standardization issues as they try to implement an organization-wide solution. They may need to rewrite backup scripts, buy new hardware and otherwise disrupt their existing backup infrastructure. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another important consideration is the actual location of the backup data. Under a replication scenario, backup data exists only at the central site, which means restoring a local file will typically require the intervention of the central IT staff. What's more the ability to restore a file at all is dependent on the network connection between the central location and the remote site. If the network goes down, the remote site is cut off from its backup data until the connection is restored.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In general, these and other challenges related to using replication for remote site backup stem from the fact that replication software wasn't designed for this purpose. As such, it has inherent limitations that are spurring a growing number of companies to seek solutions that are purpose-built for remote site backup and recovery. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Better Solution: Software-Enhanced Disk-to-Disk Appliances&lt;br&gt;===========================================================&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent months, Overland Storage has introduced a new solution that relieves the pain of consolidating and backing up remote site data. The foundation is a disk-to-disk appliance called the REO that's optimized for backup and recovery. On top of this appliance specialized software called Multi-SitePAC runs that automates the process of protecting remote site data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how it works. At each remote location, the backup software that's already in place transfers data to the appliance in virtual tape format as if it were still backing up to a tape drive or autoloader. The remote location appliances are linked via iSCSI to a central site appliance. At a user-determined time, the remote data is automatically mirrored to the central site appliance where it can be easily consolidated, managed, and even archived to tape if desired. The entire process is controlled from the central site. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are a number of benefits to this approach not the least of which is the vastly improved reliability of remote site backups. By automating the process of protecting remote site data, REO with Multi-SitePAC eliminates the potential for human error at branch offices. It also eliminates media and shipping costs - a significant savings, particularly for businesses with many remote locations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike replication solutions, customers using REO with Multi-SitePAC don't need to purchase, install, and manage additional servers or software. Instead, the platform- and backup software-agnostic appliance fits seamlessly into current environments. No changes to existing backup scripts, systems, or software are required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another important benefit is the ease and flexibility of data recovery. Because a copy of the data resides locally as well as centrally, files can be recovered from either location - no matter what the status of the network. In addition, data can often be restored locally without assistance from the central IT staff. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;br&gt;================&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's distributed businesses are struggling to comply with new regulations, fulfill service-level agreements, ensure business continuity, and reduce storage management costs across their operations. By leveraging new technologies like the REO with Multi-SitePAC, these organizations can deliver on these business imperatives while relieving the pain of protecting remote site data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About Robert Farkaly&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Farkaly is director of disk-based products at Overland Storage. He has more than 25 years of information technology sales, marketing, and business leadership experience in both startups and Fortune 100 companies. Bob is a founding member of SNIA, creator of the SAN Appliance, D2D2T and backup acceleration appliance market categories.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>819A6D20-8901-4E2C-AF9C-5B9AAA530EB2</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-06-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Automating remote data protection and disaster recovery</title>
</post>
