<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;h3&gt;config team meeting minutes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;august 18 (wed.), 2005&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;attendance: &lt;br&gt;ht (hyung-tae) &lt;br&gt;yn (yunni) &lt;br&gt;nr (nariy) &lt;br&gt;dw (dong-wook) &lt;br&gt;jk (jong-ku) &lt;br&gt;kh (kihup)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;agenda:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;To present and review assigned classes&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;API Milestones&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;UTIL &amp; Log&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;kb: &lt;br&gt;i will summarize the article contents on the coska web site.&lt;br&gt;I am going to present Util and Log classes.&lt;br&gt;I reassigned the Values class to nr.&lt;br&gt;we need to set up a test team, one person from each group&lt;br&gt;we will start doing some preparation for unit test&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;UserList &amp; User&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;jk: i updated my classes.&lt;br&gt;Do we need to have two classes?&lt;br&gt;- UserList&lt;br&gt;has main functions&lt;br&gt;has hashtable for storing user id and passwords&lt;br&gt;modifed add(...) method&lt;br&gt;- User&lt;br&gt;has 2 constructors&lt;br&gt;has user id and password accessors&lt;br&gt;two methods were renamed: encryption and decryption&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ht: UserList is for server management&lt;br&gt;ht: assymetric needs public key, symetric does not need one.&lt;br&gt;asymetric is a safer way of doing authentication. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;kb: let's ponder this later (which approach to choose) since this is not API.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;FileFilter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;dw: FileFilter&lt;br&gt;FileFilter maintains several info items - e.g. include/exclude list of files or folders&lt;br&gt;File I/O team is the target consumer of this API&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;kh: why is file size relevant?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;dw: file size will be used to determine the back up precedence&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Values&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;nr: Values has 3 major funcitons&lt;br&gt;1. contains several necessary public constants, some of these may be used in load and/or save. e.g. synchronization options&lt;br&gt;2. load &lt;br&gt;3. save&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;nr: why do we need IsUndefinedTime() method?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ht: sometimes there would be a case for comparing two times. if we provide 'undefined time', we can tell whether or not any time variable has been explicitly set.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule &amp; ScheduleList&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;yn: this is the same pattern as User &amp; UserList&lt;br&gt;one of the functions gives users an option of backup repeating interval, is this correct?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ht: yep&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;yn: i modified a few methods too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;kh: isn't Schedule supposed to be done by File IO team?&lt;br&gt;nr: i think the scheduling parameters are stored by Values. &lt;br&gt;ht: IO team does the scheduling. Schedule keeps the values that are specific to backup plan.&lt;br&gt;kb: let's ponder single vs. multiple storages for keeping configuration parameter values&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Config&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ht: Config is a place holder for the other modules.&lt;br&gt;I created TempConfig for the other team to use temporarily as needs arise (this is used for the parameters that are to be known as development progresses). Later the values in the class will be abstracted out and moved to the other actual classes. This class will be removed before product release.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++&lt;br&gt;ht: kh needs a Hangul keyboard, which might cost only about $20.00&lt;br&gt;kh: ok. i would buy one. bring a keyboard next time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;kh: we need to research on &lt;i&gt;projector&lt;/i&gt; models so that we can buy one soon. ht &amp; jk will suggest a few models for consideration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;nr (she contributed $20.00 for the projector purchase. many thanks!).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ht: we need to know nr's phone number. we could not contact her last time.&lt;br&gt;nr: 416-xxx-xxxx&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;kh: OK, this would be end of the meeting.&lt;br&gt;kh: let's spend a week or so to come up with our initial API. focus on the public ones only and disregard implemention aspects for now. The API candidate will be reviewed by the other teams to get feedback for improvements. also research background technologies - e.g. XML serialization/deserialization, encryption/decryption, and etc...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>BF1A5F08-67C0-4046-A3F2-D4EC9CCE9647</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-08-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[config] meeting minutes (8/17)</title>
</post>
