<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>신덕현</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>We always hear "the rules" from the female side.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Now here are the rules &lt;br&gt;from the male side. Please note: These are all&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;numbered "1" &lt;br&gt;ON PURPOSE! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Learn to work the toilet seat. You're&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;a big girl. If it's up, put it down. We need it up, you need it down. You&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;don't hear us complaining about&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;your leaving it down. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Sunday =&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;sports. It's like the full moon or the changing of the tides. &lt;br&gt;Let it be.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Crying is blackmail. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Ask for what you want. Let us be&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;clear on this one: Subtle hints do &lt;br&gt;not work! Strong hints do not work!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Obvious hints do not work! &lt;br&gt;Just say it! We'll get it for you, but just LET US KNOW WHAT YOU WANT!!! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. We&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;don't remember dates. Mark birthdays and anniversaries on the &lt;br&gt;calendar.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Remind us frequently beforehand. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Most guys own three pairs of&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;shoes. What makes you think we'd be any good at choosing which pair, out of&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;thirty, would look good with &lt;br&gt;your&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;dress? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Yes and No are perfectly acceptable answers to almost every&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;question. Please pick one. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Come to us with a problem only if&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;you want help solving it.&amp;nbsp; That's &lt;br&gt;what we do. Sympathy is what your&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;girlfriends are for. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Let us know about that funny noise in your car&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;engine as soon as you hear it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Anything we said six months ago&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;is inadmissible in an argument.&amp;nbsp; In fact, all comments become null and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;void after seven days.. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. If you won't dress like the Victoria's&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Secret girls, don't expect us &lt;br&gt;act like soap opera guys. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. If you&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;think you're fat, you probably are. Don't ask us.&amp;nbsp; We refuse to &lt;br&gt;answer,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;but still love you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. If something we said can be interpreted two&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ways, and one of the ways makes you sad or angry, we meant the other one.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Whenever possible, please say whatever you have to say during&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;commercials. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. Christopher Columbus did not need directions, and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;neither do we. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. ALL men see in only 16 colors, like Windows default&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;settings.&amp;nbsp; Peach, for example, is a fruit, not a color. Pumpkin is also&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;a fruit. &lt;br&gt;We have no idea what Mauve is.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. We are not mind readers and we never will be. Our lack of&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;mind-reading ability is not proof of how little we care about you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;#1. If we ask what is wrong and you say "nothing," we will act like&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;nothing's wrong. We know you are lying, but it is just not worth the&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;hassle. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. If you ask a question&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;you don't want an answer to, expect an answer you don't want to hear.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. It is neither in your best interest or ours to take the quiz&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;together. &lt;br&gt;No, it doesn't matter which quiz. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;# 1. I AM in shape.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ROUND is a shape. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you for reading this. Yes, I know, I have to&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;sleep on the couch &lt;br&gt;tonight, but did you know we really don't mind that; it's&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;like camping.</content>
    <postId>012C8008-EE98-4A3E-BB16-DA56F630A7C3</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-04-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>The Rules</title>
</post>
