<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>KB</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>==========================&lt;br&gt;(a) The Fall of Jerusalem&lt;br&gt;(b) In The Court of Saladin&lt;br&gt;(c) The Battlefield&lt;br&gt;(d) Finale&lt;br&gt;==========================&lt;br&gt;&lt;embed src=http://www.borasoft.com/mymusic/crusader.wma volume=0 autostart=true loop=0&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What do I do next?" said the bishop to the priest,&lt;br&gt;"I have spent my whole life waiting, preparing for the feast,&lt;br&gt;And now you say Jerusalem has fallen and is lost,&lt;br&gt;The king of heathen Saracen has seized the holy cross;"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then the priest said "Oh my bishop, we must put them to the sword,&lt;br&gt;For God in all His mercy will find a just reward,&lt;br&gt;For the noblemen and sinners, and knights of ready hand,&lt;br&gt;Who will be the Lord's Crusader, send word through all the land,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost,&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost,&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost;"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Tell me what to do", said the king upon his throne,&lt;br&gt;"but speak to me in whispers for we are not alone,&lt;br&gt;They tell me that Jerusalem has fallen to the hand,&lt;br&gt;Of some bedevilled eastern Heathen who has seized the Holy Land;"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then the chamberlain said "Lord, we must call upon our foes&lt;br&gt;In Spain and France and Germany to end our bitter wars,&lt;br&gt;All Christian men must be as one and gather for the fight,&lt;br&gt;You will be their leader, begin the battle cry,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost,&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost,&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost"...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ooh, high on a hill, in the town of Jerusalem,&lt;br&gt;There stood Saladin, the king of the Saracens,&lt;br&gt;Whoring and drinking and snoring and sinking, around him his army lay,&lt;br&gt;Secure in the knowledge that he had won the day;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A messenger came, blood on his feet and a wound in his chest,&lt;br&gt;"The Christians are coming!" he said, "I have seen their cross in the west,"&lt;br&gt;In a rage Saladin struck him down with his knife,&lt;br&gt;And he said "I know that this man lies,&lt;br&gt;They quarrel too much, the Christians could never unite!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am invincible, I am the king,&lt;br&gt;I am invincible, and I will win..."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Closer they came, the army of Richard the Lionheart,&lt;br&gt;Marching by day and night, with soldiers from every part,&lt;br&gt;And when the Crusaders came over the mountain and they saw Jerusalem,&lt;br&gt;They fell to their knees and prayed for her release;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They started the battle at dawn, taking the city by storm,&lt;br&gt;With horsemen and bowmen and engines of war,&lt;br&gt;They broke through the city walls,&lt;br&gt;The Heathens were flying and screaming and dying,&lt;br&gt;And the Christian swords were strong,&lt;br&gt;And Saladin ran when he heard their victory song;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are invincible, God is the king,&lt;br&gt;We are invincible, and we will win!"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What do I do now?" said the wise man to the fool,&lt;br&gt;"I have spent my whole life searching, to find the Golden Rule,&lt;br&gt;Though centuries have disappeared, the memory still remains,&lt;br&gt;Of those enemies together, could it be that way again?"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then the fool said "Oh you wise men, you really make me laugh,&lt;br&gt;With your talk of vast persuasion and searching through the past,&lt;br&gt;There is only greed and evil in the men who fight today,&lt;br&gt;The song of the Crusader has long since gone away,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost,&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost,&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem is lost...&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>2E0A4108-3927-4A25-B6E9-39CC38928DF9</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-03-17T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>CRUSADER (I - IV) - CHRIS De BURG</title>
</post>
