<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>young</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이진경</author>
            <date>2003-07-19T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>very touched!!! Thanks</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>...A TALE OF TWO FRIENDS &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A story tells that two friends were walking through the desert. &lt;br&gt;During some point of the journey, they had an argument, and one &lt;br&gt;friend slapped the other one in the face. The one who got slapped &lt;br&gt;was hurt, but without saying anything, he wrote in the sand: &lt;br&gt;"TODAY MY BEST FRIEND SLAPPED ME IN THE FACE" &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They kept on walking, until they found an oasis, where they decided to &lt;br&gt;take a bath. The one who had been slapped got stuck in the mire and &lt;br&gt;started drowning, but his friend saved him. After he recovered from the &lt;br&gt;near drowning, he carved on a stone: &lt;br&gt;"TODAY MY BEST FRIEND SAVED MY LIFE" &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The friend, who had slapped and saved his best friend, asked him, &lt;br&gt;"After I hurt you, you wrote in the sand, and now, you carve on a stone, &lt;br&gt;why?" &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other friend replied: "When someone hurts us, we should write it &lt;br&gt;down in sand, where the winds of forgiveness can erase it away, but when &lt;br&gt;someone does something good for us, we must engrave it in stone, where no &lt;br&gt;wind can ever erase it." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEARN TO WRITE YOUR HURTS IN THE SAND AND TO CARVE YOUR BLESSINGS IN &lt;br&gt;STONE. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Send this phrase to the people you'll never forget and remember to send &lt;br&gt;it also to the person who sent it to you. It's a short message to let &lt;br&gt;them know that you'll never forget them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>3885A17A-F089-4FFE-ABE7-2F99D8B01398</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>friends</title>
</post>
