<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이은목</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>박재홍</author>
            <date>2005-07-16T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Apple사 주식이 2년전에 $10 이었는데 지금은 $40 이 넘는군요. Steve Jobs 같은 visionary 공이 큰것같습니다.</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>Sonia</author>
            <date>2005-07-16T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Stay Hungry,Stay Foolsh - 용기가 나네요...</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>오승준</author>
            <date>2005-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>명강의에 명해석입니다.</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>Kelly J Lee</author>
            <date>2005-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>세월이 흘러 이렇게 말할수 있게 열심히 살아야겠지요. 초심을 잊지말자는거. 항상 명심하는데, 항상 실패하지요 ^^;; 감명입니다...</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>조복산</author>
            <date>2005-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>글 감사합니다</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>Kelly J Lee</author>
            <date>2005-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>참, 이 은목씨 오랫만입니다 넘 반가웠어요 ^____^</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>다음은 스티브 잡스가 스탠포드 대학 졸업생들에게 했던 축사를 조선일보 블로그에서 발췌온 것 입니다.&lt;br&gt;-----&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am honored to be with you today at your commencement from one of the finest universities in the world. &lt;br&gt;먼저 세계 최고의 명문으로 꼽히는 이 곳에서 여러분들의 졸업식에 참석하게 된 것을 영광으로 생각합니다. &lt;br&gt;I never graduated from college. Truth be told, this is the closest I've ever gotten to a college graduation. &lt;br&gt;저는 대학을 졸업하지 못했습니다. 태어나서 대학교 졸업식을 이렇게 가까이서 보는 것은 처음이네요. &lt;br&gt;Today I want to tell you three stories from my life. That's it. No big deal. Just three stories. &lt;br&gt;오늘, 저는 여러분께 제가 살아오면서 겪었던 세 가지 이야기를 해볼까 합니다. 별로 대단한 이야기는 아니구요. 딱 세가지만요 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first story is about connecting the dots. &lt;br&gt;먼저, 인생의 전환점에 관한 이야기입니다. &lt;br&gt;I dropped out of Reed College after the first 6 months, but then stayed around as a drop-in for another 18 months or so before I really quit. &lt;br&gt;전 리드 칼리지에 입학한지 6개월만에 자퇴했습니다. 그래도 일년 반 정도는 도강을 듣다, 정말로 그만뒀습니다. &lt;br&gt;So why did I drop out? &lt;br&gt;왜 자퇴했을까요? &lt;br&gt;It started before I was born. My biological mother was a young, unwed college graduate student, and she decided to put me up for adoption. &lt;br&gt;그 것은 제가 태어나기 전까지 거슬러 올라갑니다. 제 생모는 대학원생인 젊은 미혼모였습니다. 그래서 저를 입양보내기로 결심했던 거지요. &lt;br&gt;She felt very strongly that I should be adopted by college graduates, so everything was all set for me! &lt;br&gt;그녀는 제 미래를 생각해, 대학 정도는 졸업한 교양있는 사람이 양부모가 되기를 원했습니다. &lt;br&gt;to be adopted at birth by a lawyer and his wife. &lt;br&gt;그래서 저는 태어나자마자 변호사 가정에 입양되기로 되어 있었습니다. &lt;br&gt;Except that when I popped out they decided at the last minute that they really wanted a girl. &lt;br&gt;그들은 여자 아이를 원했던 걸로 알고 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;So my parents, who were on a waiting list, got a call in the middle of the night asking: &lt;br&gt;그들 대신 대기자 명단에 있던 양부모님들은 한 밤 중에 걸려온 전화를 받고 : &lt;br&gt;"We have an unexpected baby boy; do you want him?" &lt;br&gt;"어떡하죠? 예정에 없던 사내아이가 태어났는데, 그래도 입양하실 건가요?" &lt;br&gt;They said: "Of course." &lt;br&gt;"물론이죠" &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My biological mother later found out that my mother had never graduated from college and that my father had never graduated from high school. &lt;br&gt;그런데 알고보니 양어머니는 대졸자도 아니었고, 양아버지는 고등학교도 졸업못한 사람이어서 &lt;br&gt;She refused to sign the final adoption papers. &lt;br&gt;친어머니는 입양동의서 쓰기를 거부했습니다. &lt;br&gt;She only relented a few months later when my parents promised that I would someday go to college. &lt;br&gt;친어머니는 양부모님들이 저를 꼭 대학까지 보내주겠다고 약속한 후 몇개월이 지나서야 화가 풀렸습니다. &lt;br&gt;And 17 years later I did go to college. &lt;br&gt;17년후, 저는 대학에 입학했습니다. &lt;br&gt;But I naively chose a college that was almost as expensive as Stanford, &lt;br&gt;그러나 저는 멍청하게도 바로 이 곳, 스탠포드의 학비와 맞먹는 값비싼 학교를 선택했습니다^^ &lt;br&gt;and all of my working-class parents' savings were being spent on my college tuition. &lt;br&gt;평범한 노동자였던 부모님이 힘들게 모아뒀던 돈이 모두 제 학비로 들어갔습니다. &lt;br&gt;After six months, I couldn't see the value in it. &lt;br&gt;결국 6개월 후, 저는 대학 공부가 그만한 가치가 없다는 생각을 했습니다. &lt;br&gt;I had no idea what I wanted to do with my life and no idea how college was going to help me figure it out. &lt;br&gt;내가 진정으로 인생에서 원하는 게 무엇인지, 그리고 대학교육이 그 것에 얼마나 어떻게 도움이 될지 판단할 수 없었습니다. &lt;br&gt;And here I was spending all of the money my parents had saved their entire life. &lt;br&gt;게다가 양부모님들이 평생토록 모은 재산이 전부 제 학비로 들어가고 있었습니다. &lt;br&gt;So I decided to drop out and trust that it would all work out OK. &lt;br&gt;그래서 모든 것이 다 잘 될거라 믿고 자퇴를 결심했습니다. &lt;br&gt;It was pretty scary at the time, but looking back it was one of the best decisions I ever made. &lt;br&gt;지금 뒤돌아보면 참으로 힘든 순간이었지만, 제 인생 최고의 결정 중 하나였던 것 같습니다. &lt;br&gt;The minute I dropped out I could stop taking the required classes that didn't interest me, &lt;br&gt;자퇴를 하니 평소에 흥미없던 필수과목 대신 &lt;br&gt;and begin dropping in on the ones that looked interesting. &lt;br&gt;관심있는 강의만 들을 수 있었습니다. &lt;br&gt;It wasn't all romantic. I didn't have a dorm room, so I slept on the floor in friends' rooms, &lt;br&gt;그렇다고 꼭 낭만적인 것만도 아니었습니다. 전 기숙사에 머물 수 없었기 때문에 친구 집 마룻바닥에 자기도 했고 &lt;br&gt;I returned coke bottles for the 5￠ deposits to buy food with, &lt;br&gt;한 병당 5센트씩하는 코카콜라 빈병을 팔아서 먹을 것을 사기도 했습니다. &lt;br&gt;and I would walk the 7 miles across town every Sunday night to get one good meal a week at the Hare Krishna temple. &lt;br&gt;또 매주 일요일, 맛있는 음식을 먹기 위해 7마일이나 걸어서 헤어 크리슈나 사원의 예배에 참석하기도 했습니다. &lt;br&gt;I loved it. And much of what I stumbled into by following my curiosity and intuition turned out to be priceless later on. &lt;br&gt;맛있더군요^^ 당시 순전히 호기와 직감만을 믿고 저지른 일들이 후에 정말 값진 경험이 됐습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let me give you one example: &lt;br&gt;예를 든다면 &lt;br&gt;Reed College at that time offered perhaps the best calligraphy instruction in the country. &lt;br&gt;그 당시 리드 칼리지는 아마 미국 최고의 서체 교육을 제공했던 것 같습니다. &lt;br&gt;Throughout the campus every poster, every label on every drawer, was beautifully hand calligraphed. &lt;br&gt;학교 곳곳에 붙어있는 포스터, 서랍에 붙어있는 상표들은 너무 아름다웠구요. &lt;br&gt;Because I had dropped out and didn't have to take the normal classes, &lt;br&gt;어차피 자퇴한 상황이라, 정규 과목을 들을 필요가 없었기 때문에 &lt;br&gt;I decided to take a calligraphy class to learn how to do this. &lt;br&gt;서체에 대해서 배워보기로 마음먹고 서체 수업을 들었습니다. &lt;br&gt;I learned about serif and san serif typefaces, about varying the amount of space between different letter combinations, about what makes great typography great. &lt;br&gt;그 때 저는 세리프와 산 세리프체를 배웠는데, 서로 다른 문자끼리 결합될 때 다양한 형태의 자간으로 만들어지는 굉장히 멋진 글씨체였습니다. &lt;br&gt;It was beautiful, historical, artistically subtle in a way that science can't capture, and I found it fascinating. &lt;br&gt;'과학적'인 방식으로는 따라하기 힘든 아름답고, 유서깊고, 예술적인 것이었고, 전 그 것에 흠뻑 빠졌습니다. &lt;br&gt;None of this had even a hope of any practical application in my life. &lt;br&gt;사실, 이 때만해도 이런 것이 제 인생에 어떤 도움이 될지는 상상도 못했습니다. &lt;br&gt;But ten years later, when we were designing the first Macintosh computer, it all came back to me. &lt;br&gt;그러나 10년 후 우리가 매킨토시를 처음 구상할 때, 그 것들은 고스란히 빛을 발했습니다. &lt;br&gt;And we designed it all into the Mac. It was the first computer with beautiful typography. &lt;br&gt;우리가 설계한 매킨토시에 그 기능을 모두 집어넣었으니까요. 아마 아름다운 서체를 가진 최초의 컴퓨터가 아니였나 생각합니다. &lt;br&gt;If I had never dropped in on that single course in college, &lt;br&gt;만약 제가 그 서체 수업을 듣지 않았다면 &lt;br&gt;the Mac would have never had multiple typefaces or proportionally spaced fonts. &lt;br&gt;매킨토시의 복수서체 기능이나 자동 자간 맞춤 기능은 없었을 것이고 &lt;br&gt;And since Windows just copied the Mac, its likely that no personal computer would have them. &lt;br&gt;맥을 따라한 윈도우도 그런 기능이 없었을 것이고, 결국 개인용 컴퓨터에는 이런 기능이 탑재될 수 없었을 겁니다. &lt;br&gt;If I had never dropped out, I would have never dropped in on this calligraphy class, &lt;br&gt;만약 학교를 자퇴하지 않았다면, 서체 수업을 듣지 못했을 것이고 &lt;br&gt;and personal computers might not have the wonderful typography that they do. &lt;br&gt;결국 개인용 컴퓨터가 오늘날처럼 뛰어난 인쇄술을 가질 수도 없었을 겁니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of course it was impossible to connect the dots looking forward when I was in college. &lt;br&gt;물론 제가 대학에 있을 때는 그 순간들이 내 인생의 전환점이라는 것을 알아챌 수 없었습니다. &lt;br&gt;But it was very, very clear looking backwards ten years later. &lt;br&gt;그러나 10년이 지난 지금에서야 모든 것이 분명하게 보입니다. &lt;br&gt;Again, you can't connect the dots looking forward; you can only connect them looking backwards. &lt;br&gt;달리 말하자면, 지금 여러분은 미래를 알 수 없습니다 : 다만 현재와 과거의 사건들만을 연관시켜 볼 수 있을 뿐이죠. &lt;br&gt;So you have to trust that the dots will somehow connect in your future. &lt;br&gt;그러므로 여러분들은 현재의 순간들이 미래에 어떤식으로든지 연결된다는 걸 알아야만 합니다. &lt;br&gt;You have to trust in something - your gut, destiny, life, karma, whatever. &lt;br&gt;여러분들은 자신의 배짱, 운명, 인생, 카르마(업?) 등 무엇이든지 간에 '그 무엇'에 믿음을 가져야만 합니다. &lt;br&gt;This approach has never let me down, and it has made all the difference in my life. &lt;br&gt;이런 믿음이 저를 실망시킨 적이 없습니다. 언제나 제 인생의 고비 때마다 힘이 되워줬습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My second story is about love and loss. &lt;br&gt;두번째는 사랑과 상실입니다. &lt;br&gt;I was lucky I found what I loved to do early in life. &lt;br&gt;저는 운 좋게도 인생에서 정말 하고싶은 일을 일찍 발견했습니다. &lt;br&gt;Woz and I started Apple in my parents garage when I was 20. &lt;br&gt;제가 20살 때, 부모님의 차고에서 스티브 워즈니악과 함께 애플의 역사가 시작됐습니다. &lt;br&gt;We worked hard, and in 10 years Apple had grown from just the two of us in a garage into a $2 billion company with over 4000 employees. &lt;br&gt;차고에서 2명으로 시작한 애플은 10년 후에 4000명의 종업원을 거느린 2백억달러짜리 기업이 되었습니다. &lt;br&gt;We had just released our finest creation - the Macintosh - a year earlier, and I had just turned 30. And then I got fired. &lt;br&gt;제 나이 29살, 우리는 최고의 작품인 매킨토시를 출시했습니다. 그러나 이듬해 저는 해고당했습니다. &lt;br&gt;How can you get fired from a company you started? &lt;br&gt;내가 세운 회사에서 내가 해고 당하다니! &lt;br&gt;Well, as Apple grew we hired someone who I thought was very talented to run the company with me, &lt;br&gt;당시, 애플이 점점 성장하면서, 저는 저와 잘 맞는 유능한 경영자를 데려와야겠다고 생각했습니다. &lt;br&gt;and for the first year or so things went well. &lt;br&gt;처음 1년은 그런대로 잘 돌아갔습니다. &lt;br&gt;But then our visions of the future began to diverge and eventually we had a falling out. &lt;br&gt;그런데 언젠가부터 우리의 비전은 서로 어긋나기 시작했고, 결국 우리 둘의 사이도 어긋나기 시작했습니다. &lt;br&gt;When we did, our Board of Directors sided with him. So at 30 I was out. And very publicly out. &lt;br&gt;이 때, 우리 회사의 경영진들은 존 스컬리의 편을 들었고, 저는 30살에 쫓겨나야만 했습니다. 그 것도 아주 공공연하게. &lt;br&gt;What had been the focus of my entire adult life was gone, and it was devastating. &lt;br&gt;저는 인생의 촛점을 잃어버렸고, 뭐라 말할 수 없는 참담한 심정이었습니다. &lt;br&gt;I really didn't know what to do for a few months. &lt;br&gt;전 정말 말 그대로, 몇 개월 동안 아무 것도 할 수가 없었답니다. &lt;br&gt;I felt that I had let the previous generation of entrepreneurs down - that I had dropped the baton as it was being passed to me. &lt;br&gt;마치 달리기 계주에서 바톤을 놓친 선수처럼, 선배 벤처기업인들에게 송구스런 마음이 들었고 &lt;br&gt;I met with David Packard and Bob Noyce and tried to apologize for screwing up so badly. &lt;br&gt;데이비드 패커드(HP의 공동 창업자)와 밥 노이스(인텔 공동 창업자)를 만나 이렇게 실패한 것에 대해 사과하려했습니다. &lt;br&gt;I was a very public failure, and I even thought about running away from the valley. &lt;br&gt;저는 완전히 '공공의 실패작'으로 전락했고, 실리콘 밸리에서 도망치고 싶었습니다. &lt;br&gt;But something slowly began to dawn on me ? &lt;br&gt;그러나 제 맘 속에는 뭔가가 천천히 다시 일어나기 시작했습니다. &lt;br&gt;I still loved what I did. The turn of events at Apple had not changed that one bit. &lt;br&gt;전 여전히 제가 했던 일을 사랑했고, 애플에서 겪었던 일들조차도 그런 마음들을 꺾지 못했습니다. &lt;br&gt;I had been rejected, but I was still in love. And so I decided to start over. &lt;br&gt;전 해고당했지만, 여전히 일에 대한 사랑은 식지 않았습니다. 그래서 전 다시 시작하기로 결심했습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I didn't see it then, but it turned out that getting fired from Apple was the best thing that could have ever happened to me. &lt;br&gt;당시에는 몰랐지만, 애플에서 해고당한 것은 제 인생 최고의 사건임을 깨닫게 됐습니다. &lt;br&gt;The heaviness of being successful was replaced by the lightness of being a beginner again, less sure about everything. &lt;br&gt;그 사건으로 인해 저는 성공이란 중압감에서 벗어나서 초심자의 마음으로 돌아가 &lt;br&gt;It freed me to enter one of the most creative periods of my life. &lt;br&gt;자유를 만끽하며, 내 인생의 최고의 창의력을 발휘하는 시기로 갈 수 있게 됐습니다. &lt;br&gt;During the next five years, I started a company named NeXT, another company named Pixar,and fell in love with an amazing woman who would become my wife. &lt;br&gt;이후 5년동안 저는 '넥스트', '픽사', 그리고 지금 제 아내가 되어준 그녀와 사랑에 빠져버렸습니다. &lt;br&gt;Pixar went on to create the worlds first computer animated feature film, Toy Story, and is now the most successful animation studio in the world. &lt;br&gt;픽사는 세계 최초의 3D 애니메이션 토이 스토리를 시작으로, 지금은 가장 성공한 애니메이션 제작사가 되었습니다. &lt;br&gt;In a remarkable turn of events, Apple bought NeXT, I retuned to Apple, and the technology we developed at NeXT is at the heart of Apple's current renaissance. &lt;br&gt;세기의 사건으로 평가되는 애플의 넥스트 인수와 저의 애플로 복귀 후, 넥스트 시절 개발했던 기술들은 현재 애플의 르네상스의 중추적인 역할을 하고 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;And Laurene and I have a wonderful family together. &lt;br&gt;또한 로렌과 저는 행복한 가정을 꾸리고 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;I'm pretty sure none of this would have happened if I hadn't been fired from Apple. &lt;br&gt;애플에서 해고당하지 않았다면, 이런 엄청난 일들을 겪을 수도 없었을 것입니다 &lt;br&gt;It was awful tasting medicine, but I guess the patient needed it. &lt;br&gt;정말 독하고 쓰디 쓴 약이었지만, 이게 필요한 환자도 있는가봅니다. &lt;br&gt;Sometimes life hits you in the head with a brick. Don't lose faith. &lt;br&gt;때로 세상이 당신을 속일지라도, 결코 믿음을 잃지 마십쇼. &lt;br&gt;I'm convinced that the only thing that kept me going was that I loved what I did. &lt;br&gt;전 반드시 인생에서 해야할만 일이 있었기에, 반드시 이겨낸다고 확신했습니다. &lt;br&gt;You've got to find what you love. And that is as true for your work as it is for your lovers. &lt;br&gt;당신이 사랑하는 일을 찾아보세요. 사랑하는 사람이 내게 먼저 다가오지 않듯, 일도 그런 것이죠. &lt;br&gt;Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, &lt;br&gt;'노동'은 인생의 대부분을 차지합니다. &lt;br&gt;and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. &lt;br&gt;그런 거대한 시간 속에서 진정한 기쁨을 누릴 수 있는 방법은 스스로가 위대한 일을 한다고 자부하는 것입니다. &lt;br&gt;And the only way to do great work is to love what you do. &lt;br&gt;자신의 일을 위대하다고 자부할 수 있을 때는, 사랑하는 일을 하고있는 그 순간 뿐입니다. &lt;br&gt;If you haven't found it yet, keep looking. Don't settle. As with all matters of the heart, you'll know when you find it. &lt;br&gt;지금도 찾지 못했거나, 잘 모르겠다해도 주저앉지 말고 포기하지 마세요. 전심을 다하면 반드시 찾을 수 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;And, like any great relationship, it just gets better and better as the years roll on. &lt;br&gt;일단 한 번 찾아낸다면, 서로 사랑하는 연인들처럼 시간이 가면 갈수록 더욱 더 깊어질 것입니다. &lt;br&gt;So keep looking until you find it. Don't settle. &lt;br&gt;그러니 그 것들을 찾아낼 때까지 포기하지 마세요. 현실에 주저앉지 마세요 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My third story is about death. &lt;br&gt;세번째는 죽음에 관한 것입니다. &lt;br&gt;When I was 17, I read a quote that went something like: &lt;br&gt;17살 때, 이런 문구를 읽은 적이 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;"If you live each day as if it was your last, someday you'll most certainly be right." &lt;br&gt;하루 하루를 인생의 마지막 날처럼 산다면, 언젠가는 바른 길에 서 있을 것이다 &lt;br&gt;It made an impression on me, and since then, for the past 33 years! , &lt;br&gt;이 글에 감명받은 저는 그 후 50살이 되도록 &lt;br&gt;I have looked in the mirror every morning and asked myself: &lt;br&gt;거울을 보면서 자신에게 묻곤 했습니다. &lt;br&gt;"If today were the last day of my life, would I want to do what I am about to do today?" &lt;br&gt;오늘이 내 인생의 마지막 날이라면, 지금 하려고 하는 일을 할 것인가? &lt;br&gt;And whenever the answer has been "No" for too many days in a row, I know I need to change something. &lt;br&gt;아니오!라는 답이 계속 나온다면, 다른 것을 해야한다는 걸 깨달았습니다. &lt;br&gt;Remembering that I'll be dead soon is the most important tool I've ever encountered to help me make the big choices in life. &lt;br&gt;인생의 중요한 순간마다 '곧 죽을지도 모른다'는 사실을 명심하는 것이 저에게는 가장 중요한 도구가 됩니다. &lt;br&gt;Because almost everything ? &lt;br&gt;왜냐구요? &lt;br&gt;all external expectations, all pride, all fear of embarrassment or failure - &lt;br&gt;외부의 기대, 각종 자부심과 자만심. 수치스러움와 실패에 대한 두려움들은 &lt;br&gt;these things just fall away in the face of death, leaving only what is truly important. &lt;br&gt;'죽음' 앞에서는 모두 밑으로 가라앉고, 오직 진실만이 남기 때문입니다. &lt;br&gt;Remembering that you are going to die is the best way I know to avoid the trap of thinking you have something to lose. &lt;br&gt;죽음을 생각하는 것은 무엇을 잃을지도 모른다는 두려움에서 벗어나는 최고의 길입니다. &lt;br&gt;You are already naked. There is no reason not to follow your heart. &lt;br&gt;여러분들이 지금 모두 잃어버린 상태라면, 더이상 잃을 것도 없기에 본능에 충실할 수 밖에 없습니다. &lt;br&gt;About a year ago I was diagnosed with cancer. &lt;br&gt;저는 1년 전쯤 암진단을 받았습니다. &lt;br&gt;I had a scan at 7:30 in the morning, and it clearly showed a tumor on my pancreas. &lt;br&gt;아침 7시 반에 검사를 받았는데, 이미 췌장에 종양이 있었습니다. &lt;br&gt;I didn't even know what a pancreas was. &lt;br&gt;그전까지는 췌장이란 게 뭔지도 몰랐는데요. &lt;br&gt;The doctors told me this was almost certainly a type of cancer that is incurable, and that I should expect to live no longer than three to six months. &lt;br&gt;의사들은 길어야 3개월에서 6개월이라고 말했습니다. &lt;br&gt;My doctor advised me to go home and get my affairs in order, which is doctor's code for prepare to die. &lt;br&gt;주치의는 집으로 돌아가 신변정리를 하라고 했습니다. 죽음을 준비하라는 뜻이었죠. &lt;br&gt;It means to try to tell your kids everything you thought you'd have the next 10 years to tell them in just a few months. &lt;br&gt;그 것은 내 아이들에게 10년동안 해줄수 있는 것을 단 몇달안에 다 해치워야된단 말이었고 &lt;br&gt;It means to make sure everything is buttoned up so that it will be as easy as possible for your family. &lt;br&gt;임종 시에 사람들이 받을 충격이 덜하도록 매사를 정리하란 말이었고 &lt;br&gt;It means to say your goodbyes. &lt;br&gt;작별인사를 준비하라는 말이었습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I lived with that diagnosis all day. &lt;br&gt;전 불치병 판정을 받았습니다. &lt;br&gt;Later that evening I had a biopsy, where they stuck an endoscope down my throat, &lt;br&gt;through my stomach and into my intestines, put a needle into my pancreas and got a few cells from the tumor. &lt;br&gt;그 날 저녁 위장을 지나 장까지 내시경을 넣어서 암세포를 채취해 조직검사를 받았습니다. &lt;br&gt;I was sedated, but my wife, who was there, told me that when they viewed the cells under a microscope &lt;br&gt;저는 마취상태였는데, 후에 아내가 말해주길, 현미경으로 세포를 분석한 결과 &lt;br&gt;the doctors started crying because it turned out to be a very rare form of pancreatic cancer that is curable with surgery. &lt;br&gt;치료가 가능한 아주 희귀한 췌장암으로써, 의사들까지도 기뻐서 눈물을 글썽였다고 합니다. &lt;br&gt;I had the surgery and I'm fine now. &lt;br&gt;저는 수술을 받았고, 지금은 괜찮습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This was the closest I've been to facing death, and I hope its the closest I get for a few more decades. &lt;br&gt;그 때만큼 제가 죽음에 가까이 가 본 적은 없는 것 같습니다. 또한 앞으로도 가고 싶지 않습니다^^ &lt;br&gt;Having lived through it, I can now say this to you with a bit more certainty than when death was a useful but purely intellectual concept: &lt;br&gt;이런 경험을 해보니, '죽음'이 때론 유용하단 것을 머리로만 알고 있을 때보다 더 정확하게 말할 수 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;No one wants to die. Even people who want to go to heaven don't want to die to get there. &lt;br&gt;아무도 죽길 원하지 않습니다. 천국에 가고싶다는 사람들조차도 당장 죽는 건 원치 않습니다. &lt;br&gt;And yet death is the destination we all share. No one has ever escaped it. &lt;br&gt;우리 모두는 언젠가는 다 죽을 것입니다. 아무도 피할 수 없죠. &lt;br&gt;And that is as it should be, because Death is very likely the single best invention of Life. &lt;br&gt;삶이 만든 최고의 작품이 '죽음'이니까요. &lt;br&gt;It is Life's change agent. It clears out the old to make way for the new. &lt;br&gt;죽음이란 삶의 또다른 모습입니다. 죽음은 새로운 것이 헌 것을 대체할 수 있도록 만들어줍니다. &lt;br&gt;Right now the new is you, but someday not too long from now, you will gradually become the old and be cleared away. &lt;br&gt;지금의 여러분들은 '새로움'이란 자리에 서 있습니다. 그러나 언젠가는 여러분들도 새로운 세대들에게 그 자리를 물려줘야할 것입니다. &lt;br&gt;Sorry to be so dramatic, but it is quite true. &lt;br&gt;너무 극단적으로 들렸다면 죄송하지만, 사실이 그렇습니다. &lt;br&gt;Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life. &lt;br&gt;여러분들의 삶은 제한되어 있습니다. 그러니 낭비하지 마십쇼. &lt;br&gt;Don't be trapped by dogma - which is living with the results of other people's thinking. &lt;br&gt;도그마- 다른 사람들의 생각-에 얽매이지 마십쇼 &lt;br&gt;Don't let the noise of other's opinions drown out your own inner voice. &lt;br&gt;타인의 잡음이 여러분들 내면의 진정한 목소리를 방해하지 못하게 하세요 &lt;br&gt;And most important, have the courage to follow your heart and intuition. &lt;br&gt;그리고 가장 중요한 것은 마음과 영감을 따르는 용기를 가지는 것입니다. &lt;br&gt;They somehow already know what you truly want to become. Everything else is secondary. &lt;br&gt;이미 마음과 영감은 당신이 진짜로 무엇을 원하는지 알고 있습니다. 나머지 것들은 부차적인 것이죠. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When I was young, there was an amazing publication called The Whole Earth Catalog, which was one of the bibles of my generation. &lt;br&gt;제가 어릴 때, 제 나이 또래라면 다 알만한 '지구 백과'란 책이 있었습니다. &lt;br&gt;It was created by a fellow named Stewart Brand not far from here in Menlo Park, and he brought it to life with his poetic touch. &lt;br&gt;여기서 그리 멀지 않은 먼로 파크에 사는 스튜어트 브랜드란 사람이 쓴 책인데, 자신의 모든 걸 불어넣은 책이었지요. &lt;br&gt;This was in the late 1960's, before personal computers and desktop publishing, so it was all made with typewriters, scissors, and polaroid cameras. &lt;br&gt;PC나 전자출판이 존재하기 전인 1960년대 후반이었기 때문에, 타자기, 가위, 폴라노이드로 그 책을 만들었습니다. &lt;br&gt;It was sort of like Google in paperback form, 35 years before Google came along: &lt;br&gt;35년 전의 책으로 된 구글이라고나 할까요. &lt;br&gt;it was idealistic, and overflowing with neat tools and great notions. &lt;br&gt;그 책은 위대한 의지와 아주 간단한 도구만으로 만들어진 역작이었습니다. &lt;br&gt;Stewart and his team put out several issues of The Whole Earth Catalog, and then when it had run its course, they put out a final issue. &lt;br&gt;스튜어트와 친구들은 몇 번의 개정판을 내놓았고, 수명이 다할 때쯤엔 최종판을 내놓았습니다. &lt;br&gt;It was the mid-1970s, and I was your age. &lt;br&gt;그 때가 70년대 중반, 제가 여러분 나이 때였죠. &lt;br&gt;On the back cover of their final issue was a photograph of an early morning country road, &lt;br&gt;최종판의 뒤쪽 표지에는 이른 아침 시골길 사진이 있었는데, &lt;br&gt;the kind you might find yourself hitchhiking on if you were so adventurous. &lt;br&gt;아마 모험을 좋아하는 사람이라면 히치하이킹/엄지들고 차를 유혹해서 빌려타며 여행하는 것/을 하고싶다는 생각이 들정도였지요. &lt;br&gt;Beneath it were the words: "Stay Hungry. Stay Foolish." &lt;br&gt;그 사진 밑에는 이런 말이 있었습니다 : 배고픔과 함께, 미련함과 함께 &lt;br&gt;It was their farewell message as they signed off. Stay Hungry. Stay Foolish. &lt;br&gt;배고픔과 함께, 미련함과 함께. 그 것이 그들의 마지막 작별인사였습니다. &lt;br&gt;And I have always wished that for myself. And now, as you graduate to begin anew, I wish that for you. &lt;br&gt;저는 이제 새로운 시작을 앞둔 여러분들이 여러분의 분야에서 이런 방법으로 가길 원합니다. &lt;br&gt;Stay Hungry. Stay Foolish. &lt;br&gt;배고픔과 함께. 미련함과 함께 &lt;br&gt;Thank you all very much. &lt;br&gt;감사합니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(This is the text of the Commencement address by Steve Jobs, CEO of Apple Computer and of Pixar Animation Studios, delivered on June 12, 2005.)</content>
    <postId>5DD8BA3D-688F-419E-823A-8631DF692763</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-07-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>스티브 잡스 스탠포드 대학 졸업식 축사</title>
</post>
