<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>박선교</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I've just read a beautuful article and like to share with golfers and to-be-golgers:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; "Buddy golf trips in Myrtle Beach: For one fleeting moment, the Strand was all ours&lt;br&gt;When the sun breaks over Prestwick Country Club in Myrtle Beach, S.C., pale light creeps up the ninth and 18th fairways, mirror images of each other, and catches in the large pond between. The silhouettes of cranes dart back and forth, but everything is quiet. It is a beautiful sight.&lt;br&gt;I know this because I was there recently, sitting at the front of the cart line at 7 a.m. with my father and brother, drinking coffee, laughing, bracing against the cold and watching the daybreak for enough light to begin our round.&lt;br&gt;It was a classic male-bonding moment, there in that place, more or less alone, a golf course just waking up for the day.&lt;br&gt;Myrtle Beach is full of such moments and it's easy to see why this strand of sand and golf remains so popular with groups looking for a guys-only golf getaway, a place where guys can come, hang out, get away from it all.&lt;br&gt;My father and brother have been going to Myrtle Beach for four years on an annual four-day golf weekend. The wives stay behind. A condo is procured (near a convivial drinking establishment), courses are chosen with much care and discussion, a few favorite restaurants are revisited.&lt;br&gt;I live abroad, so this year was my first with them. Our Myrtle Beach stay was probably like yours. We battled King's North and Barefoot, we swapped skins, played some high-low and wolf and retired to Molley Darcy's for beers and relived the day's events. Sometimes we'd eat there, or the House of Blues, or Bonefish.&lt;br&gt;Golf, of course, was the point, and we played a lot of it: 27 holes one day, 36 the next two. A lot of you were doing the same: We saw you, in your coordinated shirts, playing scrambles and match-play, hugging one another on the 18th, cheering on Boston College or Ohio State or the Red Sox later that night over pitchers.&lt;br&gt;We saw you guys everywhere, having a good time. Everywhere, that is, except on the first tee that early morning at Prestwick. It was only my father, brother and me, and at that moment Myrtle Beach seemed to belong to us."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Source: WorldGolf.com</content>
    <postId>646270C5-664B-4C3D-8E70-A1CE7B7CC295</postId>
    <pubDate>2007-10-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Golf and Family bonds</title>
</post>
