<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>stevenkim</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Some very good works of wisdom. Read, enjoy and learn!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This was written by an 83 year old...The last line says it all. Am sure you&lt;br&gt;can relate to it now. If not now, perhaps sooner than later.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dear Bertha,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm reading more and dusting less. I'm sitting in the yard and&lt;br&gt;admiring the view without fussing about the weeds in the&lt;br&gt;garden. I'm spending more time with my family and friends and&lt;br&gt;less time working. Whenever possible, life should be a pattern&lt;br&gt;of experiences to savor, not to endure. I'm trying to recognize&lt;br&gt;these moments now and cherish them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I'm not "saving" anything; we use our good china and crystal&lt;br&gt;for every special event such as losing a pound, getting the sink&lt;br&gt;unstopped, or the first Amaryllis blossom.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I wear my good blazer to the market. My theory is if I&lt;br&gt;look prosperous, I can shell out $28.49 for one small bag of&lt;br&gt;groceries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I'm not saving my good perfume for special parties, but&lt;br&gt;wearing it for clerks in the hardware store and tellers at the&lt;br&gt;bank.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;"Someday" and "one of these days" are losing their grip&lt;br&gt;on my vocabulary; if it's worth seeing or hearing or doing, I&lt;br&gt;want to see and hear and do it now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I'm not sure what others would've done had they known they&lt;br&gt;wouldn't be here for the tomorrow that we all take for granted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I think they would have called family members and a few&lt;br&gt;close friends. They might have called a few former friends to&lt;br&gt;apologize and mend fences for past squabbles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I like to think they would have gone out for a Chinese&lt;br&gt;dinner or for whatever their favorite food was.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I'm guessing; I'll never know.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It's those little things left undone that would make me&lt;br&gt;angry if I knew my hours were limited. Angry because I hadn't&lt;br&gt;written certain letters that I intended to write one of these&lt;br&gt;days. Angry and sorry that I didn't tell my husband and parents&lt;br&gt;often enough how much I truly love them. I'm trying very hard&lt;br&gt;not to put off, hold back, or save anything that would add laughter&lt;br&gt;and luster to our lives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;And every morning when I open my eyes, I tell myself that&lt;br&gt;it is special. Every day, every minute, every breath truly is&lt;br&gt;a gift from God.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you received this, it is because someone cares for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you're too busy to take the few minutes that it takes&lt;br&gt;right now to forward this, would it be the first time you didn't&lt;br&gt;do the little thing that would make a difference in your relationships?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I can tell you it certainly won't be the last.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Take a few minutes to send this to a few people you care&lt;br&gt;about, just to let them know that you're thinking of them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;"People say true friends must always hold hands, but true&lt;br&gt;friends don't need to hold hands because they know the other&lt;br&gt;hand will always be there."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I don't believe in miracles. I rely on them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Life may not be the party we hoped for, but while we are&lt;br&gt;here we might as well dance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>75ADDDCA-D7ED-4927-A03A-2B5C9DEA6EBB</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Words of Wisidom from an Senior.</title>
</post>
