<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Jin</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Thought this might brighten your day! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'll be happy when... &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We convince ourselves that life will be better after we get married, have a baby, then another. Then we are frustrated that the kids aren't old enough and we'll be more content when they are. After that, we're frustrated that we have teenagers to deal with. We will certainly be happy when they are out of that stage. We tell ourselves that our life will be complete when our spouse gets his or her act together, when we get a nicer car, when we are able to go on a nice vacation or when we retire. The truth is there's no better time to be happy than right now. If not now, when? Your life will always be filled with challenges. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;It's best to admit this to yourself and decide to be happy anyway. Happiness is the way. So, treasure every moment that you have and treasure it more because you shared it with someone special, special enough to spend your time with . and remember that time waits for no one. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;So, stop waiting ... &lt;br&gt;Until your car or home is paid off. &lt;br&gt;Until you get a new car or home. &lt;br&gt;Until your kids leave the house. &lt;br&gt;Until you go back to school. &lt;br&gt;Until you finish school. &lt;br&gt;Until you lose 10 lbs. &lt;br&gt;Until you gain 10 lbs. &lt;br&gt;Until you get married. &lt;br&gt;Until you get a divorce. &lt;br&gt;Until you have kids. &lt;br&gt;Until you retire. &lt;br&gt;Until summer.. &lt;br&gt;Until spring. &lt;br&gt;Until winter. &lt;br&gt;Until fall. &lt;br&gt;Until you die. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;There is no better time than right now to be happy. Happiness is a journey, not a destination. So work like you don't need money, love like you've never been hurt, and, dance like no one's watching. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;If you want to brighten someone's day, pass this on to someone special. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I just did! &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>7C918C82-F07D-4871-8B5C-10CB0CAA2FE9</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-04-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Hope this one makes your day - everyday</title>
</post>
