<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Kelly J Lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>25&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SIGNS YOU HAVE GROWN UP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Your houseplants are alive, and you can't smoke any of them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Having sex in a twin bed is out of the question.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. You keep more food than beer in the fridge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. 6:00 a.m . is when you get up, not when you go to bed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. You hear your favorite song in an elevator.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. You watch the Weather Channel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Your friends marry and divorce instead of "hook up" and "break up."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. You go from 130 days of vacation time to 14.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. Jeans and a sweater no longer qualify as "dressed up."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. You're the one calling the police because those %&amp;@# kids next&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;door won't turn down the stereo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;11. Older relatives feel comfortable telling sex jokes around you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;12. You don't know what time Taco Bell closes anymore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;13. Your car insurance goes down and your car payments go up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;14. You feed your dog Science Diet instead of McDonald's leftovers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;15. Sleeping on the couch makes your back hurt.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;16. You take naps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;17. Dinner and a movie is the whole date instead of the beginning of one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;18. Eating a basket of chicken wings at 3 AM would severely upset, rather than settle, your stomach.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;19. You go to the drug store for ibuprofen and antacid, not condoms&lt;br&gt;and pregnancy tests.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;20. A $4.00 bottle of wine is no longer "pretty good sh*t."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;21. You actually eat breakfast food at breakfast time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;22. "I just can't drink the way I used to" replaces "I'm never going to drink that much again."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;23. 90% of the time you spend in front of a computer is for real work.&lt;br&gt;24. You drink at home to save money before going to a bar.&lt;br&gt;25. When you find out your friend is pregnant you congratulate them instead of asking "Oh sh*t what the hell happened?"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonus:&lt;br&gt;26: You read this entire list looking desperately for one sign that doesn't apply to you and can't find one to save your sorry old ass.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;오늘 집에가면 노트북 홈페이지(weather channel)부터 바꿔야겠습니다. ^^;;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>9738292D-3511-47A0-9280-E95937A8855A</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-12-06T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>25  SIGNS YOU HAVE GROWN UP</title>
</post>
