<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최종구</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>Steven Kim</author>
            <date>2004-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>Thanks...This is exactly what I need to know..Khhh...^o^</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>임정숙</author>
            <date>2004-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>It's really funny... I enjoyed reading this....</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>하하하</author>
            <date>2004-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>고맙긴 뭐가 고마우세요? 스티븐씨! 맨날 영어 안 쓰세요? 지금도 영어로 답 하고 계시네요...뭐...^0^</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>A word on fat&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those of you who watch what you eat, here's the final word on nutrition and health. It's a relief to know the truth after all those conflicting medical studies:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. The Japanese eat very little fat and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans, British or Canadians.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. The Mexicans eat a lot of fat and also suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans, British or Canadians.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. The Japanese drink very little red wine and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans, British or Canadians.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. The Italians drink large amounts of red wine and also suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans, British or Canadians.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. The Germans drink a lot of beer and eat lots of sausages and fats and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans, British or Canadians.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Ukrainians drink a lot of vodka, eat a lot of perogies, cabbage rolls and suffer fewer heart attacks than the Americans, British or Canadians.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCLUSION: Eat and drink what you like. Speaking English is apparently what kills you.</content>
    <postId>997C4437-3C7A-4BC4-A4A5-A7499280E25A</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Nutritional Wisdom</title>
</post>
