<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>KB</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>S. Suh Lee</author>
            <date>2006-04-23T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Wow!</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>My daughter's favorite, and became mine too.&lt;br&gt;Enjoy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;embed src=http://www.borasoft.com/mymusic/addicted.mp3 volume=0 autostart=true loop=0&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's like you're a drug&lt;br&gt;It's like you're a demon I can't face down&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm stuck&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm running from you all the time&lt;br&gt;And I know I let you have all the power&lt;br&gt;It's like the only company I seek is misery all around&lt;br&gt;It's like you're a leech&lt;br&gt;Sucking the life from me&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't breathe&lt;br&gt;Without you inside of me&lt;br&gt;And I know I let you have all the power&lt;br&gt;And I realize I'm never gonna quit you over time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't breathe&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't see anything&lt;br&gt;Nothing but you&lt;br&gt;I'm addicted to you&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't think&lt;br&gt;Without you interrupting me&lt;br&gt;In my thoughts&lt;br&gt;In my dreams&lt;br&gt;You've taken over me&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm not me&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm not me&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm lost&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm giving up slowly&lt;br&gt;It's like you're a ghost that's haunting me&lt;br&gt;Leave me alone&lt;br&gt;And I know these voices in my head&lt;br&gt;Are mine alone&lt;br&gt;And I know I'll never change my ways&lt;br&gt;If I don't give you up now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't breathe&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't see anything&lt;br&gt;Nothing but you&lt;br&gt;I'm addicted to you&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't think&lt;br&gt;Without you interrupting me&lt;br&gt;In my thoughts&lt;br&gt;In my dreams&lt;br&gt;You've taken over me&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm not me&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm not me&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm hooked on you&lt;br&gt;I need a fix&lt;br&gt;I can't take it&lt;br&gt;Just one more hit&lt;br&gt;I promise I can deal with it&lt;br&gt;I'll handle it, quit it&lt;br&gt;Just one more time&lt;br&gt;Then that's it&lt;br&gt;Just a little bit more to get me through this&lt;br&gt;I'm hooked on you&lt;br&gt;I need a fix&lt;br&gt;I can't take it&lt;br&gt;Just one more hit&lt;br&gt;I promise I can deal with it&lt;br&gt;I'll handle it, quit it&lt;br&gt;Just one more time&lt;br&gt;Then that's it&lt;br&gt;Just a little bit more to get me through this&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't breathe&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't see anything&lt;br&gt;Nothing but you&lt;br&gt;I'm addicted to you&lt;br&gt;It's like I can't think&lt;br&gt;Without you interrupting me&lt;br&gt;In my thoughts&lt;br&gt;In my dreams&lt;br&gt;You've taken over me&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm not me&lt;br&gt;It's like I'm not me&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C7C919EA-0AFC-44E3-B4E6-9DFA58C5AC7E</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-04-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Addicted - Kelly Clarkson</title>
</post>
