<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>khboo</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Golf Balls, Life &amp; Two Cans of Beer &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A professor stood before his philosophy class&lt;br&gt;and had some items in front of him. When the class&lt;br&gt;began, wordlessly, he picked up a very large and&lt;br&gt;empty mayonnaise jar and proceeded to fill it with&lt;br&gt;golf balls. He then asked the students if the jar&lt;br&gt;was full?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They agreed that it was. So the professor then picked&lt;br&gt;up a box of pebbles and poured them into the jar.&lt;br&gt;He shook the jar lightly. The pebbles rolled into the&lt;br&gt;open areas between the golf balls. He then asked&lt;br&gt;the students again if the jar was full.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They agreed it was. So the professor next picked up a box of &lt;br&gt;sand and poured it into the jar. Of course, the sand filled up &lt;br&gt;everything else. He asked once more if the jar was full. The &lt;br&gt;students responded with an unanimous "yes."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The professor then produced two cans of beer from under the &lt;br&gt;table and poured the entire contents into the jar, effectively&lt;br&gt;filling the empty space between the sand. The students&lt;br&gt;laughed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Now," said the professor, as the laughter subsided,&lt;br&gt;"I want you to recognize that this jar represents&lt;br&gt;your life. The golf balls are the important things-your&lt;br&gt;family, your health, your children, your friends, your&lt;br&gt;favorite passions-things that if everything else was&lt;br&gt;lost and only they remained, your life would still be full.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pebbles are the other things that matter&lt;br&gt;like your job, your house, your car. The sand&lt;br&gt;is everything else-the small stuff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If you put the sand into the jar first," he &lt;br&gt;continued, "there is no room for the pebbles or the golf balls. &lt;br&gt;The same goes for life. If you spend all your time and energy &lt;br&gt;on the small stuff, you will never have room for the&lt;br&gt;things that are important to you. Pay attention to the things &lt;br&gt;that are critical to your happiness. Play with your children. Take &lt;br&gt;time to get medical checkups. Take your partner out to dinner.&lt;br&gt;Play another 18. There will always be time to clean&lt;br&gt;the house, and fix the disposal."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Take care of the golf balls first, the things that really&lt;br&gt;matter. Set your priorities. The rest is just sand."&lt;br&gt;One of the students raised her hand and inquired&lt;br&gt;what the beer represented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The professor smiled. "I'm glad you asked. It just&lt;br&gt;goes to show you that no matter how full your life may seem, &lt;br&gt;there's always room for a couple of beers."</content>
    <postId>DB45ACD3-29D4-4DBD-8694-5CFCF6195147</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-09-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Golf Balls, Life &amp; Two Cans of Beer</title>
</post>
