<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>박재홍</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>KB</author>
            <date>2006-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>하하하하하하하하하하하하</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>허현옥</author>
            <date>2006-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>다이어트 워터 같은 경우는 잘못하면 뺨 맞지 싶네요..^^; 19번은 아이들에게 너무 가혹한 농담이 아닐까요..^^;;;</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>지나가다</author>
            <date>2006-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>8번 11번 항상 하고 잇어영</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>오승준</author>
            <date>2006-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>20. wRITE eVERY fIRST lETTER iN lOWER cASE.</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>kelly</author>
            <date>2006-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>혹시 박 재홍씨가 항상 실천하시는건 아니죠? ㅋㅋㅋ</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>1. At Lunch Time, Sit In Your Parked Car With Sunglasses on and point a Hair Dryer At Passing Cars. See If They Slow Down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Page Yourself Over The Intercom. Don't Disguise Your Voice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Every Time Someone Asks You To Do Something, Ask If They Want Fries with that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Put Your Garbage Can On Your Desk And Label It "In."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Put Decaf In The Coffee Maker For 3 Weeks. Once Everyone has Gotten Over Their Caffeine Addictions, Switch to Espresso.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. In The Memo Field Of All Your Checks, Write "For Smuggling Diamonds"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Finish All Your sentences with "In Accordance With The Prophecy."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. Don't use any punctuation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. As Often As Possible, Skip Rather Than Walk.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. Order a Diet Water whenever you go out to eat, with a serious face.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;11. Specify That Your Drive-through Order Is "To Go."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;12. Sing Along At The Opera.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;13. Go To A Poetry Recital And Ask Why The Poems Don't R! hyme?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;14. Put Mosquito Netting Around Your Work Area And Play tropical Sounds All Day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;15. Five Days In Advance, Tell Your Friends You Can't Attend Their Party Because You're Not In The Mood.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;16. Have Your Co-workers Address You By Your Wrest ling Name, Rock Bottom.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;17. When The Money Comes Out The ATM, Scream "I Won!, I Won!"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;18. When Leaving The Zoo, Start Running Towards The Parking lot, Yelling "Run For Your Lives, They're Loose!!"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;19. Tell Your Children Over Dinner. "Due To The Economy, We Are Going To Have To Let One Of You Go."</content>
    <postId>F4EDE4A3-E5F4-47F1-9B15-C6236B09B3B1</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Ways to Maintain A Healthy Level Of Insanity</title>
</post>
