<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>오승준</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>OME IMPORTANT THEOLOGICAL QUESTIONS ARE ANSWERED&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF WE THINK OF GOD AS A COMPUTER PROGRAMMER.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Does God control everything that happens in my life?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: He could, if he used the debugger, but it's tedious to step through all&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;those variables.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Why does God allow evil to happen?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: God thought he eliminated evil in one of the earlier revs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Does God know everything?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: He likes to think so, but he is often amazed to find out what goes on in&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the overnight job.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: What causes God to intervene in earthly affairs?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: If a critical error occurs, the system pages him automatically and he&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;logs on from home to try to bring it up. Otherwise things can wait until&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;tomorrow.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: How come the Age of Miracles Ended?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: That was the development phase of the project, now we are in the&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;maintenance phase.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Will there be another Universe after the Big Bang?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: A lot of people are drawing things on the white board, but doubt that it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;will&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ever be implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Who is Satan?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Satan is an MIS director who takes credit for more powers than he&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;actually possesses, so people who aren't programmers are scared of him.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;God thinks of him as irritating but irrelevant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: What is the role of sinners?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Sinners are the people who find new and imaginative ways to mess up&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the system when God has made it idiot-proof.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Where will I go after I die?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Onto a backup tape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Will I be reincarnated?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Not unless there is a special need to recreate you. And searching&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;backup files is a major hassle, so if there is a request for you, God will&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;just say that the tape has been lost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Am I unique and special in the universe?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: There are over 10,000 major university and corporate sites running&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;exact duplicates of you in the present release version.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: What is the purpose of the universe?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: God created it because he values elegance and simplicity, but then the&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;users and managers demanded he tack senseless features onto it and now&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;everything is more complicated and expensive than ever.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: If I pray to God, will he listen?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: You can waste his time telling him what to do, or you can just get off&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;his back and let him program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: What is the one true religion?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: All systems have their advantages and disadvantages, so just pick the&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;one that best suits your needs and don't let anyone put you down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: How can I protect myself from evil?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Change your password every month and don't make it a name, a common&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;word, or a date like your birthday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Some people claim they hear the voice of God. Is this true?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: They are much more likely to receive e-mail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q: Some people say God is Love.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: That is not a question. Please restate your query in the form of a&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;question. Abort, Retry, Fail?&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>FD28DC3D-98B8-4DEA-80F3-B0C06CBC068E</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-03-25T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>IF WE THINK OF GOD AS A COMPUTER PROGRAMMER.</title>
</post>
