<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>윤만호</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;너무 걱정 안했으면 좋겠습니다.&lt;br&gt;무덤덤하고 지루한 일상에서 &lt;br&gt;깜짝 놀라게 하는 얘깃거리정도가 아닌가....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Urban legends often derive from jokes or other bits of humor. As they circulate bits of "fact" are added while obvious signs of the tale's fictional nature are removed or replaced. The tale of the deadly toilet spider is a prime example of this type of social engineering. &lt;br&gt;==============================&lt;br&gt;==============================&lt;br&gt;This one has a few things wrong with it: There is no such thing as the Journal of the United Medical Association, nor is it likely that any such article on this subject by "Dr. Beverly Clark" ever appeared in any medical journal. Additionally, the Civil Aeronautics Board disbanded in 1984! There have been no reliable and valid accounts of such mysterious injuries or deaths at Olive Garden or any other restaurant. &lt;br&gt;This urban legend has taken many forms over the years. As it circulates, more detail is removed or replaced to make it seem more believable and less like the joke it was probably intended to be. This latest version is stripped of many of the "facts" that made earlier versions easy to research and debunk. The earliest Internet version (1999) I found links the mysterious deaths to "Big Chappies" restaurant in "Blare" airport in Chicago (presumably an abberation of "O'Hare") and identifies the spider as the hilariously-named "South American Blush Spider" or "arachnius gluteus." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omission of the fictitious airport and replacement of the equally fake spider with a real one (Two-Striped Telamonia) in this version, combined with a heady case of "False Attribution Syndrome" have given this old hoax new life. &lt;br&gt;This is not a notice from the Univeristy of North Florida. The school became unwillingly affiliated with this hoax when one of its employees (presumably "Officer Sylvia Steele," though her title seems incongruous with a position within the Science Department) received and forwarded it, inadvertently adding her signature and credibilitity to the message. Since it would seem that someone representing a university science department would know things like this, it makes sense to assume they are the source of it. Somewhere along the way (either coincidentally or intentionally) references to Chicago were replaced with "North Florida" to help the tale make more sense. &lt;br&gt;"False Attribution Syndrome," as we at BreakTheChain.org like to call this phenomenon, creates a lot of headache for employers and is why most prohibit their employees from using their business e-mail accounts for personal correspondence. Many employees have been reprimanded or terminated after becoming associated with a chain letter. This is just one of the very real dangers anyone faces when they forward a warning like this one without checking it out first. Break this chain! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://habitatnews.nus.edu.sg/guidebooks/spiders/pics/1133.jpg" width="146" height="99" alt="close-up of black male"&gt;Male&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="http://habitatnews.nus.edu.sg/guidebooks/spiders/pics/1132.jpg" width="120" height="98" alt="close-up of orangey female"&gt;Female&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</content>
    <postId>018D5F00-3913-473D-8115-BBDB3E83E21A</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-07-24T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re]DEADLY Spider-이건 또 뭐유?</title>
</post>
