<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김세환</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>부기흡</author>
            <date>2002-08-23T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Huhahahahaha.......</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content> &lt;br&gt;This is voted as the best e-mail joke in Australia in 2001.&lt;br&gt;Hope you enjoy it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An E-Mail To The Wrong Wife&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After being nearly snowbound for two weeks last winter, a Seattle&lt;br&gt;man departed for his vacation in Miami Beach, where he was to meet his wife&lt;br&gt;the next day at&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;the conclusion of her business trip to Minneapolis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They were looking forward to pleasant weather and a nice time together. &lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, there was some sort of mix up at the boarding gate,&lt;br&gt;and the man was told he would have to wait&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;for a later flight.&lt;br&gt;He tried to appeal to a supervisor but was told the airline was not responsible for the problem and it would do no good to complain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upon arrival at the hotel the next day, he discovered that Miami Beach&lt;br&gt;was having a heat wave, and its weather was almost as uncomfortably hot as Seattle's&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;was cold. The desk clerk gave him a message that his wife would arrive as planned. He could hardly wait to get to the pool area to cool off, and quickly sent his wife an e-mail, but due to his haste, he made an error in the e-mail address.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;His message therefore arrived at the home of an elderly&lt;br&gt;preacher's wife whose even older husband had died only the day before. &lt;br&gt;When the grieving&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;widow opened her e-mail, she took one look at the monitor, let out an anguished&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;scream, and fell to the floor dead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her family rushed to her room where they saw&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;this message on the screen:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dearest wife,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Departed yesterday as you know. Just now got checked in.&lt;br&gt;Some confusion at the gate. &lt;br&gt;Appeal was denied&lt;br&gt;Received confirmation of your arrival tomorrow.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your loving husband.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;P.S. Things are not as we thought. You're going to be surprised at&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; how hot it is&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;down here. &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5C366996-F303-4326-B2AD-FA3ABEB74A1D</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>A joke..</title>
</post>
