<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>If interested, leave a note in the comment field below.&lt;br&gt;===================================================&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Details &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; E54 15" CRT Monitor (EPP Summer Sale) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part Number: 3FND044 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Price: $99.00&lt;br&gt;Product Availability:&lt;br&gt;Available&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The IBM E54 color monitor delivers great performance at an affordable price. With a 15-inch CRT with a viewable image size of 13.8 inches (350 mm) the IBM E54 monitor is suitable for home or office applications including word processing, E-mail, data entry, spreadsheets and business graphics.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Product Details &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; E74 17" CRT Monitor (EPP Summer Sale) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part Number: 3FND045 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Price: $149.00&lt;br&gt;Product Availability:&lt;br&gt;Available&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The E74 color monitor delivers great performance at affordable price. This new monitor is suitable for small to medium businesses for applications such as: word processing, e-mail/data entry, complex spreadsheets, business graphics, and entry-level desktop publishing., It has a 17-inch CRT with a viewable image size of 16.0 inches (406 mm), incorporating a 0.27 dot pitch. It also has a maximum horizontal frequency of 69kHz for flicker-free operation at an optimum 1024x768 pels at 85Hz with a maximum addressability of 1280x1024 pels., Video Electronics Standards Association (VESA) Display Data Channel (DDC) capability for Plug and Play and asset tracking when the attaching system unit's hardware and software is DDC-enabled, Power consumption requirements of Swedish National Board for Industrial and Technical Development (NUTEK). As an ENERGY STAR partner, IBM has determined that this product meets the ENERGY STAR guidelines for energy efficiency., Timings for the VESA 85 Hz refresh rate display modes for 640x480, 720x400, 800x600, and 1024x768 addressability's. Appropriate graphics adapter hardware and software must be installed in the attaching system unit.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Product Details &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; C190 19" CRT Monitor (EPP Summer Sale) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part Number: 3FND046 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Price: $249.00&lt;br&gt;Product Availability:&lt;br&gt;Available&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The IBM ThinkVision(TM) C190 monitor is a large 19inch flat screen CRT at an attractive price. This flat screen monitor incorporates IBM ThinkVantage(TM) design to enhance usability and complement the system design as it helps to minimize glare and distortion around the edges and corners of the screen.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Product Details &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; L170p 17" Flat Panel Monitor (EPP Summer Sale) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part Number: 3FND048 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Price: $599.00&lt;br&gt;Product Availability:&lt;br&gt;Available&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The new ThinkVision(TM) L170p 17-inch LCD flat panel monitor delivers excellent performance for a variety of applications at an optimum resolution of 1280 x 1024. It incorporates IBM ThinkVantage(TM) design that enhances usability and complements the system design. The ThinkVision L170p is a Performance flat panel LCD in IBM's ThinkVision family of monitors., The monitor is best suited for:, * Graphic applications, * Complex spreadsheets, * Multitasking, * Financial analysis, * General business applications&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B58A0376-4B9F-4660-97AE-B81577C28DDF</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-06-24T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>IBM EPP Sales - Monitors ($99.00 - $599.00)</title>
</post>
