<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>코스카</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Shopping for Computer Training? - Buyer Beware!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Becoming &amp;quot;computer literate&amp;quot; can be categorized into two main levels of proficiency: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Application User&lt;br&gt;* IT Professional&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knowledge of common software applications such as Windows, Word, Excel and the Internet for example, will enable you to be productive in office administration functions and other general business activities. Many individuals fall into this category of &amp;quot;computer literacy&amp;quot; - to complement skills needed for the following types of jobs and activities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Receptionists, Secretaries and Office Administration personnel using Word and Excel to compose letters, keep records, etc.&lt;br&gt;* Engineers and Architects using AutoCad for their design presentations&lt;br&gt;* Accountants using ACCPAC to maintain financial records and reports&lt;br&gt;* Students accessing the Internet to research for home work&lt;br&gt;* Managers and sales people using PowerPoint to prepare business presentations&lt;br&gt;* And many others ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attaining this level of literacy is relatively easy. But the length of training needed to acquire an adequate skill level, will vary widely - depending on individual abilities. With dedication and discipline it's even possible to study on your own. There are many books, teaching tools, and resources available from government operated resource centers and public libraries to help you. If you prefer to take courses, these are available from many public and private schools - some available free of charge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, individuals with the desire to become a computer professional in the areas of programming, hardware, networking, web mastering, and so forth - require a higher level of knowledge, background and comprehensive technical training. Today, the IT industry has more potential opportunities than many other industries. However, not everyone can be trained to become a successful IT professional. Before deciding to commit to an expensive and extensive training program in IT technology - you must ask yourself the following soul searching questions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Do I have the necessary aptitude and capacity for logical thinking?&lt;br&gt;* How determined am I and is time on my side to build a successful career?&lt;br&gt;* Do I already have some knowledge of computers and is it extensive enough as a pre-requisite for the intended training?&lt;br&gt;* Can I afford the training in terms of finances and investment of time?&lt;br&gt;* Have I looked into and do I have realistic expectations about the target profession by talking to people already working in the field?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selecting an appropriate program in a reputable school is a task in itself. Because the IT industry has abundant opportunities, the &amp;quot;IT training industry&amp;quot; is infested with opportunists out to profit from you. These &amp;quot;opportunistic&amp;quot; organizations claim to have unbelievable success rates; make unrealistic guarantees and promises; and claim extravagant testimonials from very carefully chosen graduates. Before making this life changing, long-term and potentially expensive commitment to a training program, you must consider the following:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. The School:&lt;br&gt;* Is the school registered with the Ministry of Education and Training?&lt;br&gt;* Does it provide an adequate learning environment in terms of staff and resources?&lt;br&gt;* Does the school endeavor to accept only people with adequate background and capabilities?&lt;br&gt;* Does the school provide proper guidance and support to students in terms of counseling and placement?&lt;br&gt;* Is the school able to fully deliver on the curricula described in the advertisement?&lt;br&gt;* Is the school reputable and will you be proud of the school after graduation?&lt;br&gt;* Does the school practice business in an ethical manner?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Curriculum Content:&lt;br&gt;* Is the content of the course sufficiently up-to-date to meet the current and future job market demands?&lt;br&gt;* Is it comprehensive and intensive enough to ensure employment after graduation?&lt;br&gt;* Does it demand proper pre-requisites and is it taught in a proper sequence?&lt;br&gt;* Is the course composed of appropriate and crucial content?&lt;br&gt;* Is it a diploma program approved by the Ministry of Education and Training?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Duration and Hours of Instruction:&lt;br&gt;* Is the course intensive enough to achieve a professional skill level?&lt;br&gt;* Can you afford the time you must invest - giving consideration for life's other obligations?&lt;br&gt;* Is it a full day of classes; is it a half day of classes; is it a few hours of class with extra time for unsupervised self-study?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Teaching Method:&lt;br&gt;* Is the class size small enough for every student to get personal teacher attention?&lt;br&gt;* Is it properly taught with lectures and hands-on combination, and not just self-study?&lt;br&gt;* Are projects and testing for credits part of the evaluation process?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Course Fees and Financing:&lt;br&gt;* Is the government sponsored student loan, OSAP (both CSL and OSL) available?&lt;br&gt;* Does the school impose excessive registration fees or add unnecessary costs for computer and other materials?&lt;br&gt;* Does the school operate like a business with their financial bottom line a priority; or does it operate like a reputable educational institution that puts your training needs as a priority:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ie. -If a school charges the following:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuition for diploma course = $15,000&lt;br&gt;Total instructional hours = 720&lt;br&gt;Maximum class size = 30&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on maximum class size, the hourly rate of tuition charged for the class, by the school is $625 ($15,000/720*30) - which translates to very high profits for the school. A more adequate hourly rate of tuition should be approximately $200 for a private school operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Real Life Cases&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Success Case 1:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A middle aged electrical engineer immigrant from Europe enrolled in the Computer Programming Diploma program at SoftTrain Institute. She diligently attended the scheduled classes from 9 to 4 daily - then studied hours more at home. She successfully graduated with a diploma. Immediately after graduating, she picked up a &amp;quot;Testing Software&amp;quot; book on advice from some friends and studied the content for one week. She started to apply for Software Testing positions and subsequently had 7 job offers within a 2-month period. She decided to take the offer from a Hamilton based firm as a QA Specialist with an annual salary of $51,000 to start.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are some of the positive points to consider:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* She did a thorough research of programs available throughout the GTA to conclude that this 6-month diploma program was comprehensive and intensive enough to devote her life into. She had 2 children at home to care for, and so a longer course could not be considered. The tuition was reasonable and affordable considering the content, duration and the average class size of 10 students. She made a commitment to select the right course and school, even if she had to travel from Oakville to North York in the winter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* She was dedicated to her studies - diligently doing homework, reviewing, previewing and studying for 5 or more hours at home every night. She was always punctual and very attentive during her daily classroom studies. This kind of dedication and intensive study habits rejuvenates and revitalizes all aspects of one's life - preparing the student to be ready to work in a professional programming environment or any other career opportunities that may come along in the future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Nearing the end of the course, she was pondering on how to break into a programming position as a graduate without any experience. Thinking that the broad programming language knowledge she acquired from the diploma course will go very well with the Software Testing positions in software development environment, she decided to acquire the knowledge herself. This was a very creative and winning idea to further her career.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Success Case 2:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SoftTrain Institute offers a highly successful diploma program called PC/LAN Tech Support. In a sample class of 98 - statistics show that - 95% of students were successful in gaining employment after graduating. One graduate who did not have previous computer experience - was hired as a senior tech support personnel at a major computer support company.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The class consisted of individuals of diverse backgrounds: high school drop-outs; experienced hardware technicians; electronic assembly line workers; and others. People in their 20's, 30's and even 40's. Those students with limited computer background had some difficulties in the beginning, but soon caught up with others due to their determination and their natural capacity for learning - for which they were assessed before being accepted into the program.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are some of the positive points to consider:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* The curricula which was designed with industry needs in mind, equipped the students with a comprehensive set of computer skills in Hardware, Software, Operating Systems, Networking as well as general office applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Internationally recognized Certifications attained as part and parcel of the program such as A+ Hardware Technician, CNA, MCP and MCSE - compensated on the experience requirements of the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* The teachers were qualified and experienced individuals with 85% of their students passing the certification tests on their first attempt.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Continuous support was provided throughout the course to the students with counseling, encouragement and guidance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Tech Support and Network Systems Support programs of this kind are not usually available from the Universities and Colleges - due to the fast changing nature of the technology. The industry can best hope for good vocational schools to fill this skill shortage with competent graduates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* The school had an aggressive placement strategy working with a network of graduates actively employed in the industry and companies who are past employers waiting to hire from successful graduates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsuccessful Case 1:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 55-year-old engineer with 3 children and on welfare had a life time dream of becoming a computer repair technician. He enrolled in a 2 year long computer technician course that concentrated on hardware without software and networking content. He took advantage of OSAP to finance his career change to this prospective computer profession. He completed the first year of the course, but finds that he is having difficulty on the DOS portion of the course.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the points he should have considered before committing to the course:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Most PC hardware repair jobs pay closer to minimum wage unless you possess extensive knowledge/certification and experience. This is not a high salary profession that enables him to adequately provide for his family.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Welfare will not give him any living allowance during the study period. Therefore he will have to pay back more than $40,000 of loans that he financed - upon completion of the course.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Due to his lack of proper pre-requisite knowledge, the successful completion of his program is highly unlikely. Even if he does successfully complete the course, his age will work against him in the job market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsuccessful Case 2:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An immigrant with a bachelor degree is taking a 9 month programming course with 4 hours per day classes. Four (4) months into the course he is having difficulty with Visual BASIC. He is looking for a personal tutor to help him with this subject.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the points he should have considered before he committed to the course:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Visual BASIC being taught at a halfway point of the course, indicates that the program may not have adequate content to develop appropriate programming skills for the job market. The curriculum content should have been looked into more carefully.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* If the student is having problems on Visual BASIC - 4 months into the program, he does not have an adequate aptitude for programming and should have been advised accordingly - before he was allowed to register.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* As a mature student supporting his family while studying, he needs an intensive yet comprehensive course schedule. Four (4) hours of training per day does not adequately provide his needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some advice from an experienced training seeker&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Generally speaking, the laws of Canada protect us from misrepresentations. However, in the IT training industry it seems to be &amp;quot;no holds barred&amp;quot;. This industry has grown in leaps and bounds over the last couple of years. In the daily newspapers and monthly computer publications, there is a constant barrage of advertisements offering IT training in every possible certification - even ones for which the examinations are not yet available from the certification body. A quick and informal count showed that in just 2 computer related publications for March 1999, there were 22 advertisements in one publication and 16 advertisements in another publication. Some of the prices listed appear so ridiculously low that one wonders on the quality of such courses. The best advice to anyone seeking to further his or her training in the IT industry is: Caveat Emptor - Let the buyer beware. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best form of advertisement is word of mouth. This is the only way you are going to find out if the training school is up to par. Most print advertisements do not provide adequate details on courses and you must come up with innovative ways to gather them. The fact is - all of us end up at these schools because we fall into one of these 3 main categories and reasons:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Unemployed and we need to upgrade our skills to get back into the work force&lt;br&gt;* Want a change of career - due to stressful circumstances in our previous jobs&lt;br&gt;* A recent immigrant in need of the extra certification(s) to enhance his or her chances of getting a job&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever the reason, the common factor is that it is a very emotional time in our lives during which we are most susceptible. Therefore, do not rush into anything, do your homework methodically and unemotionally - then make your decisions based on facts. This is more difficult to do than most people want to admit in such an emotional state of mind, and we become open targets for dishonest sales people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trying to get information over the telephone from some unscrupulous organizations is a futile exercise in most cases. Usually you will be told that they cannot give information over the telephone but they can book an appointment for you to see a representative. How about mailing you the information? There will be a variety of reasons but in the end, you will not get anything. The strategy is to get you into the office and apply the sales pitch. By all means go in and see the school, but do not be forced into signing any contract until you are absolutely sure. One good strategy is to take a friend along with you, someone who is adequately informed and perhaps has been through the process before - to keep you from making emotional decisions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let me point out that there are several good schools out there who will send you the information you request but will also want you to come into the school for an interview and some form of assessment testing. The objective of these tests is to evaluate your capability of handling the rigors of the course. In some cases, they may even suggest alternate courses that may suit your needs better. These are the kinds of reputable schools to look for.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the amazing things about the human brain is its ability to retain knowledge. However, very few of us fall under the category of genius and we need time to learn new skills. The duration for the same course varies from school to school and you must be honest with yourself as to your own abilities. For example, the MCSE course is offered in various formats, some of which are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* 12 weeks full-time with 4 weeks instructor led and 8 weeks unlimited lab time&lt;br&gt;* 12 weeks full-time instructor led in both theory and lab&lt;br&gt;* 18 weeks full-time with 1 week instructor led and 2 weeks lab time for each subject&lt;br&gt;* 26 weeks full-time with 18 weeks instructor led and 8 weeks co-op&lt;br&gt;* Computer based training (CBT) during which you are sitting in front of a computer and follow an instructional material&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of interesting note is that in the US, there is a trend towards &amp;quot;MCSE Boot Camps&amp;quot; during which you are promised to be trained for certification in only 2 weeks. You must remember that it is impossible to learn new skills overnight. Anyone can read through a manual and fix things shooting from the hip but if you want to be a pro, you must learn these new skills thoroughly. Being unemployed is a financial restriction in itself and if you select the wrong IT training school you may just find yourself in deeper financial burden - and still without a job!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many schools use the sales pitch of promising a bright financial future upon course completion. Some of the sales pitch will include statistics that show large salaried positions for the IT industry. However, these statistics are misrepresented and misinterpreted to suit their sales pitch. Yes, there are IT professionals working in the $70,000 salary range, but have you checked the extensiveness of their qualifications and experience portfolio? Is it plausible for someone to take a 12-week course then find employment earning such a high salary? Sounds too good to be true? - Well, it is. Another question to ponder is, with such high salaried positions available, why is the course being offered at such a low price? The reality is that, very few schools are concerned about the final end product. As long as you have the money to pay for the course - they will eagerly accept you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B6402EA7-4E48-459C-A6AB-3E16FE8C1AFC</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-07-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Shopping for Computer Training? - Buyer Beware!</title>
</post>
