<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>직장에서 받은 메일입니다.&lt;br&gt;____________________________&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;IT HAS BEEN CALCULATED THAT IF EVERYONE IN THE UNITED STATES AND CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;DID NOT PURCHASE A DROP OF GASOLINE FOR ONE DAY AND ALL AT THE SAME TIME, THE OIL COMPANIES WOULD CHOKE ON THEIR STOCKPILES.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT THE SAME TIME IT WOULD HIT THE ENTIRE INDUSTRY WITH A NET LOSS OF OVER 4.6 BILLION DOLLARS WHICH AFFECTS THE BOTTOM LINES OF THE OIL COMPANIES.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;THEREFORE SEPTEMBER 1st&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;HAS BEEN FORMALLY DECLARED "STICK IT UP THEIR BEHIND " DAY AND THE PEOPLE OF THESE TWO NATIONS SHOULD NOT BUY A SINGLE DROP OF GASOLINE THAT DAY.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;THE ONLY WAY THIS CAN BE DONE IS IF YOU FORWARD THIS E-MAIL TO AS MANY PEOPLE AS YOU CAN AND AS QUICKLY AS YOU CAN TO GET THE WORD OUT.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;WAITING ON THE GOVERNMENT TO STEP IN AND CONTROL THE PRICES IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;WHAT HAPPENED TO THE REDUCTION AND CONTROL IN PRICES THAT THE ARAB NATIONS PROMISED TWO WEEKS AGO?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;REMEMBER ONE THING, NOT ONLY IS THE PRICE OF GASOLINE GOING UP BUT AT THE &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAME TIME AIRLINES ARE FORCED TO RAISE THEIR PRICES, TRUCKING COMPANIES ARE FORCED TO RAISE THEIR PRICES WHICH EFFECTS PRICES ON EVERYTHING THAT IS SHIPPED.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;THINGS LIKE FOOD, CLOTHING, BUILDING MATERIALS, MEDICAL SUPPLIES ETC.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;WHO PAYS IN THE END?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;WE DO!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;WE CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;IF THEY DON'T GET THE MESSAGE AFTER ONE DAY, WE WILL DO IT &lt;br&gt;AGAIN AND AGAIN.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;SO DO YOUR PART AND SPREAD THE WORD.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;FORWARD THIS EMAIL TO EVERYONE YOU KNOW.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;MARK YOUR CALENDARS AND MAKE SEPTEMBER 1ST A DAY THAT THE CITIZENS OF THE UNITED STATES AND CANADA&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SAY "ENOUGH IS ENOUGH" &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>0DFF67C4-997D-4CCC-9991-C7DC150A69F7</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-08-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>기름값..</title>
</post>
