<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Our own Kick Off Celebration!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Join us for our very own tribute to the recent&lt;br&gt;Launch of Visual Studio 2005!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEETING ANNOUNCEMENT:&lt;br&gt;When? THURSDAY, November 17 , 6:00 p.m. - 9:00 p.m. &lt;br&gt;Where? Microsoft Canada , 1950 Meadowvale Blvd , Mississauga (north of 401 at&lt;br&gt;Mississauga Road exit) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How Do I Register?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;http://www.torontoug.net - or call Ed Musters at&lt;br&gt;416-817-3330.&lt;br&gt;6:00 p.m. - Meet and greet! Arrive early! Prize give aways!! Food and drinks!!&lt;br&gt;6:30 p.m. - Opening Remarks&lt;br&gt;6:45 p.m. - Building Scalable Web Applications using Microsoft Visual Studio&lt;br&gt;2005:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Visual Studio 2005 and ASP.NET 2.0 combine to form a rich platform for&lt;br&gt;building, testing, and deploying state-of-the-art Web applications. ASP.NET 2.0&lt;br&gt;is replete with new features, from data source controls and master pages to&lt;br&gt;membership and role management services-features that reduce the amount of code&lt;br&gt;required to create a typical Web site by up to 70%. Visual Studio 2005 features&lt;br&gt;an all-new Web development interface that speeds the development process while&lt;br&gt;offering a rich design-time experience and seamless integration with Visual&lt;br&gt;Studio 2005 Team System. These products are second to none when it comes to&lt;br&gt;building scalable, high-performance, Web applications.&lt;br&gt;8:15 p.m. - Wrap up and Prizes!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: This is a repeat session as was presented at the VS Launch Tour&lt;br&gt;on November 8!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPEAKER PROFILE:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Luis Duran, UG Board Member&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;VERY IMPORTANT NOTE - BEFORE YOU REGISTER:&lt;br&gt;While the meetings are FREE to you, the meetings cost real money on the part of&lt;br&gt;our sponsors to put on, in the order of thousands of dollars.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;When you&lt;br&gt;register, we are spending money on YOU, by reserving a place, and ordering food. &lt;br&gt;So please make your registration an absolute and unwavering commitment to&lt;br&gt;attend! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOW TO REGISTER:&lt;br&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We prefer you register on the web at http://www.torontoug.net &lt;br&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;PLEASE we need your registration if you are going to attend!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We need to&lt;br&gt;know how many will come so that we can book the appropriate number of event&lt;br&gt;rooms and order adequate food.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are regularly selling out meetings with over&lt;br&gt;200 people attending, so be sure to register early!!&lt;br&gt;3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you are a member, please Login!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you are not yet a member, click&lt;br&gt;"Register".&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There is NO COST to join.&lt;br&gt;4.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you have logged in or just signed up as a new member this DOES NOT&lt;br&gt;automatically sign you up for the event!&lt;br&gt;5.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please go to the "User Group Events" section, and click on the "Read More"&lt;br&gt;to see the event details.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You will see the "Click here to register" link.&lt;br&gt;6.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If all else fails, please contact Ed Musters at 416-817-3330 and leave a&lt;br&gt;message.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Toronto .NET User Group currently has over 3,000 registered members, making&lt;br&gt;it one of the largest in North America!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Thank you to all for your tremendous&lt;br&gt;support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Musters, President&lt;br&gt;Toronto .NET User Group&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>0F90531A-E13D-4B1A-ADAC-8BD80CC30758</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-11-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Launch of Visual Studio 2005</title>
</post>
