<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>By&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Alan Williamson &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Editor's note: This report is taken from Alan Williamson's JavaOne 2003 blog. Here, he's upfront and center at the debut of Project Rave.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(June 11, 2003) - This is being blogged LIVE, as and when it happens, here at the Moscone. It's raw and uncut! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching Project Rave live, and it crashed!!! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Green is winging it... and is struggling.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And still we are waiting... phew... it's come up! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And oops - the event trigger didn't work! Demo not going too well here... I wonder what Microsoft thinks now. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And that was it ... the big tool for that is going to kill Eclipse and take over Visual Studio. In all fairness, it looks good, and seems to have all the cool bells and whistles that the Visual Studio people are use to. For example the integration of the Web services into a Web form is VERY CLOSE to the exact demo that I was given in Redmond 18 months ago. In fact, come to think of it, the demo at Redmond went on to drop the app into a mobile device. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a great quote from the "West Wing" drama series, which applies well here: "Let's not mourn the fact you're late for the party; but rejoice you finally made it!" &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early access release will be in the fall. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Update: James Gosling is about to kill the audience! He has really put a lot of effort into this! He is showing pictures of himself and an intern hacking together a WEAPON in the car parks of Sun. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurl a shirt into JavaOne for next year: "Build something cool and pointless". That's his challenge for us to deliver next year. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just watched a cool Java cartoon… this should be made available to the consumer ... as geeky as it is ... it will probably work a lot more than "Intel Inside." I can just imagine a series of children's programs with Dukey!!! LOL ... move over Barney, there's a new kid in town! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan Dvorak, deputy architect of the Mission Data System with Jet Propulsion Labs, is coming on stage with Gosling, to talk about the Mars probe. The current rover, launched yesterday, doesn't actually have any Java on it. But Rocky7, on the stage now, DOES! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has a plethora of different hardware on it for moveability and data collection. These need to be controlled in a coordinated and real time way. They are using Real Time Java. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Better than a hummer, and good bit more expensive." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has to be said, this is seriously cool. My own background is robotics/transputers and this is the sort of world that really rings my bell. So cool that Java is now delivering in this world. Sadly, it's an area that a lot of people just won't appreciate - the challenges that Java had to solve for a real time deterministic language. Real time threads with no garbage collection coming in and making problems. Simply beautiful. Well done, team. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Wright, Solutions Architect from Sun, is now up with James. Looking at embedded Java and how it is working in the real world. We are in a mocked-up retail store, selling software CDs. Automated re-order robot. There is a tiny a tag on each product, which is a small chip that has a unique number embedded on it. So it's a new barcode, for the want of analogy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wright is taking a CD from the shelf and instantly the stock-control console, says it's offshelf. Once it goes below a threshold, the robot kicks in and starts restocking! Very cool. Although what happens if you are just browsing and you pick it up and put it down again!!! LOL ... can you imagine?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Agile guys that James is talking about, is saying that these guys are the REAL EXTREME people; when they hit a bug, people die! He quips "An interesting way to look at debugging." I think I see a new addition to Ant!! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another cell phone demo, from Ansgar Hempel, VP. Jentro AG. He is walking to the stage via a navigational cell phone talking instructions to him. The cell has a GPS installed, and using Web services he is sending the coordinates of where he is, and it's telling him where to go via VOICE. Very cool. Point is, no need to carry the location data around with him, as he is using a Web service to get at the data that would normally be on the DVD in a car's navigation. VERY COOL. There is a lot of commercial potential here for making navigation come alive. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ooh, we have now a JXTA (peer2peer) from Rich Berlin at Sun. It's more than just music-swapping, he assures us. We are watching a video with a speedometer of a car. So we are looking at putting peer2peer into a scenario where all the cars in a highway can tell one another just how bad the traffic is. Real time traffic routing using peer2peer view. Using a cell phone and GPS. A little pie-in-the-sky demo, but very cool nonetheless. The notion here is that they are sharing data that is usually pointless; what is the speed I am travelling on this given road. Like the fax machine, once everyone has the hardware capabilities, it will rock. But looks like Java is ready for it now. Just need to wait until the hardware gets to critical mass. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;James is now talking about blogging. Was persuaded to do it, and he says "it's kind of entertaining." Quite a change from when I asked him if he was blogging back when i interviewed in March; saying he hadn't looked at it yet. So welcome to the blogging world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's now showing us some of the tools he hacked together for his own blogging and presentation tools. He's showing his demo on MacOSX and the Java apps are running really sweet. He's blogging live on stage, but his network isn't connected! LOL.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;James is now finished, and John Gage is up to close off the keynote. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now ... THAT WAS A JAVAONE KEYNOTE. The Project Rave, not as impressive as I was hoping, but the James Gosling stuff, worth the trip in itself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(For Sun's complete details on Project Rave, see wwws.sun.com/software/products/projectrave/.) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>0FF0ACD4-AA8B-4D7F-A031-2FB519F1CD55</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Live at JavaOne: Alan Williamson Blogs the Project Rave Keynote</title>
</post>
