<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>Robin Lee</author>
            <date>2009-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>좋은 정보 정말 감사드립니다. ^^</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hi all,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I’ll send out an announcement shortly for the next Toronto .NET User group on Thursday January 29th (mark your calendar).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;But in the meantime, join us next Saturday for the SharePoint Camp!!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It will be held at Manulife downtown which is near Church and Bloor (full directions on the site).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; It is an AMAZING day of speakers and content!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is that time of year again.....the Toronto SharePoint Camp is Saturday, January 24th!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you haven’t registered yet, please do so ASAP by going to the website http://www.torontosharepointcamp.com, and forward this email and link to anyone you know who is interested in learning how to do more with SharePoint.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The Toronto SharePoint Camp is organized by the Toronto SharePoint User Group and is about the administrative user and developer communities at large. It is meant to be a place for administrators and developers to come and learn from their peers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Topics for this years’ Toronto SharePoint Camp were based on community interest and never determined by anyone other than the community......and....it is a FREE event.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the topics for the 2009 camp include.:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Integrating SQL Server with MOSS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social Computing with SharePoint and Silverlight (from non linear’s MS Team Lead, Andy Nogueira)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advanced InfoPath Development with SharePoint&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSS Search: Why it’s not enough to just turn it on&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It should be a great turnout &amp;#8211; we are expecting at least 300 ppl this year &amp;#8211; up 20% from last years camp.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have any questions, do not hesitate to contact Susie Ibbotson at sibbotson@nonlinear.ca&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Musters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;President, Toronto .NET User Group&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>18FBCA2E-B094-4079-A9C9-C1D8A1C4ED0E</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-01-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Toronto SharePoint Camp - Saturday January 24th</title>
</post>
