<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이상훈</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>REMINDER:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It's not too late to register!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Join us for the wonderful opportunity!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;THIS MONDAY!1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next meeting of the Toronto .NET User Group will be MONDAY August 11, 2008. At this meeting, we have an amazing opportunity to have with us a member of the VB\\\\LINQ team from Redmond - Jonathan Aneja! He promises to go as DEEP, DEEP, DEEP into the subject as time allows! We'll also host a completely open half hour discussion to give YOU the opportunity to answer any LINQ questions you may have!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WE HAVE MOVED!! See below for our NEW meeting location at the MISSISSAUGA CONVENTION CENTRE at 75 Derry Road Mississauga, Ontario, L5W 1G3. We are also working hard to get all of our meetings fully catered again!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When? MONDAY August 11, 2008, 6:00 p.m. - 9:00 p.m. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where? WE HAVE MOVED!! MISSISSAUGA CONVENTION CENTRE at 75 Derry Road Mississauga, Ontario, L5W 1G3 (near corner of Hurontario St - Hwy 10).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this meeting CATERED? YES - Pizza and Pop!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6:00 p.m. - Meet and greet! Arrive early! Great Prize give aways!! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6:30 p.m. - Opening Remarks from the User Group President&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6:45 p.m. - TOPIC: VB 2008/LINQ Deep Dive&lt;br&gt;Language Integrated Query (LINQ) is a new platform feature in Visual Studio 2008 that allows you to access objects, databases, and XML through a common query syntax (in both VB and C#). In this talk, we'll take a deep dive into the language features that LINQ uses internally to process your query, and see how they can be used in your own code. Topics we'll cover include:&lt;br&gt;- Query expressions&lt;br&gt;- XML Literals&lt;br&gt;- Type Inference&lt;br&gt;- Anonymous Types&lt;br&gt;- Extension Methods&lt;br&gt;- Lambda expressions&lt;br&gt;- Closures&lt;br&gt;- Expression Trees&lt;br&gt;- Partial Methods&lt;br&gt;- Relaxed Delegates&lt;br&gt;- Performance/Deferred Execution&lt;br&gt;- LINQ to Dataset&lt;br&gt;- Dynamically constructing a LINQ query&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We'll also look at some of the cool new IDE features as well as free add-ons such as Refactor! which can greatly improve your day-to-day productivity. If you want to learn what makes VB the most powerful language for working with data then come on out!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8:15 p.m. - OPEN Q&amp;A SESSION with Jonathan! Bring your most intimate LINQ questions with you! Your most troublesome puzzles! Jonathan promises to answer your questions by example. A fabulous opportunity first hand with an expert!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8:45 p.m. - Wrap up and Prizes!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIO: Jonathan Aneja:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan is a Program Manager on the Visual Basic team at Microsoft, working on compiler, language, and runtime features. He's spent a good chunk of the past few years working on LINQ, but also other projects such as the Interop Forms Toolkit. Prior to moving to Redmond, he graduated from the University of Toronto then worked in Developer Support for Microsoft Canada. You can check out the VB Team Blog at http://blogs.msdn.com/vbteam. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPONSOR MESSAGE: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAVANTIS is very proud to sponsor the Toronto .NET User Group. We look forward to contributing to the .NET user dialogue and to sharing best practices and our development expertise with members. As a Microsoft Gold Certified Partner and an award winning provider of premium IT professional services, Navantis designs, develops and deploys innovative business solutions developed using the .NET framework for some of North America's largest organizations including; Honda, CIBC, Microsoft, CBC, Magna Entertainment Corporation, The City of Hamilton and Allstate Insurance. Our mission is simple; to deliver exceptional client service and quality every step of the way. We are always seeking passionate, client-focused and exceptionally talented individuals who share our philosophy to join our team. Please visit us at www.navantis.com &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GURULINK: GuruLink is proud to support the Toronto .NET User Group, one of Toronto's most successful and highly attended user groups. We have been involved with and attending the events for years, and are now pleased to have the opportunity to formally and publicly show our support through sponsorship. It is a great forum for people with a keen interest in Microsoft Technologies looking to expand and improve their skill set and their marketability and generally keep informed of hot new technologies. We are looking forward to contributing to its ongoing success and look forward to a long and mutually beneficial relationship.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;VERY IMPORTANT NOTE - BEFORE YOU REGISTER:&lt;br&gt;While the meetings are FREE to you, the meetings cost real money on the part of our sponsors to put on, in the order of thousands of dollars. When you register, we are spending money on YOU, by reserving a place, and ordering food. So please make your registration an absolute and unwavering commitment to attend! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOW TO REGISTER:&lt;br&gt;1. We prefer you register on the web at http://www.torontoug.net &lt;br&gt;2. PLEASE we need your registration if you are going to attend! We need to know how many will come so that we can book the appropriate number of event rooms and order adequate food. We are regularly selling out meetings, so be sure to register early!!&lt;br&gt;3. If you are a member, please Login! If you are not yet a member, click "Register". There is NO COST to join.&lt;br&gt;4. If you have logged in or just signed up as a new member this DOES NOT automatically sign you up for the event!&lt;br&gt;5. Please go to the "User Group Events" section, and click on the "Read More" to see the event details. You will see the "Click here to register" link.&lt;br&gt;6. If all else fails, please contact Ed Musters at 416-817-3330 and leave a message.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Toronto .NET User Group currently has over 4,000 registered members, making it one of the largest in North America! Thank you to all for your tremendous support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Musters, President&lt;br&gt;Toronto .NET User Group</content>
    <postId>19054579-7A5E-49FD-95DE-5C646A18CC76</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-08-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Toronto .NET User Group Meeting Announcement! - MONDAY August 11 at 6 p.m.</title>
</post>
