<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Seung Yeop Kim</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>If you think the words \\&amp;quot;free software\\&amp;quot; and \\&amp;quot;AS/400\\&amp;quot; will never be spoken in the &lt;br&gt;same sentence, think again. There are several places where you'll find free &lt;br&gt;downloads and open-source projects targeting this platform. Some of the software &lt;br&gt;you'll find will be more useful than others.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A well-known place for downloadable software -- ZD Net Downloads &lt;br&gt;(http://www.zdnet.com/downloads/) -- has only a handful of programs developed &lt;br&gt;with the AS/400 in mind, all running on desktop systems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At CodePage400 (http://207.158.252.83/codepage400.htm), all the information is &lt;br&gt;about the AS/400. This site contains more snippets, delivered in Q&amp;A format. The &lt;br&gt;tips range from the specific -- code for calling validation list API from ILE &lt;br&gt;RPG -- to the general -- where's the Java tutor? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WyattERP (http://www.opensource400.org/wyatterp/index.html), on the other hand, &lt;br&gt;is a full-blown application. This is an open-source project that builds an &lt;br&gt;enterprise resource planning package specifically for the AS/400. It consists of &lt;br&gt;a suite of functions for back-office tasks, such as general ledger, accounts &lt;br&gt;payable, accounts receivable, payroll, inventory control, sales analysis, job &lt;br&gt;costing, order entry, billing and purchasing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll also find interesting software written in Java. The AS/400 has an &lt;br&gt;optimized Java Virtual Machine and a developer kit for Java that's compatible &lt;br&gt;with Sun's JDK 1.1.7 on V4R4, so you can use any program that adheres to those &lt;br&gt;specs. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ArgoUML (http://argouml.tigris.org/index.html) is one such program. It is an &lt;br&gt;open-source project to build a unified modeling language. The group's secondary &lt;br&gt;goal is to provide cognitive support for object-oriented software design, &lt;br&gt;following UML 1.1 specifications. The application is written in Java Foundation &lt;br&gt;Classes and runs on any platform with Java 1.1. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Written by Amy Helen Johnson, a freelance writer in Seattle. &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>280038D5-8C2D-4227-B479-64CD1306EAAE</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-10-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>E-commerce tip: Free AS/400 software</title>
</post>
