<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Market for Web Services to Boom According to Study&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;September 27, 2004&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report released by Radicati Group estimates more than a four-fold increase in Web services over the next four years. Web services, which had primarily been dominated by the US in the number of new deployments, are being increasingly adopted by European countries, and Asia to a lesser extent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;By WSJ News Desk &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Web services promise to give you the ability to decouple your application into functional parts, develop those parts independently using any platform and any language, and have it all work together seamlessly. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The award-winning IDE for XML that includes XML editing and validation, DTD/Schema editing and validation, and XSLT editing and transformation, all in one easy-to-use product. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current Web services' implementations only scratch the surface of this technology's potential capabilities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to new research released today, the market for Web services is expected to grow very dramatically during the next four years. Radicati Group's, "Web Services Market 2004-2008," estimates that the combined market for Web services solutions, management, integration and security will be worth $950 million in 2004. That figure by 2008 will rise to $6.2 billion. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masha Khmartseva, the report's principal analyst, said that Web services are appealing because it offers a way for companies to integrate their various divisions into a unified portal. This enables employees to work collectively together, thus increasing efficiency and productivity. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essentially Web services, according to the report, creates new ways of doing business. Moreover, since virtually any application can be exposed as a Web service, the types of systems that can be integrated are limitless. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Khmartseva noted, "Web services can be created in different environments and be ready to communicate with each other the moment they are published." He added, "By offering reusable components, they also cut the time spent on developing applications by up to 50 percent." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Web services are not only used by developers. Increasingly companies are relying on Web services to form communication channels with partners and customers. "We estimate that about 28 percent of all deployments are being done for external purposes," Khmartseva said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developers gain more freedom with Web services, the report states, since they no longer have to limit themselves to any one platform. The ability for Web services to integrate throughout multiple platforms is a big selling point for developers. Currently the battle is between .NET and Java on the platform level. Radicati Group's research says that neither platform is currently dominating the other. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Today it's pretty equal," Khmartseva said. "The future will depend a lot on who will be able to offer customers better and more user-friendly tools to build, manage, and integrate Web services." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is striking is that the growth of Web services will most dramatically rise outside of the United States, an area in which Web services was a phenomena. According to the study, 48% of all deployment is being done outside of the US. The US did continue to lead the world in deployment of Web services, at 52 percent. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regarding growth areas, Khmartseva said that security efforts around Web services will grow as companies move from using Web services for non-sensitive information, to more business critical data. "Over the next few years we'll see further development of Web services standards," Khmartseva commented, "especially in the area of security. This will enable companies to build more sophisticated applications, and engage in high-value, multi-transactional operations. " &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>3C231553-3BE2-40BE-AECB-65B8A0CCD1E2</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-09-28T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Market for Web Services to Boom According to Study</title>
</post>
