<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김형태</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;아래 링크를 보시면 이미 앱스토어에 등록된 39가지 앱들이 소스와 함께 올라와 있네요.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;관심 있으신 분들 참조하세요. 상당히 유명한 앱도 눈에 띠네요.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://maniacdev.com/2010/06/35-open-source-iphone-app-store-apps-updated-with-10-new-apps/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Open Source iPhone App Store Apps List&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is the list in alphabetical order:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. ABC 123 &amp;#8211; Sequence memorization game. Utilizes Cocos2D. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*2. Artifice &amp;#8211; Strategy game where you try to get to the other side by moving boxes out of the way. Utilizes Cocos2D. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Colloquy &amp;#8211; Conversion of the most popular Mac IRC client to the iPhone. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*4. Countitout - A generic counting app. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Diceshaker - Dice rolling simulator designed for role-playing game enthusiasts. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Doom Classic - Classic 3D first person shooter. (itunes link) (source code) (build instructions)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;*7. Ecological Footprint - Calculate, display, and record your ecological footprint. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8. Fosdem - Calendar app for the Fosdem open source conference. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9. Freshbooks &amp;#8211; App that enables usage of Freshbooks web invoicing software from your iPhone. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10. Gorillas &amp;#8211; Classic Worms/iShoot turn based shooter type game converted to iPhone from basic. Utilizes Cocos2D. (itunes link) (source code). 1249ouFh83XA&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;11. Go Go Lotto &amp;#8211; Open source lotto ticket generator. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;12. iStrobe - Turns the iPhone 4 flash into a highly configurable strobe light. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;13. Last.fm &amp;#8211; Software that enables usage of the Last.fm platform for personal radio stations. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;14. Mobilesynth - A monophonic synthesizer designed for live performance. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;15. Molecules &amp;#8211; Allows you to view 3D models of molecules and manipulate them through touch. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;16. Mover &amp;#8211; Allows you to transfer stuff from one iPhone to another by “flicking” it to the other device. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;17. Natsulion - A basic twitter client converted from mac. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;18. NowPlaying &amp;#8211; Allows you to check local theater listings, and check rotten tomato ratings. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;19. Packlog &amp;#8211; Backpack journal client. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;20. PlainNote - Simple Open Source Notepad. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;21. PocketFlix &amp;#8211; Find movies, and manage your Netflix information. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;22. NevoChess &amp;#8211; A Xiangqi game. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;23. reMail &amp;#8211; E-mail client featuring ultra-fast search. Removed from app store, but source made available. (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;24. RobotFindsKitten &amp;#8211; Port of a very silly “classic” ASCII game. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;25. Sci-15 HPCalc &amp;#8211; Calculator app based on classic scientific HP-Calculator. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;26. SpaceBubble &amp;#8211; Space game featuring core graphics, and accelerometer usage. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;27. Star3Map &amp;#8211; Augmented reality star and planet charting application. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;28. Task Coach &amp;#8211; Personal to-do list and task manager. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;29. Tubestatus &amp;#8211; London train schedule tracker. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;30. Tweejump &amp;#8211; Platform jumping game inspired by Icy Tower. Utilizes Cocos2D. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;31. Tweetee &amp;#8211; Enhanced version of the Natsulion Twitter Client. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;32. Tweetero &amp;#8211; Basic twitter client with image uploading. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;33. Twitterfon &amp;#8211; Super-fast intuitive twitter client. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;34. ViralFire &amp;#8211; Unique game where you are a dodging blood cell. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;35. Wikihow &amp;#8211; A reader app for the popular how to wiki site. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;36. Wolfenstein 3D Classic Platinum &amp;#8211; If you haven’t heard of Wolfenstein post below so we can say a prayer for you. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;37. WordPress &amp;#8211; Client for managing WordPress blogs. Also has an iPad version. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;38. YourRights &amp;#8211; Pocket database containing a summary of your legal rights. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;39. ZBar &amp;#8211; A barcode reader. (itunes link) (source code)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check them out if you are working on something similar or think they might have a feature you could use there’s no reason to re-invent the wheel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Always make sure you understand the licenses though many are GPL and require that you open source your app.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>6353FF28-1F7E-4FFF-BF11-666A480601EA</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-09-01T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>39가지 오픈 소스 아이폰 App</title>
</post>
