<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Rick Ross is the founder of Javalobby. He is a frequent speaker at Java-related events and a well-known advocate for Java developer interests.. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;========&lt;br&gt;The final production version of Eclipse 3.1 (which is actually a much more significant than the mere 0.1 dot-level increase indicates) was released last week. As you might expect, the huge demand for this new version was stressing out the Eclipse Foundation's download servers until they wisely brought an additional 100Mbps server online to help out. You should now be able to enjoy a very speedy download of the substantial Eclipse SDK (100 megs for the Win32 version.) Mine clocked in at over 500K per second, so the new server can definitely pump out the bits. Many thanks to whoever made the call and added the new capacity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have all seen vendors use download counts to emphasize their popularity, but the Eclipse folks have set the bar at a new high level for style with their "Million Download Challenge." When the last version of Eclipse was released it took about 60 days to hit one million downloads, but this time they may reach that milestone more quickly. The challenge is to pledge a donation to your favorite charity for each day less than sixty days it takes for Eclipse 3.1 to reach a million downloads. For example, if you pledge $5/day for "Doctors Without Frontiers" and Eclipse 3.1 reaches a million in just 40 days, then you'd donate $100. You select the charity, and you set the level of your pledge, so I think this is a great-spirited idea which I hope you'll join Javalobby in supporting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out this posting at EclipseZone.com to see some more details about the crazy numbers the Eclipse.org websites are getting.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>656CC0D9-4A80-4788-9E06-6468B9FA9380</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-07-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>The Eclipse "Million Download Challenge"</title>
</post>
