<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Seung Yeop Kim</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Using passprop.exe&lt;br&gt;By Mike Marney, searchSystemsManagement memeber&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can add properties to your passwords, as this tip, from reader&lt;br&gt;Mike Marney, points out.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passprop.exe, a command-line tool from the Windows NT resource kit,&lt;br&gt;can be used to set two domain policy flags, whether passwords have to&lt;br&gt;be complex and whether the Administrator account can be locked out.&lt;br&gt;These domain password and security properties cannot be set by any&lt;br&gt;other tool, including the NET command and User Manager.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first property is password complexity. If password complexity is&lt;br&gt;enabled, the password must be mixedcase (including a combination of&lt;br&gt;upper and lowercase letters) or contain numbers or symbols. If it is&lt;br&gt;not enabled, passwords are still case-sensitive but they are not&lt;br&gt;required to be mixedcase or contain numbers or symbols.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second property is whether the Administrator user account can be&lt;br&gt;locked out. If locking out the Administrator user account is enabled,&lt;br&gt;then once it is locked out it can only be used to log on&lt;br&gt;interactively on domain controllers: network logons or logons to&lt;br&gt;non-domain controllers will fail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;passprop with no parameters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Displays domain policies for password complexity and Administrator&lt;br&gt;lockout.&lt;br&gt;For details on PASSPROP syntax and usage: at the command prompt,&lt;br&gt;type: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;passprop /?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is what will be displayed: &lt;br&gt;PASSPROP [/complex] [/simple] [/adminlockout] [/noadminlockout]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;/complex -- Forces passwords to be complex, requiring passwords to be&lt;br&gt;a mix of upper and lowercase letters and numbers or symbols.&lt;br&gt;/simple -- Allows passwords to be simple.&lt;br&gt;/adminlockout -- Allows the Administrator account to be locked out.&lt;br&gt;The Administrator account can still log on interactively on domain&lt;br&gt;controllers.&lt;br&gt;/noadminlockout -- Allows the Administrator account not to be locked&lt;br&gt;out.&lt;br&gt;Additional properties can be set using User Manager or the NET&lt;br&gt;ACCOUNTS command.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>6F8E8BF8-1E99-4342-9D51-9D95564BADB7</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-10-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Security Tip: Using passprop.exe</title>
</post>
