<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>관리자</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Bank card fraud on rise, police say&lt;br&gt;Crooked clerks use new technology to 'skim' bank account&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Sands&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The Ottawa Citizen &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday, August 05, 2002&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Crooked store clerks are using new technology with increasing frequency to clone their customers' bank debit cards and record the corresponding PINs before cleaning out their bank accounts, police say.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ottawa police fraud detectives warn the \\&amp;quot;up-and-coming\\&amp;quot; method of high-tech robbery, known as \\&amp;quot;skimming,\\&amp;quot; has been occurring at an alarming rate over the past year. Paid off by organized crime groups in Ottawa, the thieves are leaving an increasing number of victims broke and confused about how it happened.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigations conducted since the practice started to spread more than a year ago have revealed outlaw biker groups, Russian mafia and an Arab criminal network in the city are often involved, police said. They say they cannot estimate how much has been stolen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;It's a technological development,\\&amp;quot; said Staff Sgt. Maurice Coyle, head of the Ottawa police fraud unit. \\&amp;quot;The technology is readily available and people are taking advantage of it.\\&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say they don't have precise figures on the increase in debit-card fraud. But Sgt. Coyle explained skimming works this way: A customer will hand a bank card to a store clerk to make a debit purchase. The clerk, or hired thief, will quickly swipe the card's magnetic strip through an electronic device that resembles a pager and can be bought over the Internet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most often, Sgt. Coyle said, the pager is kept hidden from view under the counter or in the thief's palm. One swipe through the unit will record the card's information. A single device can hold the information of 250 bank cards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next, the clerk captures the customer's Personal Identification Number, either by watching as the customer punches it in or on videotape through a \\&amp;quot;pinhole camera\\&amp;quot; installed in the ceiling and zoomed in on the debit machine keypad.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sgt. Coyle said few customers think to shield the machine while punching in their PIN. \\&amp;quot;A bank card is useless without your PIN number,\\&amp;quot; he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police advise customers to be wary of debit keypads that are fixed to a spot on the counter -- it could be an indication a camera is watching from above.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once the deed is done, the clerk will transfer the bank card information, including the time it was recorded, from the device to a computer. Then, they'll match the card to the corresponding time on the videotape to get the PIN, police said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That done, they have access to all the accounts attached to the compromised card, Det. Richard Allman said, adding they could strike immediately or wait several months before stealing the money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before raiding the accounts, the offender will typically make an \\&amp;quot;empty envelope deposit,\\&amp;quot; in which an envelope purportedly containing $5,000 or $10,000 is fed into a bank machine. The offender will proceed to withdraw as much as possible from the victim's accounts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;A lot of times what they'll do is take out the maximum daily withdrawal two minutes before midnight and then again two minutes after midnight,\\&amp;quot; Det. Allman said. \\&amp;quot;You'll see a lot of that going on over a long weekend. The bank won't find the empty deposit envelopes until Tuesday morning.\\&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the meantime, the customer is left out of pocket until the bank investigates and decides whether to reimburse the stolen money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;The banks are coming around, but up until about a year ago, they would hold a client responsible,\\&amp;quot; Det. Allman said. \\&amp;quot;But recently, a lot of the banks have been finding out there is a lot of skimming going on.\\&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tracking down the perpetrators is not easy, Sgt. Coyle said. With the assistance of the banks, \\&amp;quot;we look at individual cases in conjunction with other ones because usually they are not isolated,\\&amp;quot; he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;We see if there are common denominators. Usually there are and it points us in a certain direction.\\&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The following preventive measures are advised by police and banks: cover your PIN; never let your bank card out of sight; change your PIN every three to six months; and reduce the number of accounts accessible through your bank card.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;It may seem like an inconvenience,\\&amp;quot; Det. Allman said, \\&amp;quot;but otherwise you're making it convenient for people out there to steal your money.\\&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>82C8C86F-0584-4D69-B6D7-B0B098826B47</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[생활정보] 은행카드 사기 급증</title>
</post>
