<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이진경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>HP's Unix beats Windows in server test&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;By Stephen Shankland &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNET News.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;July 30, 2003, 3:06 PM PT  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hewlett-Packard released new server speed-test results Wednesday that, for the first time, compare its version of Unix with Windows on the company's top-end Itanium server--and Unix came out ahead. &lt;br&gt;An HP Integrity Superdome with 64 Itanium 2 6M "Madison" processors posted a score of 824,000 transactions per minute on the Transaction Processing Performance Council's widely watched TPC-C test of a single computer running a busy database. The speed beat not only IBM's previous No. 1 result of 764,000 in June but also the previous top result before that, in May, of 707,000 transactions from a system made up of an HP Superdome server running Windows. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The result provides instructive new information in the years-long competition between Unix and Windows. Although the two operating systems have been pitted against each other, rarely has it been on the same hardware.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the system with HP's version of Unix, called HP-UX, was faster, it cost $6.8 million compared with $5.1 million for the Windows system. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HP's Superdome can simultaneously run Linux, Windows and HP-UX in separate partitions. However, the collection of software needed to make such a system is more mature for HP-UX than for Windows or Linux. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HP, which co-developed the Itanium chip designs along with manufacturer Intel, has been working for years on fostering Itanium support among programmers, software companies, business partners and customers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HP is in the process of simplifying several server lines, gradually replacing Compaq Computer's Alpha processor, SGI's MIPS and HP's own PA-RISC with Itanium. In the meantime, though, HP is updating the existing lines to give customers plenty of time to switch. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday, HP said it began shipping a new high-end AlphaServer, the 32-processor GS1280, which is based on the newer EV7 version of the Alpha. Later this year a 64-processor model will arrive. Another update in 2004 will use the faster EV79 processor, the last of the Alpha lineage originally developed at Digital Equipment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, HP's prime competitors, Sun Microsystems and IBM, are hoping to profit from the changes among HP's customers in coming years. If customers are going to switch to a new server, Sun and IBM argue, they might as well also switch to a new company. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.zdnet.co.kr/biztech/hwsw/biztrend/article.jsp?id=63396&amp;forum=1" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;font color=blue&gt;한글 version&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A4487158-F797-49D7-8FEB-30341ED3AECA</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>HP's Unix beats Windows in server test</title>
</post>
