<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권칠환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>If you are not familiar with SharePoint Saturday events, they are free, community-focused SharePoint events dedicated to educating and engaging members of the local technical community.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are excited to announce that the first-ever SharePoint Saturday Toronto event is being held in Toronto on July 11th, 2009.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are requesting that everyone interested in attending register now!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join SharePoint architects, developers, and other professionals that work with Microsoft Office SharePoint Server 2007 for ‘SharePoint Saturday’, on Saturday, July 11th, 2009 at the Microsoft Canada Conference Centre located at 1950 Meadowvale Blvd in Mississauga, Ontario, Canada.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SharePoint Saturday will be an educational, informative &amp; lively day filled with sessions from respected SharePoint professionals &amp; Microsoft MVPs, covering a wide variety of SharePoint-oriented topics.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SharePoint Saturday is FREE, open to the public and is your local chance to immerse yourself in SharePoint!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The day starts at 9:00 AM with a short introductory keynote and ends at 4:30 PM. Lunch will be provided and there will be numerous giveaways throughout the day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There will be three primary content tracks, and each track will consist of five presentations lasting approximately one hour, and ranging from introductory, 100-level content to highly technical, 400-level "expert" sessions.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Speakers will represent a broad cross-section of the community and will offer a variety of different perspectives and points of view.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SharePoint Saturday Toronto is a great opportunity to learn, share and network. Please join us on Saturday, July 11th, 2009 for a full day of education and excitement. A full session schedule will be posted soon. We look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information, please visit www.sharepointsaturday.org/toronto.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>A8C6276E-03A8-41D3-AD38-FF4682BAC193</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-06-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SharePoint Saturday Toronto on July 11th 2009</title>
</post>
