<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>By&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Linux News Desk &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linux Creator Will Devote Himself Exclusively to Linux Development &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;(June 17, 2003) - OSDL, a non-profit, global consortium of leading technology companies dedicated to accelerating the adoption of Linux, and Transmeta Corporation today announced that Linus Torvalds, the creator of Linux, will join OSDL as the first OSDL Fellow.(See Torvald's online notice about his "big news.")&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an OSDL fellow, Linus will work exclusively on leading the development of Linux, the open source software that he created in 1991 as a university student in Finland. Torvalds will dedicate himself now full-time to guiding a distributed team of thousands of Linux developers around the world. At OSDL, he will have hands-on access to its state-of-the-art computing resources and test facility. He will also help set priorities and direction for the Lab's different industry initiatives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It feels a bit strange to finally officially work on what I've been doing for the last twelve years, but with the upcoming 2.6.x release it makes sense to be able to concentrate fully on Linux," Torvalds said. "OSDL is the perfect setting for vendor-independent and neutral Linux development."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Founded in 2000, OSDL has data centers in Portland, Oregon and Yokohama, Japan used by Linux developers around the world. With investment backing from Computer Associates, Fujitsu, Hitachi, HP, IBM, Intel, NEC and others, the lab sponsors key industry projects, including industry initiatives to enhance Linux for use in corporate data centers (Data Center Linux) and in telecommunications networks (Carrier Grade Linux). OSDL is increasingly being recognized as the center-of-gravity for the Linux industry: an important and independent central body that invests in the growth and innovation of Linux for the benefit of customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linux is the fastest-growing operating system in the world. Revenue for Linux-based servers grew 62% in 2002, while overall sales of servers dropped 8%, according to Gartner Dataquest, a market research company. By 2007, Gartner predicts that Linux may grab 15% of the worldwide market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Torvalds will join OSDL on leave from Transmeta Corporation, where he is currently a Transmeta Fellow. Transmeta is an OSDL member and worked with OSDL on the transition. "Linus has made substantial technological contributions as a member of our development team here at Transmeta," said Matthew R. Perry, president and CEO, Transmeta Corporation. "Transmeta appreciates and fully supports Linus' strong interest in devoting his attention and energy to certain emerging industry-wide Open Source initiatives at OSDL." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>AC1046B2-3892-4751-B8E9-0F2AC619A5DB</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-06-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Linus Torvalds Joins OSDL</title>
</post>
