<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김승엽</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Security a concern? Get up to speed on latest security techniques &lt;br&gt;By Mark Baard, special to searchSystemsManagement&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;Fire your curren입니curity advisor, he sux.\\&amp;quot; That was the message &lt;br&gt;\\&amp;quot;Splurge\\&amp;quot; left for the New York Times when he hacked the newspaper's &lt;br&gt;Web site on Feb. 15. Indeed, if security is your responsibility, a &lt;br&gt;successful hack could send YOUR head rolling. Where teenage hackers are &lt;br&gt;exalted as geniuses, \\&amp;quot;software engineers working on Internet security &lt;br&gt;are [indicted as] idiots,\\&amp;quot; writes Elizabeth Conner, in a May 2000 &lt;br&gt;article at Tom's Hardware Guide. The hacker \\&amp;quot;gets all the glory, the &lt;br&gt;software engineer gets fired.\\&amp;quot;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conner is paraphrasing security expert Marcus Raynum, the keynote &lt;br&gt;speaker at last spring's meeting of The Internet Security Conference &lt;br&gt;(TISC). Systems managers and security experts will again meet in Los &lt;br&gt;Angeles on June 4 for TISC 2001. Firewalls and wireless security will &lt;br&gt;top the list for the show's conferences and seminars. And Internet &lt;br&gt;security consultancy Foundstone will teach systems managers to review &lt;br&gt;their companies' security systems through hands-on exercises.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is your opportunity to get up to speed on prevention measures you &lt;br&gt;can take to improve security and thwart hackers. Education now can &lt;br&gt;prevent future problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can read TISC 2000 coverage at the Tom's Hardware Guide Web site &lt;br&gt;(http://www4.tomshardware.com/business/00q2/000502). And to learn more &lt;br&gt;about TISC 2001, visit http://www.tisc.corecom.com. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We also urge you to subscribe to TISC Insight at &lt;br&gt;http://www.tisc.corecom.com/insight.html. Insight is a newsletter that &lt;br&gt;offers in-depth analyses and advice for improving network security. &lt;br&gt;Volume 2, Issue 9 lists \\&amp;quot;Ten Things to Ask Your ASP\\&amp;quot; about its network &lt;br&gt;security capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a broader perspective on security matters, read the August 2000 &lt;br&gt;Information Week story at &lt;br&gt;http://www.informationweek.com/800/security.htm. \\&amp;quot;In this customer-&lt;br&gt;centric world of instant access and continuous connections,\\&amp;quot; writes &lt;br&gt;Susan Breidenbach, \\&amp;quot;e-business initiatives that outpace security &lt;br&gt;considerations are heading for disaster.\\&amp;quot; &lt;br&gt;--------------------------------&lt;br&gt;About the author: Mark Baard is a contributing editor in Milton, Mass.</content>
    <postId>B1BA8F96-9541-438F-826D-7FFECDDBD378</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-10-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Systemmanagement:career tip:Security a concern? Get up to speed on latest security techniques</title>
</post>
