<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>khboo</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hmmm... I could not think of not using a credit card for on-line shopping.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are a few forms in providing on-line transactions including your example&lt;br&gt;and still new ideas and technologies are being rolled out even though the concept&lt;br&gt;behind does not look to be much different from each other.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Using a broker(?) membership&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the earliest (mid-nineties) and primitive(?) style. Establish a third party&lt;br&gt;company that handles transactions for both seller and buyer. This company may be&lt;br&gt;doing credit card clearing by itself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A buyer becomes a member (with norminal membership like $5.00 per year for example) &lt;br&gt;and gets assigned with an ID. This ID is used when purchasing products from the seller.&lt;br&gt;This company bills (usually through a credit card account) the buyer and the seller bills this company. The company gets some commision in return.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Using a credit card clearing house&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Again using a third party clearing house. This seems to be one of the most usual &lt;br&gt;(for small businesses) patterns these days. By the time when a buyer clicks the 'purchase'&lt;br&gt;button (after submitting his/her credit card info.), the clearing house performs necessary transactions on behalf of the seller. The money stays in the account of the clearing house &lt;br&gt;for a while before being transfered to the seller's account (after deducting a certain percentage &lt;br&gt;of the total transaction amount). For more information on this, search for web on something &lt;br&gt;like 'credit card clearing service'. Also see how to choose a clearing house at&lt;br&gt;http://www.workz.com/content/476.asp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Seller membership&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your business is big enough so everybody knows, buyers might want to be a member&lt;br&gt;of your shopping service, so you know how to charge them since they need to provide the&lt;br&gt;membership ID for purchasing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Deposit using a financial institution (your example)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I think I have never seen this form other than when using a government agency service. &lt;br&gt;When you file your tax return using the Internet, you may owe some money to you-know-what&lt;br&gt;agency :-) You can deposit that amount through one of the several designated financial&lt;br&gt;institutions. Even in this case, you might want to make an on-line deposit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some new forms are still evolving like MS eMoney and we will see how it will fly (or die?).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There might be some other methods as well, so continue your research and enjoy!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;쇼핑몰 만들때요, 한국에서는 신용카드결제부분 프로그램을 사서 했는데 이곳도 그렇겠죠? &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;쇼핑몰 돌아다니다 보면 verysign이니 entrust니 해서 비슷한 역할을 하는 제품이 있는것 같긴 한데.. 이곳에서 쇼핑몰 해본 경험 있으시면 조언좀 부탁드립니다. 만약 사면 결제부분 프로그램은 신경안써도 되는 건지 혹은 다른 사항이 있는지.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;그리고, 한국은 은행명, 계좌번호, 사람이름 알려주고 \\&amp;quot;여기로 입금하시오\\&amp;quot; 했던 것 같은데, 여기서는 웹사이트에서 이런 종류의 메시지를 한번도 못봤어요. 여기도 무통장 입금 되는거 맞죠?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;그럼 수고하시고..&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B550069F-1C8C-44B3-8A01-C9F1FE0E93E2</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-05-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] 쇼핑몰구축시 카드결제문제</title>
</post>
