<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강동욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>일단 급한데로 답변을 해본다면....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actually, I have not experience of uploading files but if I should do it, I would go to&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;http://search.microsoft.com/default.asp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and select two categories&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[v] Developer Resources&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[v] Support &amp; the Knowledge Base&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;and enter the keyword 'upload' and click [submit query] then you can see a lot of technical information about upload. There might be some source code too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe, you need to use specific Form data type in client script part and a module to save to server computer in server script part.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secondly, when you use logon page, the page should use SSL protocol that can be configured from Web setting. Then, you don't have to encrypt it directly because SSL make all data encrypted when using SSL. When saving the password to database, you should encrypt it or not depending on the significance of the site. You can use very simple encode method just not to be seen easily when somebody in the company open the database.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;회원중 한명이 질문해서 여기 올려 봅니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;좋은 자료 있으신분은 답변 부탁 드립니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; my company expects me to build VB application using Citrix Metaframe on Windows 2000 server.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; My questions are&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; 1. How upload files(probably kind of source code) from client machine to server machine?- I guess(I am familiar with Citrix things),the application will be running on the server.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; 2. When user enters user name and password , how to encrypt password? Is there any way to accomplish it programmatically rather than server setting?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B6828521-85F3-4DB9-91EE-6919A7D83B7F</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-01T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] [q] upload and password</title>
</post>
