<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Gary Pollice&lt;br&gt;Professor of Practice, Worcester Polytechnic Institute&lt;br&gt;15 Jun 2005&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;from The Rational Edge: In his monthly column, Gary Pollice discusses the virtues of Eclipse technology and explains why he and other instructors at Worcester Polytechnic Institute use it in their courses.&lt;br&gt;===&lt;br&gt; Every advance in software technology requires parallel changes in software development tools. As someone who teaches future software developers, I am constantly weighing pedagogical concerns against my students' need for tools to do their assignments. Given the rapid rate of technological change, how much can I -- or should I -- teach my students about specific tools? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the one hand, I know that if college professors don't employ good tools in the classroom, students may leave with significant book knowledge but still be at a practical disadvantage. On the other hand, teaching students to use "industrial strength" tools requires a lot of time. It would be nice to have a crystal ball to tell us which tools are worth the investment. Remember the CASE tools of the '80s? We spent a lot of time learning how to use them, but how many are still in use today?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fortunately, life has become much simpler for me lately. Eclipse is close to a perfect software development environment for my students. It is industrial strength. You don't have to know everything about it to use it effectively. And it's as flexible as you could ever want.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you don't know what Eclipse is, I urge you to take a look at the Eclipse Web pages.1 The first sentence on the main page says it all: "Eclipse is a kind of universal tool platform -- an open extensible IDE for anything and nothing in particular." It is truly the Swiss army knife of software tools. Sound too good to be true? Most of us know that when a tool tries to do everything, it ends up doing little well. But that's just not so with Eclipse!&lt;br&gt;===&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to http://www-128.ibm.com/developerworks/rational/library/jun05/pollice/index.html?ca=dnp-425 to read on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>C21534AA-AD45-4057-B037-795B7A59F312</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-06-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Why I teach Eclipse</title>
</post>
