<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강동욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>우리 회사 에서 co-op을 하고 떠나는 대학생이 남기는 글 임다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi everyone,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Today is my last day.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;I would like to take this opportunity to thank the XXX team for an enjoyable and at the same time useful and educational&lt;br&gt;work term. I had an amazing time and learned a lot. A special thanks to Johne for patiently answering all my questions and &lt;br&gt;Shawn for providing me with the opportunity.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;I wish you all the best of luck and success with the product. You have managed to combine a great idea with a great team&lt;br&gt;and I am sure the business will come.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Thank you,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;그리고 또 어떤 놈이 덧붙혀서.. 쓰길...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What he said.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Seriously though, I had a good time this summer with all you guys.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Never have I had the opportunity to work with so many smart people.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Some of you may know that I commute from more than an hour away to come here daily, and the weird thing is, I never minded coming in to work at all.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Now there's some cheese fries, for you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;All you talented guys writing that big awesome app really made me feel like, well less of a boy.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I learned alot this summer.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;I hope you guys don't forget your roots, and always remember how much of your success is based on, you know, the guy by the kitchen with the earphones.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;I'll be in school for the next year, then who knows what?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;You can reach me there at XXXX@XXXXXX.ca&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Best of luck,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;XXXX&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;그냥 가볍게 읽어 보시길...&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;여기서 태어나서 자란 아그들이 쓴글이니..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;강동욱</content>
    <postId>C9F3E2B8-4C87-4497-89D0-3DBA1C3BB45A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-08-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>(3) 실무 영어 - 현지 오피스 메일</title>
</post>
