<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김승엽</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>WebSphere administration tips&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From \\&amp;quot;AS/400 WebSphere overview\\&amp;quot; by Jim Mason, president of Cape Cod Bay &lt;br&gt;Systems, which originally appeared in the May/June edition of AS/400 Experts &lt;br&gt;Journal, Vol. 3, No. 3. Provided courtesy of The 400 Group &lt;br&gt; (http://www.the400group.com).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WebSphere Advanced edition is installed in separate directories from WebSphere &lt;br&gt;Standard edition on the AS/400, and both can reside on the same AS/400.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You must be aware of the compatibility between different levels of OS/400, Java &lt;br&gt;and WebSphere and your web applications to run your e-business environment. A &lt;br&gt;given version of WebSphere will provide runtime support for servlets at a &lt;br&gt;specific API level that may not match the level you used to develop and test the &lt;br&gt;servlets with another tool like VisualAge for Java. Currently, WebSphere &lt;br&gt;Application Server Advanced Edition 3.0 can only be run with the JDK 1.1.7. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, it is important to remain current with PTF levels. In addition, you can &lt;br&gt;see significant benefits for both performance and application function to run on &lt;br&gt;the latest version of OS/400. It is rare that older applications have problems &lt;br&gt;running in newer WebSphere environments. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember, on AS/400 you can run multiple web servers with WebSphere concurrently &lt;br&gt;if you need to. Each web server has to have a unique named instance and runs on &lt;br&gt;a specified TCP port. Usually the default production server uses the default TCP &lt;br&gt;ports 80 and 443 for HTTP and HTTPS. To access other web servers, the URL from &lt;br&gt;the client browser must specify the proper port for access (for example, &lt;br&gt;http://localhost:12001/servlet/MyServlet). Therefore, you may want to &lt;br&gt;dynamically specify port numbers at runtime for your web pages rather than hard &lt;br&gt;code them. Servlets handle this very nicely, since they can output a web page &lt;br&gt;definition dynamically. The commands WRKHTTPFCFG, STRTCPSVR SERVER(*HTTP) &lt;br&gt;INSTANCE(&amp;lt;http instance&amp;gt;), ENDTCPSVR SERVER(*HTTP) INSTANCE( &amp;lt;http instance&amp;gt;) &lt;br&gt;allow you to manage the HTTP server. To administer the HTTP server, use &lt;br&gt;STRTCPSVR SERVER(*HTTP) INSTANCE( *ADMIN). Use NET *STAT CONN to see current TCP &lt;br&gt;ports in use. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bootstrap.properties configuration file determines how WebSphere is started &lt;br&gt;with an HTTP server on your AS/400. You may need to edit the entries in this &lt;br&gt;file especially if you have servlet chains implemented with their threading &lt;br&gt;options for responses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The /QIBM/ProdData/IBMWebAS/servlets/ directory is the default directory from &lt;br&gt;which WebSphere automatically loads servlets. Servlets in this directory can be &lt;br&gt;invoked by class name. Jar and zip files are automatically searched for classes. &lt;br&gt;In addition, you can configure the servlets.properties file for WebSphere to &lt;br&gt;point to other directories where WebSphere should automatically load servlets &lt;br&gt;and JSPs from. Servlets found elsewhere on the normal Java classpath are loaded &lt;br&gt;only once when WebSphere starts and not automatically reloaded. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use the servlets properties file to configure: other directories to load &lt;br&gt;servlets from, alias names for servlets and initial arguments passed to servlets &lt;br&gt;when they are loaded.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>D3E48377-29E1-44C1-B13D-E76CEF8E45C4</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-10-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>AS/400 ADMIN TIPS:WebSphere administration tips</title>
</post>
