<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김형태</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;쉐어포인트 관심 있으신 분들,&lt;br&gt;4월 19일 North York 에서 행사가 있네요.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DevTeach Community Event &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have been register to DevTeach Special Event.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DevTeach Community Event&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;User Group SharePoint 2010 Tour (Toronto)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to increase your skills and improve productivity by leveraging the new features of SharePoint 2010 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SharePoint 2010 allows you to build web sites, manage lists of data, collaborate on documents, and so much more &amp;#65533; all done through a simple, easy to use, web interface. When you need to go beyond the native capabilities of the product, SharePoint 2010 provides the APIs and Visual Studio 2010 provides the tools that allow you to quickly and easily add customizations. Whether you&amp;#47976;e new to SharePoint development or a seasoned veteran, this session is for you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;During this complimentary session scheduled in select cities, you will learn from SharePoint experts how to leverage SharePoint 2010 for your web infrastructure and how to build applications for the SharePoint environment whether you are a web developer or SharePoint veteran. We will start with material targeted at those new to SharePoint development, covering key foundational topics (like Features and the Solutions Framework) that are vital to understanding how customizations are componentized and packaged. You will also learn about the new tools in Visual Studio 2010 that make SharePoint development easier than ever before. We&amp;#47968;l see how the new templates, wizards and designers improve productivity by automatically managing project structure and manifest files for you. We&amp;#47968;l demonstrate how you can use visual designers to speed-up the process of building Web parts. You will also learn how the new client object models and REST services enable you to make the use of SharePoint functionality from client applications across the enterprise. Finally, you will learn how to debug that SharePoint applications using the same F5 deployment and debugging experience enjoyed by .NET developers for years. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Event Description &lt;br&gt;Event: User Group SharePoint 2010 Tour (Toronto) &lt;br&gt;Date: Monday Apr 19th, 2010 &lt;br&gt;Location: Toronto Public Library&lt;br&gt;5120 Yonge Street&lt;br&gt;Toronto, ON M2N 5N9&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6:30 to 6:50 (Pizza - Meet and Greet)&lt;br&gt;6:50 to 7:00 (Group Business)&lt;br&gt;7:00 to 9:00 (Presentation) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting will be held in Room 1 on the 2nd floor of the library &lt;br&gt;Get more details at www.tvbug.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Type: User Group &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>DFFE6EDD-DDFD-4BB0-AE42-6BC243EA32BD</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>User Group SharePoint 2010 Tour (Toronto)</title>
</post>
