<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>나수환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Subject: FW: Scam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We actually received a call last week from the 809 area code.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The woman said "Hey, this is Karen. Sorry I missed you--get back to us&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;quickly.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Have something important to tell you." Then she repeated a phone number&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;beginning with 809 . "We didn't respond".&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Then this week, we received the following e-mail:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Subject: DON'T EVER DIAL AREA CODE 809, 284 AND 876&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT INFORMATION PROVIDED TO US BY AT&amp;T.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;DON'T EVER DIAL AREA CODE 809&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This one is being distributed all over the US &amp; Canada. This is pretty&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;scary,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;especially given the way they try to get you to call.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Be sure you read this and pass it on to all your friends and family so they&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;don't get scammed!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;MAJOR SCAM:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Don't respond to Emails, phone calls, or web pages which tell you to call &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;an&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;"809" area Phone Number.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This is a very important issue of Scam Busters because it alerts you to a&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;scam that is spreading *extremely* quickly, can easily cost you $2400 or&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;more, and is difficult to avoid unless you are aware of it.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We'd like to thank Verizon for bringing this scam to our attention.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;This scam has also been identified by the NationalFraudInformationCenterand&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;is costing victims a lot of money.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There are lots of different permutations of this scam.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;HERE'S HOW IT WORKS:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You will receive a message on your answering machine or your pager, which&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asks you to call a number beginning with area code 809. The reason you're&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;asked to call varies. It can be to receive information about a family &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;member&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;who has been ill, to tell you someone has-been arrested, died, to let you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;know you have won a wonderful prize, etc. In each case, you are told to &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;call&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the 809 number right away. Since there are so many new area codes these&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;days, people unknowingly return these calls.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;If you call from the US or Canada, you will apparently be charged $2425&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;per-minute.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Or, you'll get a long recorded message The point is, they will try to keep&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you on the phone as long as possible to increase the charges. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Unfortunately,&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;when you get your phone bill, you'll often be charged more than $24,100.00.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;WHY IT WORKS:&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The 809 area code is located in the British Virgin Islands (The Bahamas).&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The 809 area code can be used as a "pay-per-call" number, similar to 900&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;numbers in the US or Canada . Since 809 is not in the US or in Canada, it &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;is&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;not covered by U.S./Cdn regulations of 900 numbers, which require that you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;be notified and warned of charges and rates involved when you call a&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;pay-per-call" number.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;There is also no requirement that the company provide a time period during&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;which you may terminate the call without being charged. Further, whereas&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;many U.S. &amp; Canadian homes that have 900 number blocking to avoid these&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;kinds of charges, do not work in preventing calls to the 809 area code.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;We recommend that no matter how you get the message, if you are asked to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;call a number with an 809 area code that you don't recognize, just &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;disregard&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;the message.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Be wary of e-mail, or calls, asking you to call an 809 a real code number.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It's important to prevent becoming a victim of this scam, since trying to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;fight the charges afterwards can become a real nightmare. That's because &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;you&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;did actually make the call. If you complain, both your local phone company&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;and your long distance carrier will not want to get involved and will most&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;likely tell you that they are simply providing the billing for the foreign&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;company. You'll end up dealing with a foreign company that argues they have&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;done nothing wrong.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Please forward this entire message to your friends, family and colleagues &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;to&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;help them become aware of this scam.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Sandi Van Handel&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;AT&amp;T Field Service Manager&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>EC599039-2C58-4288-AC9E-3DA62BF95283</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-06-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>DON'T EVER DIAL AREA CODE 809, 284 AND 876</title>
</post>
