<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Seung Yeop Kim</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Planning for disasters&lt;br&gt;By Aeleen Frisch&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We all know that systems need to be backed up in case of a failure. But &lt;br&gt;what we sometimes forget is that an effective backup plan is an ongoing &lt;br&gt;process. This set of questions from Aeleen Frisch's Essential System &lt;br&gt;Administration will help you design an effective backup plan. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many factors to consider in developing a backup plan. These &lt;br&gt;questions are among the most important:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* What files need to be backed up? The simplest answer is, of course, &lt;br&gt;everything, and while everything but scratch files and directories need &lt;br&gt;to be saved somewhere, it doesn't all have to be saved as part of the &lt;br&gt;system backups. The OS, for example, came on CD-ROM. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Where are these files? This question involves both where the &lt;br&gt;important files are with the file system of any particular system and &lt;br&gt;which systems hold the most important data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Who will back up the files? The answer may depend on where the files &lt;br&gt;are. For example, many sites assign the backup responsibility for &lt;br&gt;server systems to the system administrator and the individual &lt;br&gt;workstations up to users. This may or may not be a good idea depending &lt;br&gt;on whether or not the important files are really being backed up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Where, when, and under what conditions should backups be performed? &lt;br&gt;Where refers to the computer system on which the backup will he &lt;br&gt;performed; this need not necessarily be the same as the system where &lt;br&gt;the files are physically located. Similarly, in an ideal world, all &lt;br&gt;backups would be performed after hours on unmounted file systems. &lt;br&gt;That's not always practical in the real world, however.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* How often do these files change? This information will help you &lt;br&gt;decide both when and how often to perform backups and the type of &lt;br&gt;schedule to implement. For example, if your system supports a large &lt;br&gt;ongoing development project, then the files on it are likely to change &lt;br&gt;very frequently and will need to be backed up at least daily and &lt;br&gt;probably after hours. On the other hand, if the only volatile file on &lt;br&gt;your system is a large database, its file system might need to be &lt;br&gt;backed up several times every day while the other file systems on the &lt;br&gt;same system would be backed up only once a week.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* How quickly does an important missing or damaged file need to be &lt;br&gt;restored? Backups protect against both widespread and isolated file &lt;br&gt;loss, and the timeframe in which the key files need to be back on-line &lt;br&gt;needs to be taken into account. The number of key files, how widely &lt;br&gt;spread they are throughout a file system (or network), and how large &lt;br&gt;they are will also influence matters. Your system may have only one &lt;br&gt;irreplaceable file, but you'll need to plan very differently depending &lt;br&gt;on whether it is 1K or 1GB in size. (Note that losing even a single 1K &lt;br&gt;file can wreak havoc if it's the license file without which the central &lt;br&gt;application program won't run.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* Where will the data be restored? Will the backup files be used only &lt;br&gt;on the system from which they were made, or is there an expectation &lt;br&gt;that they could be restored to a different system in an emergency. If &lt;br&gt;multisystem compatibility is important some or all of the time, it &lt;br&gt;needs to be taken into account in designing the backup and recovery &lt;br&gt;plan.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>EF8BB44A-77B5-4448-A837-E067FF3D0E0B</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-09-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>WINDOWS Administrator Tip: Planning for disasters</title>
</post>
