<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>허현옥</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>저는 프로그램 언어가 죽었다는 말은 그 언어를 지원하는 큰 밴더나 커뮤니티가 없어졌다는 걸로 개인적으로는 판단합니다.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;현재 자바때문에 먹고 살고 있는 수많은 WAS 개발 업체들이나, MS 에 대항(?)하기 좋아하는 사람들이 많은 이상 아직 사장될 것이라고 말하기는 힘들죠.&lt;br&gt;그리고, 컴퓨터 언어가 나와서 크게 부흥을 하고 나서 사라져 버리는 경우는 드물었던거 같습니다. COBOL도 그렇지만, MS의 VB 같은 경우도 VC가 잇는데 왜 굳이 계속 VB를 MS가 만들어 내겠습니까.. 쓰는 사람들이 있으니까 계속 만들어 내는 거겠죠.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;모든 것이 그렇듯이 처음에 나와서 "이야~" 할때 만큼의 큰 충격적인 기술의 변화가 없어서 이런 얘기들이 나오는 것 같기도 하구요. 또한 그런 충격적인 변화가 얼마나 개발자들에게는 힘든 일인지는 개발하시는 분들 모두 다 아실꺼에요..^^(박찬호는 아니지만, 우리도 적응기간이 필요하죠..^^)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;암튼 이런 얘기를 사람들이 하는 건 그저 "말하기 좋아하는 사람들" 이 하는 일이죠. 프로그래머들은 그저 열심히 프로그램하고 자신의 Logical 한 생각을 계속해서 쌓아간다면, 언어가 바뀌는 건 크게 문제가 되지 않는 다는 걸 모두들 알고 계실테니까요..^^( 언어는 적응기간으로 되지만, Logical Ideas 는 적응한다고 되는 문제가 아니죠...)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;암튼 모두들 열심히 하는 일에 최선을 다하면 뭐가 바뀌든지 우리는 안 살아남겠어요..^^&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;"Java Is Dead, Long Live Java!" &amp;#8211; The Future of Java&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Lightweight Frameworks Like Hibernate, Spring, and HiveMind are the Future of Java&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;By: Bryan W. Taylor&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Jan. 10, 2006 03:45 AM&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;About Bryan W. Taylor&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Bryan Taylor is a Senior Software Engineer at Rackspace Managed Hosting based in San Antonio, Texas. He has designed and developed enterprise systems for over 10 years.&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;It seems that lately lots of writers have been bashing Java. Some people seem to think that Java has stagnated, and that the "hyper-enthusiasts" have left. Well, the rest of us are just quietly coding on a platform that is more exciting than ever. Other technologies like Ruby, PHP, .NET, or AJAX might get more hype and acclaim lately, but hype aside, Java still produces the majority of innovation in the software profession. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;You can get a sense of Java's health by simply looking at how many projects are out there using Java. Pop on over to Sourceforge and look at the number of projects by language: http://sourceforge.net/softwaremap/trove_list.php?form_cat=160. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Certainly Sourceforge is not the final measure, but it's a reasonable reality check. Anyway, you'll find 17300+ Java projects, the most of any language. That's more than PHP (12675), Ruby (425), and .NET (3094 C#, 347 VB.Net) combined. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Because of its prominence, Java gets a lot of attention and with it much criticism, some of it valid. What many may not realize is that some big breakthroughs have arrived and that the Java development landscape is solving important problems. Let's take a view of where Java is going to go in the next year or two as these ideas gain traction. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;The first big arena of innovation is the addition of scripting support. Some people rightly claim Ruby or Python is better the Java for some tasks. Groovy and Beanshell solve these same problems and will become a standard (in the JSR sense) part of the Java stack. Each offers something better than standalone scripting. Both integrate into a truly mixed environment with compiled bytecode and interpreted scripts interoperating smoothly. Beanshell's syntax offers as little surprise as possible for the Java developer and Groovy gives a Ruby-like syntactic efficiency, but can also be compiled to pure bytecode and reused seamlessly, a big improvement over JRuby or Jython. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Second, the days of heavyweight frameworks are gone. J2EE-style EJBs are out. Now, the lightweight frameworks like Hibernate, Spring, and HiveMind are the future of Java. The heavy Struts of the past is being replaced with two new directions: Struts Shale based on JSF and Struts Ti is a wholesale merge with Webwork. These projects share a common idea that the framework should stay out of the way of your object model. EJB3 takes the same view. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;A third major innovation where Java leads is aspect-oriented programming (AOP). AOP will unclutter your code by moving "cross-cutting" concerns like logging and security to transparent method interceptors. AspectJ is the Rolls Royce for AOP, but Spring has lightweight AOP themes as does the new JBoss. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Fourth, the PHP crowd had a legitimate gripe that banging out a simple web page took too much work if you were using JSP and Struts. But our templating solutions like Velocity, Freemarker, and now Groovy don't make you choose between ultralight text generation and powerful mid-tier solutions. Groovlets should make for some rapid servlet solutions. For those people who really like PHP, keep it: Java 1.6 makes it the reference implementation for the new web scripting language bindings, so you can do your web views in PHP and use Java for model and controller. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Finally, Java's traditional strength in the tools arena just keeps increasing. Eclipse is the best IDE on the planet, and it appears that Eclipse has reached critical mass like Ant and JUnit did, in that people simply expect solutions that extend it. Eclipse's team coding capabilities for CVS and Subversion (via the Subclipse plugin) are first-rate. The refactoring and debugging support are top notch. Integration of standard tools like ant, compilers, JUnit, and javadocs are about as good as you can imagine. &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;So perhaps the hyper-enthusiasts have left and the buzzword mongers will proclaim that Java is dead. If Java is "dead," it's only because it was laid to rest so that a better, lighter, more agile, form of Java could replace it, so Long Live Java!&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Published Jan. 10, 2006 &amp;#8212; Reads 13,283 &lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2006 SYS-CON Media. All Rights Reserved.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>F645A56E-0005-470B-AE36-40C5ACE76D50</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>프로그래밍 언어가 죽었다...?</title>
</post>
