<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>하종수</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello COSKA,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been a long time since I have been visited here previously. &lt;br&gt;How are you doing? Some of you may remember me or maybe &lt;br&gt;do not have any clue. I was in Toronto from 1997 ~ early 2000 &lt;br&gt;and was a COSKA member. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After returning to Korea, I miss Canada from time to time when things&lt;br&gt;get rough in Seoul. Actually my life was much less stressful in Canada. &lt;br&gt;Korea seems not that much having changed even with IMF bail out situation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My job experience in Canadian firms was much greater than my jobs after returning to Seoul. It was less stressful and more faire than those jobs I had in Seoul. Politics is the still the way it is in Seoul. Works place politics became more tougher and stressful than ever even though Korean companies beginning to offer 5 days working hours.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One good thing for living in Seoul is that I have all my videos and computer screens in LCD. I have been kicked out my CRT based TV set purchased in Canada and now use LCD TV set, 22 inches. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is though certain that I will retire to Canada cause there’s no point for me to live miserable here with polluted air and stressed people with short fuse, Ha, Ha.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One crazy thins is that my English writing has been improved in Seoul while working for an American Jewish company. It is really ironical that I can even speak better. I owe this to the Jewish panacea on harsh work standard. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway life in Canada seems much more humane to me. I shall return soon to Canada however those news on depressed Canadian economy make me a little bit worried. After 911 nothing seems same in Canada as well. US economy might adversely affect Canadian economy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It already red some IT recession even here in Seoul, though nobody cares about 911 thing in Seoul. Just like SARS and North Korean nuclear threat, we are immune to any news from other part of the world as usual. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How you guys feel on those issues? Are people OK with SARS outbreak in Toronto? How about West Niles virus and mad cow disease? How these affect economy of Canada and Toronto?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I may go visit Toronto soon for settling many personal matters however I am also deadly curious on how COSKA people survives from economical setback of post 911 period. Is it sustainable? Or are there any unexpected casualties such as loss of jobs or business fails? I am&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;really interesting and curious on these things. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Korea, I must say that the country is on the verge of breaking off in every aspect. People have been divided by age, by gender and their social status. Whole country is making very big noise and surely will go down just like shipwreck. I feel very sorry for this but don’t want to be here when it really sinks down. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I really miss Canada, the streets of Toronto and summer time without sweaty humid weather. People are even better in Toronto as they only have one prejudice, racial prejudice whereas people in Seoul still has all the hateful heritage from the past. We even have racial prejudice for 3rd world aliens for 3D works here in Korea. I really hate being here but currently no other choice for me before saving all the money for returning to Canada.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I miss you guys and Canada and hope to see you soon. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bye for now.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</content>
    <postId>FFA9D393-0351-4A70-97E2-1845A22D0583</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>For those who remember me..</title>
</post>
