<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2004-04-14T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Please let me know if someone has got a response from them. Maybe 'we' can talk something about it.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>I got the mail from Procom.&#xD;
&#xD;
Here is the detail info... If you are interested in, please contact to  "hardeepm@procom.ca"&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
The position below is currently available through Procom. If you meet the qualifications and are interested in this opportunity please apply as per the instructions below. Please note, this automated email has been sent to you as the result of a successful keyword search on your resume within our database. Please use discretion by only applying to positions that best suit your qualifications. If you wish to remove yourself from future mailings, please click the link supplied below. &#xD;
&#xD;
Position: Sr. Java Developers (3 full time, 2 contract positions) &#xD;
Required: &#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is currently looking for a Sr. Java Developers for their Mississauga location with the following skill sets listed below. If you are interested and are available, please forward a soft copy of your resume in MS Word format to the e-mail address below. &#xD;
&#xD;
KEY JOB FUNCTIONS &#xD;
&#xD;
?Work closely in a software development team to develop high-quality Java software for critical business applications in an evolving, fast-paced environment. &#xD;
?Be involved in all aspects of the software development, including process design, software design, software implementation, documentation, quality assurance, deployment and production support. &#xD;
?Provide technical leadership and expertise in the design/development of new applications and enhancement of existing applications. &#xD;
?Help establish methologies for ensuring code quality and overall project success. &#xD;
?Make application architecture recommendations to management and the development team. &#xD;
?Assist in definining technical interfaces and processes with clients and partners. &#xD;
?Act as a technical advisor and mentor to less experienced Java developers. &#xD;
?Participate in special projects and ad hoc analyses as necessary. &#xD;
?Investigate system problems and propose solutions and/or design improvements. &#xD;
?Remain abreast of relevant technology developments. &#xD;
?Participate in the rotating on-call program. &#xD;
QUALIFICATIONS &#xD;
&#xD;
?5 plus years experience designing and implementing mission-critical enterprise software using object-oriented programming languages &amp; concepts ( A MUST) &#xD;
?Experience implementing applications using Java, RDBMs, XML, TCP/IP technologies &#xD;
?Experience with Extreme Programming or other agile development practices &#xD;
?Proven technical proficiency &#xD;
?Top-notch problem solving skills, demonstrated ability to perform high quality work &#xD;
?Previous experience on SUN Solaris, Oracle, Eclipse and Ant an asset &#xD;
?Previous experience in the print and/or financial industry is an asset &#xD;
&#xD;
Education: Masters or Bachlor's Degree in Computer Science, or equivalent combination of training and on the job experience. &#xD;
&#xD;
Tools: Java, Eclipse, CVS, Ant, Torque, Oracle &#xD;
&#xD;
Communication Skills: &#xD;
Above Average - Excellent teamwork skills and a service-oriented attitude are essential. Must be able to speak with management and clients and present technical information in a clear, concise manner. Must create and maintain positive peer and client relationships. Requires the ability to speak with non-technical staff about technical issues. Interacts with all levels of the organization. &#xD;
&#xD;
Location: Mississauga &#xD;
Duration: 2 Contract (3 months) &amp; 3 Full Time Roles &#xD;
Rate/Salary: Negotiable. &#xD;
Start Date: ASAP &#xD;
&#xD;
PROCOM SERVICES &#xD;
&#xD;
A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 1700 consultants on assignment. For over 25 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our consultants. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and consultants consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice. &#xD;
We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further. &#xD;
Please submit your most recent resume to: hardeepm@procom.ca &#xD;
&#xD;
NO PHONE CALLS PLEASE &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>0079B312-7BE3-49AD-94D7-41498CE51018</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-04-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Java Developers (3 full time, 2 contract positions)</title>
</post>
