<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>신민용</author>
            <date>2002-09-04T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>You are gonna end up breaking down your daughter's bike or Jennifer's!! ... how dare you??? (HEEE~~)</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>A few facts I found while riding bicycle&#xD;
&#xD;
- There are no flat roads&#xD;
  Like our lives there are no stable conditions. It is up or down. It is never flat.&#xD;
&#xD;
- If there are flat roads all the way, it is not fun to ride&#xD;
  Just like our lives it could be boring without surprises and challenges&#xD;
&#xD;
- I enjoy riding. I even surprise myself&#xD;
  I didn't think I am bicycle person. But I am. Everyone could be one.&#xD;
  Life is like a box of chocolate. You never know until you try them&#xD;
&#xD;
- I even enjoy uphill.&#xD;
  It provides me the challenges. It gives me the opportunity to response. . When I am climbing I do not look beyond then where I am going. When task is too to handle brake it to smaller pieces. So it is easier to handle  &#xD;
&#xD;
- Joon Ho Lee is very athletic&#xD;
  He rides like pro and fixes bike like pro&#xD;
&#xD;
- There are no limits unless brain sets the limit&#xD;
  Last Monday I rode from my home to Erindale park. Easily it could be 15 to 20 km away from my home. I had the notion  that kind of long distance is for special people not person like me. I did it. Because I broke my own limitation wall down.&#xD;
&#xD;
- It is fun and easier when you do it as the group.&#xD;
  I could not do it alone. I had encouragement and support from Jennifer Kang and Joon Ho Lee&#xD;
&#xD;
- Preparation helps&#xD;
  I've been riding the bike for some time like 3 to 4 weeks. It was not long ride but I did it everyday.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Experience helps. Success brings bigger success&#xD;
  Now I can do more. I want to go Milton with my bike soon.&#xD;
   &#xD;
- Know your tool/HW&#xD;
  I am riding my daughter's bike for now. I tried Jennifer's. It made difference from night to day. I am going to buy my own bike today.&#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks Jennifer and Joon Ho. I love you guys and peace&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>023B4DAA-F7A2-494B-B624-AB624BF2017C</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-04T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Thomas Lee and Riding Bicycle :Believe it or not</title>
</post>
