<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Position:		Quality Assurance Analyst&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:		3 Concorde Gate, Don Mills ON &#xD;
			(Occasional travel to business units in the GTA)&#xD;
			  &#xD;
Posting Date:	Mar 1, 2004		Closing Date:  Mar 8, 2004&#xD;
&#xD;
Reporting to the National Manager, Compliance Services, this position is responsible for evaluating, monitoring, and reviewing programs, processes, claims, documentation &amp; files to ensure compliance with internal company requirements &amp; government regulations.&#xD;
&#xD;
Position responsibilities:&#xD;
·	Identifies risks/exceptions/problems, recommends action and escalates unresolved issues to Management to ensure corrective action.&#xD;
·	Coordinates and ensures comprehensive communication between all groups including staff, WF Audit and TCC Quality Assurance.&#xD;
·	Conducts tests on internal processes for efficiency &amp; compliance &amp; recommends improvements.&#xD;
·	Participates in and/or manages projects relating to quality assurance.  &#xD;
·	Assists in the development, preparation and review of policies, procedures, training materials and other communications to ensure business units meet and maintain compliance requirements.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Knowledge, Experience, Skills&#xD;
·	Minimum 3 years experience within a Trans Canada Credit business unit. &#xD;
·	Demonstrated ability to problem-solve and synthesize multiple variables when supporting risk assessments. &#xD;
·	Proven strong analytical skills with high attention to detail.&#xD;
·	Strong organizational skills with demonstrated ability to work well independently.&#xD;
·	Familiarity with Microsoft Office Applications required.&#xD;
·	Supreme knowledge preferred.&#xD;
&#xD;
Qualified candidates should contact Katherine Karbownik at 416 382-5314&#xD;
 or e-mail Katherine.Karbownik@tcrs.ca &#xD;
Don't forget the Employee Referral Award program.&#xD;
Do you know someone who may have the qualifications for this position?  If so, talk to them about applying.&#xD;
&#xD;
You could earn  $$$$$&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>03B94534-A893-42BC-B995-6F14DE905839</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Quality Assurance Analyst</title>
</post>
