<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강윤정</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>PETA: 'Happy cows' ad is a lie&#xD;
By Elizabeth Weise, USA TODAY&#xD;
&#xD;
The animal rights group PETA plans to sue the California Milk Advisory Board Wednesday over its award-winning "Happy Cows" campaign. PETA says the idyllic conditions portrayed in the ads amount to false advertising.&#xD;
&#xD;
  The life of cows is far from ideal, People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals argues.  &#xD;
PETA &#xD;
&#xD;
The two-year-old campaign features talking and singing cows discussing the pleasures of life in warm, sunny California. The slogan: "Great cheese comes from happy cows. Happy cows come from California." The state produces 1.6 billion pounds of cheese a year, second only to Wisconsin.&#xD;
&#xD;
The suit, which is expected to be filed in California Superior Court, says California dairy cows live on muddy, feces- and urine-soaked lots devoid of any vegetation, not on grassy hillsides as depicted in the ads. &#xD;
&#xD;
"Our goal with the lawsuit is to let people know that if they're consuming dairy products, they're promoting cruelty to animals," PETA's Bruce Friedrich says. &#xD;
&#xD;
Nancy Fletcher of the California Milk Advisory Board says she hasn't seen the complaint and can't comment. But she did point out that PETA filed a similar complaint with the Federal Trade Commission in April, and the FTC found that it was without merit.&#xD;
&#xD;
The ads do portray an idealized and unrealistic view of the life of a dairy cow, but consumers know the difference between reality and fantasy, says Jim Reynolds, a professor of veterinary science at the University of California-Davis and chair of the American Association of Bovine Practitioners Animal Welfare Committee, an international association of veterinarians. &#xD;
&#xD;
"I know when I buy a beer in a bar, I don't get two women in bikinis standing next to me," Reynolds says.&#xD;
&#xD;
Still, a dairy cow's life isn't easy. At 2 years old the animals are artificially inseminated to keep them pregnant and producing milk. Calves are taken from their mothers within 24 hours of birth because calves drink only 1 to 3 gallons of milk a day, while modern dairy cows produce up to 10 gallons a day. The extra milk would be a potential source of infection, endangering the cow. The bull calves are either sent to veal pens or to feedlots, while the heifers are raised until they can be mated.&#xD;
&#xD;
After three pregnancies and thousands of gallons of milk, the cows are sent to the slaughterhouse, where they're turned into hamburger and low-grade steak.&#xD;
&#xD;
PETA, which advocates a meat- and milk-free diet, says the treatment is inhumane. &#xD;
&#xD;
"For people who are concerned about cruelty to animals, they need to wipe dairy products off their shopping list, period," Friedrich says.&#xD;
&#xD;
But Reynolds maintains that cows' lives aren't horrible. Forty percent to 50% of California dairy cattle are raised in dairies built in the past two to three years, in which cows are well cared for so they can produce more milk, he says.&#xD;
&#xD;
"A new dairy would be a happy place to be a cow. They have roofs to protect from summer heat and winter rain, comfortable stalls and clean bedding," Reynolds says.&#xD;
&#xD;
It's only in older dairies that cows might still exposed to the elements and live in the "urine- and dung-fouled dirt" referred to in the suit, Reynolds says. PETA's pictures are of such older dairies. &#xD;
&#xD;
The suit doesn't seek a ruling on whether California cows are truly happy, but rather whether the depiction of the dairy cows' living conditions is unlawfully deceptive.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>053FF584-0720-41A5-9C7F-EBBC20B57F6C</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-12-14T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>PETA: 'Happy cows' ad is a lie</title>
</post>
