<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Let’s say there are only three kinds of persons. They are religious, business centric or politically oriented persons.&#xD;
&#xD;
If I am a religious person or if I decide to devote myself to serve God of some sort, my choice could be very simple. I should love everybody. All aspect of lives, good, bad and ugly I should love. Pretty simple. I will always think the way I can justify myself to love every one.&#xD;
&#xD;
If I am a businessman, again my choice is simple. As long as I can generate profits out of the persons, my job is done. They are good persons for me. There are no good, bad and ugly peoples. There are only good, bad and ugly deals. I should weigh the person with the amount profit generation.&#xD;
&#xD;
Lastly if I am a politician, my perspective of persons should be straight. Will the persons vote for me or Can the persons bring the votes to me ? Simple questions.&#xD;
&#xD;
However there are a lot of cases that religious person loses the values like catholic priests like altar boys and business man loses the conviction that only looks for short term return and etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
Our lives are little bits more complicated because we need to adopt all above three values. We like to be ethical, financially well off and accepted by our friends. How to balance our lives with all of criteria ?&#xD;
&#xD;
Here are the questions I can come up with.&#xD;
- Why good things happen to bad peoples or reverse situation ?&#xD;
- How good do we have to be ?&#xD;
- How much money is enough ?&#xD;
- What is the meaning of happiness or what is definition of happiness ?&#xD;
- Why are the values in my life ?&#xD;
- What are my options ?&#xD;
- All together what is the meaning of life ?&#xD;
&#xD;
I want to know. Please help me to explore</content>
    <postId>06811C19-72BC-4D79-BC77-3FA87C298E88</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-12-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>RE: Workshop - What is Life ?</title>
</post>
