<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>샘 권</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>thomas lee</author>
            <date>2004-10-19T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>2 번을 하면 나중에 도움이 되는데&#xD;
일단 1번이 편할겁니다</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>에이전트 회사에서 파트너 십으로 비지니스 등록을 하라고 합니다. 월급날 전 까지 등록하라고 하는데요,&#xD;
사이트에 들어 가 보니까 양식이 여러개 있는데,&#xD;
1번 양식 아니면 5번 같은데,잘 모르겠습니다.&#xD;
=====================================================&#xD;
http://www.cbs.gov.on.ca/mcbs/english/5JGLAZ.htm&#xD;
-----------------------------------------------------&#xD;
Form 1 &amp;#8211; Registration of a Sole Proprietorship/General Partnership&#xD;
&#xD;
This form must be completed and submitted to the Companies and Personal Property Security Branch in order to register, renew, amend or cancel a business name registration for a sole proprietorship or general partnership.&#xD;
&#xD;
Form 2 - Registration of a Business Name for a Corporation&#xD;
&#xD;
This form is used to register, renew, amend or cancel a business name registration for a corporation.&#xD;
&#xD;
It must be completed and submitted to the Companies and Personal Property Security Branch when a corporation wishes to carry on business under a name different from the corporation’s name.  Not-for-profit corporations must also complete this form to publicly use a name other than their corporation name.&#xD;
&#xD;
Form 5 - Registration for a Partnership/Limited Partnership    new!&#xD;
&#xD;
This form must be completed and submitted to the Companies and Personal Property Security Branch in order to register, renew, amend or cancel a business name other than the firm name for a general partnership or limited partnership.&#xD;
&#xD;
Form 6 - Registration of an Ontario Limited Liability Partnership, Extra-provincial Limited Liability Partnership and Extra-Provincial Limited Liability Company    new!&#xD;
&#xD;
This form must be completed and submitted to the Companies and Personal Property Security Branch in order to register, renew, amend, or cancel a firm name for an Ontario limited liability partnership or extra-provincial limited liability partnership, or a company name for an extra-provincial limited liability company.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>0A4F82A7-367A-4BB5-9597-CB314710BD2A</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-10-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>파트너십 양식이 어느게 맞는지 혹시 아시는 분 계실까요?</title>
</post>
