<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김경환</author>
            <date>2009-06-18T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>그래도 아직은 java 수요가 더 많은거 같구요. 제 경험으로 java랑 .net은 비슷한 부분이 많아 쉽게 적응이 되구요 c#문법이랑 java랑 거의 같아서 다른 사람이 만들어놓은 소스봐도 편안하실겁니다 ^^ jsp랑 asp.net도 비슷하고... 근데 굳이 .net공부 하실 필요야 있을까요? 둘 양다리 걸쳐보니 하나만 하는게 더 좋을거 같던데요 -_-. 어차피 java가 없어지진 않을테니요. 전 요즘 flex에 빠져있는데 요거 앞으로 점점 많이 쓰일텐데 silverlight가 라이벌이긴 한데 쫒아오는 속도가 영 아니네요.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>요즘 순수한 자바개발자 자리는 감소한 것 같습니다. 아래 보는바와 같이 닷넷개발자 수요가 꾸준한데, 이것이 의미하는 바가 무었일까요? 닷넷등 MS의 솔루션이 중소기업에서 안정적으로 수용이되고 있는 것 같습니다. 아직 닷넷을 공부해보지 않아서 모르겠으나, 개발비용이 자바에 비해서 저렴하고 탄탄해서일까요? 요즘 Window 7 이 조만간 출시될 것이라고 합니다. Vista에 비해서 메모리사용을 줄여서 미니컴퓨터등에서도 사용될 수 있고, xp에서 바로 업그레이드를 할 수 있게 만들었다고 하는데, 그간 비스타로 upgrade를 하지 않은 많은 회사들이 Window 7으로 대거 옮겨갈 것 같습니다. 이래 저래 MS사는 2010년에 주가가 오를 것으로 예상됩니다. &#xD;
&#xD;
자, IT업계에서 향후 10년을 더 버티려는 분들은 이제 닷넷공부를 서둘러야 될 것 같습니다. 그냥 팔자려니 하고~~&#xD;
&#xD;
Trust all is well with you. If these roles are not for you, I was hoping to network with you to see if there is anyone you might know. Please see below the details on the roles that I am currently pursuing for my clients:&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
IT Application Developer - Toronto – Fulltime or Contract (Skills) - 6+ years programming experience -Oracle, SQL, .Net and C#. Ability to manage full software development life cycle. Work on several phases of application systems analysis and programming activities but may require some instruction and guidance. Strong technical, analytical and problem solving skills with ability to make independent judgements. Design, develop, test, implement and maintain application modules, debug programs and procedures, prepare elements of programming documentation. Provide detailed specifications to write programs and identify and resolve application problems before they impact business units.&#xD;
Senior Remedy Technical Consultant – Waterloo - 6 month Contract - (Skills) - 5-10 years experience hands on with Remedy 7.5. Strong knowledge of Heat and other helpdesk suites, ARS/CMDB and other modules. Many years experience with client facing. Must be passionate and articulate.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Senior Remedy Business Analyst – Waterloo - 6 month Contract - (Skills) - 7-10 years experience with technical Remedy development. Integrated solutions, diplomatic, design and common architecture are a must. Passion, articulate and creative are a strong asset.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Technical Lead – Storage Management Applications – Vancouver – Fulltime – (Skills) – &#xD;
The client is willing to relocate the right person to Vancouver.&#xD;
Must have 10+ years of software development plus a minimum of two years of team lead experience. Objected-oriented analysis and design, object-oriented programming skills (Java, C++), Web 2.0 and management applications. Strong knowledge in storage virtualization. Experience in enterprise grade applications and/or web applications in a UNIX/Linux environment including: TCP/IP networking, client-server architecture, multi process/thread programming and GUI interface development. The candidate must have a strong technical background, a proven track record in software development and domain knowledge in one or more of these areas: device management, policy management or storage virtualization and/or management.&#xD;
Technical Lead – Storage Virtualization Applications – Vancouver – Fulltime – (Skills) – &#xD;
The client is willing to relocate the right person to Vancouver.&#xD;
Experience interacting with user, business and executive groups to help define the client's needs and translating those needs into a solution of value. As a partner to our clients, we do what is necessary to help them be a success. The ability to empathize with and understand the business needs of the client is one of the single most important characteristics you bring to the job as well as a great attitude toward teamwork and superb technical ability. A minimum of 10 years of development experience. &#xD;
Objected-oriented analysis and design, object-oriented programming skills (Java, C++). Experience with networking protocols, WAN optimization, object-storage devices, data segmentation &amp; reassembly, encryption &amp; security techniques. Knowledge in storage virtualization. Experience in client/server architecture.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you or anyone you know who would be interested, please contact me immediately.&#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
Ed Rix&#xD;
Resource Planning&#xD;
Watercrest&#xD;
"Bridging People with Technology"&#xD;
(888) 244-7550 ext.110&#xD;
ed@watercrest.net</content>
    <postId>0B0E916F-4DD0-4456-8B00-94A16B62FF26</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-06-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>IT Application Developer</title>
</post>
