<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>JAVA Developer &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Type Contract,Full-time&#xD;
&#xD;
Duration 6 months&#xD;
&#xD;
Number of Positions Open 2&#xD;
&#xD;
Start Date of Employment ASAP&#xD;
&#xD;
Expiry Date 28-May-2010 &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description   &#xD;
&#xD;
Qualifying notes:  &#xD;
&#xD;
The soft skills required to make this an ideal candidate:&#xD;
&#xD;
         1. Someone who is very web savvy and stays current on web technologies, social media, mobile, etc.  Currency of skills is important.&#xD;
         2. Excellent English language skills – comprehension, articulation, etc. must be fluent&#xD;
         3. Someone who thrives in a busy environment, is motivated, someone thirsting for knowledge and a quick learner&#xD;
         4. Someone who adapts well to change&#xD;
         5. While there are no plans today to turn this role into a full-time position, these things have a way of happening over time, so assuming all other requirements are met, I would look to the candidate who would be willing to consider a full-time role at some point in the future should the situation present itself.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
POSITION SUMMARY&#xD;
&#xD;
Join the team that has made www.canadiantire.ca one of the top five web sites in Canada! The senior Java/J2EE developer will be a member of the Online Development team in the Business Solution Delivery Department, participating in projects, responsible for application support and system improvements for web-based and multi-tier J2EE applications and other integration applications linking business partners and the CTR Online system.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities&#xD;
&#xD;
This position is a hands-on role. The Java developer must be a team player and have strong web application skills, good troubleshooting and self-starting qualities with minimal supervision. He/she will work with other team members to work on new projects and support back-end and middle-tier J2EE and other batch applications in large and complex, transaction-heavy environments.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Major responsibilities are summarized as follows: &#xD;
&#xD;
    * Proactively participate in project development and new initiatives of application improvement in maintainability, reliability and process automation, and provide documentation when required.&#xD;
    * Support the J2EE applications and other batch applications including online Webstore, Contact center, interfaces, email campaign system, mainframe processes, and message oriented middleware (MOM), and utilities in all environments.&#xD;
    * Develop and implement solutions to address frequent and reoccurring problems on interfaces that link J2EE applications to various business partners and different systems either through WebSphere MQ messaging or FTP/HTTPS or other protocols.&#xD;
    * Investigate high severity application defects reported by internal and external customers in production, identify the root cause of the issue, develop a solution and implement it as early as possible per business requirements.&#xD;
    * Participate in optimization to achieve more scalable, reliable, secured, maintainable, extendable, and adaptable applications through effective refactoring, tuning and building solid and reusable frameworks.&#xD;
    * Participate in architectural design and QA test strategy review.  Make sure that the design is aligned with industry best practices, the solution is a balance of availability, reliability, reusability, maintainability, scalability, performance, security and extensibility, and that the test cases have good test coverage.&#xD;
    * Responsible for applying vendor patches at J2EE application levels in all environments and participating in major version upgrades.&#xD;
    * Be flexible to provide application support at non-business hours when required.&#xD;
    * Endeca and Blue Martini experience is a HUGE asset.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Required Positions and Skills&#xD;
&#xD;
Positions (One of the following)  Years of Experience&#xD;
&#xD;
Web Developer 5&#xD;
&#xD;
-----------------&#xD;
 Shradha Mehta, IT Recruiter&#xD;
&#xD;
GSI International Consulting Group&#xD;
&#xD;
Main Tel:   (416) 777-2525 ext. 257&#xD;
Direct Tel:  (416) 777-9021&#xD;
smehta@gsigroup.com</content>
    <postId>0B6B8247-0703-4B17-B01C-8EC550443895</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-05-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Canadia Tire - 6 months Cont'</title>
</post>
