<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Reuters&#xD;
Canada's telecom spending not yet bottomed, study&#xD;
Monday February 10, 4:19 pm ET &#xD;
By Susan Taylor &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
OTTAWA, Feb 10 (Reuters) - A spending chill that has gripped Canada's phone companies shows no signs of thawing, or hitting bottom, according to an IDC Canada study released on Monday that has a bleak outlook for 2003.&#xD;
 &#xD;
The research group said that after a dreadful 2002, when Canada's telecommunication service providers cut equipment purchases by 46 percent, 2003 won't be any better.&#xD;
&#xD;
The study said initial budget forecasts from Canada's major phone companies show a further 19 percent drop to C$5.8 billion ($3.8 billion) in spending. It's a far cry from the budgets that peaked at C$13.5 billion in 2001.&#xD;
&#xD;
But IDC Canada also provided a glimmer of hope, with a forecast that spending may thaw in 2004.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Any further reductions in the capex for them will be more fine-tuning," said Lawrence Surtees, IDC director of telecom and Internet research.&#xD;
&#xD;
"I can see 2004 (having) a little bit of a drop, but then stabilizing as most of these guys reach the targets of what they want the ratio between revenue and capital spending to be."&#xD;
&#xD;
Surtees said Canada's recovery will likely lag that of the U.S., which is expected to plateau at the end of 2003.&#xD;
&#xD;
While that prediction is at odds with industry players who suggest the worst has passed, all segments of Canada's telecommunications market plan to prune budgets, he added.&#xD;
&#xD;
The deepest cut will come from international carriers, which plan to reduce spending by 74 percent from 2002 levels, followed by long-distance and competitive local phone companies, which forecast a 47 percent drop, the study said.&#xD;
&#xD;
Canada's dominant phone companies, or incumbent local exchange carriers (ILECs), are expected to spend C$4.2 billion on wireline equipment in 2003, making up almost three-quarters of total capital expenditures for the year.&#xD;
&#xD;
Those companies, including Bell Canada, Telus, Aliant Inc. (Toronto:AIT.TO - News) and Manitoba Telecom Services Inc. (Toronto:MBT.TO - News), plan to spend 9 percent less in 2003 than last year, on average, and they see revenue increasing just 3 percent.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Despite their aggressive capex reductions, Canada's ILECs have not pruned their capital spending budgets as deeply as their U.S. counterparts, a trend that will continue in 2003," the study said.&#xD;
&#xD;
The sector's biggest spender, Bell Canada parent BCE Inc. (Toronto:BCE.TO - News), is expected to spend C$2.65 billion on equipment in 2003, a 12 percent drop from 2002. Telus Corp. (Toronto:T.TO - News), the country's second-biggest phone company, has forecast C$1.5 billion in spending, a 12 percent decline.&#xD;
&#xD;
Budgets for long distance and competitive local exchange carriers are expected to plunge by 50 percent from last year.&#xD;
&#xD;
That's no surprise given the sector's bloodied landscape, which saw AT&amp;T Canada and Group Telecom fall into bankruptcy protection, while Sprint Canada parent Call-Net Enterprises Inc. (Toronto:FON.TO - News) recapitalized operations, writing off about C$2 billion in debt.&#xD;
&#xD;
The outlook isn't much rosier for wireless carriers, which forecast a 22 percent spending decline from 2002, despite expectations of double-digit revenue growth.&#xD;
&#xD;
Spending from once-lavish overseas carriers is seen slowing to a trickle, after Teleglobe and 360networks emerged from bankruptcy protection. The two companies made up 40 percent of total capital spending in 2000.&#xD;
&#xD;
Cable companies are seen cutting spending to just over C$1 billion from C$1.58 billion in 2002, the study forecast.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>0B7F869F-7EA8-4121-BB39-1BC3CA4A58D3</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-19T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Canada's telecom spending not yet bottomed</title>
</post>
