<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>내용을 요약하면 다음과 같습니다. &#xD;
캐나다국내 소고기 부족으로 맥도널드에서는 남미의 소고기를 수입하는데, 대부분이 엄격한 사료조치가 되지 않아서 건강에 유해하다는 것입니다. 지난번 한국에서 쇠고기파동으로 익히 알고 있는 내용인데, 캐나다에서도 안전하지는 않다는 군요.&#xD;
&#xD;
Must read..CANADIAN Beef&#xD;
&#xD;
This IS A GOOD DECENT MAN WHO TOOK THE TIME TO WRITE THIS&#xD;
&#xD;
AND: HE SIGNED THE STATEMENT AND: INCLUDED HIS CONTACT INFO:&#xD;
&#xD;
I'm sure those of you who aren't in the cattle business don't&#xD;
understand&#xD;
the issues here. But to those of us whose living depends on the cattle&#xD;
market, selling cattle, raising the best beef possible... This is&#xD;
frustrating.&#xD;
&#xD;
This will keep us from ever stopping there again, even for a drink.&#xD;
&#xD;
The original message is from the Alberta Cattle Feeders Association&#xD;
&#xD;
Canadian cattle producers are very passionate about this.&#xD;
&#xD;
McDonald's claims that there is not enough beef in Canada to support&#xD;
their restaurants. Well, we know that is not so. Our opinion is they&#xD;
are&#xD;
looking to save money at our expense. The sad thing of it is that the&#xD;
people of Canada are the ones who made McDonald's successful in the&#xD;
first place, but we are not good enough to provide beef.&#xD;
&#xD;
We personally are no longer eating at McDonald's, which I am sure does&#xD;
not make an impact, but if we pass this around maybe there will be an&#xD;
impact felt.&#xD;
&#xD;
Please pass it on. Just to add a note:&#xD;
&#xD;
All Canadians that sell cattle at a livestock auction barn have to&#xD;
sign&#xD;
a paper stating that we do NOT EVER feed our cattle any part of&#xD;
another&#xD;
animal. South Americans are not required to do this as of yet.&#xD;
&#xD;
McDonald's has announced that they are going to start importing much&#xD;
of&#xD;
their beef from South America. The problem is that South Americans&#xD;
aren't under the same regulations as Canadian beef producers, and the&#xD;
regulations they have are loosely controlled.&#xD;
&#xD;
They can spray numerous pesticides on their pastures that have been&#xD;
banned here at home because of residues found in the beef. They can&#xD;
also&#xD;
use various hormones and growth regulators that we can't. The Canadian&#xD;
public needs to be aware of this problem and that they may be putting&#xD;
themselves at risk from now on by eating at good old McDonald's.&#xD;
&#xD;
Canadian ranchers raise the highest quality beef in the world and this&#xD;
is what Canadians deserve to eat. Not beef from countries where&#xD;
quality&#xD;
is loosely controlled. Therefore, I am proposing a boycott of&#xD;
McDonald's&#xD;
until they see the light.&#xD;
&#xD;
I'm sorry but everything is not always about the bottom line, and when&#xD;
it comes to jeopardizing my family's health, that is where I draw the&#xD;
line.&#xD;
&#xD;
I am sending this note to about thirty people. If each of you send it&#xD;
to&#xD;
at least ten more (30 x 10 = 300) ... and those 300 send it to at l&#xD;
east&#xD;
ten more (300 x 10 = 3,000) ... and so on, by the time the message&#xD;
reaches the sixth generation of people, we will have reached over&#xD;
THREE&#xD;
MILLION consumers!&#xD;
&#xD;
I'll bet you didn't think you and I had that much potential, did you?&#xD;
Acting together we can make a difference. If this makes sense to you,&#xD;
please pass this message on.&#xD;
&#xD;
Larry Latam&#xD;
&#xD;
Windsor (519)968-1791&#xD;
London  (519)488-2386&#xD;
www.about-voip.com&#xD;
larryl@about-voip.com</content>
    <postId>0BE37FED-47D5-4387-B926-C6845B46B5C2</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-02-20T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>맥도널드 햄버거에 사용되는 소고기에 관하여</title>
</post>
