<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello Brendan,&#xD;
&#xD;
We came across your resume and we have the following opportunity. If you are interested please send me a Word copy of your resume.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Title:              Solutions Developer III&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:              MISSISSAUGA, ___ON_______&#xD;
&#xD;
Duration:           6 Months contract &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description:&#xD;
&#xD;
Department Overview:&#xD;
The eChannels portfolio encompasses the online banking applications of EasyWeb, Info Site, Web Business Banking (WBB).&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Specific Educational Requirements / Accreditations:&#xD;
• College Diploma or University degree in Computer Science&#xD;
• +5 years working experience JAVA, JSP, Websphere, web services, object grid&#xD;
• Some knowledge of PEGA’s PRPC product would be a definite asset as would exposure to mainframe technology. .&#xD;
&#xD;
Other Qualifications / Skills / Experience:&#xD;
The successful candidate will be required to work with individual project teams, support groups, and External vendors. Competencies include:&#xD;
• Strong Leadership and people skills&#xD;
• Strong design and documentation skills.&#xD;
• Experienced in the use of SDLC methodologies&#xD;
• Excellent Java knowledge and experience&#xD;
• Proven track record developing code for medium to large size projects with high complexity. Minimum 5 years experience&#xD;
• Solid understanding of the web development cycle&#xD;
• Proven track record with code deployments&#xD;
• Ability to work effectively with others; self motivated &amp; a team player&#xD;
• Excellent communication skills with an ability to translate highly technical concepts to our Business partners&#xD;
• Flexible and able to adapt to change easily&#xD;
• Development experience / exposure on applications consuming Web services and / or development of Web Services&#xD;
&#xD;
QualificationRating&#xD;
Skills&#xD;
Is this candidate a former TD contractor? *Yes&#xD;
JAVA *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
JSP (Java Server Page) *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
Leadership *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
Program Debugging *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
Program Documentation *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
Program Encoding *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
SDLC (Software Development Life Cycle) *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
System Programming *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
Web Servers *6+ Yrs.&#xD;
WebSphere *5+ Yrs.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Thank you,&#xD;
&#xD;
Priya Darshini&#xD;
Phone: (613) 502-0967&#xD;
Email: pdarshini@gttit.com</content>
    <postId>0DEA4012-1BB3-4367-B59B-0751919C7B07</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-05-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>TD Bank, Mississauga, 6 months, Cont'</title>
</post>
