<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최이경</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>박해옥</author>
            <date>2009-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>좋은 정보감사합니다.좋은 기회인데,캘거리네요...</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Danuse.Dobiasova@sisystems.com&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Hi Sonia,&#xD;
&#xD;
You are receiving this email because you selected to be notified about Contract opportunities.&#xD;
If you no longer want to receive notifications, please browse the following link&#xD;
&#xD;
 http://www.sisystems.com/index.cfm?mg=cp.hp&#xD;
to unsubscribe/update your preferences&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
If you do not have your login and password, please go to http://www.sisystems.com/index.cfm?mg=cpcans.candidate_login,&#xD;
enter your email address and it will be sent to you by email.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Opportunity Title: Infrastructure Architect&#xD;
&#xD;
Sourcing Office: Calgary&#xD;
&#xD;
Specialization:  Network and Infrastructure&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Project Description:&#xD;
6 month contract for an 'Infrastructure Architect' our client requires immediately.&#xD;
&#xD;
          You will be responsible for the design of infrastructure related project including desktop services, server and network implementation, telecommunications, storage, systems management and data centre management.&#xD;
&#xD;
          You will set the technical direction and forecast areas of opportunity.&#xD;
          Identify technical and procedural risks on a go-forward basis.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Must Have:&#xD;
&#xD;
 Hands-on Infrastructure Experience. (&gt; 10 years)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 Infrastructure Architect Experience - at the design level. (2 - 4 years)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 Experience with Active Directory, Linux, SAN, IP networking, VPN, Exchange. (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 Leadership experience in large IT environment. (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 Strong understanding of Unix environments and applications. (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Nice To Have Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Start Date: Sep 14, 2009&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
End Date: Mar 12, 2010&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Work Environment: Client is located outside of the Calgary downtown core.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested and qualified for this opportunity, Please browse the following link&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
https://www1.sisystems.com/index.cfm?mg=cpo.details&amp;uv=%25%260%27X3LD%20%0A&#xD;
&#xD;
to view the complete opportunity and apply online, it takes less than a minute&#xD;
&#xD;
(Using this link allows your application to be recorded directly with the client&#xD;
request and forwards your resume, skills matrix and reference information directly to me,&#xD;
from our database, for priority consideration on this opportunity.&#xD;
Applications will not be accepted by phone.)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Note: Posted rates are for incorporated contractors only. Pay rates differ for sole proprietorships and employees placed in contract positions.</content>
    <postId>0ED34854-0D25-4422-8F2A-A5CF01BCD648</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Opportunity Title: Infrastructure Architect</title>
</post>
