<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>황성규</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Canada, the closer country for outsourcing work&#xD;
Published: November 30, 2004, 7:21 AM PST&#xD;
By Ian Austen &#xD;
The New York Times&#xD;
&#xD;
TrackBack Print E-mail TalkBack &#xD;
OTTAWA--Like many software outsourcing companies, Keane often sends work to its employees in India. But at the same time, Keane, which is based in Boston, is expanding its base of software developers in its original, and much closer, outsourcing location: Canada. &#xD;
&#xD;
While the debate over software and call center outsourcing from the United States focuses mainly on India, the Philippines, Singapore and other distant points, its significant growth in Canada has attracted relatively little attention. Canada lags India in the number of people working in outsourcing businesses. But its stability, proximity and cultural similarity to the United States tend to attract higher-value, more sophisticated work.&#xD;
&#xD;
At the same time, outsourcing companies, including Keane, have started dividing jobs between operations in Canada and India.&#xD;
&#xD;
"In some cases, we use Canada as a front end to India," said Alaisdar M. Graham, Keane's managing director for Canada. "We find that this takes away the issues people have with India."&#xD;
&#xD;
Canada is holding its own against India in high-end work. "We do not have the same volume of people as India," said Robert Scott, a partner at PricewaterhouseCoopers Canada, based in Toronto, and the co-author of a study on outsourcing. "But Canada is generally competing at the leading edge of technology where close interaction between business users and developers is critical."&#xD;
&#xD;
The lack of cultural differences between the United States and Canada has helped Canada also draw the call center part of the business. Mark Best, a call center industry analyst at Datamonitor, forecasts that the Canadian call center industry will grow 7.9 percent a year over the next three years, with the United States segment expanding more than 12 percent annually.&#xD;
&#xD;
Canadian outsourcers and their customers realize the business is politically sensitive. In an attempt to distance themselves from India, many people in the Canadian industry refer to their business as "nearshore outsourcing." Others prefer to call it "remote contracting."&#xD;
&#xD;
Graham said that in contrast to some of Keane's experiences with its Indian operations, few customers from the United States appear to have misgivings about moving work to Canada. "They tend to view Canada as the next state," he said.&#xD;
&#xD;
Best added: "Companies are willing to pay a premium for a destination that is close to home. The customer on the end of the phone will be able to relate much better to a representative in Canada than one in the Philippines."&#xD;
&#xD;
Best estimated that Canada had 26,300 call center "agent positions," or agent workstations, serving the United States. The actual number of workers is probably much higher, as each position is basically a phone line and a cubicle. At some call centers, three employees on separate shifts will work a single phone during each 24-hour period. The figure, however, looks almost insignificant when compared with the 2.85 million call agent jobs that remain in the United States.&#xD;
&#xD;
A recent study by PricewaterhouseCoopers Canada estimated that 15,000 to 20,000 Canadians develop software for foreign companies. The Canadian subsidiary of Electronic Data Systems alone has about 1,400 workers developing software, though the company declined to say how much of that work is for customers outside Canada. Scott, the partner at Pricewaterhouse, said he believed that the amount of software work coming into Canada was being offset by work leaving the country. &#xD;
&#xD;
Canada's role as an outsourcer began in the late 1980s, when the New Brunswick premier at the time, Frank McKenna, worked with the province's telephone company to upgrade its network before embarking on a worldwide sales campaign to lure business, sometimes sweetened with promises of government handouts. Like many provinces in Atlantic Canada, New Brunswick had an economy heavily dependent on resource industries like lumber and fishing that offered limited job opportunities.&#xD;
&#xD;
 At that time, and to a lesser extent today, governmental encouragement of outsourcing was criticized as concentrating on jobs with a reputation for low wages and relatively little advancement.&#xD;
&#xD;
But Kevin G. Bulmer, who designed the New Brunswick campaign in its early days, said that it was important to look at the alternatives. Unlike most resource-based industries, call centers generally provide steady, year-round employment. And cubicles, whatever their shortcomings, offered a far more pleasant environment than many of the province's traditional employers.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Do people in call centers work in hip waders, stand in cold water all day, like they do on the fish-packing line?" asked Bulmer, who is now the senior investment officer at the Atlantic Canada Opportunities Agency, an investment promotion arm of the Canadian government.&#xD;
&#xD;
New Brunswick's initial success soon spread to other parts of Canada with similar economic circumstances, like the rest of Atlantic Canada, rural British Columbia and the northern portions of Ontario. Even more affluent regions have attracted some work. Across the river from the Nortel Networks main research center in Ottawa, Hewlett-Packard provides technical support to American customers in Gatineau, Quebec. Similarly, the VAC Service Corporation of Middletown, N.Y., which administers warranties for appliance and electronics makers, operates a call center in suburban Ottawa that is integrated with two operations in the United States.&#xD;
&#xD;
Government grants play a minor role in bringing in companies. Cendant, for instance, received a grant of $1.5 million (1.8 million Canadian dollars) for its operation, one that Best said was typical of the general pattern of call centers here.&#xD;
&#xD;
Rather than making outgoing sales calls, the center largely handles incoming calls for Budget Rent a Car system, the Avis Rent a Car system, Cendant's nine hotel chains and its time-share resort business. &#xD;
&#xD;
Best said that banks and other financial services companies as well as catalog retailers had moved some or all of their incoming-call work to Canada. Eddie Bauer now handles all of its catalog inquiries with about 600 workers in New Brunswick, while some Spiegel and Newport News catalog calls go to Nova Scotia and to Virginia.&#xD;
&#xD;
Keane first brought some of its software work to Canada in 1996, when it was looking for extra help to deal with Year 2000-related work. But when 2000 came and went without incident, Graham said, the company was sold on the advantages of Nova Scotia and focused the Canadian operation on software development and, at a smaller level, system maintenance.&#xD;
&#xD;
Not only were there eight universities near Halifax feeding skilled employees into Keane, Graham said, but the company was quickly bombarded with resumes from highly skilled expatriate Canadians who wanted to return home. Graham said the company planned to add 100 employees to its Toronto operation.&#xD;
&#xD;
Lower costs were also a factor--even considering the 26 percent rise in the Canadian dollar since January 2002. Stephen E. Lund, president of Nova Scotia Business, a government-financed agency, estimates that a skilled software worker who can command $80,000 to $90,000 a year in Boston is paid the equivalent of $60,000 to $70,000 a year in Halifax. Costs for a typical 110-employee software development group in Halifax, he said, are about 40 percent to 50 percent lower than Boston or New York.&#xD;
&#xD;
EDS and CenterBeam, of San Jose, Calif., are among the other software companies with Canadian operations.&#xD;
&#xD;
While any customer is welcome, Bernard Courtois, president of the Information Technology Association of Canada, said that the shifting of work for American state and local governments to Canada had created some trade friction in the past and would probably continue to do so. &#xD;
&#xD;
Nevertheless, with the exception of the motion picture industry, the shifting of jobs in other sectors to Canada has rarely prompted national debate in the United States. Courtois said that was likely to be the case with software and call center outsourcing.&#xD;
&#xD;
"In the U.S., the debate is often dominated by local issues, and I think that's where it's going to continue to play out," Courtois said.&#xD;
&#xD;
Entire contents, Copyright &amp;copy; 2004 The New York Times. All rights reserved.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>14F4A129-614C-4608-A3C1-6B24D26AAADA</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-11-30T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Canada, the closer country for outsourcing work</title>
</post>
