<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title:  J2EE Team Lead  &#xD;
Skills:  Team Lead, J2EE, UML, JMS &#xD;
  &#xD;
Date:  9-10-2003 &#xD;
Location:  Toronto, CDA Canada &#xD;
Area code:  416 &#xD;
  &#xD;
Tax term:  CON_W2 &#xD;
Pay rate:  Negotiable/Hour &#xD;
Length:  Temp &#xD;
  &#xD;
Position ID:  300110 &#xD;
Dice ID:  teksyst &#xD;
  &#xD;
Job description: &#xD;
Our client, a leader in the financial industry, is currently looking&#xD;
for two Team Leads to join their current development project.&#xD;
&#xD;
The incumbent will:&#xD;
- Understand and translate business requirements into Design and&#xD;
Specification&#xD;
- Lead and mentor small development teams to develop applications.&#xD;
- Assist and code complex functionalities&#xD;
- Document the developed applications and code such that the code is&#xD;
maintainable.&#xD;
- Support applications during their initial deployment phase with&#xD;
application enhancements and bug fixes.&#xD;
&#xD;
Requirement: J2SE (Java 2 Standard Edition) Senior - JDBC J2EE (Java 2&#xD;
Enterprise Edition) Senior - Session beans / Entity beans / Message&#xD;
beans - Security - JMS - XML (SAX, DOM, XSL) - JSP, Servlets&#xD;
Experience with databases(ORACLE) and knowledge of SQL.&#xD;
Tools / miscellaneous / concepts - CVS - Unix - Design&#xD;
Patterns - Ant - UML - XML - Jakarta Struts - Experience in the&#xD;
financial services industry&#xD;
* 1-2 years of previous experience as a team-lead for a J2EE project.&#xD;
Strong&#xD;
people skills is a must.&#xD;
* Strong analytical, problem solving and presentation skills.&#xD;
* Well-developed written communication skills with proficiency in&#xD;
grammar, spelling and simple language use.&#xD;
* High standards of accuracy and detail.&#xD;
* Flexible, adaptable and able to work effectively in a constantly&#xD;
changing project team environment.&#xD;
%0&#xD;
&#xD;
Join TEKsystems, one of the leading IT consulting and services&#xD;
providers in Canada and the United States. As a result of our rapid&#xD;
growth and merger with our sister company, Maxim Group, we are&#xD;
constantly searching for talented technical professionals with all&#xD;
levels of information technology and communications skills. From the&#xD;
personal delivery of your weekly cheques, to our dedication at finding&#xD;
you the next project, we take care of our people. TEKsystems knows&#xD;
that every professional has different needs, so we'll work together to&#xD;
determine a suitable benefits package. We offer our team members&#xD;
medical, dental, provisions for vacation and holiday pay, EAP&#xD;
(Employee&#xD;
Assistance Plan), Lawline (24 hour Legal Assistance),&#xD;
FoneMed (24 hour Health Advice), and technical and professional&#xD;
training.&#xD;
 &#xD;
  &#xD;
Travel required:  none &#xD;
Telecommute:  no &#xD;
  &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Contact for more information:&#xD;
Hellard,Gary&#xD;
TEKsystems&#xD;
5975 Whittle Road Suite 200&#xD;
&#xD;
Mississauga, ON 431&#xD;
&#xD;
Phone: (905) 501-2857 &#xD;
Fax: (407) 736-8590 &#xD;
 &#xD;
E-mail: ghellard@teksystems.com &#xD;
Web: http://www.teksystems.com/ &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>1602CA6D-777A-4D79-9C49-9FEE270F4FDA</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-09-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2EE Team Lead - Toronto</title>
</post>
