<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강윤정</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>황성규</author>
            <date>2003-05-24T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>This is a good one!</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content> A shepherd was herding his flock in a remote pasture when suddenly a&#xD;
brand-new BMW advanced out of the dust cloud towards him. The driver, &#xD;
a young man in a Broni suit, Gucci shoes, Ray Ban sunglasses and YSL &#xD;
tie, leaned out the window and asked the shepherd... &#xD;
 &#xD;
 "If I tell you exactly how many sheep you have in your flock, will you give me one?" &#xD;
&#xD;
 The shepherd looked at the man, obviously a yuppie, then looked at his&#xD;
peacefully-grazing flock and calmly answered, "Sure." &#xD;
&#xD;
 The yuppie parked his car, whipped out his IBM Thinkpad and connected it&#xD;
to a cell phone, then he surfed to a NASA page on the internet where he&#xD;
called up a GPS satellite navigation system, scanned the area, and &#xD;
then opened up a database and an Excel spreadsheet with complex formulas. &#xD;
He sent an email on his Blackberry and, after a few minutes, received a&#xD;
response. Finally, he prints out a 130 page report on his miniaturized&#xD;
printer then turns to the shepherd and says....... &#xD;
 &#xD;
 "You have exactly 1586 sheep." &#xD;
 &#xD;
 "That is correct; take one of the sheep." said the shepherd. &#xD;
 &#xD;
 He watches the young man select one of the animals and bundle it into his car. &#xD;
Then the shepherd says: &#xD;
&#xD;
 "If I can tell you exactly what your business is, will you give me back my animal?" &#xD;
 &#xD;
 "OK, why not." answered the young man. &#xD;
 &#xD;
 "Clearly, you are a consultant." said the shepherd. &#xD;
 &#xD;
 "That's correct." says the yuppie, "but how did you guess that?" &#xD;
 &#xD;
 "No guessing required." answers the shepherd. "You turned up here although&#xD;
nobody called you. You want to get paid for an answer I already knew, to a question I never asked, &#xD;
and you don't know crap about my business.... Now  give me back my dog." &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>173BC796-4CBE-43A9-8323-D923CAEAA843</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>The Consultant</title>
</post>
