<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I currently have an opportunity that may match your skills.  Please review the job description and let me know whether or not you (or someone you know) might be interested.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
, Permanent&#xD;
&#xD;
 Specialization: Software Development&#xD;
&#xD;
 Candidate Required: J2EE Application and Integration Specialist&#xD;
&#xD;
 Skill Level: Intermediate&#xD;
&#xD;
 Opportunity Description: Our client is looking for a J2EE Application and Integration Specialist to provide technical guidance, analysis, design and development of application integration of various systems.&#xD;
&#xD;
Under the guidance of Team Lead, formulate and define systems scope, objectives, requirements, analysis, design and development based on both user needs and a good understanding of application business systems and industry standards.&#xD;
&#xD;
Resource Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
1. Provide integration services to projects by designing/developing J2EE solution frameworks and integrating enterprise solutions using EAI/ Middleware solutions&#xD;
2. Provide Application/Integration Design and Development for projects&#xD;
3. Define message definitions and requirements and define Integration Project Plan&#xD;
5. Design information systems to perform well logically and physically for decision support&#xD;
6. Coordinate new development and ensure it is consistent and well integrated with existing information structure&#xD;
7. Support integration testing, user acceptance testing and implementation&#xD;
8. Assist in post-implementation continuous improvement effects to enhance performance and provide increased functionality&#xD;
9. Provide after-hours support for integration components, middleware adapters/wrappers and interfaces. Occasional off-hours on-site support to resolve emergency production problems&#xD;
&#xD;
Other Resource Requirements:&#xD;
&#xD;
• Familiar with mainframe, Java and J2EE development and advise on best practices and solutions&#xD;
• Knowledge in Integration and Middleware technology and in Web Services and Middleware: WebSphere MQ, Message Broker, WebSphere Application Server&#xD;
• Knowledge in development methodologies and testing standards&#xD;
• Knowledge in Program Languages/Development Tools: Java, HTML, XML, RAD, J2EE, OOA/OOD/OOP&#xD;
&#xD;
 Specialization and Skills:  Software Development J2EE 5 - 7 years&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 Additional Requirements: Skill Name Experience&#xD;
&#xD;
 Full understanding of Unix, Windows, Middleware and web-based technologies Mandatory&#xD;
&#xD;
 Experience in developing system/technical integration specifications Mandatory&#xD;
&#xD;
 Experience in working with DB2/UDB, SQL Server, and Oracle Proficient&#xD;
&#xD;
 Experience in Integration infrastructure design and implementation Proficient&#xD;
&#xD;
 Experience in interface metadata repository management Proficient&#xD;
&#xD;
 Experience in providing end-to-end solutions incorporating legacy systems Proficient&#xD;
&#xD;
 Work Environment: Downtown location.&#xD;
&#xD;
 Average Expectation of Tenure in this job:    1yr&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks,&#xD;
&#xD;
Amy C. Miranda&#xD;
Recruiter&#xD;
S.i. Systems, Mississauga&#xD;
www.sisystems.com&#xD;
Our People Click&#xD;
&#xD;
P.S.  We are always looking for good people!  Refer your friends to us and you could receive our $500 referral bonus!&#xD;
Click here for more information: http://www.sisystems.com/index.cfm?mg=cpcanr.referral</content>
    <postId>17B28948-8FF5-45FE-A486-9F45C53A762F</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-10-05T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2EE Application and Integration Specialist</title>
</post>
