<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Good afternoon, we are showcasing a great opportunity with a large client in Mississauga and if you or someone you know is suited please let us know.&#xD;
&#xD;
Title: Middleware Specialist&#xD;
Job Reference #: 36842&#xD;
Location: Mississauga, ON&#xD;
Type: Permanent Full Time&#xD;
Compensation: 70-80K&#xD;
&#xD;
Details:&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
An opportunity with a huge &amp; reputable client that is a market leader in the financial services industry. This is an opportunity for Middleware Specialist to shape their career. This environment offers competive salary, bonus, benefits, employee share program, pension contributions and a chance to work with a proment IT solutions group with more than 1500 people total in IT.&#xD;
&#xD;
Even if you aren't interested / suited perhaps you know someone suitable? Forward this on to them and be part of them gaining an excellent opportunity.&#xD;
&#xD;
Summary of Job:&#xD;
&#xD;
Provides Detail Design, Build, Unit Test, Level 2/3 Support of software deemed Middleware across all hardware/OS platforms. This includes products such as WebSphere Application Server, WebSphere Portal, Apache Web Server, IBM Web Server (IHS), Pega Workflow, File net and others.&#xD;
&#xD;
The IT Specialist works closely with our ITS peers and will be expected to demonstrate an expert understanding of all elements to successfully manage, tune, and resolve issues in complex systems within the bank's web based environment&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
Mandatory qualifications include excellent communication (both written and oral) and interpersonal skills. The candidate must be organized, self motivated, as well as a team player and be able to participate in the knowledge transfer of information with peers and management. The candidate will also be accountable for technical coaching and developing of other team members.&#xD;
&#xD;
Requirements:&#xD;
&#xD;
ability to install and configure Pega components independently and be able to direct others in the same&#xD;
understanding of the Pega and BPM fundamentals&#xD;
assist architecture teams in designing and building out new Pega products and/or infrastructure&#xD;
consult and advise project teams on the best practices for infrastructure related configurations&#xD;
deploy and support new Pega projects into the existing / new environments&#xD;
provide level 3 support for all things Pega, which includes Pega and WebSphere (*)&#xD;
provide on-call support periodically to other infrastructure operations teams (on rotation)&#xD;
plan for and implement regular maintenance packages to WebSphere and Pega&#xD;
experience with PRPC v5.x and higher.&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience&#xD;
&#xD;
Â· Minimum 5 years of experience building, deploying and administering Pega solutions.&#xD;
Â· Expert working knowledge of supported technology (IHS Web Server, Pega ).&#xD;
Â· Expert knowledge of Unix Shell scripting,&#xD;
Â· Thorough knowledge of UNIX (Linux/Solaris/AIX) operating systems.&#xD;
Â· Knowledge of Database technologies (DB2, Oracle or MS SQL Server)&#xD;
Â· Advanced problem determination skills to identify and resolve application server problems running on multiple platforms in a large complex&#xD;
environment (AIX, Linux, Windows).&#xD;
Â· Comfortable with working in a rapidly changing, technically complex environment.&#xD;
Â· Proficiency with MS office product suite (Word, Excel PowerPoint etc.).&#xD;
Â· experience in designing and deploying infrastructures for web services&#xD;
&#xD;
Specific Educational Requirements/Accreditations&#xD;
:&#xD;
&#xD;
Â· College Diploma or University degree in Computer Science&#xD;
&#xD;
Other Qualifications/Skills/Experience&#xD;
:&#xD;
&#xD;
Â· knowledge of and ability to code Unix-based shell scripts.&#xD;
Â· WebSphere ND 6..1 / 7.0 Administration&#xD;
Â· Database experience with Oracle and DB2&#xD;
Â· Experience with SOAP/other interconnection protocols.&#xD;
Â· Experience with WESB / DATAPOWER / Web Sphere&#xD;
Â· Experience with Filenet&#xD;
Â· Experience with z/OS and mainframe technologies.&#xD;
Â· Technical knowledge of TDBFG legacy business web applications&#xD;
Â· Familiarity with the other Web and Application Servers, Workflow infrastructure&#xD;
&#xD;
The successful applicant must have a solid understanding of Incident, Change, and Problem Management methodologies as well as solid experience in a large Production environment&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Lucas Robbins&#xD;
Business Manager&#xD;
Recruiting experts in IT&#xD;
&#xD;
D: 905 366 4527&#xD;
E: lrobbins@hays.ca</content>
    <postId>19547F7D-CAFD-4043-B1A7-8D20ABC519FA</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-05-05T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Middleware Specialist - Permanent</title>
</post>
