<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최이경</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This is a broadcast message I have sent out to those of you who have matched on a Wintel role. This is a very tough market right now so if you are interested we have to move quickly. Everybody is looking for work so jobs are filling fast.&#xD;
&#xD;
If the role posted below does not interest you, and we have been in touch recently, you can just ignore this email. If you would prefer not to be bothered with future broadcasts like this, just let me know and I will add you to my "no fly" list.&#xD;
&#xD;
Please forgive me if this job does not match your skill set but I am relying on a database search engine to get this mailing list out asap. If you have any friends who might be interested, please feel free to pass my info along.&#xD;
&#xD;
If we haven't been in touch recently, please send me your latest CV as a Word doc and give me a status update and I will add some notes to your file so I can get a better match on potential opportunities in the future. We work for most of the government ministries, the big five banks, most of the telcos, Canada's biggest retailers and yes, automotive... well, the sucessful one, anyway. Our web site is a very good indicator of current market conditions, rates and salaries.&#xD;
&#xD;
Regards and thanks for your time,&#xD;
&#xD;
Fraser&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Fraser R. Fulwell&#xD;
&#xD;
ACCOUNT MANAGER&#xD;
&#xD;
GSI International Consulting Group&#xD;
55 University Avenue, Suite 1601&#xD;
Toronto, ON   M5J 2H7&#xD;
&#xD;
Direct:   416-645-7248&#xD;
&#xD;
Toll Free Line:    1-866-777-7855&#xD;
Main:    416-777-2525 (ext. 277)&#xD;
Fax:      416-777-2547 (Attention Line)&#xD;
Email:   ffulwell@gsigroup.com&#xD;
&#xD;
http://www.linkedin.com/in/fraserfulwell&#xD;
&#xD;
Web:    www.gsigroup.com&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
new requirement for a Technical Specialist (Wintel).  It is a 6 month contract, at Yonge and Eglinton and the candidate rate is $50 – 54/hr.  Job description is attached.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
THIS EXPIRES ON JUNE 24th.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
PLEASE NOTE: this is through the TalentFlow system.  I require years of experience with any technology and years of experience in a skills (i.e. yrs with Active Directory and yrs as a Systems Administrator) to get it through the system.  I also require a paragraph detailing why they are a good candidate for the role.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
TECHNICAL SPECIALIST - WINTEL&#xD;
&#xD;
Location Details Yonge and Eglinton&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Stream Information Technology&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Type Contract,Full-time&#xD;
&#xD;
Duration 6 months&#xD;
&#xD;
Salary/Rate $50-54/hr&#xD;
&#xD;
Number of Positions Open 1&#xD;
&#xD;
Start Date of Employment 06-Jul-2009&#xD;
&#xD;
Posting Date 10-Jun-2009&#xD;
&#xD;
Expiry Date 24-Jun-2009&#xD;
&#xD;
Travel Required Occasionally&#xD;
&#xD;
Educational Requirements College Diploma&#xD;
&#xD;
Languages Required English&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description&#xD;
&#xD;
POSITION SUMMARY:&#xD;
&#xD;
This position is part of the Technology Services Department.  This position deals with Intel based solutions within the CTC corporate environment and some aspects within the Retail environment.  The focus of this role is providing Intel server support for projects which are delivering new Intel based solutions to the organization.&#xD;
&#xD;
RESPONSIBILITIES:&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Working with project teams to understand requirements and build Intel server environments in support of those requirements&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Configure, deploy an maintain Wintel servers.&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Monitor servers and systems performance and troubleshoot problem areas as needed&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Maintain backup/restore and disaster recovery procedures&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Implement software and security upgrades as necessary&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Flexible after-hours support as required&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Evaluation and deployment of O/S and or application updates, (patches, hot-fixes, service packs, etc), to the environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
REQUIREMENTS:&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Must have one or more Systems or Network certifications such as: CCNA, MCSE, CCNE&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Minimum of four years experience in server support &amp; operations&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Strong working knowledge of Intel hardware platforms (server, desktop &amp; notebook)&#xD;
&#xD;
·     MSCE certification or related experience&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Strong written and verbal communication skills.&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Excellent problem solving skills&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Experience in providing 2nd line support.&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Work well in a team environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Strong knowledge of Active Directory in a production environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Strong knowledge of Windows XP in a production environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Experience with NT to Active Directory migration.&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Experience with system management tools (SMS 2003, MOM 2005, IBM Director)&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Strong understanding of information security and its role in a production environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Experience with patch management (O/S, application, anti-virus signatures) in a production environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Experience with maintaining and supporting a Citrix Server Farm&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Excellent verbal and written communication skills&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Ability to manage multiple tasks and maintain a balance of priorities&#xD;
&#xD;
·     2-3 years of IT experience&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Must have a working knowledge of TCP/IP, DNS and WINS&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Lead and assist with projects.&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Research, test, document and implement new technology.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Mandatory&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Windows 2000/2003 Operating System&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Knowledge of Active Directory in a production environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Experience using Microsoft Systems Management Server 2003&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Experience using Microsoft Operations Manager 2005&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Excellent problem solving skills&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience with the following is an asset&#xD;
&#xD;
·     VMware&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Microsoft Clustering Services in a production environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Configuring IBM IT Director&#xD;
&#xD;
·     RF Thin Clients&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Blade Technology&#xD;
&#xD;
·     SAN/NAS technology&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Task automation using a Microsoft Scripting Language (preferably VBscript and/or batch)&#xD;
&#xD;
·     Knowledge of Linux&#xD;
&#xD;
Required Positions and Skills&#xD;
&#xD;
Positions (One of the following)  Years of Experience&#xD;
&#xD;
Infrastructure Specialist 5&#xD;
&#xD;
Systems Administrator 7&#xD;
&#xD;
Server Specialist 5&#xD;
&#xD;
Core Skills (All of the following) Years of Experience&#xD;
&#xD;
MCSE 5&#xD;
&#xD;
ACTIVE DIRECTORY 5&#xD;
&#xD;
MCSA - Microsoft Certified System Administrator 5&#xD;
&#xD;
MCP - Microsoft Certified Professional 5&#xD;
&#xD;
Windows Server 2003 7&#xD;
&#xD;
VMware 5</content>
    <postId>21B7FF55-A8C8-436B-B6CC-B26D6BC7AEBE</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-06-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Wintel Role Position - 6month contract</title>
</post>
