<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Brendan&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
My name is Ali Eid and I am a Technical Recruiter with Tundra Technical Solutions, here in Toronto. I came across your online profile. I would like to connect with you to see if you are exploring potential career opportunities. Presently, we have a Senior Java Developer with one of our clients. &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
I'd like to work with you and provide more information about this position ( See Below). Please forward your updated resume and/or give me a call at 416 915 7878 ext 126.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
If this is not for you, perhaps you may know someone who is a great fit. Please feel free to pass this opportunity on to them. You can check out our Referral Bonus Program by visiting our website @ www.tundratechnical.ca.&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Position Title: Sr. Java Developer&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Location - Richmond Hill, Ontario&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Summary:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Our client a leading automotive manufacturer is currently seeking a contractor who is strong in J2EE architecture design and leadership skills.  Someone who has actually done development and work their way up the rank.  Someone who thinks outside the box.  Vignette knowledge as always an asset but not mandatory.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
This person will be responsible for leading development teams within the ISD department of Honda. We are looking for a resource with a very solid track record of past J2EE projects within an IBM based environment - Websphere/DB2/MQSeries.&#xD;
&#xD;
  &#xD;
&#xD;
Key Technologies  &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
J2EE, Websphere, WSAD, MQ, DB2, Struts, EJBs, JDBMS&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Must Have Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
5-10 years J2EE experience&#xD;
&#xD;
-------------&#xD;
&#xD;
Tundra 	&#xD;
Ali Eid                  &#xD;
Technical Recruiter  &#xD;
Phone: 416.915.7878 x 126&#xD;
Mobile: 647.722.3448&#xD;
Toll Free: 1.866.9TUNDRA (988.6372)&#xD;
Email: aeid@tundratechnical.ca</content>
    <postId>227BD33F-E8B0-40EF-BA3E-5F0DBA55381F</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr Java developer, Cont, Richmond Hill, Long term</title>
</post>
