<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Training Specialist&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Reports to:   Manager, Program Management &amp; Tech. Support&#xD;
&#xD;
Department:   Service Delivery&#xD;
&#xD;
Date:   April 2009&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
SUMMARY&#xD;
&#xD;
As Training Specialist, you are the single point of contact for all training.  Your primary responsibilities include training customers, partners and new employees on our Application Development suite, and developing training materials.  Our clients are spread throughout the world so this position affords you the opportunity to travel up to 75% of your time.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
You will report into the Program Management &amp; Tech. Support group but will also interact with the Product Development group in order to update training material based on the evolution of ---.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
RESPONSIBLITIES&#xD;
&#xD;
Deliver in-person training internally and externally, ranging from 2 days to 3 weeks in duration.&#xD;
Deliver web-based training as required.&#xD;
Develop new courses for new products&#xD;
Maintain existing courses based on product enhancements&#xD;
Schedule and coordinate all training sessions.&#xD;
Prepare post-training reports and student evaluations. Maintain all training records and partner certification programs&#xD;
Act as a backup to the Documentation Specialist for generating documentation or other product related materials as required.&#xD;
As required to perform product demos to clients and partners.&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
QUALIFICATIONS&#xD;
&#xD;
2+ years experience in the telecommunications software industry&#xD;
2+ years experience in hands-on software training&#xD;
2+ years experience in software development with JavaScript and object-oriented programming language&#xD;
1+ years experience in SQL and Oracle 10g Server&#xD;
Experience designing and development training course materials&#xD;
Excellent presentation and organizational skills&#xD;
Ability to read and interpret technical and non-technical documents.&#xD;
Ability to extract information from specification documents, and explain details with simple words and diagrams an asset&#xD;
Ability to clearly convey information and ideas through a variety of media to individuals and groups&#xD;
Ability to learn new technologies&#xD;
Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Word and PowerPoint&#xD;
Experience with software connectors such as SOAP, JMS, etc. an asset&#xD;
Experience with workflow design an asset&#xD;
Experience with HTML, application server &amp; web-services and different web-browsers an asset&#xD;
Ability to travel internationally up to 75% of the time&#xD;
Ability to work totally independently and to stay focus to complete tasks.&#xD;
A positive person who enthusiastically supports change, shares expertise, takes responsibility works with minimal supervision, and delivers with quality.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Other qualities AND skills&#xD;
&#xD;
Change Management – Accepts, adapts to change as directed; understands change is a constant and necessary path for improvement and growth.  Questions the status quo by asking “Why?” questions about own work processes and work environment.&#xD;
Customer Focus - Is dedicated to meeting the expectations and requirements of internal and external customers; gets first-hand customer information and uses it for improvements in products and services; talks and acts with customers in mind; establishes and maintains effective relationships with customers and gains their trust and respect.&#xD;
Leadership – Exchanges information with appropriate people to complete work.  Represents the company in a positive light.  Embraces entrepreneurial spirit in work through recognizing and capitalizing on opportunities and challenging the status quo.&#xD;
Problem Solving – Solves difficult problems with effective solutions; asks good questions and probes all fruitful sources for answers; can see underlying or hidden problems and patterns; is excellent at honest analysis; looks beyond the obvious and doesn’t stop at the first answers. &#xD;
Self-Development – Ability to recognize personal skills, abilities, limitations and strengths, taking appropriate action to pursue developmental activities and seeks assistance from others prior to job difficulty.&#xD;
Total Quality Management - Is dedicated to providing the highest quality products and services, which meet the needs and requirements of internal and external customers; is committed to continuous improvement through empowerment and management by data.  Open to suggestions and experimentation; creates a learning environment leading to the most efficient and effective work processes.&#xD;
Self-confidence – A belief in one’s capability to accomplish a task and select an effective approach to a task or problem.  This includes confidence in one’s ability as expressed in increasingly challenging circumstances and confidence in one’s decision or opinions.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
------------&#xD;
Karen Agulnik&#xD;
&#xD;
900-45 Sheppard Avenue East&#xD;
&#xD;
Toronto, Ontario&#xD;
&#xD;
M2N 5W9&#xD;
&#xD;
416-226-2828, 312&#xD;
&#xD;
Karen@apexsearch.com&#xD;
&#xD;
www.apexsearch.com</content>
    <postId>245A4267-AEA7-46D3-A6BC-D17049A5EED2</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-04-06T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[PERM] Toronto, Training Specialist, (Requires Traveling)</title>
</post>
