<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>백재진</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>백재진</author>
            <date>2003-05-09T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>I don't remember where I got.&#xD;
DR SEUSS = children book author&#xD;
CAPTAIN KIRK = a captian of Star Track&#xD;
SIGMUND FREUD = psychoanalyst... 100 years ago&#xD;
COLONEL SANDERS =  the guy who found KFC Kentucky Fried Chicken)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
then Who in the world is TRICIA?..somebody know? anybody?&#xD;
</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Why did the chicken cross the road?&#xD;
&#xD;
MOHAMMED ALDOURI - (Iraq Ambassador)&#xD;
The chicken did not cross the road. This is a complete fabrication. We do&#xD;
not even have a chicken.&#xD;
&#xD;
GEORGE W BUSH&#xD;
We don't really care why the chicken crossed the road. We just want to&#xD;
know if the chicken is on our side of the road or not. The chicken is either&#xD;
against us or for us. There is no middle ground here.&#xD;
&#xD;
COLIN POWELL&#xD;
Now to the left of the screen, you can clearly see the satellite image of&#xD;
the chicken crossing the road.&#xD;
&#xD;
TONY BLAIR&#xD;
I agree with George.&#xD;
&#xD;
HANS BLIX&#xD;
We have reason to believe there is a chicken, but we have not yet been&#xD;
allowed to have access to the other side of the road.&#xD;
&#xD;
DR SEUSS&#xD;
Did the chicken cross the road? Did he cross it with a toad? Yes, the&#xD;
chicken crossed the road, but why it crossed I've not been told.&#xD;
&#xD;
MARTIN LUTHER KING, JR&#xD;
I envision a world where all chickens will be free to cross roads without&#xD;
having their motives called into question.&#xD;
&#xD;
GRANDPA&#xD;
In my day, we didn't ask why the chicken crossed the road. Somebody told&#xD;
us the chicken crossed the road, and that was good enough.&#xD;
&#xD;
TRICIA&#xD;
Isn't that interesting? In a few moments, we will be listening to the&#xD;
chicken tell, for the first time, the heart-warming story of how it&#xD;
experienced a serious case of molting, and went on to accomplish its life&#xD;
long dream of crossing the road.&#xD;
&#xD;
JOHN LENNON&#xD;
Imagine all the chickens in the world crossing roads together - in peace.&#xD;
&#xD;
ARISTOTLE&#xD;
It is the nature of chickens to cross the road.&#xD;
&#xD;
KARL MARX&#xD;
It was an historic inevitability.&#xD;
&#xD;
RONALD REAGAN&#xD;
What chicken?&#xD;
&#xD;
CAPTAIN KIRK&#xD;
To boldly go where no chicken has ever gone before.&#xD;
&#xD;
SIGMUND FREUD&#xD;
The fact that you are at all concerned that the chicken crossed the road&#xD;
reveals your underlying sexual insecurity.&#xD;
&#xD;
BILL GATES&#xD;
I have just witnessed eChicken2003, which will not only cross roads, but&#xD;
will lay eggs, file your important documents, and balance your checkbook.&#xD;
And Internet Explorer is an integral part of eChicken.&#xD;
&#xD;
ALBERT EINSTEIN&#xD;
Did the chicken really cross the road, or did the road move beneath the&#xD;
chicken?&#xD;
&#xD;
BILL CLINTON&#xD;
I did not cross the road with THAT chicken. What is your definition of&#xD;
chicken?&#xD;
&#xD;
THE BIBLE&#xD;
And God came down from heaven, and he said unto the chicken THOU SHALT&#xD;
CROSS THE ROAD. And the chicken didst cross the road, and there was much&#xD;
rejoicing.&#xD;
&#xD;
COLONEL SANDERS&#xD;
Did I miss one?</content>
    <postId>2745FC32-56FB-4002-93F4-30241DAD9AB0</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Why did the chicken cross the road?</title>
</post>
