<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Sr Java Developer&#xD;
FT perm position&#xD;
North York&#xD;
&#xD;
Will be working on a team responsible for designing, configuring and implementing software solutions for enterprise customers in the Financial Services, Insurance, and Healthcare industries.&#xD;
 &#xD;
We are looking for dynamic individuals to play key contributing roles on our project teams. Ideal candidate  will bring enthusiasm, willingness to learn, initiative, excellent verbal and written communication skills, and a strong desire to work in a fast-paced and high-growth environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Description:&#xD;
The successful candidate will have the opportunity to advance their career quickly by working with new technologies, an experienced executive management team, and industry-leading company with a track record of success. This is a unique opportunity that offers leadership potential, design and development experience, and occasional travel. This role requires strong technical, analytical and problem solving skills.&#xD;
&#xD;
As a Professional Services Consultant, you will be responsible for: &#xD;
•	Gathering and analyzing customer business and technical requirements &#xD;
•	Working with members of Product Management to define and document functional requirements, workflows, and designs to meet customer requirements &#xD;
•	Modeling technical designs using our state-of-the-art model-driven framework &#xD;
•	Development and configuration of client-specific solutions &#xD;
•	Client data conversion, involving batch or real-time integration with existing systems &#xD;
•	Conducting client site implementations , including software installation and configuration &#xD;
•	Technical sales support including the implementation of software demonstrations &#xD;
&#xD;
Preference will be given to candidates with experience in the following areas: &#xD;
•	Consulting &#xD;
•	Large-scale enterprise software implementation projects &#xD;
•	Software implementations for Financial Services organizations, such as Wealth Management, Life Insurance, P&amp;C Insurance, Investment Banking and Retail Banking &#xD;
we value proven problem-solving skills, the ability to learn quickly, persistence, and the ability to manage competing priorities in a challenging atmosphere.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Candidates will be working directly with clients and will be required to travel (mainly within Canada and to the US) and work at the client site.&#xD;
&#xD;
Skill Set Requirements:&#xD;
&#xD;
This position requires a highly-focused, technically-adept individual with a thorough understanding of the Software Development Life Cycle, model-driven development methodologies and documentation standards. &#xD;
&#xD;
The following skills will be assets: &#xD;
•	Experience in Java, C++, and/or C# development &#xD;
•	Strong understanding of object-oriented design, and programming patterns &#xD;
•	Scripting languages (e.g. VBscript, Javascript, Scheme) &#xD;
•	Enterprise application architectures and SOA design &#xD;
•	SQL generation and optimization as well as schema design experience (preferably with MSSQL, DB2, and/or Oracle) &#xD;
•	Data warehousing, data marts, report generation (Crystal, Jasper, Cognos) &#xD;
•	Deployment, configuration, and management of J2EE Database systems, Exchange, and Blackberry Applications (preferably using WebSphere and/or JBoss) &#xD;
•	Microsoft Office and Adobe data-driven forms and spreadsheets &#xD;
•	Knowledge of project management methodologies and tools &#xD;
•	Strong oral and written communication skills &#xD;
•	Computer Software Engineering or Computer Science degree</content>
    <postId>27C4A5E1-87C1-4E47-9D2D-2DF7D17E03DB</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr Java Developer</title>
</post>
