<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I listened above title over last week by audio tape. It was narrated by author himself. We all heard of this book. Some of us have already read it.&#xD;
&#xD;
I do not remember I read it or not. But I heard or read the summary of the book and I used it for my job interview. And it worked very well. I can't tell I got the all the job I had interview with. But I was very successful. I did not get the position sometimes not because of my interview. It was more like it was not fit for me.&#xD;
&#xD;
This is how I used the concept of above book.&#xD;
When interview is over, I ask the interviewer to give me 2 to 3 mins to wrap-up. And I explain why he/she should hire me.&#xD;
&#xD;
Opening sentence :&#xD;
" I am technically very confident and I will bring positive influence to new team. And this are the reasons"&#xD;
&#xD;
- I have proven track records and good education background.&#xD;
   If I am confident about my technical ability, I should not be here.&#xD;
&#xD;
- I will follow standard and provide neat codes/program/solution/project  as possible&#xD;
  Whatever I do in boundary of the company, soon or latter some one else will look at my stuffs due to business or change of something.&#xD;
&#xD;
- I will be punctual : my projects and attendance will be on time&#xD;
&#xD;
- I do not quarrel : In order to be a team player I need to close to everyone&#xD;
&#xD;
- I will smile : I will smile to every person I will see or meet inside of the company. Never know that I will work together with anybody.&#xD;
It could give me the head start in relationship.&#xD;
&#xD;
- If I/other are in trouble, I will ask/assist for help :&#xD;
   I am only good as my team member. If I need help, I will ask. The same time if other member asks for help, I will help with the best of my ability&#xD;
&#xD;
- If I come up with new ideas or new technique, I will share&#xD;
  I would not hold back what I know or what I find. Because I am only good as my team.&#xD;
&#xD;
If I hire anybody, I like interviewees say something like what I have stated above. Tell the interviewer likes to hear. It is all about interviewee's attitude and behavior not knowledge.&#xD;
&#xD;
*Master Key of Interview : Good attitude, passion about work but most of all sincerity. Everybody wants to be with good people and winner. Be honest and sincere.&#xD;
&#xD;
When I am listening the second time, there were bigger things I missed at the first time. I have been struggling about the ideas of&#xD;
&#xD;
- Why bad things happen to good people ? or the same token&#xD;
- Why good things happen to bad people ?&#xD;
&#xD;
But you know what most of time "Good things happen to good people and bad things happen to bad people". There are very rare times reverse happens. That is why those things are in the news.&#xD;
I had seen bad people come to church and had pretended of their true identity. That was one of my reasons to stop attending the church. When I think of it, how foolish it is. Most of people come to church are good.&#xD;
&#xD;
These are my thoughts. I will thank to small miracles I encounter everyday.&#xD;
For example : nice friends, meals prepared by my wife, good health that I can exercise, my work, my co-worker, so on and so forth.&#xD;
&#xD;
I would not wait until tomorrow. I will do it today.&#xD;
For example : I will tell people I know how much I love them today.&#xD;
I will tell my co-workers how much I appreciate their work today.&#xD;
If I have a friend I haven't talk to for some time, I will call him today.&#xD;
If I like to share the though with Comm-one friends, I will write article today. &#xD;
I will write the comments on other member’s article today.&#xD;
&#xD;
Stop to write right now.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>29A1E0CD-418F-4A9B-9A39-70205D4B009E</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>All I really need to know I learned in Kindergarden by Robert Fulgham</title>
</post>
