<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2009-07-10T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>C#, ASP.net 이것들이 대세인가 봅니다. 순수자바는 사라지고 있는 것일까요?</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Good afternoon ,&#xD;
&#xD;
I need your assistance. One of my clients in Edmonton is looking to hire a C# / Powerbuilder Developer on a 7 months contract starting now. If you, or anyone you know, would be interested in this position, please contact me at the information below. If you do not know of someone you can refer to me, would you pass this on to a friend, colleague or associate whom you consider to be closer to this type of person. Thank you as always.&#xD;
---&#xD;
This is a contract role for 7 months - with possible extention for another year in Edmonton, AB.&#xD;
&#xD;
You will be responsible for development, maintenance, testing and support of applications and interfaces accessing desktop and web applications currently in use. Reporting to the Director of Applications, the contractor(s) will work under the direction and supervision of a Team Leader. The application environment consists of microcomputer applications running on Intel boxes utilizing Microsoft Windows NT Server, Windows 2003 or Windows XP Clients, C#, ASP.net and MS SQL Server. One application that needs to be supported uses PowerBuilder.&#xD;
&#xD;
Mandatory Requirements&#xD;
(a) Experience as an analyst designing and/or developing large mission critical applications.&#xD;
Minimum three years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(b) Experience gathering &amp; formally documenting requirements and performing detailed analysis and design of N-tier distributed applications using object oriented design techniques.&#xD;
Minimum three years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(c) Experience leading or facilitating user requirement / application design sessions with business clients.&#xD;
Minimum three years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(d) Experience working in a team environment with 3 or more developers&#xD;
Minimum three years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(e) Experience with formal change management procedures.&#xD;
Minimum three years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(f) Experience developing SQL queries and/or stored procedures for an MS SQL Server database. Experience with Oracle will be considered.&#xD;
Minimum three years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(g) Experience building applications using C# with the .NET framework. One year of experience with Java can be substituted for one year of C#.&#xD;
Minimum three years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(h) Experience programming with Powerbuilder version 10.2 or higher&#xD;
Minimum one year within the past 5 years&#xD;
&#xD;
Desirable Requirements&#xD;
(i) Experience creating artifacts using Rational Unified Process (RUP).&#xD;
One or more years within the past 5 years&#xD;
(j) A minimum of 6 years combined related experience and education as stated below. Additional education and\or experience is preferred.&#xD;
Combined education and experience:&#xD;
University graduation in computer science and 2 years experience; or&#xD;
a two year diploma in computer technology from a recognized post-secondary institution and 4 years experience; or&#xD;
a related one year certificate from a recognized post-secondary institution and 5 years experience.&#xD;
Minimum of 6 years combined education and experience as stated.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
--&#xD;
Alex Kovalenko&#xD;
Director of Operations&#xD;
http://www.kovasys.com&#xD;
alex@kovasys.com&#xD;
Tel: 888.568.2747 x701</content>
    <postId>2B2AF1CF-2CDB-4AFD-84D0-0F584B98A6F4</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-07-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>C# / Powerbuilder Contract in Edmonton</title>
</post>
