<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Reader's discretion is adviced.&#xD;
Hopefully you can read to the end. There will be great  turn around and unexpected conclusion.&#xD;
&#xD;
After all the hype of year 2000, I had the chance the visit the untamed world, Internet and Client/Server. It was exciting and fun place. However it was unorganized and uncivilized. There was the mixture of the multi cultures and multi technologies. It was very fun place to visit for experience but not the place to stay. I am from well organized and civilized world, AS400. &#xD;
&#xD;
I came back from the my trip and I came to realization of publish my experiences to my peers. They were not very interested nor aware of what is happening over the untamed world. Even through untamed world is not well organized, they had very pioneerous vision and ideas about the future.&#xD;
&#xD;
I decided to build the bridge between untamed world and my community. It will be great accomplishment for both world. Untamed world will be benefit from rich culture and information from my world. And my community will enjoy the excitment of new technologies and we could have fun.&#xD;
&#xD;
I find my plan had a hole. My English could get by daily regular life. But I had a tough time to convince or persuade my ideas to others. Before I execute my plan, I decide to improve my English specially pronounciation and presentation skill. Hopefully I will be more convincing with better English and presentaion skill.&#xD;
&#xD;
My dear friends and peers do not make the same mistakes like I made. I should improve my English when I had time and chance. Please make the best investment you could make in your life before it is late. You could be a better parents, spouse and could receive what you want little bits easier.&#xD;
&#xD;
ps : If I have offended anybody, it was not my intention. Please pardon me.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sincerely Yours&#xD;
&#xD;
Thomas Lee  </content>
    <postId>2B3B73EB-63AF-4055-981A-C410D04A3821</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>English and Untamed world</title>
</post>
