<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Tough Interview Questions&#xD;
&#xD;
1. General Questions &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Tell me about you! &#xD;
 Keep your answer to one or two minutes; don't ramble. Use  your resume summary as a base to start.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What do you know about our company? &#xD;
 Do your homework before the interview! Spend some time online or at the library researching the company. Find out as much as you can, including products, size, income, reputation, image, management talent, people, skills, history and philosophy. Project an informed interest; let the interviewer tell you about the company.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Why do you want to work for us?  &#xD;
 Don't talk about what you want; first, talk about their needs: You would like to be part of a specific company project; you would like to solve a company problem; you can make a definite contribution to specific company goals.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What would you do for us? What can you do for us that someone else can't? &#xD;
 Relate past experiences that show you've had success in solving previous employer problem(s) that may be similar to those of the prospective employer.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What about the job offered do you find the most attractive? Least attractive? &#xD;
 List three or more attractive factors and only one minor unattractive factor.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Why should we hire you?  &#xD;
 Because of your knowledge, experience, abilities and skills.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What do you look for in a job? &#xD;
 An opportunity to use your skills, to perform and be recognized.  &#xD;
Please give me your definition of a .... (the position for which you are being interviewed). &#xD;
Keep it brief -- give an actions- and results-oriented definition.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How long would it take you to make a meaningful contribution to our firm? &#xD;
 Not long at all -- you expect only a brief period of adjustment to the learning curve.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How long would you stay with us? &#xD;
 As long as we both feel I'm contributing, achieving, growing, etc. &#xD;
&#xD;
2. Experience and Management Questions &#xD;
 &#xD;
Q: You may be overqualified for the position we have to offer. &#xD;
 Strong companies need strong people. A growing, energetic company is rarely unable to use its people talents. Emphasize your interest in a long-term association, pointing out that the employer will get a faster return on investment because you have more experience than required.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What is your management style? &#xD;
 (If you've never thought about this, it's high time you did.) "Open-door management" is best ... And you get the job done on time or inform your management.  &#xD;
Are you a good manager? Give an example. Why do you feel you have top managerial potential?  &#xD;
Keep your answer achievement- and task-oriented; emphasize management skills -- planning, organizing, controlling, interpersonal, etc.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What do you look for when you hire people? &#xD;
 Skills, initiative, adaptability.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Did you ever fire anyone? If so, what were the reasons and how did you handle it? &#xD;
 You have had experience with this and it worked out well.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What do you see as the most difficult task in being a manager? &#xD;
 Getting things planned and done on time within the budget.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What do your subordinates think of you? &#xD;
 Be honest and positive ... they can check your responses easily.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What is your biggest weakness as a manager? &#xD;
 Be honest and end on a positive note, e.g. "I don't enjoy reprimanding people, so I try to begin with something positive first."&#xD;
 &#xD;
3. If You Are Leaving a Job &#xD;
 &#xD;
Q: Why are you leaving your present job? &#xD;
 Refine your answer based on your comfort level and honesty. Give a "group" answer if possible, e.g. our department was consolidated or eliminated.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How do you feel about leaving all of your benefits? &#xD;
 Concerned but not panicked.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Describe what you feel to be an ideal working environment.  &#xD;
 One in which people are treated as fairly as possible.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How would you evaluate your present firm? &#xD;
 An excellent company that afforded me many fine experiences. &#xD;
&#xD;
4. Quantifying Your Experience and Accomplishments &#xD;
 &#xD;
Q: Have you helped increase sales? Profits? How? &#xD;
 Describe in some detail.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Have you helped reduce costs? How? &#xD;
 Describe in some detail.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How much money did you account for?  &#xD;
 Be specific.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How many people did you supervise on your last job? &#xD;
 Be specific.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Do you like working with figures more than words? &#xD;
 Be honest but positive.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: In your current or last position, what features did you like the most? Least? &#xD;
 Be honest but positive.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: In your current or last position, what are or were your five most significant accomplishments?  &#xD;
 Refer to the key accomplishments already identified on your resume. &#xD;
&#xD;
5. Job Search Questions &#xD;
 &#xD;
Q: Why haven't you found a new position before now? &#xD;
Finding a job is easy; finding the right job is more difficult. (You are being "selective.")  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Had you thought of leaving your present position before?  If yes, what do you think held you there? &#xD;
Challenge, but it's gone now.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What do you think of your boss? &#xD;
 Be as positive as you can.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Would you describe a situation in which your work was criticized? &#xD;
 Be as positive as you can.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What other types of jobs or companies are you considering? &#xD;
 Keep your answer related to this company's field.&#xD;
&#xD;
6. Your Work Habits and Style &#xD;
 &#xD;
Q: If I spoke with your previous boss, what would he say are your greatest strengths and weaknesses? &#xD;
 Emphasize skills -- don't be overly negative about your weaknesses; it's always safer to identify a lack of a skill as an area for improvement rather than a shortcoming.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Can you work under pressures, deadlines, etc.? &#xD;
 Yes, it's a way of life in business.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How have you changed the nature of your job? &#xD;
 Improved it ... of course.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Do you prefer staff or line work? Why? &#xD;
 Depends on the job and its challenges.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: In your present position, what problems have you identified that had previously been overlooked? &#xD;
 Keep it brief and don't brag.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: Don't you feel you might be better off in a different size company? Different type company? &#xD;
 Depends on the job -- elaborate slightly.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How do you resolve conflict on a project team? &#xD;
 First you discuss the issues privately.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make? &#xD;
 Try to relate your response to the prospective employment situation&#xD;
&#xD;
7. Salary Questions &#xD;
 &#xD;
Q: How much are you looking for? &#xD;
 Answer with a question, i.e., "What is the salary range for similar jobs in your company?" If they don't answer, then give a range of what you understand you are worth in the marketplace.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What do you know about our company? &#xD;
 Do your homework before the interview! Spend some time online or at the library researching the company. Find out as much as you can, including products, size, income, reputation, image, management talent, people, skills, history and philosophy. Project an informed interest; let the interviewer tell you about the company.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How much do you expect, if we offer this position to you? &#xD;
 Be careful; the market value of the job may be the key answer, e.g., "My understanding is that a job like the one you're describing may be in the range of $______."  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What kind of salary are you worth? &#xD;
Have a specific figure in mind ... don't be hesitant.&#xD;
&#xD;
8. Your Career Goals &#xD;
 &#xD;
Q: If you could start your career again, what would you do differently? &#xD;
 Nothing ... I am happy today, so I don't want to change my past.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: What career options do you have at the moment? &#xD;
 "I see three areas of interest..." Relate those to the position and industry.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Q: How would you describe the essence of success? According to your definition of success, how successful have you been so far?  &#xD;
 Think carefully about your answer and relate it to your career accomplishments.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>2DBD9DAC-3C44-49DC-8E58-BC7A7C0A1024</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Interview Questions with Recommended Answers</title>
</post>
