<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2009-06-15T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>벌써 귀국하셨나요?</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Software Developer &#xD;
Location: Canada-ON-Toronto &#xD;
Job Code: 6255 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
 &#xD;
Description &#xD;
&#xD;
Software Engineer for Product Development&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Quest Software, Inc., a leading enterprise systems management vendor, delivers innovative products that help organizations get more performance and productivity from their applications, databases, Windows infrastructure and virtual environments. Through a deep expertise in IT operations and a continued focus on what works best, Quest helps more than 90,000 customers’ worldwide meet higher expectations for enterprise IT. Quest Software can be found in offices around the globe and at www.quest.com&#xD;
&#xD;
                                                                                                    &#xD;
&#xD;
Description:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Quest is revolutionizing application performance monitoring with its next-generation Foglight product.  As a member of the Foglight Development team, you will contribute to the design, implementation and maintenance of the Foglight Server and Agents.  Foglight crosses many different layers of technology (e.g. Operating Systems, Databases, Enterprise applications), as such, you have a broad working knowledge in these areas and a passion for continuous learning.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
You will be fixing product bugs and writing new features, collaboratively with software professionals located both locally (downtown Toronto) and other Quest offices world-wide.  &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Requirements: &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
• 4+ years experience developing software in a professional environment (Java, C++, OOP/OOD)&#xD;
&#xD;
• Comfortable working in Unix and Windows based environments &#xD;
&#xD;
• Experience diagnosing and resolving issues across various technology layers, including down to the system level&#xD;
&#xD;
• Experience using debugging tools/techniques&#xD;
&#xD;
• Strong work ethic and professionalism&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Asset:&#xD;
&#xD;
• The ability to trade off design and implementation alternatives based on project goals and risk assessment &#xD;
&#xD;
• Detailed knowledge of OS virtualization technologies&#xD;
&#xD;
• Experience with socket communications, network protocols, and distributed computing&#xD;
&#xD;
• Experience with caching, memory management, threading, lock management, and I/O optimization &#xD;
&#xD;
• Working experience with source revision control and build tools (CVS, Ant)&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
We offer a relaxed yet professional work environment with a competitive salary and excellent benefits. We are an equal-opportunity employer and welcome all candidate applications that meet the requirements listed above.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
EOE M/F/D/V &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
    &#xD;
&#xD;
    &#xD;
      &#xD;
Previous Applicants: &#xD;
Email:  &#xD;
Password:  &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
If you do not remember your password click here.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
&lt;&lt; Back to Search Results&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
New Search</content>
    <postId>2E985739-B9D8-4529-A0BB-708C542337F2</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-06-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>QUEST 에서 사람 뽑습니다.</title>
</post>
