<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이홍식</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>실천하기만 하면 효과를 볼 수 있는 제안들이라고 생각합니다. 저도 요즘 뱃살땜이 고민인데...&#xD;
&#xD;
Secrets Of Successful Losers &#xD;
Tired of riding the diet yo-yo? Here's how to drop pounds and keep them off &#xD;
First published in Chatelaine.com's June 2001 issue.&#xD;
&amp;copy; Gabrielle Bauer &#xD;
&#xD;
Two years ago, at the age of 24, Deborah Whalley decided to get rid of the "80-pound backpack" of extra weight she was carrying on her five-foot-nine frame. It wasn't the first time that Whalley, a retail assistant manager in Toronto, embarked on a diet. &#xD;
&#xD;
"I lost 30 pounds in Grade 9," she recalls. "Not only did I gain the weight back in short order, I put on about 50 extra pounds over the next nine years." This time, however, Whalley has not only lost the excess baggage but has kept it off for two years (and counting). &#xD;
&#xD;
If you've ever been on a diet, you've probably discovered, as Whalley did, that taking off extra pounds is a lot easier than keeping them off. In fact, 95 per cent of people who lose weight end up gaining it back, and then some--the familiar phenomenon known as yo-yo dieting.&#xD;
&#xD;
Cycling back and forth between higher and lower weights is not just demoralizing. "There's some evidence that yo-yoing within a 20- or 30-pound range puts more stress on your heart than carrying those 20 or 30 extra pounds," says Stephen Cunnane, a professor of nutritional sciences at the University of Toronto. "The overall message here is that it's better to stay heavier than to yo-yo." &#xD;
&#xD;
Better still, of course, is to maintain the lower weight you achieve after dieting. But how? Researchers and doctors who've studied the five per cent of dieters who keep the weight off have found common threads in their approaches and attitudes. Here are the secrets to their success:&#xD;
&#xD;
Listen to your heart&#xD;
According to Linda McCargar, associate professor of human nutrition at the University of Alberta and one of Canada's leading experts on the effects of yo-yo dieting, you're much more likely to succeed if your motivation comes from within--a new awareness of your mortality, a desire to take better care of yourself or, in her words, "a significant emotional event that causes you to re-evaluate your lifestyle choices." This doesn't mean you need to get sick before taking action. &#xD;
&#xD;
Endocrinologist Ronnie Aronson, who runs the Lifestyle Metabolism Centre in Oakville, Ont. (where Deborah Whalley signed up), suggests small behavioural changes, such as taking after-dinner walks, to get into the mindset for self-motivation.&#xD;
&#xD;
On the other hand, people who use pressure from their partner or doctor to kick-start weight loss are more likely to fail, says Dr. Aronson. "Women are more often under such pressure from others to lose weight."&#xD;
&#xD;
Plan ahead to beat temptation&#xD;
If you know you have a "danger zone" coming up--say, a week-long family reunion at a hotel that serves buffet meals--you need to develop coping strategies well before you're "in the moment, surrounded by temptation," says Susan Cantwell, a wellness trainer based in Fredericton. For example, you might picture yourself choosing one serving of scrambled eggs and a single slice of lightly buttered toast from the breakfast buffet. "Do this exercise for a few days in a row and your mental imagery becomes your ally."&#xD;
&#xD;
Cantwell cautions against battling too much temptation during the early weeks of a weight-loss effort. "For the first 30 days or so, I tell my clients to say no to invitations that spell temptation, such as coffee at your favourite dessert hangout," she says. "After the first month, it becomes safer to accept such invitations, as long as you do the mental preparation for them." &#xD;
&#xD;
Focus on process, not results&#xD;
Cantwell says long-term success is much more likely if the goal is the new behaviour pattern itself--getting to the gym three times a week, for instance--rather than the figure on the bathroom scale. In fact, she suggests doing away with the scale altogether. "It's a poor indicator of increasing fitness and body tone," she explains.&#xD;
&#xD;
Cantwell drew on her 10 years of experience in getting people to change ingrained habits for her book Mind Over Matter: Personal Choices for a Lifetime of Fitness (Stoddart). Her thesis: setbacks plague people who are trying to change and the key to staying on track in the face of these inevitable setbacks is to make "a daily commitment to your new behaviours, regardless of what happened yesterday."&#xD;
&#xD;
Take it slowly&#xD;
"No more than two pounds a week and no fewer than 1,100 calories a day," is Dr. Aronson's rule of thumb. "Extreme self-denial doesn't work...it usually leads to an 'escape' from the self-denial."&#xD;
&#xD;
Another problem with extreme caloric deprivation is that your basal metabolic rate will drop temporarily while you're on this regimen, says McCargar. "This means your body is in an energy-conserving mode. The result is that you're not burning up as much fuel, calorie for calorie, as if you were on a more moderate diet."&#xD;
Honour your preferences&#xD;
When you're in the weight-maintenance phase, Dr. Aronson stresses the importance of creating a regimen you could follow for the rest of your life. "If you adore Belgian chocolates, then you need to build the occasional taste of Belgian chocolates into your eating plan. Otherwise, you run the risk of not being able to stop after you have one." This philosophy helped Whalley maintain her weight loss. Rather than give up her favourite cheesecake and fast foods, she buys or prepares lighter versions and occasionally treats herself to a serving of the real McCoy. "There's no single food that's off limits to me," she says. "It's a question of how much and how often." &#xD;
Trade fat for protein and fibre&#xD;
Calorie for calorie, protein is more satisfying than fat, so people on protein-rich diets tend to feel fuller on fewer calories, says Angelo Tremblay, a metabolism researcher at Laval University in Quebec City. "You're less likely to overstep your caloric requirements if your diet has a high protein content," he says. Conversely, fats and alcohol are least likely to make you feel sated. "You can have a lot of them and still not feel full, which increases the likelihood you'll overeat." Tremblay is the first to admit that fat makes things taste good, so you may have to give yourself some time to adjust to the taste of lower-fat foods. Still, Whalley says lower-fat ready-made cheesecakes are just as tasty and she hardly notices the difference. &#xD;
&#xD;
Cunnane explains that fibre-rich foods promote a feeling of fullness or satiety. So, eating more fibre should help you eat less food. "Hopefully, this will lead to losing weight." &#xD;
&#xD;
Shake it up&#xD;
Referring to a U.S. registry of successful dieters--people who lost 13 kilograms (about 30 pounds) or more and kept it off for five years--McCargar says the behaviour that most consistently distinguished the successful folks from the wannabes was regular physical activity. Those people who had embarked on an exercise program involving at least 2,500 extra calories a week in energy output (equal to about five hours of vigorous aerobic exercise) fared especially well. &#xD;
&#xD;
"Physical activity balances out your hunger mechanism and also leads to greater muscle mass, which uses extra calories to maintain itself," says Peter Jones, a professor at McGill University's school of dietetics and human nutrition in Montreal. "With less activity, your brain tells you that you're comfortable at a heavier weight." &#xD;
&#xD;
Dr. Aronson has also observed that successful weight maintainers tend to incorporate physical activity into their everyday lifestyle--walking upstairs instead of taking the elevator or parking farther away from the mall door--rather than just devote a few blocks of time to formal exercise. &#xD;
&#xD;
Share the load&#xD;
Cantwell says her clients who succeed in changing behaviour patterns talk about their resolutions. "They share their new mindset with other people and enlist their help." Other research studies led McCargar to a similar conclusion: "Next to exercise, having social support from family, friends or community groups stands out as key to long-term weight maintenance." &#xD;
&#xD;
When you're just starting out on a new eating/exercising plan--an especially vulnerable period--Cantwell suggests asking a friend to call periodically to cheer you on. "Just make sure that friend is not an 'enabler' who lets you off the hook too easily." &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>30F18000-8716-474E-AF47-97A77C59ACA3</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-05-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>살빼고 싶으신 분, 특히 뱃살 혹은 허벅지살???</title>
</post>
