<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Senior Programmer Analyst&#xD;
&#xD;
Requirement:&#xD;
&#xD;
CIHI requires a Senior Programmer Analyst to address some immediate resource challenges. The Senior Programmer Analyst will work under the direction of the Technical&#xD;
Lead as part of a technical development team. This work is to be performed in our Toronto Office and the expected timeframe for completion is the end of March 2009.&#xD;
&#xD;
Knowledge and Experience:&#xD;
&#xD;
The successful candidate should have:&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Extensive experience in IT development, testing and implementation of complex multiuser&#xD;
information systems (full development life cycle) in a web-based environment using industry-standard tools.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Demonstrated experience with systems development standards and methodologies, tools and techniques and quality assurance principles.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Extensive experience and proven expertise in web-based back-end, middle tier and front-end development.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Proven strong programming experience on the J2EE platform including common frameworks and tools to include Struts, Ibatis and JDeveloper IDE. Certification is a&#xD;
definite asset.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Very strong experience with web-based development, front-end experience using HTML, JavaScript, CSS, JSP and Struts.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Proven experience with ORACLE RDBMS 9i and up.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Solid understanding and experience using J2EE design patterns and best practices.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Experience with UML, Use Case Tools, MS Project, OOP, COM and C++.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Ability to understand and prioritise user and business requirements, and to conceptualise information processing solutions in response to them.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Ability to analyse, scope and define work effort required to correct program deficiencies and problems.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Ability to effectively plan and coordinate workload effectively.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Strong team player with a client/user orientation focus.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Excellent interpersonal, written and verbal communication skills, with the ability to communicate complex ideas/processes in simple terminology and create technical&#xD;
documentation.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Sun Java Developer Certification is a definite asset.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Familiarity with health informatics is desirable.&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Fluency in both official languages is desirable.&#xD;
&#xD;
Background:&#xD;
&#xD;
The Canadian Institute for Health Information (CIHI) is one of Canada’s premium sources of high quality, reliable and timely health information. CIHI is a not-for-profit, pan-&#xD;
Canadian organization and a focal point for collaboration among major health players &amp;#8211; from provincial governments, regional health authorities and hospitals to the federal&#xD;
government, researchers and associations representing health care professionals.&#xD;
&#xD;
CIHI provides Canadians with essential statistics and analysis about their health and their health care system. Over the past 14 years, we have grown into an indispensable source of information for health care managers, researchers, policy-makers and members of the public seeking answers to critical questions around the delivery of health care. For more information, visit our website at www.cihi.ca.&#xD;
&#xD;
Scope of Work:&#xD;
&#xD;
During the effective date of this agreement, the contractor will perform the tasks outlined below:&#xD;
&#xD;
1. Work as part of a technical team to develop information systems, to include the full range of requirements and feasibility analysis, design, coding, testing, quality&#xD;
assurance, implementation and documentation, as well as system application upgrades.&#xD;
&#xD;
2. May work closely with clients and maintain ongoing contact to ensure client satisfaction by meeting their needs through information systems development,&#xD;
enhancements and/or customizations.&#xD;
&#xD;
3. Analyze and generate solutions to resolve software design and program deficiencies/problems in existing or new systems. May be required to oversee and ensure timely analysis and generation of solutions for the project team.&#xD;
&#xD;
4. Analyze software change requests and implement the changes within the information systems. May be required to oversee and ensure timely implementation of change requests for the project team.&#xD;
&#xD;
5. Develops, modifies and executes test plans and test cases and ensures the correct testing and sign-off procedures which are part of CIHI’s quality assurance review.&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsible for the promotion and implementation of applications utilizing CIHI’s Technology Change Management Protocols.&#xD;
&#xD;
6. Participates in the planning, development and delivery of end user training.&#xD;
&#xD;
7. Participates in the definition and selection of appropriate tools and techniques to support CIHI’s standards and methodologies.&#xD;
&#xD;
8. Demonstrates a thorough understanding of systems development standards and methodologies, quality assurance principles and processes, tools and techniques&#xD;
and best practices.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Deliverables:&#xD;
&#xD;
1. The contractor will participate in the development of information systems to include design, coding, full range of testing and implementation&#xD;
&#xD;
2. The contractor will create required technical documentation according to CIHI’s standards and methodologies.&#xD;
&#xD;
3. The contractor will develop test cases and execute unit, module and system integration test plans and conduct comprehensive testing of information systems according to CIHI’s quality assurance standards and processes.&#xD;
&#xD;
4. The contractor will conduct end user training as required.&#xD;
&#xD;
5. The contractor will provide oral briefings on an ongoing basis to appraise CIHI’s Technical Lead and/or IT Service Manager as to the project status, challenges,&#xD;
risks and performance.&#xD;
&#xD;
---------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
Ariel Leizerowich&#xD;
Information Technology &#xD;
Account Manager &amp; Consultant &#xD;
&#xD;
416) 483-7424 ext. 248&#xD;
&#xD;
ariel@datalist.com&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>35AB343E-4109-4E2F-B127-F1F95CE7798C</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-10-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[Contract] Senior Programmer Analyst (J2EE, Toronto)</title>
</post>
