<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I have pasted a position description below for a Technical Consultant role with a combination of J2EE and Weblogic SDLC - this is currently a priority of mine and I would like to ask you for some help in identifying qualified people who would find this position interesting.  If you, or anyone you know, would like to learn more about this opportunity please reply to this message with a formatted copy of your resume and let me know when the best time would be to receive a phone call from me.&#xD;
&#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
&#xD;
Tony French&#xD;
Managing Partner&#xD;
Mpower&#xD;
tel. 416.640.4614&#xD;
tfrench@mpower.ca&#xD;
www.mpower.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
---------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
This hire will have a wide range of responsibilities focused on providing technical solutions to meet the needs of our clients. You will be a part of a team of professionals that play a key role in implementing solutions and delivering results. &#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities will include:&#xD;
&#xD;
- Participate in the full lifecycle of a client implementation such as Requirements Gathering, Business Analysis, System Configuration, Design, Testing, and Support&#xD;
&#xD;
- Collaborate with the Functional Consultant to write the design specifications.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Develop an understanding of the capabilities and limitations of the application, architecture, database schema, and development tools to properly and creatively use features to meet client needs.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Provide guidance for business decisions from a technical perspective on issues such as: performance, scalability, reliability, and security.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Travel as required (up to 80% throughout North America)&#xD;
&#xD;
Required Skills/Qualifications:&#xD;
&#xD;
- Full SDLC background&#xD;
&#xD;
- Experience with Java-based technologies: J2SE, J2EE, JSP, JDBC.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Experience with database technologies: Oracle, SQL Server, DB2.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Experience with application servers: BEA Weblogic, Oracle 9iAS, IBM WebSphere.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Experience with client-based enterprise implementations and n-tier web application architecture.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Ability to analyze problems and provide innovative solutions</content>
    <postId>39F2BEAF-7A78-4886-8DAC-B94E2B9D0D94</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-04-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Consultant (J2EE)</title>
</post>
