<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Developing job skills in tight-budget times&#xD;
By John Epperheimer&#xD;
Special to the Mercury News&#xD;
&#xD;
   &#xD;
Now is the time to do more with less when it comes to your career development.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are employed, you are probably finding that participating in formal, classroom-based development is difficult. Funds for training have dried up. Tuition reimbursement programs have been put on hold.&#xD;
&#xD;
Companies are emphasizing performance management, not employee development, to make sure they are getting maximum productivity.&#xD;
&#xD;
Yet you cannot afford to put your learning on hold until the economy improves. You need to stay competitive in the job market, and that means having up-to-date skills and showing that you are improving in your work.&#xD;
&#xD;
Get creative to foster inexpensive but effective ways of developing. Here are some ideas.&#xD;
&#xD;
1. Analyze key meetings and major projects to see what you could have done better.&#xD;
&#xD;
Before you leave the meeting room, take a few minutes with your colleagues to discuss what just happened. Simple questions can prompt productive discussions: ``What worked? What didn't? What could I have done differently to be more effective?''&#xD;
&#xD;
On large projects, build in time to review how the work was accomplished. As the review takes place, ask yourself where you might have been involved to try new assignments. For the next project, request that type of work.&#xD;
&#xD;
2. Combine learning and networking.&#xD;
&#xD;
I had a conversation recently with a manager whom I hadn't seen in several years. In the course of our catching up, he asked what business books I had recently read, and whether I would recommend them.&#xD;
&#xD;
We are now trading reading lists, and have pointed each other to books we otherwise would have missed.&#xD;
&#xD;
One high-tech vice president who traveled a great deal used much of that time to feed his reading habit. He kept a running list of good business books on his laptop, with a sentence or two about each. He happily shared the list with anyone who asked.&#xD;
&#xD;
If, like many people, you are uncomfortable at networking, set up a meeting with someone for the specific reason of trading information. (``David, this is Joe Smith. I'm trying to get up to speed on widget replication, and Harry Jones said you've been doing a lot of work in that area. Can I buy you a cup of coffee and chat about it?'')&#xD;
&#xD;
3. Seek informal help.&#xD;
&#xD;
Having a good mentoring relationship with a senior executive is one of the best ways to prepare yourself for greater responsibilities.&#xD;
&#xD;
Identify a manager several levels above you in the organization whose performance and leadership style you admire.&#xD;
&#xD;
See if that leader will spend some time with you to provide his perspective on a topic or two of interest to you. Be specific when you make the request for the executive's time, and come prepared with good questions. Perhaps the session will go so well that more get-togethers will follow. At the least, you will receive some valuable insight, and the executive will know more about you.&#xD;
&#xD;
4. Ask for developmental assignments.&#xD;
&#xD;
Volunteer for some duties that will stretch your capabilities. Deliberately put yourself in a situation where your learning curve will be steep -- it's probably the best way to learn, and to draw positive attention to yourself.&#xD;
&#xD;
Don't let a lack of funds in your company put your mind in hibernation. There are many ways to grow on the job.&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>3A4FFF52-3EBF-4081-9C90-814099154B1E</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-03-31T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Developing job skills in tight-budget times</title>
</post>
