<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이홍식</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>어제와 오늘 나이아가라에서 열린 CLARICA workshop에 다녀왔습니다.&#xD;
주제는 "Presentation Skill"이었구요.  CLARICA Presenter고수들로부터 많은 것을 배웠습니다. 일 테면...&#xD;
&#xD;
내 생각을 어떻게 Delivery해야 대중을 사로잡을 것인지,&#xD;
어떻게 사로잡은 대중의 관심을 유지할 것인지, &#xD;
내게 던져진 질문을 어떻게 효과적으로 Handling 할 것인지, &#xD;
심지어 Seating Arrangement는 어찌 해야 하는지 등등 구체적이고도 실제적인 제안들이 다루어졌습니다. 버릴 것이 없었습니다!&#xD;
&#xD;
Share할 만한 내용을 소개하겠습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
1. Handling Question Effectively.&#xD;
&#xD;
If someone in the audience asks you a question during the seminar you are conducting and you know the answer, then you would respond this way...&#xD;
&#xD;
"That's an excellent question! did everybody here that question?  John just asked me what RRSP stands for.  Well, RRSP stands for Retirement Registered Savings Plan and it's a very effective way to maximize your savings and minimize paying tax to the government."&#xD;
&#xD;
That's an excellent question!&#xD;
- 다른 청중들도 질문하고 세미나에 참여하도록 격려하고 있죠. 그와 동시에 진행자가 자기 생각을 정리할 수 있는 시간을 순간적으로 벌게 해 줍니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
Did everybody here that question?&#xD;
- 질문을 뒤에 앉아 있거나 딴청을 피고 있는 사람이 missing할 수 있으므로 다시 한번 반복해 줍니다.  그리함으로 모든 청중들이 다루어지고 있는 내용에 집중할 수 있도록 리드하고 있습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
Well, RRSP stands for Retirement Registered Savings Plan and it's a very effective way to maximize your savings and minimizing tax to the government."&#xD;
- maximize 혹은 minimize와 같은 대구표현으로 전달코자 하는 내용이 contrast/stand out 하게 하죠.&#xD;
&#xD;
If someone in the audience asks you a question during the seminar you are conducting and you DO NOT know the answer, then you would respond this way.&#xD;
&#xD;
"That's a good question! I don't have the answer for that now.  Let me get back to you after I find it out."  Then make sure you DOCUMENT the question and deliver your promise within a reasonable time frame.  You don't have to apologize for not knowing the answer.  Never lie or pretend you know the answer though.  That’s detrimental to your credential!&#xD;
- Honesty is the best policy! 그러나 질문자에게 납득할 만한 답을 찾아주겠다는 약속은 확실히 지킵니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
2. Memorizing the intro/closing.&#xD;
&#xD;
Practice, Practice, and Practice!  Write down your intro and closing script so that you don't rumble.</content>
    <postId>3D3E8552-572A-4DE8-BBB8-0F4DE8949F41</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Presentation Skill</title>
</post>
