<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>황인세</author>
            <date>2011-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>I wish and try to apply this positions.&#xD;
but I'm afraid I am in Korea, now.&#xD;
I will go back Toronto in september.&#xD;
Is it possible to apply this for me?</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hello Brendan,&#xD;
&#xD;
I hope this finds you well!&#xD;
&#xD;
It has been some time since we spoke, but I wanted to get back in contact with you regarding some of the Java openings that are going to be available throughout the summer.  This is for a new client in downtown Toronto (near Yonge &amp; Dundas) who is looking to bring on multiple new people, from intermediate developers with 3 – 5 years experience, right up to Sr Solutions Architects.  Best of all, they are flexible with both permanent and contract options.  The attached job description is for a Sr Java Developer, but again, my client is looking to bring on multiple people at a variety of skill levels, so feel free to pass this around to anyone in your network, from new graduates to seasoned professionals.&#xD;
&#xD;
Of course, if you are interested yourself, I would be happy to have a detailed conversation around the specific projects, responsibilities and salary range/contract rate.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Let me know if you want to talk!&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Again - if you, or anyone in your network, is interested in this new opportunity,  please call me directly and we can talk about the key components of the role. Further, if anything has changed in your current situation, please let me know and I would be happy to consult with you on your career progression.&#xD;
&#xD;
Thank you and I look forward to hearing from you. &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Kenneth Ian McLeod&#xD;
Technical Recruiter&#xD;
Email: kenneth.mcleod@quantum-qtr.com&#xD;
Tel: 416-601-5529&#xD;
www.Quantum-qtr.com</content>
    <postId>3D73D031-3D64-4432-BAEF-0823DF5CCD69</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Web developer, Toronto, multiple positions (perm/cont)</title>
</post>
