<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>홍대의</author>
            <date>2002-07-25T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>계속 기르세요!  중년의 기품이(dignity) 느껴질 것 같습니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Some of you know I've started growing the beard not mustache. I like it. I suppose it is every man's dream have a great looking set of mustache and beard. I had tried the mustache. i did not have enough density. I tried for about 5 days. It looked awful. It is the first time I am doing the beard. I like it very much. I did not have the plan to do it. It just happened. About 10 days ago I usually do not shave over the weekend. In Monday morning I started shaving after I'd done with whiskers (sideburns)and under the nose parts. Then I looked at myself at the mirror I liked it. I had decided to keep it for a while.&#xD;
&#xD;
There are the three different reactions by the demography by age and sex.&#xD;
&#xD;
Male : No reactions Everybody tried at least in their adult life. I got odd comments like "When are you going to shave it ?", "You need the fertilizer.", "There are few gray hairs."&#xD;
Not bad At least they are not against it.&#xD;
&#xD;
Female under early 30 : No comments or they like it. Some told me I looked tough. That was I was looking for&#xD;
&#xD;
Female over early 30 : They do not like a bit. They want me to shave it this instance.&#xD;
&#xD;
My wife : Looks dirty but she will survive. She had been through a lot worse.&#xD;
&#xD;
My Daughter : Looks dirty but it is father's face not hers&#xD;
&#xD;
Thomas : He likes it very much even though some odd times he wish there are more population of facial hairs. But it is better than a lot of other guys. At least I have some and looks O.K..&#xD;
&#xD;
I have decided to keep it for at least another two more weeks. My opinion counts the most, isn't it.&#xD;
&#xD;
If anyone of you do not like, go to hell and don't come back. Those people like my beard. Please add nice comments.&#xD;
&#xD;
la'vie en rose : Life is beautiful when you are trying something stupid and enjoying it.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>3F3FA603-18C6-4A8F-A3E8-959F70F7657F</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>My Beard</title>
</post>
