<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Site Admin</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>MARCH 12, 2001   BY STACY KING &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
One of the hardest things to deal with during economic turbulence is the sense of losing control. That's especially true when it looks like layoffs are around the corner. There's a sense of randomness about staff reductions that can make employees feel nervous and vulnerable. Rather than giving in to those sensations, it is crucial to focus on what you can do to help improve your odds if trouble is brewing.&#xD;
&#xD;
When a company is cutting corners, only the indispensable employees are kept on board - and there are several tactics that may help you avoid the cuts. Every employer uses different standards to judge which employees should be kept on board when reducing staff, but there are some general strategies that can help position you for continued employment. &#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=red&gt;Upgrade your skills:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; When companies are forced to cut corners, they look for the people who can keep operations running despite their smaller numbers. That means a broad skill set, since layoff survivors often find themselves combining their old role with new responsibilities. Taking the initiative to learn new skills will not only make it more likely that your present company will want to keep you on board, it also enhances your value if you do wind up on the job market.&#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=red&gt;Focus on the team:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  While skills are required to get the job done, communication and a positive attitude are just as important. Don't just focus on what your specific tasks involve. Think about the company's mission and goals and always be on the alert for new ways that you can contribute. As well, try to motivate and assist your coworkers. A proactive attitude and strong team spirit are qualities that can make you indispensable. &#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=red&gt;Think long-term:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  When faced with cutbacks, it's tempting to start thinking about the company's goals as a short-term proposition. While doing so may seem practical, it also sends a message to management that you don't have faith in the company's future. A blend of short-term practicality and long-term planning is a better approach. &#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=red&gt;Make your boss look good:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Chances are, your immediate boss, or his/her supervisor, will be the person who has to make the uncomfortable choices about which employees in your department are vital - and which ones are expendable. While they will be keeping the company's best interests in mind during that process, they are sure to have their own best interests in mind as well. By understanding what your boss needs to look good in the eyes of higher-ups and delivering on that, you can position yourself as an important team player on both a departmental and company-wide scale. In addition, if your work helps ensure that your boss manages to survive the layoffs, the odds of your survival will increase in turn. &#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=red&gt;Be visible:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  Some people think that, by being unnoticed in their day-to-day work, they'll also go unnoticed when layoff lists are being drawn up. Typically, the opposite is true. If your manager doesn't know what you are contributing to the company on a daily basis, they won't have a justification for keeping you on board. Brag a bit! Don't assume that your manager is aware of all the details of your projects - make sure by providing them with e-mailed progress reports and casual chats that highlight your work and enthusiasm. &#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=red&gt;Don't be a gossip:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  Staying plugged in to the office rumor mill is definitely important, as is socializing with a broad range of people from around the company. Doing so can help you keep abreast of potential changes before they impact. However, spreading negative rumors, especially with a personal slant, will do nothing to enhance your own reputation. Steer clear of malicious gossip that can harm the company's team spirit and avoid spending too much time with those who indulge in such rumors. The simplest rule of thumb is just like in kindergarten - if you can't say something nice about a person, it's often better to say nothing at all. &#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=red&gt;Make it your job:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  Refusing to take on new challenges and opportunities can make a manager think twice about how you'll fare in a post-layoff company where job roles may merge to compensate for the missing staff. When possible, adopt a positive attitude towards new responsibilities - it's a chance to expand your skill set and prove your versatility. If you are really too swamped, make sure that your manager understands that it is a matter of priorities, not your disinterest in taking on new tasks&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>406540B2-29DC-4B8B-A889-77FC35CA65A5</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-03-15T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Layoff Proof - Strategies for Survival </title>
</post>
