<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>One of TEKsystems largest Insurance clients is looking for Sr. Java developers for contract and fulltime opportunities starting in January 2011.  Candidates must have at least seven years of development experience in a Java/J2EE environment and need to be experienced in the entire SDLC.&#xD;
&#xD;
Especially JSF experience&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Summary&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
To perform system and programming requirements analyses for a Commercial Lines Property, J2EE application in order to identify noted problems and propose solutions including programming specifications. Under general supervision, to develop system specifications, code, change, test and debug computer programs as assigned and within target time frames.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Principal Duties and Responsibilities (*Essential Functions):&#xD;
&#xD;
1.            To improve and/or develop computer systems in order to meet users' needs by finding solutions, solving complex or moderately complex problems, making estimates concerning work to be done, programming, testing, debugging and documenting systems.&#xD;
&#xD;
2.            To take part in all project phases to ensure project completion by co-operating with and offering advice to users, meeting deadlines and communicating status reports.&#xD;
&#xD;
3.            To apply the SDLC (System Development Life Cycle) development methodology adopted by Intact Financial Corporation to ensure that established standards are met.&#xD;
&#xD;
4.            To provide on-call support for production systems to guarantee their functionality.&#xD;
&#xD;
5.            To make sure that systems are optimal and meet the quality standards of the business area by making analyses, suggestions and developing assessments.&#xD;
&#xD;
6.            To make recommendations in order to participate in improving development and system maintenance processes.&#xD;
&#xD;
To provide technical assistance to the Application Development junior staff.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Meghan Stewart Technical Recruiter&#xD;
150 York St. Suite 1206, Toronto, Ontario, M5H 3S5&#xD;
877.342.5004  T 416.342.5032 F 416.342.5070  M 416-316-6174&#xD;
&#xD;
http://www.teksystems.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
cid:image002.gif@01CA1B53.4A4AEBE0</content>
    <postId>40C89D01-FB25-47BD-879F-E14C6AF14912</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-12-11T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Java developers for contract and fulltime opportunities</title>
</post>
