<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2010-03-26T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>http://www.ca.gi-de.com/ This is a fantastic company that is sooo close my home, but I couldn't apply unfortunately.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>One of TEKsystems’ financial clients in the Toronto area is currently seeking a full time Java Developer to join their team. The successful candidate will be responsible for the design, development and testing of enterprise-level financial software products. The solution includes, but not limited to, enterprise application developments, smart client application, web application and database application development.  &#xD;
 &#xD;
Duties and Responsibilities:&#xD;
 &#xD;
·         Understand Stakeholder Requirements and overall product architecture.&#xD;
·         Provide effort estimates for assigned components&#xD;
·         Design, implement, unit test assigned components of the product and integrate with components developed by other team members.&#xD;
·         Resolve problems arising during various phases of the development&#xD;
·         Create proof of concepts (PoCs) to validate design assumptions&#xD;
·         Participate in Software Development process improvement activities&#xD;
·         Help drive a culture of professionalism and continuous improvement&#xD;
 &#xD;
Qualifications and Skills:&#xD;
 &#xD;
·         Bachelors or Masters Degree in Computer Science or a related discipline.&#xD;
·         5+ years of experience with Java technologies and frameworks (EJB, JMS, JMX, Servlet, Design Patterns, Web Containers, Web Services, Ajax, Hibernate, Spring)&#xD;
·         Solid experience with J2EE Application Servers preferably WebSphere&#xD;
·         Strong object oriented analysis, design and development skills &#xD;
·         Experience with RDBMS technology (Oracle, SQL Server, DB2) &#xD;
·         Familiarity with ERP and/or GL Systems&#xD;
·         Experience with performance tuning of J2EE/Database components&#xD;
·         Strong troubleshooting and debugging skills with distributed multi-tier applications&#xD;
·         Experience with Eclipse integrated development environment (IDE) including ANT and JUnit.&#xD;
·         Experience with industry standard version control and defect management tools&#xD;
·         Good understanding of software development methodologies&#xD;
·         Excellent written and verbal communication and interpersonal skills, and a passion for delivering high quality software required.&#xD;
·         Able to focus on key deliverables in a fast-paced development environment&#xD;
·         A self-starter who can co-ordinate with a team, yet work independently towards a common goal&#xD;
 &#xD;
If you are interested in this opportunity please contact me as soon as possible. As well, if you could send me an updated word version resume, that would be great. If you are unavailable at this time, but do know of someone who would be interested, please feel free to pass along my contact information. Thanks in advance for your time.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 Nicole Padfield PROFESSIONAL RECRUITER LEAD&#xD;
350 Burnhamthorpe Rd. W, Mississauga, ON, L5B 3J1&#xD;
800.254.0778 T 905.283.1327&#xD;
F 905.283.1390 &#xD;
Wednesday and Thursdays (519) 707-1010 or &#xD;
1-877-707-1080 ext. 1010</content>
    <postId>437F9449-A99E-405F-912E-C7C31312950F</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Permanent Java Developer Job Opportunity</title>
</post>
