<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This is LONG TERM, and a LONG requirement...please read carefully...we WILL need to have references as well....&#xD;
&#xD;
TxMQ Direct Client Requirement  Front End J2EE/Websphere developer&#xD;
Location:  Fort Worth, TX&#xD;
Number of positions to fill:   2&#xD;
REFERENCES WILL BE REQUIRED (Min 2 up to 3 refs)&#xD;
Duration:   1.5 years&#xD;
Rate:  UP TO 60-65/hour c2c….less for w2&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Detail:&#xD;
Candidate will have a broad knowledge and experience level with the core technologies used to render web sites and web application User Interfaces including HTML/XHTML, Javascript, and Cascading Stylesheets. Additionally they have a strong understanding of the server side technologies often used to generate the markup that is delivered to a User Agent (browser), for example Struts/Tiles, Spring, JSP, ASP, etc. They also are involved with implementing coding best practices so that web sites and web pages are produced using Semantic markup that is Accessible, Performs and follows a strategy of Progressive Enhancements so as to make the site/application available to the largest audience of user agents (ie: browsers, screen readers etc) through the incorporation of cascading style sheets for site theming and scripting to manipulate the DOM.&#xD;
&#xD;
Candidate requires minimal supervision and is relatively autonomous in all aspects of assigned work. May supervise lower level developers acting as a team lead or checking other developers' work. Typically reports to a department manager or project manager. May be responsible for training new team members.&#xD;
&#xD;
Skills Grid:--REQUIRED…Please fill in per the example below!&#xD;
Skill:  The area/skill we are asking you about&#xD;
Self Rating:  Self Rating from 0-5 (for this, tell us how strong you feel you are, with 0 meaning you do not have the skill, and 5 meaning you are an expert&#xD;
Years of experience:  Best estimate for how many years you have using this skill HANDS ON please.&#xD;
Example:&#xD;
Skill           |       Self Rating     |       Years of Experience&#xD;
.Net                  |  I am a 4 out of 5      |       I have 5 years of experience&#xD;
===========|================|=============================&#xD;
Agile Methodology&#xD;
Ajax *&#xD;
College Degree *&#xD;
       Yes&#xD;
CSS *&#xD;
Eclipse&#xD;
EJB&#xD;
Experience with enterprise web-based applications&#xD;
Hibernate&#xD;
HTML *&#xD;
J2EE *&#xD;
Java Messaging Service (JMS) *&#xD;
JavaScript *&#xD;
JDBC (Oracle)&#xD;
JSP *&#xD;
Object Oriented Analysis&#xD;
Object Oriented Methodologies&#xD;
Oracle&#xD;
Parasoft Test Suite&#xD;
Spring&#xD;
Struts/Struts 2 *&#xD;
Web Design *&#xD;
Web Development *&#xD;
Websphere Application Server *&#xD;
XML&#xD;
Does Contractor Need Their Own Laptop?&#xD;
       Yes&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Chuck Fried&#xD;
716-636-0070 ext 22&#xD;
Cell:  716-998-4665&#xD;
http://www.txmq.com&#xD;
&#xD;
Middleware solutions and staff augmentation services including permanent and temporary placements&#xD;
&#xD;
Follow me on Twitter:   www.twitter.com/chuckfried&#xD;
&#xD;
On Facebook www.facebook.com/chuckfried&#xD;
&#xD;
Look for me on LinkedIn!</content>
    <postId>439416EE-3B1F-4FF0-84AB-39A0C16DAD2B</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-12-04T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>1.5 year long project in Dallas-j2ee developer</title>
</post>
