<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권경화</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Kyeonghwa (Fred),&#xD;
&#xD;
We currently have an opportunity open that I believe could be a great match to your skillset.&#xD;
&#xD;
25376 Technical Lead - Storage Management Applications&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is a small company driving a shift to a new class of high performance storage solutions for medium and large enterprises.  As part of their growing team they are looking to bring on a Technical Lead for Storage Management Applications.  This person will be responsible for providing technical leadership to a team of software designers in the development of a new class of enterprise storage solutions.  This successful candidate for this position:&#xD;
&#xD;
o Participates in establishing product requirement specifications&#xD;
o Independently investigates and proposes solutions to fulfill requirements&#xD;
o Participates in system design activities&#xD;
o Leads and writes system design specifications&#xD;
o Leads a team of software designers in detailed design and implementation&#xD;
o Leads System Integration with teams of software designers&#xD;
o Establishes and leads software engineering and quality practices&#xD;
&#xD;
Must Haves:&#xD;
Experience in Development, specifically Product Development (&gt; 10 years)&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience in OO Analysis, Design, and Programming (Java, C++) (5 - 7 years)&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience in Web 2.0 and management applications (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience in client/server architecture (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience in enterprise grade applications and/or web applications in a UNIX/Linux environment including: TCP/IP networking, client-server architecture, multi process/thread programming and GUI interface development (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience with Storage Management - ISCI, SAN, NAS (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
Completion of a Bachelor’s degree in Electrical Engineering/Computer Science (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
Nice to Haves:&#xD;
- Experience working on the development of a storage product&#xD;
- Experience in a Team Lead capacity&#xD;
&#xD;
Entrepreneurial and technology driven company - high energy and fun environment well suited for an enthusiastic person driven to help achieve exciting business solutions&#xD;
&#xD;
Length: Permanent&#xD;
Salary: Min: $95,000.00  Max: $105,000.00&#xD;
Approximate start date: ASAP&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested in this opportunity, please fill out an online application or respond directly to this email. I may also be reached by voice mail, however my response time is generally quicker via email.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you know someone that may be interested please feel free to pass this along to them. Si Systems offers a $500 referral bonus to anyone referred to us not already in our system that we manage to place on contract.&#xD;
&#xD;
Best regards,&#xD;
Aaron Brown&#xD;
Recruiter&#xD;
Si Systems - Vancouver&#xD;
604 669-1387 ext.234&#xD;
&#xD;
We Make the Match!!</content>
    <postId>43FFC6E0-56B7-423A-81E6-053300BEE553</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-09-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Lead - Storage Management Applications</title>
</post>
