<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>the opportunity&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client has built a future friendly national team, one that embraces change and initiates opportunity, has a passion for growth, believes in spirited teamwork and has the courage to innovate. Our success is based as much on the dedication and hard work of our team as it is on the innovative wireless solutions we offer.&#xD;
&#xD;
Our commitment to providing our clients with unsurpassed coverage, cool phones, great rates and outstanding client care, is what we're all about. Join our team of wireless professionals working in one of Canada's fastest-growing industries and make your future friendly too.&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Overview:&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is looking for qualified and seasoned professionals to fill numerous Sr. Programmer Analyst positions in our Information Systems Development team in Scarborough. As a Sr. Programmer Analyst, you will provide technical leadership, analysis, design, development, testing, deployment, documentation, and application support for the systems and projects related to the support of our internal business partner. &#xD;
&#xD;
Our current Sr. Programmer Analyst opportunities are available in the following areas:&#xD;
&#xD;
·Systems for Application Infrastructure and Standards&#xD;
·Systems for Sales and Distribution&#xD;
·Systems for Client Operations&#xD;
·Systems for HR&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
·Design, develop, implement and test new applications and other system components in a Solaris environment. &#xD;
·Responsibilities also include application support, problem solving, infrastructure software installation, configuration, testing, deployment and performance tuning.&#xD;
·Review all programs, applications and system designs to manage the appropriate use of standardized components and approve development of new ones as required. &#xD;
·Support performance tuning and system availability and co-ordinate stress testing with both end-users, third party vendors and quality assurance groups. &#xD;
·Manage projects and implement systems with excellent attention to detail. &#xD;
·Support the co-ordination of the IT resourcing of DBA's, IT operations and Change Management. &#xD;
·Support IT operations in the ongoing operations of these environments in production including incident resolution and root-cause analysis. &#xD;
·Support IT operations by pro-actively assessing server and application performance. &#xD;
·Provide support documentation and training for operations.&#xD;
&#xD;
qualifications&#xD;
&#xD;
Education and Experience&#xD;
&#xD;
·Min. 5 years of previous development experience in a business driven information systems environment, preferably within the telecommunications industry. &#xD;
·Demonstrated knowledge of Internet infrastructure and e-Business application design, development, testing and implementation. &#xD;
·Excellent knowledge of a formal Systems Development Life Cycle methodology. &#xD;
·Detailed knowledge and experience with J2EE standards and architecture.  &#xD;
·Highly skilled in and practical experience with Java, WebLogic, Message Broker, Java, C/C++, Perl, SQL, RDBMS, Oracle &#xD;
·Undergraduate degree in Computer Science or related subject area or equivalent work experience &#xD;
·Strong presentation and training skills/experience in coaching and mentoring of other team membersFunctional Competencies&#xD;
·Demonstrated problem solving and analytical skills. &#xD;
·Takes initiative, self-directed, and able to adapt readily to fast paced change &#xD;
·Excellent organizational, planning and communication skills, capable of managing a large number of tasks and indirectly, resources &#xD;
·Excellent understanding of the application of information technology to support business processes &#xD;
·Excellent written and verbal communication skills - in both technical and non-technical environments is critical &#xD;
·Demonstrated ability to facilitate meetings and negotiations on deliverables, timelines and resourcing of projects &#xD;
·Proficient with personal computer productivity tools such as Microsoft Office, MS Project and technical design tools including Visio, and Rational Rose.Core Competencies&#xD;
·Takes action to align systems design with strategic priorities &#xD;
·Ensures that system designs support reliable, scalable, secure, and flexible solutions &#xD;
·Demonstrates support for corporate and business unit strategic direction &#xD;
·Uses communication approaches that are effective and appropriate &#xD;
·Strong inter-personal skills and team player &#xD;
·Facilitate joint requirements definition &#xD;
·Find creative solutions to end-users' problems&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Matt Zweig&#xD;
Client Sales and Solutions &#xD;
Pegasus Consulting Inc. &#xD;
matt@pegsoft.com &#xD;
WWW.pegsoft.com &lt;http://WWW.pegsoft.com&gt; &#xD;
416-488-7007 X 232 (local) &#xD;
877-688-8818 X 232 (Toll Free) &#xD;
55 Eglinton Avenue East, Suite 208 &#xD;
Toronto, ON&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>44123EC6-7249-4C9D-A5FA-8A8943E56220</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-08-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Programmer Analyst </title>
</post>
