<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello! My name is Jeff Vainio, I am a Technical Recruiter with PROCOM in Toronto. I am conducting a search for a client of ours in Toronto for a Sr. J2EE Developer/Team Lead for a 6 month contract. Please read the description below and if you are interested, please send me a resume in WORD format. No phone calls please, only suitable candidates will be contacted. THANK YOU! &#xD;
&#xD;
Position: J2EE Sr. Developer/Lead &#xD;
&#xD;
Required: The incumbent will be part of a team, designing, specifying and developing applications under a J2EE environment. &#xD;
&#xD;
The incumbent will: &#xD;
-Understand and translate business requirements into Design and Specification &#xD;
-Lead and mentor small development teams to develop applications. &#xD;
-Assist and code complex functionalities &#xD;
-Document the developed applications and code such that the code is maintainable. &#xD;
-Support applications during their initial deployment phase with application enhancements and bug fixes. &#xD;
&#xD;
Requirement: &#xD;
-J2SE (Java 2 Standard Edition) Senior &#xD;
-JDBC &#xD;
-J2EE (Java 2 Enterprise Edition) Senior &#xD;
-Session beans / Entity beans / Message beans &#xD;
-Security &#xD;
-JMS &#xD;
-XML (SAX, DOM, XSL) &#xD;
-JSP, Servlets &#xD;
-Experience with databases(ORACLE) and knowledge of SQL. &#xD;
&#xD;
Tools / miscellaneous / concepts &#xD;
-CVS &#xD;
-Unix &#xD;
-Design Patterns &#xD;
-Ant &#xD;
-UML &#xD;
-XML &#xD;
-Jakarta Struts &#xD;
-Experience in the financial services industry &#xD;
-1-2 years of previous experience as a team-lead for a J2EE project. Strong people skills is a must. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Nice to have: &#xD;
&#xD;
-Eclipse &#xD;
-JUnit &#xD;
-WebLogic &#xD;
-Oracle &#xD;
-Previous J2EE Team Lead experience in a Banking Environment &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Location: Downtown Toronto &#xD;
Duration: 6 months &#xD;
Rate/Salary: $75/hr (if Incorporated as a contractor) &#xD;
Start Date: ASAP &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
PROCOM SERVICES &#xD;
A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 1200 consultants on assignment. For over 20 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our consultants. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and consultants consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice. &#xD;
&#xD;
We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further. NO PHONE CALLS PLEASE &#xD;
&#xD;
Please submit your most recent resume to: &#xD;
&#xD;
Jeff Vainio &#xD;
Technical Recruiter &#xD;
PROCOM &#xD;
JeffV@Procom.ca </content>
    <postId>4479B5B6-9BCA-4A3F-8231-A283A23707A5</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-09-09T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2EE Sr. Developer/Lead </title>
</post>
