<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Role 1 - RBC  (1202020) &#xD;
 &#xD;
 Knowledge of CM business is bonus but not required.  Candidate will be responsible for&#xD;
- Developing JMS interfaces to our client repository system, which is a database&#xD;
&#xD;
- Encapsulate JDBC calls into JMS calls&#xD;
&#xD;
- Expose JMS as a web service onto the Enterprise Service Bus (ESB)&#xD;
&#xD;
- Process all service requests and return acknowledgement &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Role 2 Citibank&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
We are seeking C++ Software Developers with a BS in Computer Science, Engineering, or related field, with 3-5 years of financial services industry experience to support a credit risk technology organization. Strong programming skills in C++, Java, and SQL; knowledge of Perl and/or Excel a plus. Ideal candidate will have an aptitude for math and analytical problem solving. Experience in distributed computing and/or financial modeling a strong plus. Responsibilities include: all phases of software development on product, analytics calculation engine, and distributed computation infrastructure; investigation and resolution of client issues; working with Risk managers to specify and design new functionality; interfacing with other groups in the firm.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
•       Design and develop credit risk platform components in distributed grid environment&#xD;
&#xD;
•       Provide end to end platform integration testing including developing regression test scripts&#xD;
&#xD;
•       Provide application support for the OTC counterparty credit risk system&#xD;
&#xD;
•       Provide support to the Credit Risk Analytics for analyzing numerical problems&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
CANDIDATE QUALIFICATIONS&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
•       Minimum 3-5 years of hands on software development experiences in financial services organization&#xD;
&#xD;
•       Strong C++ design and development skills with knowledge of  design patterns and application architecture, experience with multi-threaded programming is a plus&#xD;
&#xD;
•       Java/J2EE design and development experience with Web applications and Databases is highly desired&#xD;
&#xD;
•       Proven analytical and problem solving skills&#xD;
&#xD;
•       Must be able to communicate and interact effectively with clients, project manager and IT stakeholders&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Priyanka Mehandiratta&#xD;
&#xD;
Resource Manager&#xD;
&#xD;
Ajilon Consulting&#xD;
&#xD;
10 Bay Street, Seventh Floor&#xD;
&#xD;
Toronto, Ontario M5J2RB&#xD;
&#xD;
Direct # 416- 941-5988</content>
    <postId>44F46511-0074-45C6-9E4F-525204196172</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[Contract] Banking - RBC &amp; Citibank</title>
</post>
