<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>심성준</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;a href="http://cibc.njoyn.com/cibc/xweb/Xweb.asp?tbtoken=bFxbR1USNxtzYnR1TFRJZiY6BHldcVQpb1wnW1sRDBBaXzccUUoedGQuJS5ALiRePApRXRdQQD5l&amp;chk=dFlbQBJf&amp;page=jobdetails&amp;jobid=J0411-0571&amp;clid=49229&amp;lang=1&amp;brid=537364"&gt;Advisory Application Developer (J2EE, WebLogic)&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Job Number:  J0411-0571 &#xD;
Job Type:  Full Time &#xD;
Category:  Information Technology &#xD;
City:  Toronto, Ontario, Canada &#xD;
Job Location:  595 Bay Street 14th Floor &#xD;
Posting Date:  April 19, 2011 &#xD;
Expiry Date:  April 30, 2011 &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;hr/&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Business Unit Description:&#xD;
&#xD;
Technology: responsible for the delivery of technology in support of all CIBC businesses and customers. Directly aligns to CIBC's businesses, with a technology team for each business. Delivers world class solutions in support of business strategies, through a combination of in-house systems development and working with leading technology partners. This group also manages CIBC's core computing facilities, telecommunications and networks globally.&#xD;
&#xD;
Retail Markets Technology: plans, delivers and supports end-to-end technology solutions for the various distribution channels and full range of products that service all of CIBC's Retail clients: CIBC's retail branch network, Internet, Automated Banking Machines (ABM's), telephone banking, credit products, GICs, Deposit Accounts, Global Payments and Wealth Management/Investment Products. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Career Overview:&#xD;
&#xD;
PURPOSE OF JOB:&#xD;
&#xD;
Lead the technical design, development and integration of cross-functional, multi-platform application systems.&#xD;
&#xD;
MAJOR ACTIVITIES:&#xD;
&#xD;
• Analyze, define and document requirements for data, workflow, logical processes, hardware and operating system environment, interface with other systems, internal and external checks, controls, and outputs.&#xD;
• Provide estimates for assigned work packages to support the development of time tables and project plans; analyze and estimate feasibility, cost, time, and compatibility with hardware and other programs. Ensure that expected application performance levels are achieved.&#xD;
• Coordinate coding, testing , implementation, integration and documentation of solution. Develop program specifications.&#xD;
• Perform complex applications programming activities. Code, test, debug, document, maintain, and modify complex applications programs. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Requirements:&#xD;
&#xD;
KNOWLEDGE/SKILL REQUIREMENTS:&#xD;
&#xD;
Extensive Work Experience:&#xD;
• Managing Multiple Priorities--Ability to manage multiple concurrent objectives, projects, groups or activities. effective judgment in prioritizing and time allocation.&#xD;
• Application Delivery Process--Knowledge of major tasks, deliverables, formal methodologies and disciplines for delivering new or enhanced.&#xD;
• Presentations--Ability to present information to groups with the appropriate degree of formality.&#xD;
• Interpersonal Relationships--Knowledge of approaches, tools and techniques for working with individuals and groups in a constructive and collaborative manner.&#xD;
• Consulting--Knowledge of approaches, tools, techniques and roles and responsibilities in providing technical or business guidance to clients within and outside own area.&#xD;
• Conflict Management--Knowledge of tools and techniques for anticipating, recognizing and effectively dealing with existing or potential conflicts at the individual, group or situation level.&#xD;
• Decision Making and Critical Thinking--Knowledge of tools and techniques for effective use of a broad range of factors, assumptions, frameworks and perspectives when solving problems.&#xD;
&#xD;
Work Experience:&#xD;
• Team Management and Team Building--Ability to form, build and manage effective teams.&#xD;
• Relationship Management--Ability to establish and build healthy working relations and partnerships with clients, vendors and peers.&#xD;
&#xD;
CONTACTS: &#xD;
&#xD;
• Peers and middle to senior management including end-users.&#xD;
&#xD;
JOB COMPLEXITIES/CHALLENGES:&#xD;
&#xD;
• Analyzing project and/or technical risk, using available information, to support business recommendations.&#xD;
• Analyzing business and/ or client processes and practices to identify and recommend opportunities for enhancement.&#xD;
• Interacting with end users and business analysts to gather requirements and prepare design specifications, conducting impact analysis and provide feedback on problems and recommends solutions.&#xD;
• Maintaining an understanding of current project management tools and methods to develop project plans based on the appropriate standards and methodology.&#xD;
• Acting as a team lead for a small team and/or technical solution provider (subject matter expert) for complex application problems. &#xD;
• Providing solutions that potentially impact other dependent projects and applications and the quality of deliverables.&#xD;
• Ensuring that errors are detected to avoid production outages and wrong business decision-making process/regulatory reporting.&#xD;
• May have people management responsibilities (e.g., PMM) for small teams of 3 – 5.&#xD;
&#xD;
Must have:&#xD;
- J2ee (5 years)&#xD;
- Weblogic (2years)&#xD;
- Webservices(3years)&#xD;
- Unix (5years)&#xD;
- Oracle (3years)&#xD;
&#xD;
Education and accrediations:&#xD;
- Related education required: Computer Science, WebServices, Sun certificate&#xD;
&#xD;
PHYSICAL DEMANDS/WORKING CONDITIONS:&#xD;
&#xD;
• Requires carrying a pager.&#xD;
• May be on call 24 / 7 depending on application supported&#xD;
&#xD;
ATTRIBUTES:&#xD;
&#xD;
• Accountability&#xD;
• Teamwork &amp; Partnering&#xD;
• Building Trust&#xD;
• Results Orientation&#xD;
• Service Orientation&#xD;
• Analytic/Systematic Thinking&#xD;
• Communication &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Accountability&#xD;
Analytic/Systematic Thinking&#xD;
Building Trust&#xD;
Communication&#xD;
Problem Solving &amp; Decision Making&#xD;
Results Orientation&#xD;
Service Orientation&#xD;
Teamwork &amp; Partnering&#xD;
Thorough&#xD;
Time &amp; Self Management&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <postId>450C5881-01B5-4B28-8470-95B125DC5B5F</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-04-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>CIBC-Advisory Application Developer (J2EE, WebLogic)</title>
</post>
