<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>황성규</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Job agency에서 제게 온 메일인데 여기다 올립니다. &#xD;
관심있는 분은 Spencer Hwang을 통해 알게되었다고 연락해 보세요. &#xD;
2년반전에 저도 이 에이전트회사를 통해 첫번째 퍼머넌트 잡을 얻었습니다. &#xD;
--------------------------------------------- &#xD;
Dear Spencer: &#xD;
&#xD;
I hope everything is going well with you. I would be happy to hear about your current status and career goals. Please send us your updated resume. This will enable us to look for suitable and challenging positions for you. Urgently, we are looking for a Sr. Unix/Java/Oracle Developer for large financial institution. Following is the details: &#xD;
&#xD;
Position: Sr. Unix/Java/Oracle Developer (VTRAC Job Order #1629) &#xD;
Conpensation: $70K - $80K, depending upon experience + participation in Incentive Pay Program &#xD;
Location: Toronto &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description: &#xD;
This position involves Unix software development as well as support for existing applications in a team setting. The prospective candidate should be experienced with the software development life cycle. Involve and responsible for some of the system design for existing on going enhancements and new system development. Provide day-to-day support for selected brokerage production systems. Support activities include; working with business analyst, user community, 3rd party software vendors and/or other brokerage technical support groups to investigate and resolve problems related to these applications; work on in-house developed applications to debug or enhance their functionality; participate in activities that will improve the stability and operations of the applications. &#xD;
&#xD;
Skill Sets Requirements &#xD;
· Hands-on experience with UNIX systems development for minimum of 6 years (preferably Sun OS &amp; Solaris) &#xD;
· Experienced with relational databases and SQL (preferably Oracle PL/SQL). &#xD;
· Programming knowledge in Java and UNIX shell scripting languages &#xD;
· Ability to develop process and data models and design software components &#xD;
· Write good and high quality and well documented code &#xD;
· Write good and high quality technical documents &#xD;
· Experienced with System development life cycle process &#xD;
· Experienced with version control process (preferably Clearcase) &#xD;
· Experience with web-based development is preferred &#xD;
· Graduate of university with a Computer Science or Engineering degree &#xD;
· Minimum of 8 years of working experience with minimum of 3 years work experience in a finance related field &#xD;
· Willing to perform application support for existing and new applications &#xD;
&#xD;
Personal Attributes &#xD;
· Demonstrated flexibility and initiative. &#xD;
· Excellent analytical &amp; problem solving skills. &#xD;
· Strong interpersonal and communication skills. &#xD;
· Ability to manage multiple tasks in a fast pace work environment. &#xD;
· Self starter and highly motivated. &#xD;
&#xD;
Additional Information: &#xD;
· Successful applicant needs to be available for on-call duties after hours. &#xD;
May need to travel. &#xD;
&#xD;
If you already obtained a position through VTRAC, please disregard this message and kindly forward this message to your friends. &#xD;
&#xD;
Please let us know if you are interested or you know anyone who might be interested in any of these positions. (Your name will remain confidential, and we will have bonus for you). Also, We would appreciate it if you could pass our company’s name and our web site www.vtrac.com to your friends who have strong expertise in JAVA, C++ , VB, database, network and systems administration. &#xD;
&#xD;
Please e-mail your resume as MS-Word attached document in confidence to &#xD;
Krista Ray kristar@vtrac.com (416) 227-9293 ext. 225 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Thank you and best regards, &#xD;
VTRAC IT Consultants Corporation &#xD;
E-Commerce &amp; Client Server Specialists &#xD;
121 Willowdale Ave., Suite 301 &#xD;
North York, Ontario &#xD;
M2N 6A3, Canada &#xD;
www.vtrac.com &#xD;
 &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>4543D2E0-3143-4689-9C68-A0863B6DB6EA</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Job opening: Sr. Unix/Java/Oracle Developer </title>
</post>
