<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Interview Questions&#xD;
&#xD;
2005-01-11&#xD;
&#xD;
A LIST OF TESTED QUESTIONS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	WARM-UP QUESTIONS&#xD;
·	WORK HISTORY&#xD;
·	JOB PERFORMANCE&#xD;
·	EDUCATION&#xD;
·	CAREER GOALS&#xD;
·	SELF-ASSESSMENT&#xD;
·	CREATIVITY&#xD;
·	DECISIVENESS&#xD;
·	RANGE OF INTERESTS&#xD;
·	MOTIVATION&#xD;
·	WORK STANDARDS&#xD;
·	LEADERSHIP&#xD;
·	ORAL PRESENTATION SKILLS&#xD;
·	WRITTEN COMMUNICATION SKILLS&#xD;
·	FLEXIBILITY&#xD;
·	STRESS TOLERANCE&#xD;
·	STABILITY &amp; MATURITY&#xD;
·	INTEREST IN SELF DEVELOPMENT&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
WARM-UP QUESTIONS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What made you apply for this position?&#xD;
·	How did you hear about this job opening?&#xD;
·	Briefly, would you summarize your work history &amp; education for me?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
WORK HISTORY&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What special aspects of your work experience have prepared you for this job?&#xD;
·	Can you describe for me one or two of your most important accomplishments?&#xD;
·	How much supervision have you typically received in your previous job?&#xD;
·	Describe for me one or two of the biggest disappointments in your work &#xD;
      history?&#xD;
·	Why are you leaving your present job? (or, Why did you leave your last job?)&#xD;
·	What is important to you in a company? What things do you look for in an &#xD;
      Organization?&#xD;
&#xD;
JOB PERFORMANCE&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Everyone has strengths &amp; weaknesses as workers. What are your strong points &#xD;
      for this job?&#xD;
·	What would you say are areas needing improvement?&#xD;
·	How did your supervisor on your most recent job evaluate your job &#xD;
·	performance? What were some of the good points &amp; bad points of that rating?&#xD;
·	When you have been told , or discovered for yourself , a problem in your job &#xD;
      performance, what have you typically done? Can you give me an example?&#xD;
·	Do you prefer working alone or in groups?&#xD;
·	What kind of people do you find it most difficult to work with? Why?&#xD;
·	Starting with your last job, tell me about any of your achievements that &#xD;
      were recognized by your superiors.&#xD;
·	Can you give me an example of your ability to manage or supervise others?&#xD;
·	What are some things you would like to avoid in a job? Why?&#xD;
·	In your previous job what kind of pressures did you encounter?&#xD;
·	What would you say is the most important thing you are looking for in a job?&#xD;
·	What are some of the things on your job you feel you have done particularly &#xD;
      well or in which you have achieved the greatest success? Why do you feel &#xD;
      this way?&#xD;
·	What were some of the things about your last job that you found most &#xD;
      difficult to do?&#xD;
·	What are some of the problems you encounter in doing your job? Which one &#xD;
      frustrates you the most? What do you usually do about it?&#xD;
·	What are some things you particularly liked about your last job?&#xD;
·	Do you consider your progress on the job representative of your ability? &#xD;
·	Why?&#xD;
·	How do you feel about the way you &amp; others in the department were managed by &#xD;
      your supervisor?&#xD;
·	If I were to ask your present (most recent) employer about your ability as &#xD;
      a____________________, what would he/she say?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
EDUCATION&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What special aspects of your education or training have prepared you for &#xD;
       this job?&#xD;
·	What courses in school have been of most help in doing your job?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
CAREER- GOALS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What is your long-term employment or career objective?&#xD;
·	What kind of job do you see yourself holding five years from now?&#xD;
·	What do you feel you need to develop in terms of skill &amp; knowledge in order &#xD;
       to be ready for that opportunity?&#xD;
·	Why might you be successful in such a job?&#xD;
·	How does this job fit in with your overall career goals?&#xD;
·	Who or what in your life would you say influenced you most with your career &#xD;
      objectives?&#xD;
·	Can you pinpoint any specific things in your past experience that affected &#xD;
       your present career objectives?&#xD;
·	What would you most like to accomplish if you had this job?&#xD;
·	What might make you leave this job?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
SELF-ASSESSMENT&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What kind of things do you feel most confident in doing?&#xD;
·	Can you describe for me a difficult obstacle you have had to overcome? How &#xD;
      did you handle it? How do you feel this experience affected your personality &#xD;
      or ability?&#xD;
·	How would you describe yourself as a person?&#xD;
·	What do you think are the most important characteristics &amp; abilities a &#xD;
       person must possess to become a successful ( )? How do you rate yourself in &#xD;
       these areas?&#xD;
·	Do you consider yourself a self-starter? If so, explain why ( and give &#xD;
      examples)&#xD;
·	What do you consider to be your greatest achievements to date? Why?&#xD;
·	What things give you the greatest satisfaction at work?&#xD;
·	What things frustrate you the most? How do you usually cope with them?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
CREATIVITY&#xD;
&#xD;
·	In your work experience, what have you done that you consider truly &#xD;
      creative?&#xD;
·	Can you think of a problem you have encountered when the old solutions &#xD;
      didn't work &amp; when you came up with new solutions?&#xD;
·	Of your creative accomplishments big or small , at work or home, what gave &#xD;
       you the most satisfaction?&#xD;
·	What kind of problems have people recently called on you to solve? Tell me &#xD;
       what you have devised.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
DECISIVENESS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Do you consider yourself to be thoughtful, analytical or do you usually make &#xD;
      up your mind fast? Give an example. (Watch time taken to respond)&#xD;
·	What was your most difficult decision in the last six months? What made it &#xD;
      difficult?&#xD;
·	The last time you did not know what decision to make, what did you do?&#xD;
·	How do you go about making an important decision affecting your career?&#xD;
·	What was the last major problem that you were confronted with? What action &#xD;
      did you take on it?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
RANGE OF INTERESTS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What organizations do you belong to?&#xD;
·	Tell me specifically what you do in the civic activities in which you &#xD;
      participate. (Leading questions in selected areas. i.e. sports, economics, &#xD;
      current events, finance.)&#xD;
·	How do you keep up with what's going on in your company / your industry/ &#xD;
      your profession?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
MOTIVATION&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What is your professional goal?&#xD;
·	Can you give me examples of experience on the job that you felt were &#xD;
      satisfying?&#xD;
·	Do you have a long &amp; short-term plan for your department? Is it realistic?&#xD;
·	Did you achieve it last year?&#xD;
·	Describe how you determine what constitutes top priorities in the &#xD;
      performance of your job.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
WORK STANDARDS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What are your standards of success in your job?&#xD;
·	In your position, how would you define doing a good job? On what basis was &#xD;
      your definition determined?&#xD;
·	When judging the performance of your subordinate, what factors or &#xD;
       characteristics are most important to you?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
LEADERSHIP&#xD;
&#xD;
·	In your present job what approach do you take to get your people together to &#xD;
      establish a common approach to a problem?&#xD;
·	What approach do you take in getting your people to accept your ideas or &#xD;
      department goals?&#xD;
·	What specifically do you do to set an example for your employees?&#xD;
·	How frequently do you meet with your immediate subordinates as a group?&#xD;
·	What sort of leader do your people feel you are? Are you satisfied?&#xD;
·	How do you get people who do not want to work together to establish a common &#xD;
      approach to a problem?&#xD;
·	If you do not have much time &amp; they hold seriously differing views, what &#xD;
      would be your approach?&#xD;
·	How would you describe your basic leadership style? Give specific examples &#xD;
      of how you practice this?&#xD;
·	Do you feel you work more effectively on a one to one basis or in a group &#xD;
      situation?&#xD;
·	Have you ever led a task force or committee or any group who doesn't report &#xD;
      to you, but from whom you have to get work? How did you do it? What were the &#xD;
      satisfactions &amp; disappointments? How would you handle the job differently?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
ORAL PRESENTATION SKILLS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Have you ever done any public or group speaking? Recently? Why? How did it &#xD;
      go?&#xD;
·	Have you made any individual presentations recently? How did you prepare?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
WRITTEN COMMUNICATION SKILLS&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Would you rather write a report or give a verbal report? Why?&#xD;
·	What kind of writing have you done? For a group? For an individual?&#xD;
·	What is the extent of your participation in major reports that have to be &#xD;
      written?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
FLEXIBILITY&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What was the most important idea or suggestion you received recently from &#xD;
      your employees? What happened as a result?&#xD;
·	What do you think about the continuous changes in company operating policies &#xD;
      &amp; procedures?&#xD;
·	How effective has your company been in adapting its policies to fit a &#xD;
      changing environment?&#xD;
·	What was the most significant change made in your company in the last six &#xD;
      months which directly affected you, &amp; how successfully do you think you &#xD;
      implemented this change?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
STRESS TOLERANCE&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Do you feel pressure in your job? Tell me about it.&#xD;
·	What has been the highest pressure situation you have been under in recent &#xD;
       years? How did you cope with it?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
STABILITY &amp; MATURITY&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Describe your most significant success &amp; failure in the last two years.&#xD;
·	What do you like to do best?&#xD;
·	What do you like to do least?&#xD;
·	What in your last review did your supervisor suggest needed improvement?&#xD;
·	What have you done about it?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
INTEREST IN SELF DEVELOPMENT&#xD;
&#xD;
·	What has been the most important person or event in your own self &#xD;
       development?&#xD;
·	How much of your education did you earn?&#xD;
·	What kind of books &amp; other publications do you read?&#xD;
·	Have you taken a management development course?&#xD;
·	How are you helping your subordinates develop themselves?&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>454A681E-5737-4573-ACB4-D886E35BF37C</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Interview Questions</title>
</post>
