<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>아래 internal job posting에 관심있으신 분은 제게 연락 주시면 감사하겠습니다. 지금 근무하는 회사에서 바로 올라온 따근따근한 내용입니다.&#xD;
416-382-5300 x3438&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Position:		Sr. Unix System Analyst&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:		Trans Canada Credit - Information Systems&#xD;
			3 Concorde Gate, Don Mills&#xD;
&#xD;
Posting Date:	February 28, 2002		Closing Date:  March 8, 2002	  &#xD;
&#xD;
This position is responsible for supporting the Unix network and environment, including installation, maintenance, trouble-shooting and problem-solving, disaster planning, security, upgrades,  future planning of server hardware and software needs.&#xD;
&#xD;
Specific Duties and Responsibilities&#xD;
&#xD;
Performs UNIX environmental planning for projects (including technologies, communication networks, capacities, analysis and implementation).  &#xD;
&#xD;
Conducts internal/external data communications analysis in concert with network analysts, for the design and implementation of a robust UNIX environment.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Co-ordinates and prepares the hardware/software and communications infrastructure documentation.  Provides architectural schematics and descriptions of configurations.  Maintains detailed documentation of server architectures and configurations for the purposes of support and Disaster Recovery.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Monitors and controls the performance and status of all UNIX servers (AIX/Sun Solaris).&#xD;
&#xD;
Maintains and recommends hardware technologies, configurations, and upgrades. Maintains and recommends software technologies, configuration, standards, and evaluations.  Installs and customizes more complex “off the shelf” and “custom-coded” products.  Designs and implements software and hardware configuration.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Provides Disaster Recovery support by maintaining detailed documentation, ensuring back-up systems are operative, and taking disaster recovery into consideration when designing or implementing upgrades.&#xD;
&#xD;
Provides on-call support.&#xD;
&#xD;
Knowledge, Experience, Skills&#xD;
&#xD;
Requires university/college graduate with a minimum of five years of experience in a systems environment at an analyst level, or equivalent work experience.  &#xD;
Certification on AIX  with exposure to MVS is preferred.  &#xD;
Expertise with TCP/IP, HTTP, Websphere.and MQ Series required.  &#xD;
Strong interpersonal, communication, trouble shooting and problem solving skills.  Ability to handle shifting priorities in a frequently changing environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
Qualified candidates should contact Katherine Karbownik at local 5314.&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>45A58B84-DAC5-4F0C-BE37-E55CC0F7663D</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Job opportunity</title>
</post>
