<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>SYSTEM DEVELOPMENT MANAGER&#xD;
Our client requires a System Development Manager to join their headquarters team. Midtown Toronto location with direct access to public transit &amp; freeway. One-year initial contract term, with possibility for extensions.&#xD;
This is a high level position reporting to the Project Manager responsible for software and hardware design, integration, testing, prototyping, pilot implementation and full production implementation enterprise-wide. The client is upgrading/replacing an Automated Vehicle Location (AVL) System composed of individualized voice &amp; radio-based communication units inside a large fleet. The client uses cellular as a backup system to their central data processing centre, along with distributed supervisory centres that respond to emergencies &amp; manage routes &amp; schedules. &#xD;
The system has reached the stage in it’s life cycle where in order to continue to obtain value from it, the client is required to initiate a project to address various system issues in conjunction with major subcomponents &amp; assemblies.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
  &#xD;
Responsibilities of this Role:&#xD;
-System Operation Deficiency Document&#xD;
- RFP to hire a vendor for AVL system software development&#xD;
- Vendor offering analysis documentation&#xD;
- Detailed System Requirements Document&#xD;
- System Functional Specifications and requirements traceability&#xD;
- Detailed design(s) for AVL system software&#xD;
- AVL Life Cycle Replacement Study&#xD;
- Return on investment analysis documentation&#xD;
- AVL system integration study and design documents&#xD;
- System design documentation such as data flow diagrams, flow charts and pseudo code&#xD;
- Code review reports&#xD;
- Project change requests&#xD;
- Other related documentation as assigned&#xD;
 &#xD;
Special Skills &amp; Certifications Required:&#xD;
- Extensive AVL software engineering experience on large scale systems and projects.&#xD;
- Extensive experience leading a large AVL software development project.&#xD;
- Extensive experience with software engineering technologies methodologies and practices as they apply to real time AVL systems.&#xD;
- Extensive knowledge of Geographical Information Systems and tools.&#xD;
- Extensive experience interfacing with proprietary AVL systems and associated software.&#xD;
- AVL software development project experience for fixed route transit agencies.&#xD;
- University degree in computer science.&#xD;
- Master's degree in computer science preferred.&#xD;
- Project Management Professional (PMP) preferred.&#xD;
- Exceptional communication and presentation skills.&#xD;
- Exceptional team leadership and motivational skills.&#xD;
- Demonstrated ability to deliver product on schedule in a fast paced, multi stakeholder environment.&#xD;
- Demonstrated ability to handle multiple priorities and achieve conflict resolution as required.&#xD;
- 10 years minimum programming experience with C++ in a UNIX environment&#xD;
- Expert level in C#&#xD;
- Experience with AIX administration &#xD;
- Previous experience with software engineering and software design methodologies&#xD;
- Expertise with AVL system design and architecture &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Interested Candidates Should Forward Their CV for Immediate Consideration To:&#xD;
Raman Aneja&#xD;
&#xD;
Professional Search &amp; Placement Consultant&#xD;
Noramtec Consultants, Inc.&#xD;
Office 416.972.5065 Cell 416.543.7911 &#xD;
raman@noramtec.com &#xD;
Join my LinkedIn network &#xD;
Click &#xD;
here for all jobs at Noramtec</content>
    <postId>45A5BF32-B307-4A97-BA7C-8432B4105B07</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-09-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SYSTEM DEVELOPMENT MANAGER</title>
</post>
