<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>신민용</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2003-08-14T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>앗, 리더 자격이라 좀 부담이 되지만, 스펙은 일단 좋아보이네요... 신민용씨 감사합니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hello!  My name is Peter Kalafatis, I am a Technical Recruiter with PROCOM in Toronto.  I am conducting a search for a client of ours in Toronto for a Technical Lead for a permanent position.  Please read the description below and if you are interested and qualified, please send me a resume in WORD format.  No phone calls please, only suitable candidates will be contacted.  THANK YOU!&#xD;
&#xD;
Position: Java Technical Lead&#xD;
&#xD;
Required:&#xD;
&#xD;
RESPONSIBILITIES:&#xD;
·	Provide Application Design &amp; Engineering for Loyalty Management Group?s Travel Management Systems during all phases of the system life cycle.&#xD;
·	Complete problem solving, addressing business requirements and providing robust systems design.&#xD;
·	Support and as required lead the application development activity.&#xD;
·	Liaise with Architecture, DB &amp; Integration teams to ensure robust, scalable consistent design.&#xD;
·	Provide technology leadership in an J2EE, Oracle DB with WebLogic in depth knowledge&#xD;
·	Establish unit and end-to-end performance tests and monitoring.  Resolve performance issues in design; support resolution in production environments.&#xD;
&#xD;
	&#xD;
	REQUIREMENTS:&#xD;
·	7-10 years Information Technology experience with progressive roles leading to a Technical Lead capability.&#xD;
·	Travel industry experience strongly preferred.&#xD;
·	Experience with enterprise implementations of J2EE, WebLogic, XML, and Oracle DB.&#xD;
·	Sound knowledge of Software Development and Systems Management Life Cycles for enterprise class systems.  &#xD;
·	Experience with service and capability based system architectures.&#xD;
·	Experience with rules based decisions support systems.&#xD;
·	Strong written and verbal communication skills at all organizational levels&#xD;
·	Flexibility, energy and confidence; ability to drive delivery in dynamic, matrixed organizations.&#xD;
·	University Degree in Computer Sciences or Equivalent&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
	&#xD;
Location: Toronto&#xD;
	&#xD;
Duration: Permanent	&#xD;
&#xD;
Rate/Salary: 70-78k&#xD;
Start Date: ASAP&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
PROCOM SERVICES&#xD;
A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 1200 consultants on assignment. For over 20 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our consultants. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and consultants consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice.&#xD;
&#xD;
Please submit your most recent resume to:&#xD;
&#xD;
Peter Kalafatis&#xD;
peterk@procom.ca&#xD;
www.procom.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>46818A34-8FD8-4781-A5C5-5E03BF3AF877</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-08-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Technical Lead (Permanent) from Procom</title>
</post>
