<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello All...&#xD;
&#xD;
Last Tuesday night I had two friends came over to my summer office, my garage and had very enjoyable night. We'd talked until 1:30 am in the morning. We talked about a lot things such as life, world peace, world cup and etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
It made me think about what I want to do with my life or what I want from my life. Hopefully Tony Robins', well known motivation speaker, summarizes the best.&#xD;
&#xD;
There are 4 essential things and 2 additional ones.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Consistency : good steady job/business/school&#xD;
- Surprise : spice the life, special occasions, horny chatting, hobby&#xD;
- Appreciation : recognition from your friends, peers and ...&#xD;
- connection : persons who could share your success with&#xD;
&#xD;
with above 4 items person could be successful and famous. However success and fame do not guarantee happiness in life. We have seen quite often-unhappy persons with money, power and good career. If I win 5 million dollars coming Saturday, I will be 5 million dollars richer but am I going to be 5 million dollars happier?&#xD;
&#xD;
Funny isn't it. After 5 million dollars then what?. With 5 million dollars I could get a lot of new toys - sport cars, mistress, monster house. It will put me into better position to get what I want but no guarantees. I know I am old enough to know there are no guarantees in life. If money and power are not true elixir of life, then what is it ?&#xD;
&#xD;
It brings additional 2 items from Tony’s suggestions&#xD;
- personal growth : learn something new, does not matter how old you are. Are you    better/wise/stronger whatever than yesterday or last year?&#xD;
- contribution/sharing : share your wealth. Being a bigger man/woman Return your knowledge to society, world peace&#xD;
&#xD;
If there are no personal growth or you're stuck no room to grow. Person will be frustrated and despair. I have also seen a lot happy people without fame and wealth. Why is that ?&#xD;
&#xD;
I believe happiness comes within. Person should enjoy their daily life and small things - nice weather, good food, nice conversation, Java User group. Person should be comfortable with one's life. Let's appreciate small things in life then let's share. Koreans have old saying "When you share the unhappiness it will shrink but when you share the happiness it will double”.&#xD;
 &#xD;
There three items I have promised to delivery to myself.&#xD;
- My personal memoir : I like to complete it about 100 pages memoir and present to my beautiful daughter on her high school graduation day. I like to tell her in the book. What I think of love, money, life, sex, friends and etc. Also what kind of stupid mistakes I made during my life&#xD;
- Baby Journal : there are about 110 days left before my new baby. I am going to write 100-day countdown journal for my unborn baby - very simple daily activities&#xD;
- Kiss : I am going to tell my wife how much I love her and appreciate her every day. I eat at least three times per day. That is my goal. I am going to tell my wife, Dianne - at least three times I love you. I will marry you again and again even my next lives. &#xD;
&#xD;
I was going to write about fulfillment of life and stuffs. But I had written personal action items. Well that's life according to Thomas Lee. c'est la vie&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>4702028F-4630-446E-859E-97F7020F90F1</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>one summer night</title>
</post>
