<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>One of TEKsystems’ clients in the Markham area is currently seeking a full time Senior Java Developer. This client is a leader in selling software as a service in the CRM space. The ideal candidate will have experience delivering applications in a fast paced environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Senior Java Developer Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
•           Provide estimates for development work during project planning&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Design, develop and unit test application components&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Participate in peer reviews of business requirements architectural design&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Interact with the team to ensure design fits in with the larger initiative&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Communicate risks and issues to the team in a timely manner&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Comply with mandated policies and procedures and contribute to procedural improvements&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Qualifications:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
•           5+ years of software development experience&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Solid understanding of OO design principles, patterns and UML&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Experience with Java EE, EJB 2.1 and 3.0, Servlets, JDBC, Hibernate/iBATIS, JMS, Web services&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Experience with DBMS including DB2 or SQL Server&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Solid knowledge of Ant, Eclipse IDE, Subversion, Websphere&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Experience with Solaris and/or Linux&#xD;
&#xD;
•           Any experience with Mule Enterprise Service Bus is an asset&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested in hearing more about this opportunity, please contact me as soon as possible. If you reach my voicemail, please press ‘0’ to have the receptionist page me. In the interim, please also send an updated word version of your resume. If you are unavailable at this time, but do know of someone who would be interested, please feel free to pass along my contact information. Thank you in advance for your time.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Imad Khalil TECHNICAL RECRUITER&#xD;
350 Burnhamthorpe Road West, Suite 700, Mississauga, Ontario, L5B 3J1&#xD;
&#xD;
905.283.1331 Office&#xD;
800.254.0778 Toll Free&#xD;
905.283.1390 Fax&#xD;
&#xD;
WWW.TEKSYSTEMS.CA&#xD;
&#xD;
http://ca.linkedin.com/in/imadk</content>
    <postId>482D89D4-F547-42C3-8100-C34265DCA817</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-06-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>full time Senior Java Developer</title>
</post>
