<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I went through second time father experience last two weeks. It was overwhelming experience. I am not very emotional person. I had witnessed the birth of my second daughter. I did not experience the modern medical science. My wife did the most of the work. We, myself and medical personals, were merely observers. I am not in position to testimony the miracle of birth nor preach how valuable my experience was. Maybe I am still in shocking stage.&#xD;
&#xD;
However I like to express my second coming opportunity. Not too many peoples receive the second chance to reflect the parenthood. I will have the other chance to make the mistakes. I do not think I was wise father. I was hard on my first daughter. There is no manual for fatherhood. Even though there was I did not know how good the manual was.&#xD;
I had the time to think about my mistakes of being a father.&#xD;
&#xD;
I can’t promise you I am going to perfect father. At least I have the opportunity to mess up different ways. &#xD;
&#xD;
Things I am going to try&#xD;
- To write baby journal : It could be good for me to re-exam and  good for my daughter. Good reading materials&#xD;
- I am going to confess my mistakes to my first daughter when I come up with better way to raise my second kid&#xD;
- Be more understandable : meaning patience&#xD;
- I will be more doer than talker&#xD;
- More active role as baby care taker&#xD;
- Spend as much time as possible with the kid&#xD;
- Do it together : playing, answering questions, biking, etc&#xD;
- most of all I will enjoy my fatherhood : having fun&#xD;
- To leave good memory of me &#xD;
&#xD;
Good to be alive.&#xD;
&#xD;
Quote of Parenthood&#xD;
“If you must hold yourself up to your children as an object lesson, hold yourself up as a warning and not an example.”&#xD;
      - George Bernard Shaw&#xD;
  &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>4D0193A3-270C-44F7-AEB2-32C1B74D4683</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-11-19T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Second chance</title>
</post>
