<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I used to think Korean are as smart as American. Yet as a group American had better processes and systems. Now I am going to change my mind. Look what’s happening in America. How stupid Americans are. They just believe blindly what TV and Newspaper are saying /writing. Osama Bin Laden is still alive after 1 ½ year later. How can they destroy Iraq and North Korea. If they start the war, they will pay the price dearly years to come.&#xD;
&#xD;
Brief Summary of what happened in America.&#xD;
&#xD;
Abraham Lincoln had been assassinated by a former confederation major. Was it one person planned it all ? I believe there were the groups of people planned it. Freedom of African American was delayed by at least 50 years.&#xD;
&#xD;
Assassination of John F. Kennedy 1963&#xD;
Assassination of Martin Luther King 1964&#xD;
Assassination of Robert Kennedy 1964&#xD;
What do these sequences imply ?  After John F. Kennedy’s assassination Oswald was a only person got charged. Also Warren commission files could not be disclosure for 50 years. Then disclosure had been stopped for another 25 years. Because those guys associated with the assassination was still alive. Warren Commission : The person investigated the assassination. &#xD;
&#xD;
Background of Kennedy family : produced the first non-WASP &#xD;
                                                 president&#xD;
                    Wanted to change foundation of America&#xD;
                    More freedom to African Americans&#xD;
                    Against the Vietnam war&#xD;
&#xD;
Very similar situation is happening right now.&#xD;
Regular American loved John F. Kennedy but not old power group. It started Hippies movement. Wanted to change what it was but failed and frustrated.&#xD;
*Note : Jesse Jackson was the follower of Martin L. King&#xD;
&#xD;
Nixon : The first president who got impeached from the presidency&#xD;
Why ? not because of Watergate scandal&#xD;
He and Kisinger liked to open the channel with Chinese&#xD;
Old power group did not like it. Old power group owned military manufacturing. Peace talk was only good for regular Joe not for power group.&#xD;
&#xD;
Regan and Bush family &#xD;
- Regan was a former actor then the leader of anti-communist group in Hollywood&#xD;
- Bush senior : former leader of  CIA&#xD;
&#xD;
Clinton and Gore : best economic growth in 30 years &#xD;
                                    American History&#xD;
                   World peace&#xD;
                   Believers of old John F. Kennedy way&#xD;
 &#xD;
Democratic party and Minjoo : for regular Joe&#xD;
Republic party and Hannara : for old power group &#xD;
&#xD;
It will be interesting that compare the American History with Korean. &#xD;
Mr. Park, Mr. Chun to YS vs. Kim Gu, Cho Beong Wok, DJ and &#xD;
                                                    Roh&#xD;
Truman, Eisenhower, Johnson, Regan, Bush vs. Lincoln, &#xD;
                                    Kennedy, Nixon, Clinton&#xD;
  &#xD;
American was and still is controlled by old power group not by American Dream.&#xD;
Now Korea can make the difference of world power. Korea is that big and smart.&#xD;
I believe the power of Internet and wireless. Korean are educated and exposed to new information in speed of the light.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>4E30E598-F188-4776-AC70-EC047BB1BA7B</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Brief History of America : Thomas Lee's Interpretation</title>
</post>
