<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>A little girl: was talking to her teacher about whales.&#xD;
&#xD;
The teacher: said it was physically impossible for a whale to swallow&#xD;
a human because even though it was a very large mammal its throat was very small.&#xD;
&#xD;
The little girl: stated that Jonah was swallowed by a whale.&#xD;
&#xD;
Irritated, the teacher: reiterated that a whale could not swallow a&#xD;
human; it was physically impossible.&#xD;
&#xD;
The little girl: said, "When I get to heaven I will ask Jonah".&#xD;
&#xD;
The teacher: asked, " What if Jonah went to hell?"&#xD;
&#xD;
The little girl: replied, "Then you ask him".&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
A Kindergarten teacher: was observing her classroom of children while&#xD;
they were drawing. She would occasionally walk around to see each&#xD;
child's work.&#xD;
&#xD;
As she got to one little girl who was working diligently, she asked&#xD;
what the drawing was.&#xD;
&#xD;
The girl: replied, "I'm drawing God."&#xD;
&#xD;
The teacher: paused and said, "But no one knows what God looks like."&#xD;
&#xD;
Without missing a beat, or looking up from her drawing, the girl:&#xD;
replied, "They will in a minute."&#xD;
&#xD;
A Sunday school teacher: was discussing the Ten Commandments with her five and six year olds.&#xD;
&#xD;
After explaining the commandment to "honor" thy Father and thy Mother,&#xD;
she asked, "Is there a commandment that teaches us how to treat our brothers and sisters?"&#xD;
&#xD;
Without missing a beat one little boy: (the oldest of a family)&#xD;
answered, "Thou shall not kill."&#xD;
&#xD;
The children had all been photographed, and the teacher was trying to persuade them each to buy a copy of the group picture.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Just think how nice it will be to look at it when you are all grown&#xD;
up and say, 'There's Jennifer, she's a lawyer,' or 'That's  Michael,&#xD;
He's a doctor.'&#xD;
&#xD;
A small voice at the back of the room rang out, "And there's the&#xD;
teacher, She's dead. "&#xD;
&#xD;
A teacher was giving a lesson on the circulation of the blood. Trying&#xD;
to make the matter clearer, she said,  "Now, class, if I stood on my&#xD;
head, the blood, as you know, would run into it, and I would turn red in the face.."&#xD;
&#xD;
"Yes," the class said.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Then why is it that while I am standing upright in the ordinary&#xD;
position the blood doesn't run into my feet?"&#xD;
&#xD;
A little fellow shouted,&#xD;
&#xD;
"Cause your feet ain't empty."&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
The children were lined up in the cafeteria of a Catholic elementary&#xD;
school for lunch. At the head of the table was a large pile of apples.&#xD;
The nun made a note, and posted on the apple tray:&#xD;
&#xD;
"Take only ONE. God is watching."&#xD;
&#xD;
Moving further along the lunch line, at the other end of the table was a large pile of chocolate chip cookies.&#xD;
&#xD;
A child had written a note, "Take all you want. God is watching the&#xD;
apples.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>53F9F196-8325-4790-93F6-F30846D93F65</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Don't mess with children</title>
</post>
