<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Good Morning,&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
I hope and trust all is well.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Currently one of TEKsystems global clients has a 3 month contract opportunity (that will most likely be extended – and the team members have been onsite for 2 years). &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
The job description  is listed below for your review:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Role Summary/Purpose:&#xD;
&#xD;
Reporting to the Program Manager of Gateway Products, the GUI Programmer will support the execution of New Product Introductions used in smart grid applications.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Essential Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Please let me know if you are interested in hearing about this role and call me directly at 905-283-1353 or simply by replying to this email.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Sincerely,&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Dawn&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Perform root cause analysis and corrective action on defects found in the GUI component of an embedded Linux product.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Author and revise detailed design documentation and develop new features for the same GUI component.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         The GUI component consists of HTML/CSS/Java Script /Java client-side code with Perl and C/C++ CGI back-end code. The GUI Java client-side code makes heavy use of the Swing and Spring frameworks. The GUI Java client-side code also reads and writes complex XML files that represent the configuration of the embedded Linux product.  The GUI developer will need to be familiar with all these technologies since defects and features may cross over all these areas.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Develop an upgrade program using bash script, Java and XSLT to upgrade XML configuration files from one version of the Linux product to the next.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         The GUI component also runs locally on the platform in a browser hosted by the platform. The GUI developer may be involved in changing configuration files for the FVWM window manager, Firefox, X-Windows, JRE to resolve defects on the platform.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Ensure all text fields and labels are internationalized according to the methods used in the product.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Ensure all work is maintained under version control using CVS.&#xD;
Qualifications/Requirements&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Development experience in&#xD;
&#xD;
o   Linux&#xD;
&#xD;
o   Java web application development&#xD;
&#xD;
o   Java Swing&#xD;
&#xD;
o   Java Spring Framework&#xD;
&#xD;
o   JavaScript&#xD;
&#xD;
o   HTML&#xD;
&#xD;
o   CSS + XSLT&#xD;
&#xD;
o   XML&#xD;
&#xD;
o   C and C++ for CGIs&#xD;
&#xD;
o   Perl for CGIs&#xD;
&#xD;
o   CVS&#xD;
&#xD;
o   Bash shell scripting&#xD;
&#xD;
o   Ant&#xD;
Desired Characteristics&#xD;
&#xD;
    Knowledge in the Substation Automation domain would be a strong asset.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Dawn Badiuk  ACCOUNT RECRUITING MANAGER&#xD;
350 Burnhamthorpe Road West, Suite 700, Mississauga, Ontario, L5B 3J1&#xD;
Toll Free: 1.800.254.0778&#xD;
Local: 905.283.1353&#xD;
&#xD;
Mobile: 416.407.9899</content>
    <postId>5412CFE8-B839-480B-8710-C0D0F62C7861</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2EE Developer, Cont', 3months to start</title>
</post>
