<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Estimated Start Date:	April 1, 2009&#xD;
Anticipated Duration:	12 months&#xD;
Duration of Potential Extension:	9 months&#xD;
Description of  Assignment/Scope of Work&#xD;
The City’s Information &amp; Technology Division and the Elections and Registry Services are currently involved in the preparation, development and improvement of systems and technology required for the 2010 Municipal Election. For this reason, it is required to acquire professional services of two (2) Java Developers to assist in the systems development for the TEIS 2010 project for City Clerk’s.  The estimated duration of the required services is for a period of approximately twelve (12) months, with a possible extension to an additional nine (9) months; working 35 hrs/wk.  &#xD;
The professional Java Developers will be responsible for carrying out the duties described below, commencing on or about April 1st, 2009.&#xD;
&#xD;
Assignment Duties&#xD;
The  Java Developer is responsible for: &#xD;
Performing analysis and design duties as well as programming (coding), modeling, scripting, testing, documentation and deployment preparation.&#xD;
Participating in detailed systems and functional design, workflow diagrams for quality systems development&#xD;
Performing information and application data conversions&#xD;
Participating as a team member in the development of work breakdown structures (WBS) and execution of project plans providing technical expertise and advice re: architecture, development tools, work effort estimates&#xD;
Contributing to project status reports, variance explanations, risk identification and mitigation planning&#xD;
Contributing to post-implementation project reviews&#xD;
Qualifications&#xD;
Qualifications:&#xD;
It is important that the Services be undertaken by a Java Developer who can demonstrate specific knowledge of, and experience in performing similar work for projects of comparable nature, size and scope as detailed below.  &#xD;
&#xD;
University degree in computer science or related discipline, and considerable years of progressively more responsible experience working on large-scale information technology projects or the equivalent combination of education and/or experience.&#xD;
Demonstrated experience in the development of Java/J2EE based database driven web-applications.&#xD;
Demonstrated experience in the development web based IBM Websphere applications using Oracle databases.&#xD;
Demonstrated experience in and knowledge of current and emerging Web-based technologies, including web servers, browsers and middle-ware.&#xD;
Demonstrated usage of SDLC methodology, RAD, standards and documentation.&#xD;
Demonstrated experience in applying design patterns and J2EE development practices and tools.&#xD;
Demonstrated experience in unit and system integration testing; Strong debugging and trouble-shooting skills;&#xD;
Performed this role on multiple (3-4) large projects with a track record of success;&#xD;
Proven experience as a senior programmer/analyst;&#xD;
Demonstrated experience preparing and presenting technical materials, including standards, procedures, and technical specifications to all levels of management and staff.&#xD;
Good interpersonal and communication skills (oral and written), presentation skills, analytical and problem-solving abilities; and Good team player.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Technical Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
6+ years software development experience, with a minimum 4 in Java/J2EE development;&#xD;
3+ years of JSP/Servlet experience;&#xD;
3+ years experience in database driven java based web applications;&#xD;
3+ years in SQL programming experience. Oracle database and MS-Access experience is ideal, but other major databases such as DB2 are  also acceptable;&#xD;
2+ years of experience in WSAD5.1/RAD/Eclipse 3.x;&#xD;
2+ years of hands on experience in using open source projects such as Struts and Hibernate;&#xD;
2+ year of experience in large Java/J2EE development-projects;&#xD;
Advanced knowledge of Java/J2EE architecture (EJB, JSP, JDBC) and OOA/D;&#xD;
Extensive experience in XML, Javascript;&#xD;
Experience with testing methodologies, unit and integration testing including experience using CVS. Maven and CruiseControl experience is an asset;&#xD;
      &#xD;
Deliverables&#xD;
Deliverables: &#xD;
Design, code, test, implement and support web-based J2EE applications.&#xD;
Perform bug fixing and support the QA process&#xD;
Prepare technical design document;&#xD;
Prepare detailed program specifications;&#xD;
Prepare application framework.&#xD;
&#xD;
-------------------&#xD;
Jeannette McClenny&#xD;
Ian Martin IT&#xD;
mcclenny@ianmartin.com&#xD;
www.ianmartin.com&#xD;
416-439-6400  ext 4225&#xD;
1-866-752-6744</content>
    <postId>56EA65D9-32B9-4BC0-88E4-BB388A88D8D7</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[Cont.] Senior Application (Java) Developer, Toronto</title>
</post>
