<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>If you are not in golf, probably you would not know who she is. Annika Sorenstam is #1 player in LPGA tour. She is the one Pak Se Ri tries to catch up. She has been in the news since she had decided to compete in one of PGA, Colonial, competition held on May 22nd to May 25th. &#xD;
&#xD;
What’s the buzz? Because it rarely happens. Last time any lady played in the men’s golf competition is 58 years ago. Even through she is #1 in the Lady’s tour, she is against the daunting tasks such as pure strength which means guys will overdrive her by 20 to 30 yards in every shots. She and SeRi became #1 and 2 because of their long driver. From the get go she will lose her strength and she has to consider many more obstacles to overcome like longer rough, speedy green and overwhelming pressure.&#xD;
&#xD;
She has a lot to lose and also LPGA has a lot to lose. If LPGA #1 player can’t make the cut after 2 days, what a disappointment for many peoples! There are many reasons that LPGA tour is allowing her to play in PGA tour. Reasons are TV rating is low for LPGA, no interest from the public, some kind of events to boost the interest and can’t go any lower than now. &#xD;
&#xD;
But I like to see in personal level only. She is making good income, I believe she can generate 2 to 3 million dollars including endorsement and ad. She is #1 in the lady ‘s tour for last few years. What is trying to proof? There are many upsides and also a lot of downsides. Upsides are she can empower her values if she plays well. Conversely she could lose her reputation and marketing values if she plays poorly. &#xD;
&#xD;
If she sees this try as other challenge, situation could be quite simple. But I can’t stop contemplating. It is just like any other happenings in the world or it is one person tries to overcome the adversity of one’s life. What would you do if you’re in her shoe?  Stay in her comfort zone or face your worst fear. It will be very interesting to see her performance on May 24th.&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>5A3B8686-E244-43CF-87E3-906996FACB14</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Annika Sorenstam Story</title>
</post>
