<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이홍식</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Canada tops gloomy forecast&#xD;
By Terry Weber&#xD;
Globe and Mail Update&#xD;
Wednesday, September 25 - Online Edition, Posted at 11:44 AM EST &#xD;
&#xD;
주위 대륙들에서는 못살겠다고 아우성인데 유독 캐나다만큼은 불경기를 극복함은 물론 G7 국가내에서도 경제성장을 주도하고 있다는 반가운(?) 소식입니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
...the IMF forecast (경기예측보고서)more tepid(미지근한) European growth than originally predicted, while Japan's forecast was better although it remains stuck in a recession. Latin America, hampered (저지, 방해) by Argentina's woes (알젠틴의 경제난), is expected to continues to face heightened economic and financial uncertainties.&#xD;
&#xD;
IMF 보고서는 유럽경제성장세가 예상보다 미온적일 것으로 예측한 반면 일본경제는 불황에 같혀 있음에도 불구 향상될 것으로 보고함.  알젠틴의 경제난에 저지를 받고 있는 남미는 계속해서 경제 및 재정불안의 깊은 고랑을 극복해야 하게 될 것으로 내다봄.&#xD;
&#xD;
야후사전.&#xD;
ham·per1 &#xD;
－ v.t.&#xD;
1 …을 저지하다, 방해하다, 훼방하다.&#xD;
ㆍ Her long dress ∼ed her freedom of movement. 그녀는 긴 옷을 입고 있어서 자유롭게 움직일 수가 없었다. ☞ PREVENT [동의어]&#xD;
2 …을 제한하다, 삭감하다, 빼앗다.&#xD;
&#xD;
－n.&#xD;
1 방해가 되는 것, 방해물, 속박.&#xD;
2 『海』 (평상시에는 필요하나 폭풍 때 등에는) 방해가 되는 선구(船具). &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Cambridge dictionary...&#xD;
hamper (CAUSE DIFFICULTY)&#xD;
verb [T] &#xD;
to prevent (something) being done easily or (someone) doing something easily &#xD;
Is it always easier working on a computer, or does it sometimes hamper you?&#xD;
Fierce storms have been hampering rescue efforts and there is now little chance of finding more survivors. &#xD;
&#xD;
m-w dictionary...&#xD;
1 a : to restrict the movement of by bonds or obstacles : IMPEDE b : to interfere with the operation of : DISRUPT&#xD;
2 a : CURB, RESTRAIN b : to interfere with : ENCUMBER&#xD;
synonyms HAMPER, TRAMMEL, CLOG, FETTER, SHACKLE, MANACLE mean to hinder or impede in moving, progressing, or acting. HAMPER may imply the effect of any impeding or restraining influence &lt;hampered the investigation by refusing to cooperate&gt;. TRAMMEL suggests entangling by or confining within a net &lt;rules that trammel the artist's creativity&gt;. CLOG usually implies a slowing by something extraneous or encumbering &lt;a court system clogged by frivolous suits&gt;. FETTER suggests a restraining so severe that freedom to move or progress is almost lost &lt;a nation fettered by an antiquated class system&gt;. SHACKLE and MANACLE are stronger than FETTER and suggest total loss of freedom &lt;a mind shackled by stubborn prejudice&gt; &lt;a people manacled by tyranny&gt;. &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>5B4C93CF-9093-4233-B314-F1E4359D29D3</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>hamper</title>
</post>
