<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>제게 인터뷰 요청이 왔다가 취소한 내용인데요, 이 에이전트가 저와 유사한 스킬셋이 있는 사람을 추천해달라고 합니다. 누구라고는 말씀 안드리겠지만, 레쥬메 빨리 바꾸시고 지원하세요!!&#xD;
물론 전화나 이메일하시고 제 이름 (Brendan Kim) 대시길 바랍니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
Hi Brendan: &#xD;
&#xD;
- omitted...&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description: &#xD;
Contract 1 - Back End Processing Project &#xD;
Team Size: 5 &#xD;
Job Duties: Development, unit testing, and support of an EJB based back-end application. The application was written in legacy and PL/SQL. The task is to convert the application into an EJB based application. Developers will focus on design, implementation, debugging, and testing of EJBs. &#xD;
Key Skills: Java (4 yrs), Struts (2 yrs), JDBC (3 yrs), HTML (4 yrs), JavaScript (4 yrs), EJB (3 yrs), XML/XSL (2 yrs), PL/SQL (2 yrs). &#xD;
&#xD;
Contract 2 - Utility Computing &#xD;
Team Size: 9 &#xD;
Job Description: Development, unit testing, and support of a stand alone metering infrastructure application. Developers will work with the web tier, business tier, and data access tier of the application. Struts, JDBC, JSPs are heavily used in this application. &#xD;
Key Skills: Java (4 yrs), Struts (2 yrs), JDBC (4 yrs), HTML (4 yrs), JavaScript (4 yrs). &#xD;
&#xD;
Contract 3 - Brainhunter Redesign &#xD;
Job Description: Development, unit testing, and support of a Recruiting/Vendor Management/Applicant Tracking system which is used internally as well as sold to clients. Developers will be responsible for development, design, unit testing, and troubleshooting/support. &#xD;
Key Skills: Java/J2EE (4 yrs), JDBC (4 yrs), HTML (4 yrs), JavaScript (4 yrs). &#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks and please call me after the interview to let me know how it went! &#xD;
&#xD;
Sincerely, &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
TRACY WOLBAUM&#xD;
MANAGER, RECRUITING &#xD;
416.225.9900 x387&#xD;
F. 416.225.9104  &#xD;
tracy.wolbaum@brainhunter.com&#xD;
www.brainhunter.com &#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>5C3A9D97-B3AB-49D0-99AF-63365E7F83C0</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-05-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java 개발자 포지션 3</title>
</post>
