<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김중수</author>
            <date>2004-05-26T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>요즘...자리를 찾아야 하는 관계로...여러 회사를 접촉하는 기회가 많았습니다. 제일 먼저 제가 접촉했던 회사가 Keane인데요..글쎄 모든 인터뷰를 마치고 나서의 느낌이 별로 가고 싶지 않은 회사더군요.&#xD;
무엇보다 우리와 별로 가깝지 않은 쪽 사람들(신민용옹께 여쭤보면 어느인종인지 판별가능)이 주류를 이루고 있구요..인터뷰 및 기타 여러 절차에서의 느낌은 엔지니어를 고용한다는 느낌보다는 마음 놓고 부려 먹을 수 있는 하인을 고용하려 한다는 느낌이 먼저 들더군요..회사 Benefit도 그리 좋은 편이 아닌데, 자기들 자랑은 엄청 늘어 놓더군요. 인도에 개발센터가 하나 있다구 하구요..인도에서 회사운영하는게 거의 북미에서의 1/10밖에 안든다고 자랑스레 떠들더군요.&#xD;
제 느낌은 이래도 다른 분들의 느낌은 다를 수도 있으니..뭐..그냥 제 느낌입니다..</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>My name is Lauren Faherty and I am a Recruiting Associate with Keane, Inc. I am &#xD;
writing to invite you to a recruiting event for IT professionals that we are &#xD;
having in Toronto Thursday, June 3, 2004. &#xD;
&#xD;
We are currently hiring for multiple positions in our Advanced Development &#xD;
Center in Halifax, Nova Scotia and our new office in Toronto, Ontario. We are &#xD;
looking for candidates with hands-on experience in Unix development, plus any of &#xD;
the following skills: Core Java, Perl, Sybase,Unix, Natural Adabas. Financial &#xD;
services experience is a big plus. &#xD;
&#xD;
Please note: there are full-time opportunities that may require relocation to &#xD;
Halifax. &#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested in attending our event Tuesday night and learning more &#xD;
about a career with Keane, please register on our website at &#xD;
http://www.keane.com/careers/toronto Once you've registered, a recruiter will &#xD;
follow up with you and provide directions to the event, etc. &#xD;
&#xD;
I look forward to hearing from you. &#xD;
&#xD;
Lauren Faherty &#xD;
Recruiting Associate &#xD;
Keane, Inc. &#xD;
Lauren_M_Faherty@keane.com &#xD;
http://www.keane.com </content>
    <postId>5CC9975B-07AA-41F4-9A59-0FC93E140C75</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-05-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Recruiting event</title>
</post>
