<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello,&#xD;
&#xD;
I thought this may interest you. Its with the investment division of a Canadian Bank in downtown Toronto.&#xD;
&#xD;
#31802&#xD;
Technical Analyst (J2EE, C++,)&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Overview:&#xD;
&#xD;
To support Retail Trading, Security Operations and Sales Support Applications&#xD;
for the Broker Dealer Platform&#xD;
Develop, test and support Java, J2EE, C++, Microsoft Visual .Net and Microsoft&#xD;
Visual Studio applications built on their own infrastructure and interfaces to&#xD;
other systems&#xD;
Provide input and coordinate with DBA in creating new and modifying existing&#xD;
database structures using different types of databases and recommending&#xD;
appropriate DB based on required functionality&#xD;
Develop, code, write and execute unit test using different languages and testing&#xD;
tools for complex functions&#xD;
Application support, problem solving, infrastructure software installation,&#xD;
configuration, testing, deployment and performance tuning&#xD;
Support IT operations in the ongoing operations of these environments in&#xD;
production including incident resolution and root-cause analysis&#xD;
Develop master distribution lists, implementation and contingency plans ensuring&#xD;
verification is performed&#xD;
Support IT operations by pro-actively assessing server and application&#xD;
performance&#xD;
Provide Detail Design, Functional Requirement Document and CMM documentation as&#xD;
required&#xD;
Contribute to successful project completion by identifying risks and&#xD;
developing/recommending mitigation strategies&#xD;
Provide estimation of work effort for technical solutions for major systems /&#xD;
application components or enhancements&#xD;
Provide input to technical design reviews to ensure that business requirements&#xD;
are met&#xD;
Provide support, direction for application development groups &amp; end users in the&#xD;
specific use the of end user tools&#xD;
&#xD;
Required Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
Min. 5 years of previous development experience in a business driven information&#xD;
systems environment, preferably within the financial industry&#xD;
Several years experience with JAVA, C++ (Delphi, Borland experience an added&#xD;
advantage), STL and MFC class libraries, MS SQL, Java 2, JavaScript, HTML,&#xD;
Crystal Reports, Sybase Knowledge .NET and XML technology and advantage.&#xD;
Experience of design, coding and support of large-scale C++ class applications&#xD;
Proficient knowledge of multiple platforms and ability to select appropriate&#xD;
platform to meet business partner needs&#xD;
Demonstrated knowledge of Internet infrastructure and e-Business application&#xD;
design, development, testing and implementation&#xD;
Proficient with personal computer productivity tools such as Microsoft Office,&#xD;
MS Project and technical design tools including Visio.&#xD;
Nice to have knowledge of JCL and Word Macros&#xD;
Ability to facilitate small to large group meetings for technical design,&#xD;
decision making, problem solving and task implementation&#xD;
&#xD;
Salary is competitive with great benefits, bonus, g-RSP match, stock purchase&#xD;
plan etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you, or perhaps someone you know, are interested in this job, please contact&#xD;
Carlos with a new resume, details of experience and salary. Thank you,&#xD;
&#xD;
Carlos Goncalves&#xD;
C. G. Consulting Group Inc.&#xD;
Tel: 1 (905) 753-8400 Fax: 1 (905) 753-2112&#xD;
Email: carlos@cgconsultinggroup.com&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>61E43E2F-3C17-43FF-BFD0-C40BEA5C0F37</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-12-18T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Analyst (J2EE, C++,) in Downtown Toronto - Bank</title>
</post>
