<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2003-05-26T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>참석자들의 질의를 들으면서 속으로 뜨끔했습니다. 어쩌면 그간 내가 고민했던것들을 저리 잘 맞출까?...다음에 새로운 프로젝트를 하게되면 아예, 디자인들어가기전에 한번 요구사항만 발표하여, 여러분의 의견을 듣고싶군요. 마지막에 홍영기씨께서 제안한 내용을 상세히 못들었습니다. </content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>     First of all I like to thank Scott for new concept of sharing knowledge. His preparation was excellent and presentation of requirements and scope of work was easy to understand. Scott has shared the all the information as possible to increase the understanding of project objectives. It was rewarding meeting and learned a lot that our knowledge and experience go beyond our imagination as a group. &#xD;
&#xD;
     Initially I was skeptical about design forum because of participation of attendees. It is neither easy nor fun thing to understand and think about some other companies’ project. However Scott’s excellent preparation and enthusiastic participation from the attendees resulted fun and constructive discussion.&#xD;
&#xD;
     There are few things we should consider in my opinion prior to next design forum&#xD;
&#xD;
- Scope of project for design forum should be easy to understand. Our first design forum scope was easy to understand because it involved data migration and data verification&#xD;
&#xD;
- Interesting projects such as Steve Kang’s product, Yellow.ca project, could be the candidates because projects like them can attract the interests from general public of Comm. One.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Scott presented his project beginning to end. It provided the chance to understand Scott’s design concept and principle. However his presentation blocked our creativity in a way. If Scott only gave us the requirements and objectives, we could come up with Comm. One design. We could compare with Comm. One and Scott design afterward. The comparison could be very interesting.&#xD;
&#xD;
- We could come up with design discussion template. We could entertain meeting concept like six thinking hat, making better decisions, and etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
We went to the place we haven’t gone before. We used to share our technical knowledge through our regular meeting. Scott showed us other possibility like sharing our concept and experiences. It is far more advanced stage, isn’t it ?&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>6249E34F-E130-404A-8A6B-0D84EFD9B3D0</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>After First Design forum</title>
</post>
