<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Systems Analyst 	&#xD;
 	&#xD;
&#xD;
the opportunity&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client has built a future friendly national team, one that embraces&#xD;
change and initiates opportunity, has a passion for growth, believes in&#xD;
spirited teamwork and has the courage to innovate. Our success is based&#xD;
as much on the dedication and hard work of our team as it is on the&#xD;
innovative wireless solutions we offer.&#xD;
&#xD;
Our commitment to providing our clients with unsurpassed coverage, cool&#xD;
phones, great rates and outstanding client care, is what we're all&#xD;
about. Join our team of wireless professionals working in one of&#xD;
Canada's fastest-growing industries and make your future friendly too.&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Overview:&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is looking for qualified and seasoned professionals to fill&#xD;
numerous Systems Analyst positions in our Information Systems&#xD;
Development team in Scarborough. As a Systems Analyst, you will provide&#xD;
e-Business application and systems design, development, project&#xD;
management and implementation for projects related to the support of&#xD;
e-Business initiatives for our business partner. Our current Systems&#xD;
Analyst opportunities are available in the following areas:&#xD;
*	Systems for Sales and Distribution&#xD;
*	Systems for Client Operations&#xD;
*	Systems for Application Infrastructure and Standards&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
*	Lead the design of data, application and technology elements of&#xD;
technical designs supporting a variety of business requirements. &#xD;
*	Ensure technical designs of applications are architected to be&#xD;
flexible, scalable, maintainable, and open in our clients n-tier&#xD;
environment. &#xD;
*	Team with Business Systems Analysts to review business&#xD;
requirements and functional designs. &#xD;
*	Work with highly talented colleagues in a fun, fast paced team&#xD;
to deliver significant business changing applications. &#xD;
*	Identify, review and refine the processing requirements of&#xD;
systems to define appropriate application architectures. &#xD;
*	Identify, review and refine the technology requirements of&#xD;
systems to define appropriate technology architectures (technology,&#xD;
platform, hardware/software components). &#xD;
*	Take a lead role in making necessary changes to the architecture&#xD;
to resolve systems issues. &#xD;
*	Deliver high quality, thoroughly tested applications, that will&#xD;
sustain current and expected loads. Re-evaluate the designs of such&#xD;
systems routinely to ensure that they are scalable to meet the growth of&#xD;
the business needs. &#xD;
*	Assume a consulting role during the System Development, System&#xD;
and User Acceptance Testing and Production implementation phases to&#xD;
ensure that the system is developed and implemented as per requirements&#xD;
and the defined architecture. &#xD;
*	Assume other roles as required such as project management, team&#xD;
leadership, QA planner/coordinator, etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
qualifications&#xD;
&#xD;
*	Min. 5 years of progressive systems development and analysis&#xD;
experience in a telecommunications environment is strongly preferred. &#xD;
*	Extensive experience delivering application design, including&#xD;
object oriented analysis and design, component based Web architectures&#xD;
and data structure design. &#xD;
*	Thorough understanding of technology in a distributed&#xD;
architecture environment including UNIX, Windows 2000, Web Application&#xD;
Server, Application Server, and Oracle required. &#xD;
*	Highly experienced in J2EE platform, Java, Java applets/Java&#xD;
servlets, EJBs, and HTML/XML. &#xD;
*	Experience with a formalized System Development Lifecycle&#xD;
including requirements definition, functional design, detailed design,&#xD;
source control, change control, and integration testing. &#xD;
*	Highly organized, analytical, detail and action oriented. &#xD;
*	Superior leadership, facilitation, communication and&#xD;
interpersonal skills. &#xD;
*	Ability to handle multiple projects efficiently and effectively.&#xD;
&#xD;
*	Post secondary degree in Computer Science or Engineering.&#xD;
&#xD;
	&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Matt Zweig&#xD;
Client Sales and Solutions &#xD;
Pegasus Consulting Inc. &#xD;
matt@pegsoft.com &#xD;
WWW.pegsoft.com &lt;http://WWW.pegsoft.com&gt; &#xD;
416-488-7007 X 232 (local) &#xD;
877-688-8818 X 232 (Toll Free) &#xD;
55 Eglinton Avenue East, Suite 208 &#xD;
Toronto, ON&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>65563850-0226-4E6F-AEFE-34B5F3F50BC6</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-08-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Systems Analyst - Toronto</title>
</post>
