<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Technical Analyst - T12408 &#xD;
 &#xD;
The position below is currently available through Procom. If you meet the qualifications and are interested in this opportunity please apply as per the instructions below. Please note, this automated email has been sent to you as the result of a successful keyword search on your resume within our database. Please use discretion by only applying to positions that best suit your qualifications. If you wish to remove yourself from future mailings, please click the link supplied below. &#xD;
&#xD;
Position: Technical Analyst &#xD;
Mandatory Skills: J2EE, EJB, ORACLE, SQL, UML, UNIX, Weblogic, XML, Struts. &#xD;
Nice-to-Have Skills: &#xD;
Location: Toronto &#xD;
Duration: 6 Months &#xD;
Rate/Salary: &#xD;
Start Date: &#xD;
Job Description: &#xD;
&#xD;
1. Analyze business requirements, plan, design and implement moderately to highly complex technology enabled solutions to meet business opportunities/problems. &#xD;
2. Analyze and document fairly complex business/technical data/information and processes. &#xD;
3. Under minimal supervision, participates in analysis of complex business opportunities/problems to deliver designs meeting requirements. &#xD;
4. Participates in estimation of tasks and assists in the development of project plans for small to medium sized projects. &#xD;
5. Under minimal supervision, codes or makes modifications to programs of high complexity, according to detailed specifications. &#xD;
6. Acquires solid business knowledge in assigned application programs and information technologies. Conducts walkthroughs and quality review of deliverables. &#xD;
&#xD;
Business, Relational and/or Technical Skills &#xD;
·Understand and translate business requirements into Design and Specification within the constraints of overall architecture. The technology platform includes J2EE (EJB 2.0) architecture, WebLogic 7.02, Oracle &#xD;
·Ability to understand and contribute to Logical and Physical Data Model &#xD;
·It is multi-team effort. Communication skills are must as is the ability to work with multiple teams &#xD;
·Lead and mentor small development teams to develop applications. &#xD;
·Assist and code complex functionalities &#xD;
·Good organization, planning and basic management principles. &#xD;
·Proven excellent interpersonal and communication skills, including the ability to prepare clear and concise documents/presentations using the appropriate technical and business language. &#xD;
·Experience with UML, object-oriented concepts, and object modeling tools. &#xD;
·Experience with Oracle and PL/SQL. &#xD;
·Good command of XML technologies. &#xD;
·Windows NT and UNIX. &#xD;
·Experience in the Financial Industry &#xD;
·Proven success in handling multiple activities/projects as well as conflicting demands and priorities effectively under time constraints ·Proven analytical, decision-making and problem solving skills. &#xD;
·Expert knowledge of software development, testing and evaluation procedures. &#xD;
·Team building skills. &#xD;
·Ability to work both independently and as a team member, and take a lead role on key projects. &#xD;
·Extensive knowledge of J2EE (Java 2 Enterprise Edition) - 4 or more years hands on. &#xD;
·Entity bean EJB 2.0 (BMP, CMP, CMR), JUnit, JDBC, JSP, Servlets - 4 or more years hands on &#xD;
· Maven, Struts, Ant, CVS, Eclipse, open source - hands on experience &#xD;
·RDBMS, Oracle, SQL, and PL/SQL - 4 or more years hands on &#xD;
·Erwin ·UML - 4 or more years hands on &#xD;
·XML (SAX, DOM, XSL) ·SQL - 4 or more years hands on &#xD;
·J2EE Containers and application servers &#xD;
- WebLogic, Tomcat, and others &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further. &#xD;
&#xD;
Please submit your most recent resume to: ronc@procom.ca &#xD;
 &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>65AFC560-0548-4DFC-AAD2-49C9CF127527</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-10-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Analyst - T12408 by Procom</title>
</post>
