<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Source : http://www.meritide.com/eaiglossary.htm&#xD;
&#xD;
Here is the some terminologies which you better know the meaning of the words for better understanding of EAI...&#xD;
&#xD;
Middleware, Enterprise Application Integration (EAI), and Business to Business e-Commerce. . . this trio is remaking our industries (and our lives) today. We are moving from traditional business, where IT was a prisoner in the glasshouse, to a new age of money-making, where IT is right at the cutting edge of commerce.  No longer is IT behind the scenes. On the Web and in the network, IT is the place where business gets done. &#xD;
&#xD;
With a new world, comes a new vocabulary. &#xD;
&#xD;
A2A &#xD;
===============&#xD;
See Application to Application Integration&#xD;
&#xD;
API &#xD;
===============&#xD;
Application Program Interface - an interface that enables programs to communicate with each other.&#xD;
&#xD;
APPC &#xD;
===============&#xD;
Advanced Program-to-Program Communication&amp;#8212;IBM’s solution for program-to-program communication, distributed transaction processing and remote data access across the IBM product line.&#xD;
&#xD;
Application Service Provider&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Companies which allow business customers to rent or lease the use of e-business applications over secured Internet connections.&#xD;
&#xD;
Application to Application Integration (A2A)&#xD;
============================================&#xD;
A form of enterprise application integration in which two or more applications, usually but not exclusively within the same organization, are linked.&#xD;
&#xD;
Asynchronous Communications&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A form of communication by which applications can operate independently, so that they do not have to be running or available simultaneously. A process sends a request and may or may not wait for a response. It is a non-blocking communications style.&#xD;
&#xD;
Automatic Binding&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Describes the action when an RPC client stub locates a specific server on a list of servers.&#xD;
&#xD;
B2B&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Business to Business. In reference to commerce conducted between companies rather than between companies and private individuals or consumers. See B2C&#xD;
&#xD;
B2C&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Business to Consumer. This refers to commerce conducted between companies adn individuals or consumers. In contrast to B2B.&#xD;
&#xD;
Backbone&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A series of connections that forms a major communications pathway within a network.&#xD;
&#xD;
Bandwidth&#xD;
===============&#xD;
The amount of data that can be sent through a connection; usually measured in bits per second. A fast modem can move about 15,000 bits in one second (about a page of English text).&#xD;
&#xD;
Binding&#xD;
===============&#xD;
The association of a client and a server.&#xD;
&#xD;
BizTalk&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A Microsoft sponsored set of guidelines for how to publish schemas in XML and how to use XML messages to easily integrate software programs together in order to build rich new solutions.&#xD;
&#xD;
Blocking Communications&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A synchronous messaging process whereby the requestor of a service must wait until a response is received.&#xD;
&#xD;
Buffered Queue&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A message queue that resides in memory.&#xD;
&#xD;
Business Process Management&#xD;
===============&#xD;
The concept of shepherding work items through a multi-step process. The items are identified and tracked as they move through each step, with either specified people or applications processing the information. The process flow is determined by process logic and the applications (or processes) themselves play virtually no role in determining where the messages are sent.&#xD;
&#xD;
COM&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Component Object Model&amp;#8212;Microsoft’s standard for distributed objects, an object encapsulation technology that specifies interfaces between component objects within a single application or between applications. It separates the interface from the implementation and provides APIs for dynamically locating objects and for loading and invoking them (see DCOM).&#xD;
&#xD;
Communications Middleware&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Software that provides inter-application connectivity based on communication styles such as message queuing, ORBs and publish/subscribe.&#xD;
&#xD;
Communications Protocol&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A formally defined system for controlling the exchange of information over a network or communications channel.&#xD;
&#xD;
Connectionless Communications&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Communications that do not require a dedicated connection or session between applications.&#xD;
&#xD;
CORBA&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Common Object Request Broker Architecture&amp;#8212;a standard maintained by the OMG.&#xD;
&#xD;
CPI-C&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Common Programming Interface-Communications&amp;#8212;IBM’s SNA peer-to-peer API that can run over SNA and TCP/IP. It masks the complexity of APPC.&#xD;
&#xD;
Customer Relationship Management (CRM)&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Customer Relationship Management (CRM) is the art of integrating every aspect of IT that relates to the customer - quite literally everything from marketing through sales to accounts receivable and bill collection.&#xD;
&#xD;
Customer Relationship Marketing (CReM)&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Using a company's knowledge and understanding of a customer to more effectively market to that customer. While most often used in B2C e-commerce, CReM techniques are still frequently employed in B2B situations.&#xD;
&#xD;
cXML&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Commerce XML. A meta-language that defines the necessary information about a product. It is a set of document type definitions (DTD) for the XML specification. Eventually, it will be used to define the exchange of transaction data for secure electronic transaction over the Internet.&#xD;
&#xD;
Data Level Integration&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A form of EAI that integrates different data stores to allow the sharing of information among applications. It requires the loading of data directly into the database via its native interface and does not involve the changing of business logic.&#xD;
&#xD;
Data Knowledge and Decision Support&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Using IT technology and information to both measure and improve an organization's performance.&#xD;
&#xD;
Data Transformation&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A key requirement of EAI and message brokers. There are two basic kinds: syntactic translation changes one data set into another (such as different date or number formats), while semantic transformation changes data based on the underlying data definitions or meaning.&#xD;
&#xD;
Database Middleware&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Allows clients to invoke SQL-based services across multi-vendor databases. This middleware is defined by de facto standards such as ODBC, DRDA, RDA, etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
DCE&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Distributed Computing Environment&amp;#8212;from the Open Software Foundation, DCE provides key distributed technologies such as RPC, distributed naming service, time synchronization service, distributed file system and network security.&#xD;
&#xD;
DCOM&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Distributed Component Object Model&amp;#8212;Microsoft’s protocol that enables software components to communicate directly over a network in a reliable, secure, and efficient manner. DCOM is based on the DCE-RPC specification and works with both Java applets and ActiveX components through its use of the COM.&#xD;
&#xD;
Directory Services&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A way for clients to locate services. Usually contained in a single system image of available servers.&#xD;
&#xD;
DOM&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Document Object Model - a platform- and language-neutral interface that will allow programs and scripts to dynamically access and update the content, structure and style of documents.&#xD;
&#xD;
DRDA&#xD;
===============&#xD;
IBM’s Distributed Relational Database Architecture.&#xD;
&#xD;
EAI&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Enterprise Application Integration is a set of technologies that allows the movement and exchange of information between different applications and business processes within and between organizations.&#xD;
&#xD;
E-Business&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Also "E-Biz." The use of Internet technologies, and the Web in particular, to conduct business operations.&#xD;
&#xD;
E-Procurement&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Using the Internet and other open networks to perform the procurement function; a B2B application.&#xD;
&#xD;
Extranet&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A network that links an enterprise to its various divisions and business partners which uses secured Internet links. In this way, it has the advantages of a private network at the cost of a public one. See VPN.&#xD;
&#xD;
Gateway&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A hardware and/or software setup that performs translations between disparate protocols.&#xD;
&#xD;
Groupware&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A collection of technologies that allows the representation of complex processes that center around collaborative human activities. It is a model for client/server computing based on five foundation technologies: multimedia document management, workflow, e-mail, conferencing and scheduling.&#xD;
&#xD;
Heterogeneity&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A typical enterprise information system today includes many types of computer technology, from PCs to mainframes. These include a wide variety of different operating systems, application software and in-house developed applications. EAI solves the complex problem of making a heterogeneous infrastructure more coherent.&#xD;
&#xD;
IIOP&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Internet Inter-ORB Protocol&amp;#8212;a standard that ensures interoperability for objects in a multi-vendor ORB environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
Integrity&#xD;
===============&#xD;
In a client/server environment, integrity means that the server code and server data are centrally maintained and therefore secure and reliable.&#xD;
&#xD;
Invasive Integration&#xD;
===============&#xD;
An implementation approach that requires changes or additions to existing applications. Opposite of non-invasive integration.&#xD;
&#xD;
IOTP&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Internet Open Trading Protocol. this is a set of standards developed by the IETF to define an interoperable framework for Internet commerce.&#xD;
&#xD;
Load Balancing&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Automatic balancing of requests among replicated servers to ensure that no server is overloaded.&#xD;
&#xD;
LU6.2&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Logical Unit 6.2&amp;#8212;IBM’s device-independent process-to-process protocol provides the facilities for peer-to-peer communications between two programs and also supports asynchronous networking.&#xD;
&#xD;
Message Broker&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A key component of EAI, a message broker is an intelligent intermediary that directs the flow of messages between applications, which become sources and consumers of information. Message brokers provide a very flexible communications backbone and provide such services as data transformation, message routing and message warehousing.&#xD;
&#xD;
MOM&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Message-Oriented Middleware is a set of products that connects applications running on different systems by sending and receiving application data as messages. Examples are RPC, CPI-C and message queuing.&#xD;
&#xD;
Message Queuing&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A form of communication between programs. Application data is combined with a header (information about the data) to form a message. Messages are stored in queues, which can be buffered or persistent (see Buffered Queue and Persistent Queue). It is an asynchronous communications style and provides a loosely coupled exchange across multiple operating systems.&#xD;
&#xD;
Message Routing&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A super-application process where messages are routed to applications based on business rules. A particular message may be directed based on its subject or actual content.&#xD;
&#xD;
Message Warehousing&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A central repository for temporarily storing messages for analysis or transmission.&#xD;
&#xD;
Middleware&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Software that facilitates the communication between two applications. It provides an API through which applications invoke services and it controls the transmission of the data exchange over the network. There are three basic types: communications middleware, database middleware and systems middleware.&#xD;
&#xD;
Non-Blocking Communications&#xD;
===============&#xD;
An asynchronous messaging process whereby the requestor of a service does not have to wait until a response is received from another application.&#xD;
&#xD;
Non-Invasive Integration&#xD;
===============&#xD;
An implementation approach that does not require changes or additions to existing applications.&#xD;
&#xD;
Object Middleware&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Allows clients to invoke methods or objects that reside on a remote server. This middleware revolves around OMG’s CORBA and Microsoft’s DCOM.&#xD;
&#xD;
ODBC&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Open Database Connectivity&amp;#8212;a Windows standard API for SQL communication.&#xD;
&#xD;
OMG&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Object Management Group&amp;#8212;a consortium of object vendors and the founders of the CORBA standard.&#xD;
&#xD;
Open Applications Group (OAG)&#xD;
===============&#xD;
An indusgtry consortium formed to promote the easy and cost-effective integration of key business application software components.&#xD;
&#xD;
OpenDoc&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A set of shared class libraries with platform-independent interfaces.&#xD;
&#xD;
ORB&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Object Request Broker&amp;#8212;software that allows objects to dynamically discover each other and interact across machines, operating systems and networks.&#xD;
&#xD;
Persistent Queue&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A message queue that resides on a permanent device, such as a disk, and can be recovered in case of system failure.&#xD;
&#xD;
Publish/Subscribe&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Pub/Sub is a style of inter-application communications. Publishers are able to broadcast data to a community of information users or subscribers, which have issued issued the type of information they wish to receive (normally defining topics or subjects of interest). An application or user can be both a publisher and subscriber.&#xD;
&#xD;
RDA&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Remote Data Access, usually to an RDBMS via SQL.&#xD;
&#xD;
Router&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A special-purpose computer or software package that handles the connection of two or more networks. Routers check the destination address of the packets and decide the route to send them.&#xD;
&#xD;
RPC&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Remote Procedure Call&amp;#8212;a form of application-to-application communication that hides the intricacies of the network by using an ordinary procedure call mechanism. It is a tightly coupled synchronous process.&#xD;
&#xD;
Scalability&#xD;
===============&#xD;
The ability of an information system to provide high performance as greater demands are placed upon it, through the addition of extra computing power,&#xD;
&#xD;
SCM&#xD;
===============&#xD;
See Supply Chain Management.&#xD;
&#xD;
Server&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A computer or software package that provides a specific capabilities to client software running on other computers.&#xD;
&#xD;
SNA&#xD;
===============&#xD;
System Network Architecture&amp;#8212;a network architecture from IBM.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sockets&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A portable standard for network application providers on TCP/IP networks.&#xD;
&#xD;
Stored Procedure&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A program that creates a named collection of SQL or other procedural statements and logic that is compiled, verified and stored in a server database.&#xD;
&#xD;
STP&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Straight Through Processing occurs when a transaction, once entered into a system, passes through its entire life cycle without any manual intervention. STP is an example of a Zero Latency Process, but one specific to the finance industry which has many proprietary networks and messaging formats.&#xD;
&#xD;
Supply Chain Management&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Supply Chain Management (SCM) is that set of skills and disciplines, including those of IT, which shepherd a product from its original design to its ultimate delivery to the buyer.&#xD;
&#xD;
Synchronous Communications&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A form of communication that requires applications to run concurrently. A process issues a call and until it receives a response.&#xD;
&#xD;
Systems Middleware&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Software that provides value-add services as well as inter-program communications. An example is transaction processing monitors which are required to control local resources and also cooperate with other resource managers to access non-local resources.&#xD;
&#xD;
TCP/IP&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol&amp;#8212;the network protocol for the Internet that runs on virtually every operating system. IP is the network layer and TCP is the transport layer.&#xD;
&#xD;
Trigger&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A stored procedure that is automatically invoked on the basis of data-related events.&#xD;
&#xD;
Two-Phase Commit&#xD;
===============&#xD;
A mechanism to synchronize updates on different machines or platforms so that they all fail or all succeed together. The decision to commit is centralized, but each participant has the right to veto. This is a key process in real time transaction-based environments.&#xD;
&#xD;
VPN&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Virtual Private Network. A solution by which an enterprise may link to its customers and business partners via secure Internet connections. The company thus has a network which is "just like" a private network, but isn't. (That is, it is "virtual.") This gives the company the advantages of a private network at the much lower cost of a public one.&#xD;
&#xD;
Workflow&#xD;
===============&#xD;
Software used to automatically route events or work-items from one user or program to another. Workflow is synonymous with process flow, although traditionally has been used in the context of person-to-person information flows.&#xD;
&#xD;
X/Open&#xD;
===============&#xD;
An independent open systems organization. Its strategy is to combine various standards into a comprehensive integrated systems environment called Common Applications Environment, which contains an evolving portfolio of practical APIs.&#xD;
&#xD;
Zero Latency&#xD;
===============&#xD;
No delay between an event and its response.&#xD;
&#xD;
Zero Latency Enterprise&#xD;
===============&#xD;
An enterprise in which all parts of the organization can respond to events as they occur elsewhere in the organization, using an integrated IT infrastructure that can immediately exchange information across technical and organizational boundaries.&#xD;
&#xD;
Zero Latency Process&#xD;
===============&#xD;
An automated process with no time delays (i.e. no manual re-entry of data) at the interfaces of different information systems. STP is an example.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>668E3E0D-184F-4F7B-9CC0-E97CB146613E</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-08-15T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>EAI Glossary - Brief Descriptions of EAI related term..</title>
</post>
