<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>It confirmed with Scott that this is from his former company. (You can get more information from him if necessary, I think)&#xD;
&#xD;
Published Description:	 	&#xD;
For more than 25 years, our client has grown to be one of Canada’s leading tour operators. They have worked with international partners spanning over 30 countries. Their reputation for reliability, innovation and responsiveness has established themselves as a leader in the travel industry.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Our client is looking for a seasoned Java Developer to join their growing team.&#xD;
 &#xD;
The mandate of the role is to plan, negotiate and program interfaces between the client’s back-end Canada Connect Reservation System (CCRS) and the Web methods used to communicate with its clients including but not limited to the their Web site and Web Services&#xD;
 &#xD;
Responsibilities&#xD;
 &#xD;
Develop routine to complex applications, using multiple technologies, platforms, and interfaces or work on defined subsets of new development with complete responsibility for the design, testing, and implementation of these subsystems. &#xD;
Work on all aspects of programming and analysis assignments and are fully knowledgeable in middleware design. &#xD;
Perform the full range of applications design, analysis, and programming functions around multi tiered, client server computing utilizing.&#xD;
Apply their technical knowledge creatively to identify and solve complex problems.&#xD;
Provide guidance and counsel to less experienced staff.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Requirements&#xD;
 &#xD;
Bachelor  degree in Computer Science or Diploma in Computer Programming.&#xD;
Minimum 5 years experience utilizing the following technologies;  Web Services, JAVA, SPRING/JSF, AJAX, JDBC.&#xD;
Minimum of 5 years experience programming in a multi-tiered environment utilizing at least one of; Sybase EA Server, Websphere, Weblogic or similar middleware server.&#xD;
Knowledge of database diagrams and detailed system diagrams&#xD;
Strong team player that is able to work in a fast-paced environment.&#xD;
French language skills are a definite asset.</content>
    <postId>6741C5DA-D1F0-4097-8D71-C0D495984E1E</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-10-06T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java developer</title>
</post>
