<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2011-05-06T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>These 2 positions are filled. Will let you know when there's another chance.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hello.&#xD;
&#xD;
Where I'm working now, there's an opening of Sr. Java developer position for a long-term contract. The person has to be very skillful and can do the job professionally. Even though the job description is from an agency, you could ask me any questions regarding it. I will become a refferal once you apply for it.&#xD;
&#xD;
Also, I just know what they want/look for and how you can win the opp. The location is Woodbine Av &amp; 16th Av in Markham just beside 404. The rate is not bad and competitive indeed.&#xD;
&#xD;
LifeRay is a bonus, Wicket is much preferred, Java5+, Spring and JPA is the key.&#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks.&#xD;
Brendan&#xD;
&#xD;
---------------------------------&#xD;
Sourcing Office : Toronto&#xD;
Title : Sr. Java Developer&#xD;
Project Description : This is an opportunity to work for a leading supplier of smart cards and cutting edge system solutions in the field of Finance- electronic payments, transportation, healthcare, identity, customer loyalty, pay TV and internet security.&#xD;
&#xD;
Client is seeking a Sr. Java Developer (6-12mth contract- long term contracting opportunity.&#xD;
&#xD;
•Very strong knowledge of Core Java, Hibernate, JPA, Spring, knowledge of portal development&#xD;
&#xD;
•Very strong knowledge of database design and database normalization and optimization techniques (ORM) Object relational modelling&#xD;
•Experience with Apache Wicket (or eqivelant)&#xD;
•Comfortable with UML concepts and diagrams&#xD;
•Sun Certified Java Professional would be preferred.&#xD;
•Very strong analytical skills&#xD;
•Strong communication skills&#xD;
&#xD;
Technology stack....&#xD;
&#xD;
Function        Tool&#xD;
O/R Mapping:    JPA Hibernate   3.4.0.GA&#xD;
&#xD;
Database:       hsqlDB (for testing only) but Oracle is the main for a developer&#xD;
Oracle          10, 11&#xD;
&#xD;
Security:       Spring Security&#xD;
               Apache Wicket Auth-Roles&#xD;
&#xD;
Application Server: Apache Tomcat and JBoss AS&#xD;
&#xD;
Object Management: Spring Core&#xD;
&#xD;
GUI Framework:     Apache Wicket&#xD;
                  Apache Wicket Extensions&#xD;
                  Apache Wicket Spring&#xD;
&#xD;
Web Services:      Spring WS&#xD;
&#xD;
Portal Server      Liferay Portal Server&#xD;
                  Liferay Ext SDK&#xD;
                  Liferay Plugin SDK   5.2.3&#xD;
&#xD;
Specialization and Skills :&#xD;
   -  Software Development&#xD;
         - Java   (8 - 10 years)&#xD;
&#xD;
Additional Requirements :&#xD;
   - Explain your experience in CORE JAVA Development (Mandatory)&#xD;
   - Explain your expertise with JPA, hibernate and spring. (Mandatory)&#xD;
   - Do you have any open source portal framework experience... explain. (Mandatory)&#xD;
   - Explain extent of your knowledge in and experience in database design and normalization/optomization techniques. (Mandatory)&#xD;
   - Explain your work with multi-tier web applications (Mandatory)&#xD;
   - Explain your experience with Apache and Tomcat. (Mandatory)&#xD;
   - Explain your expertise with ORM- Object relational modelling, database connection and modelling. (Mandatory)&#xD;
&#xD;
Start Date : May 16, 2011&#xD;
End Date : Nov 09, 2011</content>
    <postId>6DB32E3E-7FCA-40A0-88BC-D547414B7477</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-04-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Sr. Java Developer - Contract</title>
</post>
