<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>신민용</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi There, &#xD;
&#xD;
We are currently hiring for 30 Java related opportunities, and 10 .NET related opportunities in Toronto and surrounding areas. These are time sensitive requisitions for which we are working directly with hiring managers. &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Java:&#xD;
&#xD;
-----&#xD;
&#xD;
-          16 of Java opportunities that we have is with a global bank : Permanent fulltime opportunities that pays Maximum upto 90K, Location - Mississauga&#xD;
&#xD;
-          14 of these opportunities are with a company in Insurance Space: Contract opportunities, 9-10hour days, Hourly billing at $55-per hour, Location – North York, ambiguous environment – DO NOT APPLY IF YOU ARE NOT WILLING TO WORK LONG HOURS.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
.NET:&#xD;
&#xD;
------&#xD;
&#xD;
-          16 of Java opportunities that we have is with a global bank : Permanent fulltime opportunities that pays Maximum upto 90K, Location - Mississauga&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested in applying then please respond with following:&#xD;
&#xD;
1) Please reply along with your most up-to-date resume attached. &#xD;
&#xD;
2) Availability: Immediately (or a date)&#xD;
&#xD;
3) Preference: Contract or Perm&#xD;
&#xD;
4) Current working status: Working or not working&#xD;
&#xD;
5) Rates: Contract Rates preferred / Perm rates prefer&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Please respond to ALL THREE EMAIL ADDRESSES&#xD;
&#xD;
Tim.Gorewich@randstad.ca; Saumil.Patel@randstad.ca; Diane.Servos@randstad.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
In your opinion, if you are senior for these roles we would still recommend that you us send us your resume as we might be able to assist you when the time is right for you.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are currently working, or are not interested in these roles but know an individual that you believe would be a good fit for any/all of the roles described above please do not hesitate to send their updated resume. &#xD;
&#xD;
Many thanks,&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Diane Servos | Recruitment Administrator Intern | Diane.Servos@randstad.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
Randstad Technologies (formerly Sapphire Canada)&#xD;
60 Bloor Street West, Suite 1400, Toronto, Ontario M4W 3B8&#xD;
T 416.962.9262 | TF 1.800.540.3594 | F 416.962.4489</content>
    <postId>6F71792A-95C2-4B13-A422-C619A182EF56</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-09T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>30 java developers</title>
</post>
