<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강윤정</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>The "Stella" awards rank up there with the Darwin awards. &#xD;
Stella Liebeck is the 81 year old lady who spilled coffee on herself and&#xD;
sued McDonalds, winning millions of dollars. This case inspired an annual&#xD;
award - The "Stella" Award - for the most frivolous lawsuits in the U.S.&#xD;
The following are this year's candidates: &#xD;
&#xD;
7. January 2000: Kathleen Robertson of Austin Texas was awarded $780,000&#xD;
by a jury of her peers after breaking her ankle tripping over a toddler&#xD;
who was running inside a furniture store. The owners of the store were&#xD;
understandably surprised at the verdict, considering the misbehaving&#xD;
little bastard was Ms. Robertson's son. &#xD;
&#xD;
6. June 1998: A 19 year old Carl Truman of Los Angeles won $74,000 and&#xD;
medical expenses when his neighbor ran over his hand with a Honda Accord. &#xD;
Mr. Truman apparently didn't notice there was someone at the wheel of the&#xD;
car, when he was trying to steal his neighbor's hubcaps. &#xD;
&#xD;
5. October 1998: Terrence Dickson of Bristol, Pennsylvania was leaving a&#xD;
house he had just finished robbing by way of the garage. He was not able&#xD;
to get the garage door to go up since the automatic door opener was&#xD;
malfunctioning. He couldn't reenter the house because the door connecting&#xD;
the house and garage locked when he pulled it shut. The family was on&#xD;
vacation. Mr. Dickson found himself locked in the garage for eight days. &#xD;
He subsisted on a case of Pepsi he found, and a large bag of dry dog food.&#xD;
&#xD;
He sued the homeowner's insurance claiming the situation caused him undue&#xD;
mental anguish. The jury agreed to the tune of $500,000 dollars. &#xD;
&#xD;
4. October 1999: Jerry Williams of Little Rock, Arkansas was awarded&#xD;
$14,500 and medical expenses after being bitten on the buttocks by his&#xD;
next door neighbor's beagle. The beagle was on a chain in its owner's&#xD;
fenced-in yard. &#xD;
The award was less than sought because the jury felt the dog might have&#xD;
been just a little provoked at the time by Mr. Williams who was shooting&#xD;
it repeatedly with a pellet gun. &#xD;
&#xD;
3. May 2000: A Philadelphia restaurant was ordered to pay Amber Carson of&#xD;
Lancaster, Pennsylvania $113,500 after she slipped on a soft drink and&#xD;
broke her coccyx. The beverage was on the floor because Ms. Carson threw&#xD;
it at her boyfriend 30 seconds earlier during an argument. &#xD;
&#xD;
2. December 1997: Kara Walton of Claymont, Delaware successfully sued the&#xD;
owner of a night club in a neighboring city when she fell from the&#xD;
bathroom window to the floor and knocked out her two front teeth. This&#xD;
occurred while Ms Walton was trying to sneak through the window in the&#xD;
ladies room to avoid paying the $3.50 cover charge. She was awarded&#xD;
$12,000 and dental expenses. &#xD;
&#xD;
1. And the winner is: Mr. Merv Grazinski of Oklahoma City. In November&#xD;
2000 Mr. Grazinski purchased a brand new 32 foot Winnebago motor home. On&#xD;
his first trip home, having joined the freeway, he set the cruise control&#xD;
at 70 mph and calmly left the driver's seat to go into the back and make&#xD;
himself a cup of coffee. Not surprisingly the Winnebago left the freeway,&#xD;
crashed and overturned. Mr. Grazinski sued Winnebago for not advising him&#xD;
in the handbook that he couldn't actually do this. He was awarded&#xD;
$1,750,000 plus a new Winnebago. (Winnebago actually changed their owners&#xD;
manuals because of this court case, just in case there are any other&#xD;
complete morons buying their vehicles.) &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>6F980DAB-C209-42B3-8D02-E31FC85F0032</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Stella award</title>
</post>
