<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>To me life is about me, myself, I and me again. If anybody ask me "what is the meaning of life ?". I will tell them “Life is all about me and myself”. I had always struggled that maybe I am very selfish or maybe I am not good person. I am going to drop those ideas for time being. I might change my mind later. At least for the time being I am selfish and I am full of it.&#xD;
&#xD;
I faced and challenged by my above though many times and failed miserably. However I have not altered my mind yet. Because I know I am right but my delivery wasn't good enough. I came to realization that in order to satisfy my needs I need to give little bits first. That is the reason why "Give and Take" not "Take and Give". Most of times we are going to invade other people's domain in order to satisfy our needs. We should learn how to get what I want without invading others.&#xD;
&#xD;
For instance why do we have meetings ?. Reason is to get projects or whatever objects to resolve and set the plan without interrupt or disturb other people's current plans. At least let them know we're coming to disturb in near future. We are not trained to be politicians or diplomats in nature. There are very seldom those exceptional cases. But we are not that lucky. &#xD;
&#xD;
Once again I am very selfish and life is all about me and myself. I need to be trained by many different invading skills such as how to persuade others, how to say "No" to others without pissing them off, how to ask without giving up a lot, how to make others becomes my friends in order to make my job easier, how to give orders without condescending others and how to listen prior to speak. Bottom line is "how can I get what I want with the least effort". I need others help/assistance.&#xD;
&#xD;
Without above skills does not matter how smart, how hardworking you are. You are not going anywhere. You are stuck. Think about it. You need to give up some in order to receive more. This is the reason why you need to&#xD;
- Honest&#xD;
- Sincere&#xD;
- Good communicator&#xD;
- Risk Taker &#xD;
- Good Listener&#xD;
- and many more&#xD;
&#xD;
Too much isn't it. But life is not fair. It is uphill battle all your life. If you have all the fame, knowledge and power, you do not have to do any of above. People will come to you and listen. But you are not people's person you are going to lose fame and power soon enough. Also you are not people's person you can get there in the first place.&#xD;
&#xD;
What the heck is Thomas talking about ? Life is about me and myself. Think about it. Really think about it. You like to get the best out of it. Think about it again.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tip : There are two truths in life "Tax 'n Death"&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>7034952C-30D5-4837-AD2D-DB6E4B63F118</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>What is the meaning of life according to Thomas Lee</title>
</post>
