<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This is for the Dept of Homeland Security.  They can ONLY bring on US Citizens, sorry...no green cards, canadians, ead, h1b, etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
MAX rate is 70/hour c2c&#xD;
One year, in Virginia&#xD;
&#xD;
J2EE &amp; BPEL Developer&#xD;
Position Summary&#xD;
Developer will play an integral role in the upgrades of BPEL applications from WBISF to WPS. This position will be responsible for building and upgrading BPEL applications integrated with Portlets. In addition, this position may be expected to later develop middle-tier Java-based services. Developer must be comfortable working in a heterogeneous technical environment.&#xD;
Candidate Profile and Experience Prerequisites&#xD;
Required Skills:&#xD;
•       5+ years of J2EE development.&#xD;
•       3+ years in EJB development and transaction management programming in a complex, large-scale environment involving the integration of J2EE applications with other environments.&#xD;
•       2+ years experience with integration technologies including XML, XPDL, BPEL, SOAP, and WSDL.&#xD;
•       2+ experience developing JSP/Servlets and in the use of STRUTS framework.&#xD;
•       2+ years experience with development and deployment on IBM Websphere application server platform.&#xD;
•       2+ years experience with use of XML, JAXB, Hibernate and web services in a J2EE environment.&#xD;
•       2+ years experience using the IBM Rational toolset, WSAD IE, WID.&#xD;
•       2+ years experience developing with IBM WebSphere Message Broker.&#xD;
•       5+ with J2EE concepts.&#xD;
•       Proficiency with portal themes and skins.&#xD;
•       Excellent debugging skills.&#xD;
•       Familiar with performance tuning.&#xD;
Optional but a plus:&#xD;
•       Sun certified on JAVA platform preferred.&#xD;
•       Exposure to other middleware products (IBM HTTP Server, Tivoli Web Seal, Tivoli Access Manager, DB2,  IBM Directory Server, Active Directory).&#xD;
Knowledge, Skills and Abilities&#xD;
•       Experience working in a Scrum or Agile environment.&#xD;
•       Familiarity with Design Patterns &amp; other Abstract Data Structures.&#xD;
•       Strong interpersonal, influencing and communications skills.&#xD;
•       Should have practical work experience in a multi-tiered architectural environment.&#xD;
•       Must be detail-oriented, extremely organized, with exceptional written and communication skills.&#xD;
•       Demonstrated a record of developing successful applications that are highly integrated and reliable.&#xD;
•       Ability to operate effectively, and with a sense of possibility, in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment.&#xD;
Academic Qualifications&#xD;
•       At least a four-year degree in Computer Science, MIS or a related field.&#xD;
•       Ability to operate effectively, and with a sense of possibility, in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Chuck Fried&#xD;
716-636-0070 ext 22&#xD;
Cell:  716-998-4665&#xD;
http://www.txmq.com&#xD;
&#xD;
Middleware solutions and staff augmentation services including permanent and temporary placements&#xD;
&#xD;
Follow me on Twitter:   www.twitter.com/chuckfried&#xD;
&#xD;
On Facebook www.facebook.com/chuckfried&#xD;
&#xD;
Look for me on LinkedIn!</content>
    <postId>703E78AD-D53F-4574-B059-2FB4C2877283</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-10-16T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>One Year Java contract-US Govt, MUST be Citizen</title>
</post>
