<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>요즈음 갑자기.. 나는 프로인가? 라는 질문이 저에게 강한 도전을 주고 있습니다. 인터넷에서 다음과 같은 리스트를 찾았기에 올립니다. 일단 읽어 보시구.. 자아비판 한번 해보시지요..&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional learns every aspect of the job. An amateur skips the learning process whenever possible.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional carefully discovers what is needed and wanted. An amateur assumes what others need and want.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional looks, speaks and dresses like a professional. An amateur is sloppy in appearance and speech.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional keeps his or her work area clean and orderly. An amateur has a messy, confused or dirty work area.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional is focused and clear-headed. An amateur is confused and distracted.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional does not let mistakes slide by. An amateur ignores or hides mistakes.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional jumps into difficult assignments. An amateur tries to get out of difficult work.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional completes projects as soon as possible. An amateur is surrounded by unfinished work piled on unfinished work.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional remains level-headed and optimistic. An amateur gets upset and assumes the worst.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional handles money and accounts very carefully. An amateur is sloppy with money or accounts.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional faces up to other people’s upsets and problems. An amateur avoids others’ problems.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional uses higher emotional tones: Enthusiasm, cheerfulness, interest, contentment. An amateur uses lower emotional tones: anger, hostility, resentment, fear, victim.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional persists until the objective is achieved. An amateur gives up at the first opportunity.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional produces more than expected. An amateur produces just enough to get by.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional produces a high-quality product or service. An amateur produces medium-to-low quality product or service.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional earns high pay. An amateur earns low pay and feels it’s unfair.&#xD;
&#xD;
- A professional has a promising future. An amateur has an uncertain future.&#xD;
&#xD;
The first step to making yourself a professional is to decide you ARE a professional.&#xD;
&#xD;
Are you a professional?&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>70FD2336-2490-477F-A82D-E61FC2C119F9</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-10-05T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>프로의식... 아마츄어와 무엇이 다른가 ?</title>
</post>
