<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>황성규</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I agree on your opinion and thanks for the good article.&#xD;
&#xD;
In fact, the 80:20 rule reminds me of my ex-manager.&#xD;
He used to mention 80:20 rule quite often.&#xD;
&#xD;
One thing I remember from him is ...&#xD;
&#xD;
As a software developer, we tend to make things 80%.&#xD;
And the other 20% remains imperfect.&#xD;
Maybe it's impossible making something 100% perfect especially in I.T. world.&#xD;
But, what he wanted to say was we need to change the 80:20 rule to 85:15 or even 90:10.&#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
thomas lee wrote:&#xD;
&gt; You must have heard about the 80 : 20 rule. It is a very common phrase that often gets used.  Such as 20 % of the people do 80 % of the work or a 20 % effort gets 80 % othe core PGM work done.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt;  There could be other examples. but I would like to talk about this rule under different circumstances, the "Personal effort or work habits"&#xD;
&gt; from an article I read.  The average person uses 80 % of their energies dealing with things that might happen such as what other peoples are going to think, what should I do or shouldn't do and etc. Average persons only use 20 % of total resource to productive things. Rather than worrying about things might happen. let's concentrate on things happen.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; For example there are persons that worry about their job security. Rather than worrying about their job security the persons are more contributing to the team or the company. Those individuals will have better job security than others because they are valuable. Even they are let go by the company. They are better prepared for next job or challanges.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; In my own estimation all the sucessful persons had the ability to convert negative energies to positive one. Succesful persons are optimistic and enthusiastic. Let's be a doer rather than a worryer. Let's change  80:20 rule to 70:30 even 60:40. When you are in 60:40 braket you are twice produtive than average.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; ps : Let's do one thing you do not like to do every day.&#xD;
&gt;      Don't do many things in one day. Let's do one things &#xD;
&gt;      you don't like to or things you forgot.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt;      Create big things to do list in your computer or on blank paper. List all the things you like to or not like to. Cross them out if you've done them or add new things if you forgot or new. You will see how much you are doing. Things could be work related or home related. You will see big changes in your life and you could enjoy your life a lot more.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Sincerely Yours   &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>73ED3E7E-E702-4DAB-A559-5BFC3399084A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>RE: 80 : 20 Rule</title>
</post>
