<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Our client has built a future friendly national team, one that embraces change and initiates opportunity, has a passion for growth, believes in spirited teamwork and has the courage to innovate. Our success is based as much on the dedication and hard work of our team as it is on the innovative wireless solutions we offer. &#xD;
&#xD;
Our commitment to providing our clients with unsurpassed coverage, cool phones, great rates and outstanding client care, is what we're all about. Join our team of wireless professionals working in one of Canada's fastest-growing industries and make your future friendly too. &#xD;
&#xD;
Position Overview:&#xD;
Our client is looking for qualified and seasoned professionals to fill numerous Business Systems Analyst positions in our Information Systems Development team in Scarborough. As a Business Systems Analyst, you will provide business contact, business and system functional requirements analysis and evaluation, documentation, project management and implementation of projects related to the support of initiatives of our internal business partners. Our current Business Systems Analyst opportunities are available in the following areas:&#xD;
&#xD;
·Systems for Sales and Distribution&#xD;
·Systems for Human Resources&#xD;
·Systems for Client Operations &#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
·Maintains ongoing, proactive relationship with our business partners of our client to facilitate planning and expectation management. &#xD;
·Responsible for reviewing, analyzing and evaluating business and functional requirements for client projects, which includes detailed documentation, process flows and data models. &#xD;
·Provides documentation of existing processes and systems.&#xD;
·Responsible for verification of systems components, flow charting of business processes and running standard models and methodologies. &#xD;
·Understands and applies business processes to the customer's specific market segment. &#xD;
·Facilitates agreement on scope, resourcing and cost estimates for the project. &#xD;
·Supports system application design and/or program design.&#xD;
·Aids in preparation of test plans and scripts related to the specific project and provides support through the Quality Assurance testing phase. &#xD;
·Supports the implementation process and production readiness by co-coordinating change management, IT operations and development, and the business.&#xD;
&#xD;
qualifications&#xD;
&#xD;
Education and Experience:&#xD;
&#xD;
·Minimum 5 years of Business Systems Analysis experience in an Information Systems Development environment, preferably within the telecommunications industry. &#xD;
·Good knowledge of wireless network technologies and n-tiered applications. &#xD;
·Demonstrated knowledge of application design, development, testing and implementation, methodologies and tools. &#xD;
·Excellent knowledge of a formal Systems Development Life Cycle methodology. &#xD;
·Familiar with relational database concepts, and client-server concepts &#xD;
·Experience with Java, Web Logic, e-Business, and J2EE is highly desired. &#xD;
·Good knowledge and experience with any of the following is strongly desired: wireless and e-Business applications, CRM systems, Call Centre applications, network element provisioning, telephony, POS and sales applications. &#xD;
&#xD;
Functional Competencies:&#xD;
&#xD;
·Knowledge of Business Workflow modeling and data modeling. &#xD;
·Use Case experience. &#xD;
·Delivery of functional presentations and demonstrations. &#xD;
·Knowledge of estimating technologies. &#xD;
·Strong presentation, project management and training skills/experience. &#xD;
·Demonstrated problem solving and analytical skills. &#xD;
·Excellent understanding of the support business processes. &#xD;
·Excellent written and verbal communication skills in both technical and non-technical environments. &#xD;
·Demonstrated ability to facilitate meetings and negotiations on deliverables, timelines and resourcing of projects. &#xD;
·Proficient with personal computer productivity tools such as Microsoft Office, MS Outlook and Project Management tools.&#xD;
&#xD;
Core Competencies:&#xD;
&#xD;
·Takes action to align tasks, objectives, and resources with strategic priorities. &#xD;
·Demonstrates support for corporate and business unit strategic direction. &#xD;
·Uses communication approaches that are effective and appropriate. &#xD;
·Strong inter-personal skills and team player to work with end-users to: &#xD;
  - Facilitate joint requirements definition; &#xD;
  - Find creative solutions to end-users' problems&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Matt Zweig&#xD;
Client Sales and Solutions &#xD;
Pegasus Consulting Inc. &#xD;
matt@pegsoft.com &#xD;
WWW.pegsoft.com &lt;http://WWW.pegsoft.com&gt; &#xD;
416-488-7007 X 232 (local) &#xD;
877-688-8818 X 232 (Toll Free) &#xD;
55 Eglinton Avenue East, Suite 208 &#xD;
Toronto, ON&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>754DB761-A7D4-4901-B935-B2C82AED9822</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-08-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Business Systems Analyst</title>
</post>
