<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Site Admin</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Source: The Dallas Morning News &#xD;
Publication date: 2001-03-16&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Mar. 16--Compaq Computer Corp. followed many of its technology peers by announcing Thursday that it would cut 5,000 jobs, or 7 percent of its workforce. &#xD;
The Houston-based company also lowered its earnings forecast for the first quarter. &#xD;
&#xD;
The personnel move is expected to cut costs as much as $600 million. &#xD;
&#xD;
"We see continued weakness in the U.S. economy, and resultant pricing pressures," said Michael Capellas, chairman and chief executive officer. &#xD;
&#xD;
Compaq said the job cuts will take place over the next four to six weeks and will be concentrated in three units: personal computers, marketing and supply-chain management. The company declined to disclose where the job cuts will occur, saying it has not yet notified all affected employees. &#xD;
&#xD;
In an e-mail to all Compaq employees, Mr. Capellas said the actions are necessary given the economic slowdown. &#xD;
&#xD;
"What started as a broad-based slide in consumer confidence has now spread to corporate capital spending. Market demand for traditional desktop PCs in both the consumer and commercial markets has been hit the hardest," he said. &#xD;
&#xD;
Compaq reduced its first-quarter earnings outlook to 12 cents to 14 cents a share, which is flat compared with the first quarter last year. Compaq estimated that revenue will range between $9 billion and $9.2 billion, or about 4 percent under the first quarter last year. &#xD;
&#xD;
The newest figures are significantly less than the 18 cents analysts expected, according to a survey by First Call/Thomson Financial. &#xD;
&#xD;
Compaq shares closed up 15 cents Thursday to $18.50. &#xD;
&#xD;
Many analysts anticipated Compaq's actions. "We cut our numbers given the Intel announcement last week on slowing NT server sales, which is a very profitable piece of business for Compaq," said Eric Rothdeutsch, of Robertson Stephens. &#xD;
&#xD;
Compaq will take a $125 million to $150 million restructuring charge in the first quarter. &#xD;
&#xD;
In an indication of how tough the market is for personal computers, Compaq said it will no longer maintain separate units for commercial and consumer PC operations. &#xD;
&#xD;
To save money, they will be combined into a single unit called the "access business group." &#xD;
&#xD;
Last month, Compaq's chief competitor, Dell Computer Corp. of Round Rock, Texas, laid off 1,700 people, citing similar reasons. &#xD;
&#xD;
Mr. Capellas said the company intends to "get aggressive" in the way it prices standard server computers, which he conceded would erode profit margins. He said server sales have slackened in the United States, particularly in the telecommunications industry. &#xD;
&#xD;
He said Compaq is winning new customers in Europe from its competitors by selling "bundled" products, which include hardware, software and services. He said these packages appeal to corporate customers with tight budgets. &#xD;
&#xD;
In the same announcement, Compaq said Jeff Clarke, vice president of finance and strategy for sales and services, was named chief financial officer. Jesse J. Greene Jr., who was CFO, was named senior vice president of strategic planning. &#xD;
&#xD;
----- &#xD;
&#xD;
To see more of The Dallas Morning News, or to subscribe to the newspaper, go to http://www.dallasnews.com/ &#xD;
&#xD;
(c) 2001, The Dallas Morning News. Distributed by Knight Ridder/Tribune Business News. CPQ, INTC, DELL, &#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>76F8BDC3-9FC4-44C7-ACCC-3A1FC084FFA3</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-03-16T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Compaq Announces 5,000 Job Cuts</title>
</post>
