<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>황성규</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2004-06-15T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Thanks</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Yahoo to launch 100MB free e-mail&#xD;
Last modified: June 15, 2004, 5:55 AM PDT&#xD;
By Jim Hu &#xD;
Staff Writer, CNET News.com&#xD;
&#xD;
               &#xD;
update Yahoo began offering on Tuesday 100MB of storage to people who use its free e-mail service. &#xD;
&#xD;
As part of an overall redesign of its mail service, Yahoo also upgraded Mail Plus paid users to 2GB of storage and lowered its subscription rate from $29.99 a year to $19.99. Other a la carte services, such as POP e-mail forwarding, are consolidated under this plan and will no longer be sold on a standalone basis. &#xD;
&#xD;
The storage boost comes as no surprise. Yahoo arch-rival Google in April announced plans to launch a free e-mail service called "Gmail" with 1GB of storage. The upcoming launch of Gmail has changed the landscape for free-e-mail users, but also raised privacy concerns because of Google's decision to serve advertisements based on scanning the content of e-mail text. Yahoo executives last month announced the company would offer its own storage upgrade as part of overall changes to the service. &#xD;
&#xD;
"There are new competitors on the scene, and we want to make sure the things we're focused on are important with users." &#xD;
--Brad Garlinghouse, Yahoo's&#xD;
VP of communications products  &#xD;
Brad Garlinghouse, Yahoo's vice president of communications products, said the changes were enacted to make "e-mail storage a nonissue." He acknowledged that competition was a factor as well. &#xD;
&#xD;
"There are new competitors on the scene, and we want to make sure the things we're focused on are important with users," Garlinghouse said. &#xD;
&#xD;
The new storage limits amount to a strategic turnaround for Yahoo. In 2002, the company began charging for various tiers of storage size for its photo and briefcase products. Yahoo also lowered its free e-mail memory from 6MB to 4MB for new members. &#xD;
&#xD;
Aside from allowing people to keep more e-mails, most changes to the new Yahoo Mail are cosmetic with a stress on making the service sleeker and faster. The product will also place more emphasis on a mail search bar at the top of the page. Unlike Google's, the Yahoo bar will not search e-mail text to serve advertisements, but will let people more easily hunt for buried correspondence. &#xD;
&#xD;
Garlinghouse also said the company will free 50 million identities into circulation. That means identities that have remained dormant will become available again for general use. While Yahoo has maintained a policy of recycling user identities after six months of dormancy, the company has taken a "very conservative approach" to offering these names back to users, Garlinghouse said. &#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>77D04019-910E-47AC-A972-D37828F3D8BD</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-06-15T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Yahoo to launch 100MB free e-mail</title>
</post>
