<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>박영준</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2010-08-24T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Excuse me, but where should it be the workplace? NJ, NY, CA, or TX? Also it seems contradictory as it mentions "Legally authorized to work in U.S. without sponsorship".</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>안녕하세요 &#xD;
캐나다 시민권 소유자며 미국에서 TN비자로 일할&#xD;
의향이 있으신분은 연락주시면 감사하겠습니다.&#xD;
참고로 TN비자는 Computer Science전공자에 한해&#xD;
발급하는것으로 알고 있습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
연락처 : peteryj.park@samsung.com&#xD;
&#xD;
JOB DESCRIPTION:&#xD;
We are a visionary leader in the IT Business Intelligence industry that is looking for an experienced software engineer to assist us with the maintenance, development, and implementation of web site and backend systems. The candidate must have a solid development background across multiple technical disciplines including J2EE web application development, Java client/server development, and Database Development. &#xD;
&#xD;
The role will primarily involve working with the Marketing and Customer Service stakeholders in defining, planning and implementing Marketing and Customer Service related content directives, but will also include some traditional user interface and application module implementation as well. Responsibilities cover the entire development lifecycle, from requirements gathering and brainstorming, analysis, and driving development, testing and documentation. &#xD;
&#xD;
Requirements:&#xD;
●	3+ years in Internet related system development including the ability to showcase advanced methods for Content Management, usage of templates and excellent communications skills&#xD;
●  Experienced Java Developer with either knowledge in web framework based development &#xD;
   and internet technologies (MVC Model, Struts, Java, Database, Weblogic, RIA, Web 2.0)&#xD;
●  Expertise in development and deploying content management system. &#xD;
   (Interwoven Teamsite experience preferred)&#xD;
●  Experience with web applications development in Eclipse environment&#xD;
●  Experience with either applications servers: Weblogic, Websphere&#xD;
●   Experience with Oracle database, multiple O/S's: UNIX platforms.&#xD;
●  BS/BA or higher in Computer Science or related field&#xD;
●  Must fluent in English and speaking in Korean fluently is a plus, &#xD;
●  Legally authorized to work in U.S. without sponsorship&#xD;
&#xD;
Special Skills:&#xD;
●	Goal oriented and self-motivated.&#xD;
● 	Candidate must have the ability to work independently or within a team environment. &#xD;
●	Strong oral and written communications skills with ability to create software design and engineering documents.&#xD;
●	Ability to multi-task and deliver high quality work under tight deadlines is essential.&#xD;
●	Ability to work in a fast paced environment is crucial.&#xD;
●       Ability to learn, excel and deliver at a quick pace is required.</content>
    <postId>7871E2F7-EB1A-42EC-AC27-44140D82C564</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>미주 samsung.com 개발자 급구!!!!</title>
</post>
