<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2004-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>그런 일이... 이런 이야기가 생각나네요. 칼이란 어떤 사람이 쓰느냐에 따라 그 의미가 완전히 달라진다는... 뜨거운 감자가 될만한 이슈같군요.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content> 제목에서 암시하다시피, 원하시는 분들의 이력서를 서로 공유하는 것을 제안하고자 합니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
 그 취지는 잡을 구하는 사람에서 아주 좋은 툴이 됨과 동시에, 자신의 위치와 능력을 제 점검할 수 있는 좋은 기회가 될 것이라고 생각합니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
원하시는 분의 이름을 남겨주십시요.(암호 :1)&#xD;
&#xD;
최덕선&#xD;
고상호&#xD;
이성기 &#xD;
박영선&#xD;
김경환&#xD;
&#xD;
*** I would like to clarify some of the concerns briefly.&#xD;
1. First of all, this is only voluntary participations as we do in our community.&#xD;
2. Second, we better answer "why we want to share" and "why we can not share". When these questions are reasonable/acceptable to yourself, then we can do actions.&#xD;
 Many of experts posted their profiles in the public(internet) to advertise themself. Some people share their work(code) in the open source communities.&#xD;
3. Third, this suggestion is not only for the job seeker but also the people who working now. The reason is that we are working in a very fast-paced environments. So I think it is nice to be equipped with some tools and some examples to be competitive in a very competitive situations.&#xD;
4. Fourth, again we better answer "does this profile contain too confidentail or sensitive information to show to others ? address/phone#/email address...etc. I would like to leave to you to decide. Personally, I do not see too personal information.&#xD;
5. Finally, I would like to honor many of our memebers who are helping all the time through the seminars and off-line times. I understand some worries and concerns about this suggestions publicly, but it is up to us how to utilize in a constructive ways.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>7939B0E2-F955-46B1-B494-F433F3C3E51C</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>리소스 공유</title>
</post>
