<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>허현옥</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Re: I have this Permanent Team leader of C++/Java/J2ee/Unix Scripting/Oracle development in Mississauga and I am wondering if you might know someone interested in it?&#xD;
&#xD;
Hide Details&#xD;
FROM:&#xD;
Glenn Steinberg&#xD;
 &#xD;
TO:&#xD;
allthatjava@yahoo.ca&#xD;
Message flagged Wednesday, September 21, 2011 9:21:34 PMMessage body&#xD;
Hello Hyeonok,&#xD;
Hope you are doing well? I have this Permanent Team leader of Java/J2ee/C++/Unix Scripting/Oracle development in a Leading Health Care company in Western Mississauga and I am wondering if you might know someone interested in it? They do want to start off with a 3 month contract (or it can go long-term) and then maybe it will flip to a Permanent position! BASE SALARY EXPECTATIONS is 85K (Maybe slightly higher), however we can talk about it! &#xD;
The team leader should play the following roles: Create and execute development plans according to business objectives, bridge between healthcare operational requirements and application software implementation, bridge between management and development team, leadership of the team, controller of software process, and application system architecture designer. The team lead will perform staff evaluation as well as mentor the team. This position Reports to the Director of Applications. &#xD;
Essential Functions are: Software process life cycle control, which includes requirement analysis, software specification writing, system architecture design, key component architecture design, implementation and programming quality control, testing organization, release and deployment planning, and maintenance control (ticket handling). Team management, which includes developers? difficulty solving, and team member cooperation control. Ready to be called at any time (24/7) for any urgent incident. Lead tester to control the development repository, testing process, and software documentation and user training. Introduce and try new technology. Performs other duties as required. Expreince includes: Experienced service-oriented, aspect-oriented, and component-oriented software design. High level knowledge in design patterns and architecture patterns. Very experienced in UML. Strong communication and leadership skills. Expert knowledge of the SDLC and QA and the ability to effectively modify this processes to ensure quality software. Ability to work in a fast paced environment. Experience: 5+ years experience of development team leader, team management, and software process control. 5+ years senior level development experience on Oracle and database modeling. 5+ years senior level development experience on Java (Spring and Servlet are mandatory), 5+ years senior level development experience on C++ and Unix scripting. 5+ years very strong experience in system programming, TCP/IP networking, and client-server architecture. 3+ years release management experience&#xD;
Other requirements: Health Care industry experience preferred, however not a must! May require after hours and weekend work. Must possess excellent verbal and written communication skills and the ability to to interact in a professional manner with all stakeholders. Must be able to handle confidential information discreetly. &#xD;
If you know anyone interested in any of these, please have them contact me, and I thank you in advance for any considerations that you may have in this matter!!&#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
Glenn&#xD;
&#xD;
Glenn&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Glenn H. Steinberg, President&#xD;
H.B.Sc., M.Sc.Phm., Ph.D.&#xD;
&#xD;
Glenn Partners Staffing Solution Inc.&#xD;
4950 Yonge St., Suite 2200&#xD;
Toronto, ON&#xD;
M2N 6K1&#xD;
Office: 416 218 5557 ext. 2198 &#xD;
Alt.: 416 512 1179 &#xD;
www.glennpartners.com</content>
    <postId>7B9A8DCC-0075-4A5D-8089-9ED2E3B8F516</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Permanent Team leader of C++/Java/J2ee/Unix Scripting/Oracle</title>
</post>
