<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이현정</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>How To Keep A Healthy Level Of Insanity&#xD;
&#xD;
1. At lunch time, sit in your parked car with sunglasses on and point a hair dryer at passing cars.  See if they slow down.&#xD;
&#xD;
2. Page yourself over the intercom. Don't disguise your voice.&#xD;
&#xD;
3. Every time someone asks you to do something, ask if they want fries with that.&#xD;
&#xD;
4. Put your garbage can on your desk and label it "in"&#xD;
&#xD;
5. Put decaf in the coffee maker for 3 weeks.  Once everyone has Gotten over their caffeine addictions, switch to espresso.&#xD;
&#xD;
6. In the memo field of all your cheques, write "for sexual favors".&#xD;
&#xD;
7. Finish all your sentences with "in accordance with the prophecy."&#xD;
&#xD;
8. Don't use any punctuation marks&#xD;
&#xD;
9. As often as possible, skip rather than walk.&#xD;
&#xD;
10. Ask people what sex they are. Laugh hysterically after they answer.&#xD;
&#xD;
11. Specify that your drive-through order is "to go".&#xD;
&#xD;
12. Sing along at the opera.&#xD;
&#xD;
13. Go to a poetry recital and ask why the poems don't rhyme.&#xD;
&#xD;
14. Put mosquito netting around your work area. Play a tape of jungle sounds all day.&#xD;
&#xD;
15. Five days in advance, tell your friends you can't attend their party because you're not in the mood.&#xD;
&#xD;
16. Have your coworkers address you by your wrestling name, Rock Hard Kim.&#xD;
&#xD;
17. When the money comes out the ATM, scream "I won!", "I won!" "3rd time this week!!!!!"&#xD;
&#xD;
18. When leaving the zoo, start running towards the parking lot, yelling "run for your lives, they're loose!!"&#xD;
&#xD;
19. Tell your children over dinner. "due to the economy, we are going to have to let one of you go."&#xD;
&#xD;
And the final way to keep a healthy level of insanity.......&#xD;
20. Send this e-mail to everyone in your address book, even if they sent it to you or asked you not to send them stuff like this.&#xD;
&#xD;
Have a nice day!&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>7C18F021-1737-4AEA-8815-6FAEEA5D1BF3</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-05T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Subject:        FW: Laugh out Loud</title>
</post>
