<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Toronto, GTA   &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Team Lead SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER Function Note: The Sr. Web Developer is responsible for .net software infrastructure, from initial design through the full Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), guiding a growing team of intermediate and entry-level developers. They work closely with the IS&amp;T Director to ensure the Executive are kept abreast of development efforts and are able to plan accordingly. Taking concepts and ideas to the Software Design stage, through Build Ensure appropriate Quality Assurance is applied at all stage Ensure impeccable, secure code Working with the Director of IS&amp;T, build out multi-year, multi-phase plan for software development, based Ensure efficient use of resources, including appropriate use of technologies (databases, programming languages, Integrated Development Environments, etc) Ensure the development team work within the policies and processes set by the director of IS&amp;T Ensure that form isn't lost in function Ensure that Reliability, Availability, Maintainability, Performance, and Security (RAMPS) is part of the design philosophy Provide order and process to R&amp;D, choosing a methodology (waterfall, agile etc), providing a defensible time-line based development plan Requirement Note: Knowledge PHP, Perl, SQL, HTTP, DHTML, CSS, XML University degree or college diploma or equivalent experience Skills/Abilities Professional and courteous Superior communication skills including a strong writing ability are a must Excellent administration and   [view full job] &#xD;
 &#xD;
Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location &#xD;
  &#xD;
Type Permanent &#xD;
Advertiser Advanced Recruitment Consultants (Employment Agency) &#xD;
Contact Hr &#xD;
Ref JS7624 &#xD;
Date 17/04/2009 07:32:02</content>
    <postId>7DA0020E-D205-4809-876A-96761183A911</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-04-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Team Lead SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER</title>
</post>
