<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This is the internal job posting in my company.&#xD;
&#xD;
Please let me know if anybody is interested or know who has &#xD;
interests in this position.&#xD;
&#xD;
............................................&#xD;
&#xD;
Position:		Risk  Analyst&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:	 	Risk Management&#xD;
			3 Concorde Gate, Don Mills&#xD;
  &#xD;
Posting Date:	Nov 4, 2003		Closing Date:  Nov 10, 2003&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Reporting  to the Director Risk Management   This position is responsible for performing research, analysis and monitoring on credit portfolio performance as well as for supporting marketing and loan development initiatives through data retrieval and tracking.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Portfolio Analysis&#xD;
Identifies opportunities to reduce delinquency and write-offs for assigned portfolio, improve growth and increase service charge revenue, by reviewing various operational reports against forecasted measures and performing analysis of underlying trends and anomalies. &#xD;
&#xD;
Marketing Support&#xD;
Supports marketing programs / campaigns, by providing data expertise and monitoring on selected segments / accounts and identifying new targets based on performance and characteristics similarity, in order to maximize profits and minimize the risk for the company. &#xD;
&#xD;
Reporting&#xD;
Prepares standard and ad hoc risk related reports such as delinquency tracking and vintage reports, using queries and specialized reporting tools including SAS and Easytrieve.&#xD;
&#xD;
Data Management&#xD;
Develops tables, views, and queries using SQL and SAS programming in order to identify, retrieve and compile data from databases, in support of the analytical process. Liaises with database administrator to ensure data integrity and accuracy.  &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Knowledge, Experience, Skills&#xD;
Requires minimum college diploma or equivalent work experience with three or more years of data analysis and/or database management skills. &#xD;
Advanced knowledge of SQL, PC or mainframe SAS programming languages required along with strong Microsoft Excel skills. Additional computer language skills such as Visual Basic and C++ would be an asset. &#xD;
Must have strong analytical and problem solving skills, deliver accurate and detailed results and be capable of handling multiple priorities. &#xD;
Knowledge of statistical methods an asset.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>7F1016BD-4735-4FA5-B633-0E7D1781511C</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-11-04T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Risk  Analyst</title>
</post>
