<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2003-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>CORBA가 문제로군요. 흠...</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>최근 며칠 사이에 에이전트로 부터 몇개의 이메일을 받았는데, 대부분이 아주 오래전에 보낸 이력서를 보고 연락을 했더군요.&#xD;
그중 한 에이전트는 "the marketplace is heating up"이라고 하는군요. 잡을 알아보시는 분들에게는 좋은 기회라고 생각합니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
그중 한 에이전트가 다음과 같은 개발자를 구하고 있습니다(다른 에이전트들은 구체적으로 기술한것이 없어서, 연락을 해보고 가능한 여기에 포스팅하도록 하겠습니다):&#xD;
&#xD;
As Systems Analyst, you will have an analysis and programming background&#xD;
working with web technology and database systems such as Oracle . You have&#xD;
worked within a formal systems analysis and design methodology, and are&#xD;
able to write high level and detailed  requirements and design&#xD;
documentation ( ie user requirements,  version descriptions and other&#xD;
documents).  Your written communication skills must be very good and you&#xD;
must still have the ability to read code and estimate the impact of&#xD;
requested changes on the existing systems. This is considered an&#xD;
Intermediate level position within the team.&#xD;
&#xD;
NOTE    Candidates could be an existing Progammer Analysts who has had&#xD;
analysis and design experience, has an interest/aptitude for this work,&#xD;
and wishes to do this full time .  There will be very little coding in this&#xD;
job - the emphasis of the work is analyzing and documenting the existing&#xD;
reporting systems which will be re-engineered beginning in 2004 for&#xD;
deployment on as J2EE apps on WebLogic server.&#xD;
&#xD;
    Requirements&#xD;
    · Post-secondary degree in Computer Science or equivalent work&#xD;
    experience&#xD;
    · 3-5 years of experience in systems analysis support/development and&#xD;
    process development&#xD;
    · Expertise in systems processes analysis, relational databases,&#xD;
    client-server system architecture, web system architecture&#xD;
    · Strong team management and interpersonal skills&#xD;
    · Attentive to detail and work plan deadlines&#xD;
    · Excellent oral and written communication skills including&#xD;
    facilitation and presentation skills&#xD;
    · Knowledge of industry best practices in work planning, software&#xD;
    testing, gathering requirements, documenting functional specifications&#xD;
    and software quality assurance techniques&#xD;
    · Ability to work a flexible schedule to accommodate project deadlines&#xD;
    including limited travel and on call rotation&#xD;
&#xD;
    Technical Skills needed:  a programming background with Java  (&#xD;
    servlets, JSP) , XML, CORBA ,  and the ability to write clear and&#xD;
    concise systems documentation&#xD;
&#xD;
    Assets&#xD;
&#xD;
    Previous Experience in Dental Insurance and/or extended health&#xD;
    insurance industry.&#xD;
&#xD;
관심있으신 분은 제에게 이력서를 보내주세요.&#xD;
jameslee99@sympatico</content>
    <postId>83E6D391-2916-4F86-9DF9-AFAB2A6C6BB5</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Job market is heating up</title>
</post>
