<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Brendan,&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Please see below for the JD….&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
As a Technical Lead/Manager, you will be responsible for all the overall planning, execution, and success of complex technical projects. The Technical Lead/Manager needs to be a technical leader and motivator who is comfortable leading the software engineer team in a high-pressure and dynamic environment. Technical Lead/Manager is expected to contribute technically to all projects.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
III.           Accountabilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
·        Provides leadership and management to Internet Capabilities Group for new projects execution, application design and smooth daily operations. Maintains awareness of new technologies and trends and identifies practical opportunities.  Also is responsible for Disaster Recovery. (40%)&#xD;
&#xD;
·        Writes client and server-side code for web-based applications, creates robust high-volume production applications and develops prototypes quickly.  Has a strong understanding of, and practical experience with, java web application development. (30%)&#xD;
&#xD;
·        Proactively interfaces with other teams and stakeholders, creates and updates relevant documentation and provides support to business users. (20%)&#xD;
&#xD;
·        Strong leadership skills. Becomes trusted advisor to IT and business group. Develops effective Human Resources within team to meet current and future departmental and corporate objectives. (10%)&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
IV.                Qualifications:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Specific training or job experience required before appointment includes:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
·         BA/BS degree in Computer Science&#xD;
&#xD;
·         At least 10 years of web application programming experience.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Strong Java skills and object oriented design experience, including working knowledge of core libraries, design patterns, JSP, Servlets, Spring Framework and Hibernate on both Windows and *nix environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Excellent database development skills including advance SQL programming, a solid understanding of database technologies including Oracle, MySQL and MS SQL&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Excellent skill on XML parsing, payment gateway integration and application security&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experiences with JavaScript, CSS, PHP, ASP, .NET, Objective-C and AJAX desired.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experiences with Apache, Tomcat and open source technologies desired.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experiences with distributed systems, large-scale storage systems and mobile applications desired.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
&#xD;
Sean Kelly&#xD;
&#xD;
Consultant – Information Technology Division&#xD;
&#xD;
Innovative Management Solutions&#xD;
&#xD;
Grady Management Group Inc. (Contract Division)&#xD;
1881 Yonge St. Suite 708&#xD;
Toronto, Ontario M4S 3C4&#xD;
(416) 515-2939 Ext. 260&#xD;
sean@imsgroup.com</content>
    <postId>84255D13-5B8E-4B78-AC6E-D72A83AE4506</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Technical Lead/Manager, Perm</title>
</post>
