<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>First assumption&#xD;
&#xD;
By year 2010 or 2015 Whites will be the minority race in USA. Population ratio 30: 20 : 40 :10, Blacks, Hispanics, Whites and Asians. Whites need to alliance with other color of skin. It could be Hispanics or Asians in my perspective. Let’s say Whites pick Asians as their partner. The way Whites treat us will be upgraded drastically. Our children’s way of life will be quite different. Their social status will be upgraded and role of our children will be very crucial to the future of North America. I do not think Canada will be any different. I want to be ready for the future. The way we educate our children or way of our though process needs to be adjusted. We will be no longer the guest of the society. We will be the leader. If Korea get united, the situation will be improved for a lot better.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Second assumption&#xD;
&#xD;
I have been here in Canada for some time. I always feel I have more similarity with Japanese and Taiwanese than Hong Kong people. Of course Peoples from Hong Kong are not  real Chinese. When I went to Japan for business trip, I felt very comfortable. However at Hong Kong I felt remorse or distant. Korean Trend starts from two counties Vietnam and Taiwan. I thought about the reasons why. My conclusion is we have the same wavelength. We all share the same cultures.&#xD;
&#xD;
Comparison between   Korean and     Chinese&#xD;
                                  Hot temper       patience&#xD;
                                  Party animal      not really&#xD;
                                  Doer                  thinker&#xD;
                                  Trendy              conservative&#xD;
                              Make it happen      take time&#xD;
 &#xD;
Third assumption&#xD;
&#xD;
Koreans are direct inherited from main Mongolian bloodline. Our brother countries are Turkey, Vietnam, Middle Asia (Stan countries), Eskimos and North America Indians. Korea is the part of big Mongolian picture.&#xD;
First emigration  - from Magnolia to North America through Bering strait.&#xD;
Second emigration &amp;#8211; gradual movement of Huns, Turk + Mongolian  &#xD;
                                Invasion to Europe including Russia and China&#xD;
Third   emigration &amp;#8211; us&#xD;
&#xD;
Fourth assumption&#xD;
&#xD;
The winners have written history. Those winners have a lot of things in common. I like to view only one thing in this article. “Speed &amp;#8211; highway of some sort”&#xD;
Ex) Asia to America &amp;#8211; Ice highway during ice age : Eskimo and   &#xD;
                                                                               Indians&#xD;
      Roman Empire &amp;#8211; All the road towards Rome : old brick style &#xD;
                                                                            highway&#xD;
      Mongolian Invasion to Europe : use horse as carries, vehicle &#xD;
                              and battle weapon    Eurasia prairie as highway&#xD;
      English common wealth : use ship to exploit, sea as highway&#xD;
      America : build highway as we know with mass production of &#xD;
                     automobiles&#xD;
      Korea     : use Internet as virtual information highway&#xD;
&#xD;
My conclusion&#xD;
&#xD;
We have been reading the history written by Chinese, Japanese and European. It is about time we should write our own history by perspective of Mongolian. Mongol was the biggest empire in the history. The first people in America continent both North and South was Mongolian. Turkey controlled Europe for 600 years, the longest reign of European history.&#xD;
My observation of Mongolian &#xD;
- have never been in slavery : always ruler status&#xD;
- very adoptable : learn from the mistakes. Win a lot more than lose&#xD;
- adventurous : go West go East every which way and succeed&#xD;
- never giveup : do not accept no for answer&#xD;
- trustworthy : cruelty to the opposition but give our soul to our friend &#xD;
- smart : intelligent and physical smart&#xD;
&#xD;
I am very proud being Korean and I want to strive for immense possibility. Glory of our future is on our way. Let’s get ready.  &#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>84607FF2-6EBB-4B6F-9649-676ADF3B413D</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>What are we doing here in Canada ?</title>
</post>
