<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>RFS Number:             154922&#xD;
&#xD;
Veritaaq Toronto is currently looking for a Sr. Systems Analyst to take on a 70 day contract with the Ministry of Transportation in the GTA.   The System Analyst will be responsible for the design, development, maintenance and enhancement activities for applications that support the core programs for the Road User Safety Division.   If you are interested in learning more about this opportunity please contact Mike Thomson at miket@veritaaq.ca or by phone at 416-360-6120.&#xD;
&#xD;
Deliverables: This assignment will include the completion of the systems/user acceptance testing, implementation and post implementation support. This will include:&#xD;
&#xD;
   1. Work with the Business and Programmer Analysts to prepare detailed Technical Specifications and Design documents as required.&#xD;
&#xD;
2.    Create object-oriented models in UML as design artifacts using tools such as Power Designer.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
   3. Provide assistance in preparation of the Test Strategy and Test Plan for Unit and&#xD;
&#xD;
            Integration testing.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
   4. Develop/enhance JEE middle-tier systems using Java, EJB, JSP, Servlets, JDBC, JPA, XML (DOM, SAX, XSLT), DHTML/HTML, Web Service, WebLogic, Toplink, Oracle.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
   5. Prepare fully documented operational procedures for system and production system support staff as required.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
   6. Test the system and meet the acceptance requirements of the implementation.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
   7. Provide problem resolution support to database staff, system and user acceptance test teams, and other staff members.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
   8. Co-ordinate system development activities and technical consultative support to other staff members.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
   9. Provide knowledge transfer to ministry staff at all stages of this assignment.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
  10. Provide consultation support to the user community as required.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
  11. Design test cases and perform unit testing.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
  12. Support systems and user testing.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
  13. Resolve defects wherever possible.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
  14. Prepare implementation package.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
  15. Provide post implementation support.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Required Skills and Knowledge&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
The mandatory skills must include the requirements for the Systems Analyst role level 2 as specified in the Task-based I&amp;IT Consulting Services VOR 1019.  Additional mandatory skills are as follow:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Solid experience in development of N-tier applications, middleware and gateways.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Knowledge of, and experienced with the following computing environments:&#xD;
&#xD;
    * MQ, TCP/IP, WAN/LAN environment&#xD;
    * Database: Oracle&#xD;
    * Operating Platforms: Unix (Solaris),  Windows (Server)&#xD;
    * Web/Application Servers: WebLogic, Microsoft IIS&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with Microsoft Visual Basic and ASP&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with SQL&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with UI design principles and guidelines.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with Object Oriented Analysis &amp; Design using UML – Use Case, Class, Sequence, Collaboration and State diagrams.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience in developing web-based applications using JEE (Java, EJB, JPA, JSP, Servlets, JDBC, JNDI), XML using DOM, SAX, XSLT, DHTML/HTML, Struts, Javascript, Web Services.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with JEE Design Patterns.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with toolsets that support object oriented languages and web application development including:&#xD;
&#xD;
o      Vision Control and Build tools: (i.e. Harvest, or similar, Ant)&#xD;
&#xD;
o      UML modeling tools&#xD;
&#xD;
o      Eclipse&#xD;
&#xD;
o      JUnit, Log4J&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Excellent analytical, problem solving, communication (verbal and written), and interpersonal skills.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         A team player with the ability to coordinate multiple projects with competing priorities and strict deadlines.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Proven ability to perform to successful completion assignment of high magnitude and complexity.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Desirable Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
The desirable skills are:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Familiar with PC COBOL&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Object to Relational mapping: e.g. Toplink&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Power Designer&#xD;
&#xD;
·         IBM IMS Connect&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with software based load balancing and clustering&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Knowledge of PKI&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Knowledge of emerging IT technologies and trends&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Mike Thomson&#xD;
Technical Recruiter, VERITAAQ&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
W 416-360-6120&#xD;
&#xD;
F  416-360-8639</content>
    <postId>87528017-7FA1-4709-AF28-3664546E7BA8</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-12-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>MTO Contract - Downsview, 70 working days.</title>
</post>
