<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이홍식</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>POSTED AT 5:26 PM EDT    Friday, September 27&#xD;
Markets: Dow falls 300 points&#xD;
By ROMA LUCIW &#xD;
Globe and Mail Update&#xD;
&#xD;
...Pervasive(만연, 온통퍼짐,충만) worries about the health of the U.S. economy, the possibility of a war in the Middle East and continued worries about corporate governance (통제, 지배, 관리) are holding stocks back...&#xD;
&#xD;
미국경제의 건전성에 대한 우려가 충만해 있는데다가  중동지대의 전쟁발발 가능성, 게다가&#xD;
기업의 (회계부정) 통제에 대한 끊임없는 문제등이 주식시장의 발을 동여매고 있음.&#xD;
&#xD;
per·vade &#xD;
－ v.t. (-vad·ed, -vad·ing) [Ⅲ[명]([부])] &lt;장소에&gt; 온통 퍼지다, 고루 미치다, 성해지다, 보급되다; &lt;냄새·감정·분위기 등이&gt; …에 배어들다, 충만하다.&#xD;
ㆍ a kitchen ∼d with the aroma of spices 양념 냄새가 가득한 부엌.&#xD;
ㆍ The holiday spirit ∼d the air. 휴일 기분이 주위에 충만해 있었다.&#xD;
ㆍ Corruption ∼s the city. 부정 부패가 시 전체에 만연되어 있다.&#xD;
ㆍ A curious happiness ∼d his entire being. 그는 형언할 수 없는 행복감으로 충만해 있었다.&#xD;
[어원]&#xD;
☞ 라틴어 pervadere에서. (per- 통하여 ＋ vadere 가다). ▷ INVADE, EVADE, WADE&#xD;
▷ -vad·er n., -va·sion n., -va·sive adj.&#xD;
&#xD;
(from Cambridge International Dictionary of English)&#xD;
pervade&#xD;
verb [T] &#xD;
FORMAL &#xD;
(of qualities, characteristics or smells) to spread through (a place or thing) and be present in every part of it &#xD;
성질, 특성, 혹은 냄새가 온통 퍼짐, 그 여파가 온 사방에 존재함&#xD;
An intense poetic quality pervades her novels.&#xD;
The film is a reflection of the violence that pervades American culture.&#xD;
As she walked through the office, her perfume pervaded the whole room. [T]&#xD;
&#xD;
pervasive&#xD;
adjective &#xD;
FORMAL &#xD;
If a quality, characteristic or smell is pervasive, it is present or noticeable throughout a thing or place. &#xD;
The influence of Freud is pervasive in her work.&#xD;
There is a pervasive smell of diesel in our garage.&#xD;
The government's reforms are being undermined by the all-pervasive corruption in the country. &#xD;
&#xD;
m-w dictionary...&#xD;
: to become diffused throughout every part of &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>87A3D4AB-C258-4B86-B439-F2C82C36CA34</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>pervasive</title>
</post>
