<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&#xD;
I am currently looking for a Senior Java Developer for one of our client in Toronto. Below is the job description. If you are interested by such an opportunity, please forward me your resume in MS Word format along with your salary expectations at jean@proex.ca.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Thanks,&#xD;
Jean-Sebastien Leroux&#xD;
President&#xD;
PROEX&#xD;
416-502-2575&#xD;
jean@proex.ca&#xD;
www.proex.ca&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Senior Java Developer&#xD;
Location: Toronto &#xD;
Our client has developed a proven technology that enhances the delivery of networking solutions in a variety of Service Provider environments. With patent protected technology and an installed customer base they are able to offer a unique opportunity to work in an emerging organization with a proven product. &#xD;
As part of the evolution of their core product line, they are looking for developers to participate in taking their product to the next level. Working as integral members of the development team, the successful candidates will be responsible for contributing to product architecture, performing software design, and implementing the software. &#xD;
&#xD;
They are seeking candidates with proven expertise in the development of mission critical software that is deployed on a large scale. You will work with Team Leads, Architects, and other Senior Developers within the Product Development team, wherein you will be responsible for detailed OO design, coding, unit testing, and integration. &#xD;
&#xD;
Specific activities will involve: &#xD;
&#xD;
Be responsible for key components from analysis, through to design and implementation &#xD;
Provide work estimates for software development effort &#xD;
Design, write, test, and document software &#xD;
Ensure that the software meets product specifications &#xD;
Work within formal software development processes &#xD;
Identify and resolve bugs &#xD;
Successful candidate must have a background that encompasses: &#xD;
&#xD;
Over six years of software development industry experience &#xD;
Over three years of formal Object Oriented design experience &#xD;
Over four years of Java server-side development experience in a Unix environment &#xD;
University degree in engineering, computer science or related education &#xD;
Strong understanding of, and experience with, formal software development processes &#xD;
Experience with object modeling / CASE tools and UML &#xD;
Strong written and oral communications skills &#xD;
Experience working in a fast paced environment &#xD;
Experience working on commercial software products &#xD;
&#xD;
Additional Skills which are desired:&#xD;
C++&#xD;
Experience with TogetherSoft Control Center &#xD;
Experience building commercial software products &#xD;
Experience with SIP, VOIP, CTI, Enterprise telephony extremely beneficial &#xD;
Experience with SOAP, XML, sockets, threads &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>8843B88A-9F49-48E8-98A2-987F154881B9</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-10-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>C++ network developer</title>
</post>
