<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2010-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>I'm conracting at TD Securities since Monday this week. Murex is one of the source systems that provides risk analytic data. You'd learn quite a lot about the capital market, wholesale banking and trades, etc.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>My name is Varnika Sharma, an IT Recruiter from Bevertec Cst Inc., and I am contacting you for a job opportunity with a client of ours. Please review the below given job specs to confirm your interest and availability by earliest possible. Thank you and I look forward to your response&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Business:  Wholesale Banking&#xD;
&#xD;
Division/Region:  TD Securities Technology Solutions&#xD;
&#xD;
Report Location:  66 Wellington St.,  Toronto,  ON&#xD;
&#xD;
Job type : Full Time / Perm&#xD;
&#xD;
Hours:  M - F         &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Title:  Java Software Developer (Back end developer expertise)&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Department Overview: &#xD;
Wholesale Banking Technology Solutions&#xD;
We are seeking a candidate for the position of a Java Software Developer within the Global Equity Derivatives and FX Options group. &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description: &#xD;
At TD Securities, we currently use Murex (3rd party product) as our trading platform for Equity Derivatives and FX Options.  The candidate for this position will be responsible for developing applications that sit outside of Murex, but interact with the platform and database that is proprietary to Murex.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities&#xD;
&#xD;
Candidates will be involved in delivering new technology solutions and functionality to support the Equity Derivatives and FX Options businesses.  This will include the systems analysis, design, development, build, testing, and documentation of new features and enhancements based on the requirements from the Front/Middle/Back office, while working with other developers and business analysts.  The candidate must have the ability to design, develop, test and document complex programs, while working on multiple concurrent projects in an ongoing changing environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Some possible projects include the design and development of the following:&#xD;
&#xD;
    * Straight-through processes (STP) for uploading trade feeds&#xD;
    * Automated market data input process&#xD;
    * Process for computing VAR/Stress/P&amp;L reports&#xD;
    * Various web applications&#xD;
    * Status tracking, scheduling and monitoring applications&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
The more senior candidates will have technical leadership responsibility, including directing and mentoring of junior members, technical design and implementation management.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Qualifications/Skills/Experience: &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Minimum 3 years application development experience.&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with Java, XML, SQL, jBPM development&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with Web Development, Web Services, J2EE, Struts, AJAX&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Experience with source control, Eclipse, jProbe, ANT and C++ would be an asset&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Excellent verbal and written communication skills&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Excellent analytical and creative problem solving skills&#xD;
Experience with development in the financial industry is desirable&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Ability to multi-task and work on multiple concurrent projects&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Flexibility to work in an ongoing changing environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Ability to work both in teams and individually&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Specific Educational Requirements/Accreditations:&#xD;
&#xD;
·         University Degree or equivalent work experience&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Best regards,&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Varnika Sharma&#xD;
IT Resource Consultant&#xD;
Bevertec Cst Inc&#xD;
5935 Airport Rd, Suite 400&#xD;
Mississauga , Ontario L4V 1W5&#xD;
Tel: 416-695-7525 ext: 270&#xD;
Fax 416-695-7526&#xD;
Email: vsharma@bevertec.com&#xD;
&#xD;
Please feel free to visit our website www.bevertec.com</content>
    <postId>89048847-C9DA-433F-8F14-E718FB827CBE</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Software Developer Job opportunity /Job # 1039</title>
</post>
