<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2009-11-18T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>최덕선씨와 통화했는데요, MFX란 회사고요, Don Mills와 Eglinton에 있습니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Location : Markham&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
ROLE:              Senior J2EE Developer&#xD;
  &#xD;
SERVICE AREA:              Open Technology             &#xD;
 &#xD;
REPORTING TO:              Manager&#xD;
 &#xD;
*Client allows you to work from home on Tuesdays and Thursdays.&#xD;
 &#xD;
JOB RESPONSIBILITIES:&#xD;
 &#xD;
·              Provide fast and quality production support to customers by closely working with the BAs and customers to analyze and resolve issues through data and/or code fixes.&#xD;
·              Design and implement new product feature enhancements and provide recommendations on best approaches.&#xD;
·              Work with a team of developers and/or independently as needed to execute tasks within the allotted timeframe and deliver quality solutions. Provide guidance to junior staff as required.&#xD;
·              Conduct thorough unit testing and assist the BAs with functional, system and interface testing. &#xD;
·              Analyze business requirements and provide accurate technical work estimates. &#xD;
·              Perform other duties as required.&#xD;
 &#xD;
TECHNICAL QUALIFICATIONS:&#xD;
 &#xD;
Must Have&#xD;
·               Strong communication skills (both verbal and written)&#xD;
·              7-10 years of experience in the design, development and deployment of n-tier enterprise applications using industry standard J2EE, utilizing technologies such as Servlets, MVC, JSP using Struts framework, Hibernate, EJB, and JDBC&#xD;
Must have frontend and backend support experience with J2EE&#xD;
·              Familiar with Design Patterns and SDLC process&#xD;
·              Proficient in HTML, Javascript, XML and XSLT.&#xD;
·              Proficient in SQL Inner join &amp; Outer join&#xD;
·              Excellent analytical, debugging and problem solving skills.&#xD;
·              Excellent team player with strong interpersonal skills.&#xD;
·              Ability to design, develop and test new enhancements using various J2EE technologies.&#xD;
·              Experience with WebLogic 6.1 or 8.1 or WebSphere&#xD;
·        Frontend and Backend support experience with J2EE&#xD;
 &#xD;
Nice to Have not mandatory&#xD;
·              Familiarity with Unix, MQ Series, and LDAP.&#xD;
·              Working knowledge of oracle 8i/9i, and PL/SQL&#xD;
·              Visual Basic 6, VB.Net, COM, DCOM, ActiveX, Excel and Word VBA, and MS SQL Server.&#xD;
·        Insurance&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
EDUCATION:&#xD;
·              University Degree or College Diploma&#xD;
 &#xD;
              HANDS ON EXPERIENCE IS A MUST&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Debbiera@intps.com&#xD;
&#xD;
Debbie Rae&#xD;
INTPS Inc&#xD;
(International Placement Services)&#xD;
905-940-6003</content>
    <postId>89B681ED-ED78-42D8-8694-9C01842F03D7</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-11-18T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2EE 6 month contract - working home two days a week</title>
</post>
