<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권경화</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Christian Harris&#xD;
Senior Consultant&#xD;
www.gurulink.ca&#xD;
c. 416.562.6525&#xD;
w. 416.642.6846&#xD;
w. 416.644.8855 x 318&#xD;
359 Richmond Street West, Toronto, Ontario, M5V 1X3&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Title: 	J2ME Device Developer&#xD;
Location: 	Toronto -West, Ontario, Canada&#xD;
Posted: 	9/25/2008&#xD;
Expires: 	11/11/2008&#xD;
Starting: 	ASAP&#xD;
Type: 	Permanent&#xD;
Travel: 	25% Within and around GTA&#xD;
Dress Code: 	Business Casual&#xD;
 &#xD;
Job Description:&#xD;
&#xD;
As a member of the Platform Solutions team, you will be working on the next generation of collaborative tools available on the wireless devices. You will be involved in the design and development of device-side applications providing Web 2.0-style of collaboration and social networking. Your responsibilities will spread over the full application development lifecycle - starting from requirements analysis, design, coding, debugging and product releasing - and will be part of highly innovative and dynamic team. Use of your creativity skills would be required on daily basis.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Must Have Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
B.Sc. in Computer Science, Computer or Electrical Engineering or similar&#xD;
Expert hands-on Java knowledge (incl. optimizations, multi-threading), sound knowledge of J2ME&#xD;
Knowledge of REST, RSS, ATOM and Ajax trends&#xD;
Familiarity with social networks&#xD;
Familiarity with the Web 2.0 trends in web development (Ajax, Flash, Google APIs)&#xD;
Creativity and strive for technical innovation are mandatory&#xD;
Good knowledge of XML (including DTD, XML Schema, Namespaces), XML Web Services (SOAP, WSDL)&#xD;
Sound knowledge of software architectures, OOA/OOD, design patterns, and UML&#xD;
Excellent communication skills and team work are a must.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Nice to Have Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience in utilizing HTTP protocol for implementing application-level communication&#xD;
Security experience (authentication and authorization, access control, Access Control, dig. signatures, etc.)&#xD;
Familiarity with common Internet Protocols (SMTP, POP, FTP, TCP/IP)&#xD;
Experience developing wireless applications for BlackBerry, PocketPC/WinCE, PalmOS, or Symbian</content>
    <postId>8A2BA59E-5AAA-452C-9F59-508CAB66BA8D</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-11-12T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2ME Device Developer</title>
</post>
