<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Dear Scott,&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
We are hiring multiple numbers of experienced JAVA DEVELOPER for one of our prestigious clients in INDIA. Our client is a global MNC having offices all over the world. &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Type: Permanent &#xD;
Location: Singapore &#xD;
Start Date: Immediate &#xD;
Salary Range: SGD 5000 – 5500 &#xD;
&#xD;
REQUIREMENTS: &#xD;
&#xD;
Education and professional qualifications: &#xD;
• Bachelors Degree in Computer Science or Engineering &#xD;
• Masters Degree in Computer Science or Engineering &#xD;
&#xD;
Work Experience/Background: &#xD;
• 6 - 7 years of work experience in medium to large scale projects in the Financial Industry &#xD;
• Familiarity with Transactional costs of various securities, Trade Capture, Exception Handling, and Rate Calculations, Invoice matching, Adjustments and Postings. &#xD;
• Strong database development. &#xD;
• Hands on in Client side and Server side Java development in Unix environment. &#xD;
• Post Trade Processing Experience &#xD;
• Exposure to Transactional Expense Calculations &#xD;
• Ability to carry out adaptive changes necessitated by changes in Business Requirements, Source systems, Technology. &#xD;
• Display sound analytical, problem solving, presentation and inter-personal skills to handle various critical situations &#xD;
&#xD;
Technical/business skills &amp; knowledge: &#xD;
• Extensive hands-on experience with Java, client side and server side development, J2EE &#xD;
• Experience in SQL* Plus, PL/SQL and Store Procedures with various data sources like Oracle, Sybase/Db2 on Unix/Linux &#xD;
&#xD;
Working with NY team to match their time zones may be required. &#xD;
&#xD;
Interested candidates can apply to kamal@ensoft.com.sg ASAP for an immediate processing along with the following info: &#xD;
* Total experience in investment banking &#xD;
* Total experience &#xD;
* Relevant experience &#xD;
* Current employer &#xD;
* Current location &#xD;
* Nationality &#xD;
* Current salary &#xD;
* Expected salary &#xD;
* Notice period (buying option available) &#xD;
* Visa Status in Singapore &#xD;
&#xD;
ATTENTION: &#xD;
&#xD;
This is not a spam mail. EnSoft is a genuine Executive Search Agency and keeps working on various positions day in and day out for the clients. In case if you feel that you are not suitable for this position and doesn’t wish to receive such kind of mails from any of the recruitment companies; we would advise you to hide your resume details so that you can apply for selected positions as and when you are open for a job opening. We seek your attention in understanding that Monster sends these emails automatically based on a standard keyword search our recruiters do everyday. Though you are not suitable for any position emailed to you; your resume might have been highlighted by Monster automatically based on the same standard search criteria. All the applications will be treated confidential and will be used only for Recruitment Purposes. Other than this; EnSoft doesn’t have any other intentions or to disturb your privacy. In case if you are not interested and/or engaged in another assignment, we would appreciate if you could refer any of your friends and / or colleagues for the same requirement.</content>
    <postId>8D098C84-9F11-4608-8AA3-E4D52CA944A3</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-10-06T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java developer @ Singapore</title>
</post>
