<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권경화</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2010-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Should you need some more information for technical interview, please contact.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hi Fred,&#xD;
&#xD;
I am the HR Recruiter for Guidewire Software. Our Professional Services team is currently looking for a Sr. Technical Consultant/Integration Architect for our Toronto based customers.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Guidewire Professional Services organization includes business analysts, functional consultants, and technical integration consultants who work together to implement Guidewire applications at customer sites. Our projects are complex and can last from three months to two years depending on the specific customer requirements. During a project, the team will identify customer business requirements, configure the Guidewire application to meet those requirements, and integrate the Guidewire application to other internal or external systems. Guidewire implementation consultants are expected to spend the majority of their time on site with the client business and technical teams. Guidewire employs a flexible travel model that requires consultants to be on site four days per week and away from home three nights per week. Consultants work the fifth day from their home office.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
This is a FULL TIME/DIRECT HIRE OPPORTUNITY with us.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested, please send me your resume as a Word or PDF attachment. If you know of anyone interested/qualified please feel free to share my contact info with them. I have provided the link to our careers page with the full job description below:&#xD;
&#xD;
http://hire.jobvite.com/j/?cj=oLtiVfwb&amp;s=Linkedin&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Our website is www.guidewire.com&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Competitive Base Salary- Bonus- Stock Options and Excellent Benefits&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Edward Baker&#xD;
Guidewire Software | Recruiting Manager&#xD;
Tel: 760 448 6536 begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              760 448 6536      end_of_the_skype_highlighting | Cell: 858 945 6435 begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              858 945 6435      end_of_the_skype_highlighting&#xD;
ebaker@guidewire.com | www.guidewire.com&#xD;
Deliver insurance your way with flexible core systems from Guidewire.</content>
    <postId>8DBFA483-DF20-4837-A180-84BB87A0D6CD</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-05-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Guidewire Software - Sr. Technical Consultant</title>
</post>
