<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>고상호</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Dear BRAD,&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
One of our clients has recently tasked TDM Technical Services with the responsibility of recruiting a top-calibre SENIOR PROGRAMMER ANALYST for their team. &#xD;
&#xD;
If, after reviewing the profile below, you wish to be considered for this assignment, please reply to this email granting us permission to present your resume to our client. If you have not forwarded us a copy of your most current resume, please attach one with your reply. (Word format only, please!)&#xD;
&#xD;
SHOULD THIS OPPORTUNITY FAIL TO ADEQUATELY MATCH YOUR BACKGROUND AND CURRENT JOB SEARCH CRITERIA, PLEASE ACCEPT OUR APOLOGIES. &#xD;
&#xD;
To be kept abreast of more appropriate opportunities in future, please email us a copy of your most current resume as well as a brief summary of your skills, abilities and experience. In addition, if you know of anyone else who may be interested in, and qualified for, this assignment, please encourage him/her to forward a resume to us ASAP.&#xD;
&#xD;
Check out our website for other contract/permanent job opportunities…http://www.tdm.ca/&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Regards, &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
NAWAZ SHAREEF, Consultant &lt;nawaz@tdm.ca&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Type &amp; Duration:	&#xD;
PERMANENT, &#xD;
&#xD;
Position Location:	&#xD;
TORONTO, ON , CANADA&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Title:	&#xD;
SENIOR PROGRAMMER ANALYST&#xD;
&#xD;
TDM Client Company:	&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Summary:	&#xD;
Our Client is looking for top caliber Senior Programmer Analyst. This is Permanent position based in down town Toronto.&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
                       &#xD;
-Reviews and confirms the functional needs of business users.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Identifies project activities and tasks.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Plans, designs, and develops new applications with the business.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Interfaces/integrates new applications to back-end/legacy systems.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Manages enhancements to existing systems.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Produces detailed system, functional, design and programming specifications that satisfy business requirements and development standards.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Works with vendors and other third parties to define/design information technology solutions to business problems.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Acts in the role of senior technical authority on projects.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Provides technical support to production systems to ensure they are running error-free.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Facilitates the development and maintenance of process maps. &#xD;
&#xD;
                 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience Required:	&#xD;
Qualifications:                 &#xD;
&#xD;
 -Computer Science Degree/Diploma or equivalent.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Minimum three years experience in senior systems analyst role, focusing on client server and internet technologies.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Minimum five years progressive experience in programming and analysis.&#xD;
&#xD;
-Strong Java/J2EE programming skills - experience with Weblogic, SOAP/XML, JSP/GUI development, Webservices, EJB&#xD;
&#xD;
- Programming experience with C and C++&#xD;
&#xD;
- UNIX shell scripting, SQL &amp; PL/SQL, HTML&#xD;
&#xD;
- Good knowledge of Unix, Oracle, Win 2000 server, TCP/IP, DNS, HTTP&#xD;
&#xD;
- Excellent knowledge of UML, sequence diagrams, use cases and other design methodologies.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Good knowledge of Application Servers.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Telecommunications industry knowledge is an asset.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Excellent interpersonal skills.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Excellent problem solving skills&#xD;
&#xD;
- Good organizational skills, including ability to use project management tools (e.g. MSProject, PWW).&#xD;
&#xD;
- Ability to work in a dynamic team environment&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Hourly rate:	&#xD;
&#xD;
Notes:  &#xD;
&#xD;
1.	When you reply to this email, please ensure the job title is in the subject line. &#xD;
&#xD;
2.	Again, if you do not have an up dated text resume with us, please attach one to your reply. &#xD;
&#xD;
3.	If you know anyone else who may be interested in this opportunity, please encourage him/her to send a resume to me. &#xD;
&#xD;
4.	Please continue to monitor our web site for other job/contract openings at http://www.tdm.ca.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>8E5755D0-FF3B-413C-9E61-27225E5F1942</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>TDM - Permanent Opportunity - Sr Programmer Analyst</title>
</post>
