<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>강윤정</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>이미 여러 많은 분들이 알고 계시겠지만...&#xD;
6월에 잼있는 주제가 있어서 관심있는 분들과&#xD;
그곳에서 만나면 반가울 것 같아요.&#xD;
&#xD;
                 WWW.JUG.ORG&#xD;
&#xD;
This is a reminder notice that our June meeting will be held this &#xD;
coming Tuesday (June 4th).  The meeting will be held at our regular time and &#xD;
location: 7PM at Ryerson's Eaton Theatre.  Please note that this is the &#xD;
last meeting before our summer break.  We will resume in September.&#xD;
&#xD;
Storing Java Objects and EJBs in Relational Databases&#xD;
-----------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
This month's talk will focus on the challenges posed to Java developers &#xD;
by the mismatch between objects and databases. Storing objects in Java &#xD;
is more than simple JDBC calls; a solid design incorporates a &#xD;
persistence layer that separates the details of the database from the business &#xD;
logic. The persistence layer should address mapping and run-time issues &#xD;
such as caching, object identity, inheritance, legacy database &#xD;
integration, querying, stored procedure use, storing objects across multiple &#xD;
tables, and transaction management. Additional challenges arise through &#xD;
the use of multi-tier architectures and application servers.&#xD;
&#xD;
The talk will outline the persistence issues for Java objects and EJBs, &#xD;
and describe the various strategies employed by persistence layers to &#xD;
solve these problems. The challenges and solutions in the context of &#xD;
various EJB application architectures will also be discussed.  It is &#xD;
assumed the audience has some knowledge of Enterprise JavaBeans, basic &#xD;
relational database concepts and object modeling.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>8E850A1B-447D-4AA1-A84A-18E692B4B0B1</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-05-31T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>www.jug.org - Storing Java Objects and EJBs in Relational Databases</title>
</post>
