<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This is not a developer position, please have a look in details.&#xD;
&#xD;
-------------------&#xD;
Hi, Brendan,&#xD;
&#xD;
I came across your resume on Workopolis, are your currently looking for a job? we have a full time job with a major bank, I paste the job description below, if you think that you area fit and interested, please reply me asap, Thanks.&#xD;
&#xD;
   2. Systems Integrator&#xD;
&#xD;
This role concentrates on the deployment of code packages for our client:&#xD;
&#xD;
The key skill sets for this role are:&#xD;
&#xD;
DB2&#xD;
Java&#xD;
JSP&#xD;
Running on a Websphere platform.&#xD;
&#xD;
RAD&#xD;
&#xD;
Experience in these technologies is mandatory.&#xD;
&#xD;
Main job is to package code; deploy code; test deployment and verify its working and some production system support activities&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are an integrator with experience in deployment, or you are a developer with these skills and looking to move into integration, this is the job for you.&#xD;
&#xD;
Location: Downtown Toronto&#xD;
&#xD;
Hours of Work: The successful candidate has to be open to non-standard hours. Deployment is usually done in non-business hours for example the deployment can start at 6 PM and go on till 4 AM or on the weekends etc. The person has to be willing and able to work these hours as needed. Time in lieu of, or overtime is available.&#xD;
&#xD;
Communication skills: Stellar communication skills are a requirement for this job. The successful candidate will be communicating frequently with system administrators in a variety of locations. Ability to present thoughts in a clear and succinct manner is critical to the success of the individual.&#xD;
&#xD;
Benefits: Some of the best in the industry.&#xD;
&#xD;
Additional Requirements&#xD;
- Development using DB2 on UNIX or Linux. Meaning DB2 database running on UNIX/LINUX platform (I.e operating system). The people that TD has already interviewed has experience with DB2 UDB (I.e Windows Operating system). And the DB2 on LINUX/UNIX platform is totally different in terms of admin from the Windows. Please note it is not a must to have DB2 on UNIX/LINUX skills but its super asset.&#xD;
_ If the candidate have developed with Windows DB2 (ie not Linux/UNIX) then he must have experience with UNIX operating system as a standalone skills&#xD;
- Any type of DBA certification on any platform (preferably UNIX/LINX) is super asset&#xD;
- Last but not least comm skills have to be 9 and above.&#xD;
&#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
 &#xD;
Nelson Chu&#xD;
Consultant&#xD;
PentaCan&#xD;
&#xD;
416-788-5460&#xD;
nelson@pentacan.com   &#xD;
www.pentacan.com</content>
    <postId>903D20E3-EEBE-4941-B139-77E74FF11799</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-11-12T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>System Integrator, Deployment specialist, Toronto, perm</title>
</post>
