<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Thank you for your time this afternoon - it was a pleasure speaking with you.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
It is not often that I, too get to speak with many Korean I.T. professionals.&#xD;
&#xD;
 I am forwarding the job description for the position I mentioned at Triversity.&#xD;
&#xD;
 If you know of any collegues or friends who might be interested, please have them contact me.&#xD;
&#xD;
 Thank you for your help.&#xD;
I hope you and I can get the chance to work together in the near future.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kind regards,&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
James Lee&#xD;
(905) 940-0255 Ext. 224&#xD;
james@w5.net&#xD;
&#xD;
W5 Staffing Inc.&#xD;
100 Allstate Parkway, Suite 302&#xD;
Markham, ON  L3R 6H3&#xD;
Fax: (905) 940-0258&#xD;
www.w5.net&#xD;
&#xD;
=============================================	&#xD;
Role:	Possesses intimate knowledge of all design aspects of assigned product area and coordinates development work related to this product.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:	Toronto&#xD;
&#xD;
Key Responsibility Areas: &#xD;
&#xD;
·	Work as a key member of the team whose mandate is to ship market leading products&#xD;
·	Design and implement strategic enhancements to international software&#xD;
·	Gives input to the scope of projects to ensure deliverables will be met&#xD;
·	Participate in project planning to ensure that the team can deliver outstanding projects on time&#xD;
·	Keep current with technology and software engineering practices and passes information onto teammates&#xD;
·	Review the design and code of other software engineers&#xD;
·	Mentor junior software engineers&#xD;
·	Write high quality code&#xD;
	&#xD;
	Typical Activities:&#xD;
	&#xD;
·	Write up design documents based upon user requirements.&#xD;
·	Develop solid code with unit testing code based upon design documents&#xD;
·	Participate in development status meeting, design review meeting, functional review meeting to ensure that the team can deliver outstanding products on time&#xD;
·	Work closely with QA to resolve defects in a timely manner&#xD;
·	Review other developers’ code to guarantee the quality of the product.&#xD;
	&#xD;
	Requirements:&#xD;
	&#xD;
·	Several years experience in a software development capacity (software development industry preferred)&#xD;
·	Atl east two years of working experience with J2EE, four years of working experience with JAVA&#xD;
·	Working knowledge of UML, preferably in a design role&#xD;
·	In depth knowledge of several of the following technologies: JMS, JDBC, XML, EJB, Servelets&#xD;
·	Must have experience with Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle, Sybase SQL Anywhere or other Database Management Systems&#xD;
·	Must have experience of IBM WAS, WebLogic or other Application Servers.&#xD;
·	Experience of Point Of Sale application, JUNIT is definitely an asset.&#xD;
&#xD;
Additional information:&#xD;
&#xD;
Triversity website: www.triversity.com. &#xD;
Please play specific attention to the section regarding Transactionware Enterprise (http://www.triversity.com/products/transactionware_ent.html), which is the product suite that Triversity is working on. &#xD;
 &#xD;
The development environment is all IBM - Java, J2EE, WebSphere, AIX, DB2/UDB, and they are getting more heavily involved in Weblogic and Tomcat Application servers as well. **Hot buttons that will push a candidate over the edge include any database management/administration/development experience, and any previous exposure to Retail and/or POS applications** &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>90C2B687-6D2F-4B20-94FB-4C8D6BFC3AE6</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-09-09T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Software Engineer ( 6 months contract) -from Korean agency</title>
</post>
