<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>SR QA/DEV&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Reports to: Director – Customer Services   &#xD;
&#xD;
Date: January 2010   &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
JOB SUMMARY&#xD;
&#xD;
The Sr QA/DEV is a senior position under the guidance of the Director – Customer Services. The Sr QA/DEV will be responsible for:&#xD;
&#xD;
   1. Designing test suits for the company products&#xD;
   2. Developing scripts and programs for automatic execution of the test cases&#xD;
   3. Creating test environments&#xD;
   4. Running the test cases in automatic mode&#xD;
   5. Running regression tests in automatic mode&#xD;
   6. Keeping track of defects and fixes in subsequent builds and releases&#xD;
   7. Selecting tools for test automation&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS&#xD;
&#xD;
    * Designing new tests - 35% of the time&#xD;
    * Developing tests - 35% of the time&#xD;
    * Designing the test environments - 15% of the time&#xD;
    * Selecting test tools and training the testers to use them - 15% of the time&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
QUALIFICATIONS&#xD;
&#xD;
    * Masters degree in Computer Science or equivalent.&#xD;
    * Working level Java development skills.&#xD;
    * Working knowledge of operation systems – UNIX, LINUX, AIX and Windows&#xD;
    * Working knowledge of ORACLE data base&#xD;
    * Working knowledge of application servers – WebLogic and/or WebSphere&#xD;
    * Good knowledge of testing process and testing tools.&#xD;
    * Willingness to work in software testing area&#xD;
    * Requires well-developed communication skills both oral and written and the ability to maintain positive and cooperative working relationships with the test and the product development team.&#xD;
    * An appreciation for technical alternatives and knowledge of emerging technologies.&#xD;
    * Understanding of performance measurement and performance testing&#xD;
    * Conceptual/big picture thinker. &#xD;
    * Flexible, willing to backtrack and seek multiple innovative alternate solutions.&#xD;
&#xD;
Other qualities and skills&#xD;
&#xD;
    * Leadership – Exchanges information with appropriate people to complete work.  Represents the company and department in a positive light.  Embraces entrepreneurial spirit in work through recognizing and capitalizing on opportunities and challenging the status quo.&#xD;
    * Organizing - Can marshal resources (people, funding, material, and support) to get things done; can orchestrate multiple activities at once to accomplish a goal; uses resources effectively and efficiently; arranges information and files in a useful manner. &#xD;
    * Problem Solving – Solves difficult problems with effective solutions; asks good questions and probes all fruitful sources for answers; can see underlying or hidden problems and patterns; is excellent at honest analysis; looks beyond the obvious and doesn’t stop at the first answers. &#xD;
    * Self-Development – Ability to recognize personal skills, abilities, limitations and strengths, taking appropriate action to pursue developmental activities and seeks assistance from others prior to job difficulty.&#xD;
    * Total Quality Management - Dedicated to providing the highest quality outcomes.  Is open to suggestions and experimentation; creates a learning environment leading to the most efficient and effective work processes.&#xD;
    * Self-confidence – A belief in one’s capability to accomplish a task and select an effective approach to a task or problem.  This includes confidence in one’s ability as expressed in increasingly challenging circumstances and confidence in one’s decision or opinions.&#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------&#xD;
Karen Agulnik&#xD;
&#xD;
900-45 Sheppard Avenue East&#xD;
&#xD;
Toronto, Ontario&#xD;
&#xD;
M2N 5W9&#xD;
&#xD;
416-226-2828, 312&#xD;
&#xD;
Karen@apexsearch.com&#xD;
&#xD;
www.apexsearch.com</content>
    <postId>91341B9C-1C4A-40FF-9730-40FAF0EBB086</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SR QA/DEV - F/T, Mississauga</title>
</post>
