<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2009-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>런던? 휴,, 너무 멀지요...</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hello! I'm reaching out to you as I just got a really great opportunity for a client of ours in the London, Ontario that might be of interest to you. I've pasted the details below so please take a look! They are looking for a QA Analyst who has experience working on web based/eCommerce projects. Please get back to me ASAP and let me know if you are interested and we'll go from there. &#xD;
&#xD;
Position: Quality Assurance Analyst- 2 positions &#xD;
&#xD;
Mandatory Skills: &#xD;
-Coordination * 2+ Yrs. &#xD;
-E-Commerce * 2+ Yrs. &#xD;
-Executing Test Cases * 2+ Yrs. &#xD;
-Mercury Testing Tools QC * 3+ Yrs. &#xD;
-Mercury Testing Tools QTP * 2+ Yrs. &#xD;
-MS Office Applications * 3+ Yrs. &#xD;
-QA * 3+ Yrs. &#xD;
-Quick Test Professional * 2+ Yrs. &#xD;
-SDLC (System Development Life Cycle) * 3+ Yrs. &#xD;
-Testing * 3+ Yrs. &#xD;
-Web Applications * 2+ Yrs. &#xD;
&#xD;
Location: London &#xD;
Duration: 6 Months &#xD;
Start Date: June 1, 2009 &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description On behalf or our large, financial services client, PROCOM London is searching for 2 Quality Assurance Analysts to assist with testing activites for an ongoing project team. &#xD;
&#xD;
The IT Test/Quality Analyst’s main responsibility is the hands on maintenance, development and execution of test cases. This person may also lead small test teams or act as the Defect Manager on a project. &#xD;
&#xD;
Main Accountabilities include: &#xD;
- Define, Deliver &amp; Support Technology Solutions &amp; Service Clients &#xD;
- Develop &amp; Manage Relationships / the team / teamwork &#xD;
- Advanced knowledge and understanding of software development &amp; project management life cycle, testing &amp; development life cycle for distributed applications. &#xD;
&#xD;
Candidates that have experience with Web applications (EasyWeb, Infosite &amp; Web Business Banking applications) and GUI interface will be considered above all others. &#xD;
&#xD;
ADDITIONAL QUALIFICATIONS (DESIRED, BUT NOT MANDATORY): &#xD;
- Years of Testing Work Experience: 2 – 4 yrs. Financial Service Experience &#xD;
- Education: Post Secondary Degree/Diploma (computer science, or business with IT focus). &#xD;
- Accreditation: Certified Software Tester (CSTE) or equivalent. &#xD;
&#xD;
One of the two positions may lead to full time after the contract ends. &#xD;
&#xD;
The Quality Assurance Analyst role is to plan, design, architect, and deploy effective test suites and regimes for in-house product development, software application development, information system launches, and operations systems enhancements. This individual will apply proven analytical and problem-solving skills to help validate, verify, communicate, and resolve systems/software application issues through careful testing in order to maximize the benefit of IT investments and initiatives Coordinate formal quality assurance review with information systems. Responsible for the formal quality assurance role in audits/reviews. Implement policies and standards and take into account standards/legislation. Recommend new or replacement policies and/or standards. Ensure that a consistently high standard of information systems is maintained. Assess and evaluate current technologies and information systems trends. &#xD;
A vacancy exists for a QA Team Lead to join the team and be responsible for various aspects of software application testing, ensuring application is stable and defect free. &#xD;
As part of this team, prime responsibility will be to: &#xD;
• Lead the design, development, execution and analysis of manual and/or automated tests for functional, system, regression, and performance testing ensuring traceability and coverage. &#xD;
• Provide input to QA test estimates. &#xD;
• Prepare test scripts. &#xD;
• Liaise with QA environment team to schedule test lab, ensure environment configuration is set up correctly, and prepared documentation for same. &#xD;
• Coordinate test execution. &#xD;
• Develop, document, and maintain test deliverables (test requirements, test strategy, test plans, test cases, test procedures, defect logs, status reports, and test result summaries). &#xD;
• Meet with business partners and project manager for sign off on deliverables (overall test strategy, test plan, test cases, etc.). &#xD;
• Work with all QA team members to accomplish shared goals. Work with project team members to resolve quality issues. &#xD;
• Mentor other team members on test and quality processes. SKILLS: Coordinates work for medium size projects and may supervise staff on an ongoing basis &#xD;
University degree or college diploma with experience in the IT industry &#xD;
&#xD;
PROCOM SERVICES &#xD;
A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 2800 consultants on assignment and place hundreds of people in permanent positions annually. For over 30 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our candidates. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and candidates consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice. &#xD;
&#xD;
PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES are committed to employment equity and make every attempt to allow equal representation for all within the workplace. &#xD;
&#xD;
We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed and all applicants will receive a followup within 2 business days. &#xD;
&#xD;
Please submit your most recent in confidence to: cindyw@procom.ca</content>
    <postId>91B283E2-E0A9-440F-BD48-DBD47DFFB8FC</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>QA Analyst</title>
</post>
