<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>샘 권</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2004-12-30T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>예수가 산상설교를 한 부분이군요. 좋은 글들이긴 합니다만, James King 버전인지 궁금하네요.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>&#xD;
God blesses those people who depend only on him. &#xD;
They belong to the kingdom of heaven! &#xD;
&#xD;
God blesses those people who grieve. &#xD;
They will find comfort! &#xD;
&#xD;
God blesses those people who are humble. &#xD;
The earth will belong to them! &#xD;
&#xD;
God blesses those people who want to obey him &#xD;
more than to eat or drink. &#xD;
They will be given what they want! &#xD;
&#xD;
God blesses those people who are merciful. &#xD;
They will be treated with mercy! &#xD;
&#xD;
God blesses those people whose hearts are pure. &#xD;
They will see him! &#xD;
&#xD;
God blesses those people who make peace. &#xD;
They will be called his children! &#xD;
&#xD;
God blesses those people who are treated badly for doing right. &#xD;
They belong to the kingdom of heaven! &#xD;
&#xD;
God will bless you when people insult you, mistreat you, and tell all kinds of evil lies about you because of me.  Be happy and excited!  You will have a great reward in heaven.  People did these same things to the prophets who lived long ago. &#xD;
&#xD;
You are like salt for everyone on earth.  But if salt no longer tastes like salt, how can it make food salty?  All it is good for is to be thrown out and walked on. &#xD;
&#xD;
You are like light for the whole world.  A city built on top of a hill cannot be hidden, and no one would light a lamp and put it under a clay pot.  A lamp is placed on a lampstand, where it can give light to everyone in the house.  Make your light shine, so that others will see the good that you do and will praise your Father in heaven. &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
                                                                                         Matthew 5:1-16</content>
    <postId>95F41EDC-20FF-43B9-916F-86AA036CF054</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-12-30T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>신이 없다는 생각이 들 때 읽으면 좋은 글</title>
</post>
