<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>As Technology Evolves, So Will Our Jobs &#xD;
----------------------------------------&#xD;
Abridged: Boston.com &#xD;
&#xD;
BOSTON, MA -- In March 1964 a group of top scientists sent President Lyndon Johnson a letter warning that the growing use of computers would lead to mass unemployment. Forty years later we are still worried about our jobs in a world in which improving technology and outsourcing are making business ever more productive. &#xD;
&#xD;
Frank Levy is reasonably hopeful things will work out all right. ''We are going in the right direction, but getting there won't be pretty," said Levy, an economist at MIT. Levy and Richard Murnane of Harvard have written a book, ''The New Division of Labor," that tries to explain how technology influences the job market.&#xD;
&#xD;
The reason for their optimism is pretty basic. Computers and outsourcing cut costs and boost productivity. Over time rising productivity creates new wealth and new job opportunities, even as old jobs disappear. ''Good jobs will increasingly require expert thinking and complex communications," the authors write. That is good news for people with the requisite education and talent. On the whole, you can take comfort from the message Levy and Murnane deliver: Technology isn't going away, but neither are our jobs.&#xD;
&#xD;
A Great Free Resource For Job Seekers &#xD;
-------------------------------------&#xD;
Staff Writer, The Career News &#xD;
&#xD;
FREDERICKSBURG, VA -- Have you had the chance to visit Job.com? It has quickly become one of the more meaningful career sites on the web. Posting your resume on this top career site is a simple process that takes less than 5 minutes and is free to use. By joining you'll gain immediate exposure to their proprietary database of employers and recruiters. Additionally, you'll receive the following complimentary services when you sign up:&#xD;
&#xD;
Notifications of newly posted jobs in your targeted industry and state; &#xD;
Articles and tips on how to advance your job search; &#xD;
Access to salary data in Job.com's Salary Center; &#xD;
Access to research on 1000's of companies; &#xD;
A free resume critique and job search evaluation; &#xD;
If you're still in the job market and haven't signed up to Job.com, perhaps now's the time. To sign up, go to Job.com.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Great Manners Matter: Impress Interviewers &#xD;
------------------------------------------------&#xD;
Rochelle Melander, Wellness &amp; Writing Coach &#xD;
&#xD;
MILWAUKEE, WI -- Do you talk while you chew your food? Interrupt other people when they are talking? Barrel through doors without concern for who might be ahead of you? Manners may not seem important during college or graduate school, but young employees need good manners to succeed in a tight job market. Great manners can impress interviewers.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Consider your appearance. Besides choosing appropriate clothes, make sure your hair and nails look great. Go easy on scents -- some interviewers may be allergic to strong fragrances.&#xD;
- Arrive early. Get to the interview location with enough time to be on time. No one is eager to hire the candidate who runs in breathless or arrives late.&#xD;
- Turn off your cell phone. Make certain your cell phone and pager are off for the duration of the interview, even if it includes lunch and a company tour. When your phone rings they will think you're rude.&#xD;
- Say thank you. At the beginning of the interview, thank the interviewers for this amazing opportunity. At the end, thank them for their time.&#xD;
If you have a sinking feeling you may need more help with your manners, ask around. If your colleagues agree -- and are brave enough to tell you -- consult an etiquette coach.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Employees Seek Greener Pastures; Employers at Risk &#xD;
------------------------------------------------&#xD;
Abridged: US Newswire &#xD;
&#xD;
ALEXANDRIA, VA -- The Department of Labor announced this month another increase in hiring for April, further indicating that the economy is in recovery mode. However, according to data released by the Society for Human Resource Management (SHRM), companies could be at risk of losing key intellectual capital as the economy continues to rebound and employees begin seeking greener pastures. &#xD;
&#xD;
In a recent SHRM survey, nearly two-thirds of the HR professionals who responded indicated that their organizations did not have policies in place to protect trade secrets. In addition, only 30 percent said that current and new employees sign non-compete agreements. This presents a potential serious conclusion since, according to a July 2003 survey conducted by Spherion, 75 percent of the 3,000 workers surveyed said that they were likely to leave their current jobs within a year.&#xD;
&#xD;
"With the job market improving every quarter and predictions that many employees will begin looking for new opportunities, it is paramount that organizations proactively manage trade secrets beginning with educating and training employees about what can and cannot be shared outside of the company," said SHRM President and CEO Susan R. Meisinger, SPHR.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sure-Fire Way To Get A Job? Play The Numbers. &#xD;
--------------------------------------------&#xD;
Staff Writer, The Career News &#xD;
&#xD;
LOS ANGELES, CA -- People may not realize this, but thousands of successful businesses are in desperate need of competent and skilled employees. These days, to land a job over the competition, you have to work smarter. The hard part is to get your resume read by the right people at the right time. Good jobs aren't on the market very long. To succeed your resume has to be available to the employer the moment they decide to fill a position.&#xD;
&#xD;
One easy way to be found by employers who are looking to hire someone with your skills, is to post your resume on all the top career sites. As soon as an employer needs someone, this is usually the first place they look. This is a proven, documented method of successful job searching. While it may take a fair amount of time to find and fill out the forms of all these sites, you will definitely multiply your chances of landing a job.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you want all the benefits without all the work, you can use a service like ResumeRabbit to do it for you. You fill out one simple form and they'll instantly post your resume on up to 90 top career sites like Monster, HotJobs, CareerBuilder, Dice &amp; more! You'll be seen by over 1.5 million employers &amp; recruiters daily. It takes about 15 minutes and saves 60 hours of research and data entry! To try ResumeRabbit today, click this link.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
When Should You Show 'em the Money? &#xD;
--------------------------------------&#xD;
Wendy Terwelp, Certified Career Management Coach &#xD;
&#xD;
MILWAUKEE, WI -- When asked about your salary requirements, your response depends on who is asking you the question. If you are responding to a request from a recruiter, you will need to provide your salary history or your requirements. Recruiters need this information in order to place you in an appropriate position based on their client company's requirements. If you're a fantastic candidate but the client can't afford you, they don't want to waste your time. &#xD;
&#xD;
If your resume is not going to human resources, but rather a key decision maker listed in the ad (such as vice president of sales and marketing), you may get away with stating that you'd appreciate the opportunity to meet with her in person to discuss a salary that would be agreeable to both parties. You may also be able to provide a range or non-specific number, such as "mid 60's."&#xD;
&#xD;
If the ad specifies that you send your resume to human resources, more than likely someone will be screening the responses to see if candidates are following directions. If that's the case, it's a good idea to include your salary requirements -- at least a desired range. For additional strategies, a quick read is Jack Chapman's "Negotiating Your Salary: How to Make $1,000 a Minute." &#xD;
&#xD;
Free Business Cards: Great For Networking &#xD;
-----------------------------------------&#xD;
Staff Writer, The Career News &#xD;
&#xD;
LEXINGTON, MA -- When you're looking for a job, chances are you're meeting with lots of different people, attending trade shows, job fairs, etc. As difficult as it is for you to remember names of people you meet, those people are probably having just as hard a time remembering your name! Make it easier for you and for them - pass out business cards.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you're unemployed and don't have current professional business cards, consider creating personal ones. Is money tight? Well, now you can create cards at no charge. VistaPrint has many templates from which you can choose - from wild and colorful to simple and sophisticated. Pick the template you prefer, type in your information, preview your new card and order it. It's so simple to use.&#xD;
&#xD;
Don't let anyone forget who you are. Hand out a business card during every interaction you have...you never know who might want to remember you. For your complimentary business cards, click this link.&#xD;
&#xD;
California Job Creation Accelerating &#xD;
-----------------------------------------&#xD;
Abridged: LAtimes.com &#xD;
&#xD;
LOS ANGELES, CA -- Hiring in California remained sluggish in April, but economists said there were signs that the state's employment growth might soon accelerate. California employers added a net 16,300 nonfarm jobs last month, according to a report released Friday by the state Employment Development Department. &#xD;
&#xD;
Nationally, a burst of hiring generated 625,000 net new positions in March and April, leaving little doubt that the long jobless recovery was over. That can't yet be said for California. Although the state's payroll growth in March was revised up to 21,500, the tally for the last two months still left California well short of expected gains.&#xD;
&#xD;
"We don't seem to have our fair share of employment gains, so that is a concern," said Keitaro Matsuda, senior economist at Union Bank of California. But he and other economists have said that the pace of job creation in California was likely to pick up in the next few months. They cited several factors: growing demand for California-made goods, an improvement in the hard-hit Bay Area economy and pressures on companies that have refrained from hiring to finally add permanent full-time workers to meet sales demands.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>9651CD13-58E0-4C27-8930-B07A72697526</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-05-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>The Career News May 2004</title>
</post>
