<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Another link: Joel on Software Guerilla Guide to Interviewing&#xD;
http://www.joelonsoftware.com/articles/fog0000000073.html.&#xD;
&#xD;
My interviewing technique goes against the grain, I ask tonnes of advanced&#xD;
fact based short questions across a wide breadth of technologies.  I want to&#xD;
see a general competency and a couple areas of above average experience.&#xD;
This is more for knowing where on a large team to best position people.&#xD;
This is administered verbally with some whiteboard work as the difference&#xD;
between candidates shows up in their reasoning process not their raw scores.&#xD;
I understand that new technologies are always around the corner so I am not&#xD;
looking for specific expertise per se.  This technique is good at revealing&#xD;
false claims on resumes.  I do ask for one short coding exercise mostly to&#xD;
weed out those people that are too far from being able to put up&#xD;
syntactically correct code although I am lenient with errors, it is amazing&#xD;
what this can reveal.&#xD;
&#xD;
I agree that resume screening is an essential skill for hiring before you&#xD;
get to the interview stage.  The following are my directions to recruiters&#xD;
who screen resumes for me:&#xD;
&#xD;
I was looking for 12 permanent employees at the senior, team lead and&#xD;
architect level (no juniors).  Some of this is geared to the particular&#xD;
environment the candidates would be in.&#xD;
&#xD;
Red Flags:&#xD;
  a.. Looking for contract position&#xD;
  b.. Salary expectations out of line, either way (very low expectations are&#xD;
not a positive)&#xD;
  c.. Recent grads or bulk of experience showing as course work&#xD;
  d.. Little or no North American experience - this is not hard and fast,&#xD;
some resumes with only foreign experience do stand out, but it is harder to&#xD;
qualify the caliber of the organizations&#xD;
  e.. Poor spelling, grammar or composition&#xD;
  f.. Too much jumping around, many short stays (with some sensitivity due&#xD;
to the recent job market downturn)&#xD;
  g.. Too much emphasis on certifications without relevant project&#xD;
experience&#xD;
  h.. Too much education (this one is contentious), I find the brightest and&#xD;
most productive developers I've worked with don't have Masters and PhDs (who&#xD;
can sometimes get lost on the theory and perfectionism and don't like&#xD;
committing to approaches as a better one might be out there) and that those&#xD;
that do have these degrees (while not a problem in itself) often come with&#xD;
an ego and social ranking system that make it difficult for them to respect&#xD;
and take direction from the less formally educated brilliant hackers that&#xD;
are often their team leads.  Caveat, candidates from parts of the world&#xD;
where advanced higher education is the norm since it is free or a way to&#xD;
stay out of the military.  I will try to identify the ego issues if they&#xD;
exist in the interview.  I recently had one developer slip by due to&#xD;
undeclared degrees and this exact attitude problem has been a nightmare to&#xD;
deal with.&#xD;
If none of the above are a concern I start to look for the following:&#xD;
  a.. Descriptive sentences on roles and responsibilities, not just long&#xD;
lists of technology acronyms&#xD;
  b.. Descriptions of projects that show recognition of their business value&#xD;
  c.. Statements about workplace attributes that are attractive.  e.g.&#xD;
commitment to continual improvement, open environment with effective&#xD;
communication, transparent management style, working with top caliber&#xD;
peers...  i.e. Some indication they are reflective about these issues&#xD;
  d.. Proactive in improving own and team's work (process improvement, tool&#xD;
adoption, etc...)&#xD;
  e.. For Team Leads, demonstrated leadership / mentorship experience&#xD;
  f.. Demonstrated work experience with the technologies listed in the job&#xD;
description, not just appearing in a skills summary&#xD;
  g.. High caliber organizations and projects, commercial software&#xD;
production / external facing applications experience is a plus&#xD;
  h.. Enterprise level project visibility versus internal departmental&#xD;
operational tools&#xD;
  i.. Balanced skill set, recent Java, past C/C++ and/or others&#xD;
  j.. Emphasis on Object Oriented design&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>9793856F-47F1-40D1-A41F-7E4E144BBE1F</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-04-03T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>[XPToronto] How to Interview a Programmer</title>
</post>
