<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>박해옥</author>
            <date>2009-06-25T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>앗! 제가 한국에서 했던 일하고 거의 비슷합니다. 지원하고 싶어서 전화를 드렸는데 안받으시네요.레쥬메를 어떻게 보내면 될까요? 그리고 감사합니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Manager Architecture &amp; Infrastructure&#xD;
Tracking Code&#xD;
304146-618 &#xD;
Job Description&#xD;
Working in a fast-paced, mission-critical environment, the Manager, Infrastructure &amp; Architecture is responsible for designing and maintaining the IT infrastructure of a high-availability, 24x7 electronic payments network and INTERAC member&#xD;
&#xD;
This position is for a 1 year contract.&#xD;
&#xD;
Specific Responsibilities Include:&#xD;
&#xD;
Administer Hardware, Operating Systems, and Logical Security in the Production Data Centre &#xD;
Design solutions and Implement changes to  Hardware, Operating Systems, and IT security utilizing various technologies and in compliance with PCI standards &#xD;
Oversight of LAN/WAN administration via management of Network Analysts &#xD;
Provide leadership and guidance to internal teams and customers on infrastructure technologies &#xD;
Produce required documentation including technical specifications, procedures, infrastructure and network schematics, etc. &#xD;
Investigate and implement tools to aid in automation, improve performance, and track critical metrics &#xD;
Research and recommend new technologies and champion them within current business infrastructure &#xD;
Understand business goals and requirements of Open Solutions customers &#xD;
Conduct performance reviews, grow expertise of the team, prepare team to meet new business requirements &#xD;
Administer Backup management and recovery planning &#xD;
Project management and team lead on various projects &#xD;
24x7 Pager Support &#xD;
Required Skills&#xD;
Required Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
University degree in Computer Engineering, Electrical Engineering, or Computer Science &#xD;
ITIL V2 ICT Infrastructure Management Certificate or equivalent &#xD;
Minimum 7 years hands-on experience designing, building, and supporting complex IT infrastructures including LAN, WAN, SSL, and VPN architectures &#xD;
Minimum 5 years management experience &#xD;
Minimum 3 years experience supporting high-availability, mission-critical Data Centre operations &#xD;
Formal Project management training - PMI certification an asset &#xD;
Hands-on experience with Disaster Recovery Operations and Incident Management &#xD;
Knowledge of SOX, PCI, and/or other IT-related controls and standards &#xD;
Technical Proficiency with theory, practices, and tools of: &#xD;
Common Operating Systems (e.g., Windows, HP-UX, Linux) &#xD;
VMWare &#xD;
LAN/WAN &#xD;
Enterprise Networking products (e.g., Cisco Routers, F5 BigIP). &#xD;
Network protocols (e.g., TCP/IP, VPN) &#xD;
HP EVA/SAN &#xD;
Microsoft Active Directory &#xD;
In-depth knowledge of: &#xD;
High-Availability Data Centre environment &#xD;
Disaster Recovery environments &#xD;
Strong human relation skills with a positive attitude and strong work ethic &#xD;
Proven Analytical and Problem-solving skills  with strong priority management skills &#xD;
Outstanding Documentation and Verbal Communication skills &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Location&#xD;
Oakville, ONT, CANADA &#xD;
Position Type&#xD;
Temporary</content>
    <postId>9BBEE169-31B5-4DC1-B8DE-D830E77BE3FF</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-06-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>opensolutions canada (관심있는 분은 연락바람)</title>
</post>
