<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이홍식</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>POSTED AT 12:30 PM EDT    Thursday, September 12&#xD;
IT spending expected to make gains&#xD;
By RANDY RAY&#xD;
Special to The Globe and Mail&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
After keeping a tight rein on information technology spending for the past year, Real Facilities Inc. of Toronto has doubled its IT budget for 2002. By the end of this year, the two-year-old company will have spent $600,000 to improve in-house communications and upgrade the proprietary software used by its commercial, industrial and retail clients to locate, lease and outfit their commercial premises, president Stan Krawitz says. &#xD;
&#xD;
"작년까지만해도 엄격히 통제된 Toronto의 Real Facilities Inc 회사 IT 지출이 2002년에 들어서면서 배로 치솟았다. 올해 말까지 2년된 이 회사는 사내 통신, 자사소유의 software 개선을 위해   $600,000을 쏟아붙는다."&#xD;
&#xD;
같은 기사에서는 또한 회사들의 최근 IT 지출증가 현상을 다음 3 가지 이유로 꼽고 있습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
1. 하이테크업체들도 자동차업체처럼 replacement cycle이 존재하며 지금이 바로 그 시점이라는 점.&#xD;
2. 새로운 기술도입은 가장 빠르게 생산성 향상을 가져옴.&#xD;
3. 회사들 대부분이 정리해고, restructuring을 마쳤다는 점.&#xD;
&#xD;
Software의 수요는 증가하는 반면 Hardware의 수요는 감소하고 있는 추세라는 내용도 동 기사에서 읽을 수 있었습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
오늘의 A word for the day는 rein인데요 말을 제어하는 가죽고삐를 의미하나 그의미가 확대되어 제어나 control을 표현할 때 사용되기도 합니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
naver 사전은...&#xD;
rein [r&amp;eacute;in] 【L「누르다」의 뜻에서】 n. &#xD;
1 [종종 pl.] 고삐 ((보통 가죽으로 된)); 유아 보호용 벨트&#xD;
on a long ~ 고삐를 늦추어&#xD;
throw (up) the ~s to (말의) 고삐를 내던지다, 제멋대로 굴게 하다, ···의 자유에 맡기다 &#xD;
2 통제 수단; 통어, 제어; 구속, 견제, 지배&#xD;
without ~ 구애 없이, 자유롭게 &#xD;
3 [종종 pl.] 제어(력), 통제권, 지휘권&#xD;
assume[drop] the ~s of government 정권을 잡다[놓치다]&#xD;
hold the ~s 정권 ((등))을 잡고 있다&#xD;
take the ~s (현재의 지배자 대신에) 지휘하다, 지배하다 &#xD;
4  [종종 pl.] 행동의 자유 &#xD;
draw in the ~(s) (고삐를 잡아당겨) 말을 멈추게 하다 &#xD;
draw ~ &#xD;
(1) &lt;보조 등을&gt; 늦추다 &#xD;
(2) = draw in the REIN(S). &#xD;
give a horse (the) ~(s) 말을 제멋대로 가게 하다 &#xD;
give ((a) free [full]) ~ [the ~s, a loose ~] to ···에게 자유를 주다, 멋대로 하게 하다 &#xD;
hold [keep] a tight ~ over [on] ···을 엄격히 통제하다[제어하다, 가르치다, 다루다] &#xD;
keep a slack [loose] ~ on ···의 고삐를 느슨히 하다, 엄하게 대하지 않다&#xD;
vt. &#xD;
1 &lt;말에&gt; 고삐를 매다; 고삐로 조종하다[몰다]; &lt;고삐를 당겨 말을&gt; 세우다; &lt;고삐를 당겨 말의&gt; 보조를 늦추다&#xD;
~ a horse well 말을 잘 몰다 &#xD;
2 제어하다, 통제[억제]하다; 지배하다, 통어하다, 이끌다&#xD;
《~+목+부》 ~ in one's temper 울화를 억제하다&#xD;
~ one's tongue 입조심하다&#xD;
vi. &#xD;
1 &lt;말이&gt; 고삐를 따라 움직이다 &#xD;
2 고삐를 써서 말을 세우다 ((in, up, back))&#xD;
~ back[up] &lt;고삐를 당겨 말 등을&gt; 멈추게 하다&#xD;
~ in 고삐를 당겨 &lt;말을&gt; 세우다; 억제하다 &#xD;
&#xD;
(from Cambridge International Dictionary of English)&#xD;
rein&#xD;
noun [C usually pl] &#xD;
a long thin piece of material, esp. leather, which helps you to control and direct a horse, or Br something similar used to control and direct young children &#xD;
You pull (on) both reins to stop or slow a horse, but only the left rein to turn left.&#xD;
BRITISH She always put the reins on her little son when they went for walks.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you give free rein to someone or something, you allow them freedom to act. &#xD;
The young film-makers were given free rein to experiment with new themes and techniques.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you keep a tight rein on someone or something or keep someone or something on a tight rein you firmly control them. &#xD;
My father always kept us on a tight rein.&#xD;
&#xD;
rein&#xD;
verb [T usually + adv/prep] &#xD;
If you rein in/back a horse or rein a horse in/back, you make it go more slowly or stop it. &#xD;
FIGURATIVE We tried to rein in our excitement and curiosity. &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>9BF7847F-0E94-4DCF-89D5-5DEE072E4880</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>rein</title>
</post>
