<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content> This is the internal posting in my current company.&#xD;
If anyone might be interested, please contact me.&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Position:			Risk Database Analyst ( Full Time )&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:			Trans Canada Retail Services - Risk Management&#xD;
&#xD;
Date Posted:		June 17, 2002			Closing Date:	June 24, 2002&#xD;
&#xD;
This position provides research, analysis and performance models through the use of the data warehouse system (Teradata) and PC - related applications by means of PC, mainframe and reporting tools.&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Researches and analyzes initiatives for internal and external clients using PC, Easytrieve and reporting tools within the data warehouse (Teradata) and the mainframe.  Documents results using formats that are understood by the requestor, including portfolio trends, changes and summary of findings.&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Provides database support to internal and external clients.  Provides suggestions and recommendations regarding information availability.  Ensures database integrity and liases with the database administrator.&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Ensures superior and co-workers are kept advised of any trends or information which could impact the overall effectiveness of the Risk Department or NRCS.&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Develop ad hoc and risk related reporting utilizing Easytrieve, SQL programming and reporting tools against mainframe/masterfile data and other databases as requested by management.&#xD;
&#xD;
Knowledge, Experience, Skills&#xD;
&#xD;
·	Post secondary education in economics or related field with three to five years of financial/credit/retail experience. &#xD;
·	Technical skills required include advanced knowledge of SQL, all Microsoft Office Applications with a strong understanding of Access, and working knowledge of Easytrieve;  Knowledge of Hummingbird products would be an asset (i.e. BI/Query, BI/Reports).&#xD;
·	Strong understanding of data extraction techniques with knowledge of data mining, data modeling and reporting tools.  &#xD;
·	Demonstrated ability to work independently and manage multiple tasks simultaneously in a deadline driven environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
Qualified candidates should contact Katherine Karbownik at local 5314  &#xD;
Remember to include your resum&amp;eacute; with the Application for Transfer form&#xD;
&#xD;
Don't forget the Employee Referral Award program!&#xD;
Do you know someone who may have the qualifications for this position.  If so, talk to them about applying. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Katherine Karbownik&#xD;
Employee Relations Specialist&#xD;
Trans Canada Credit Corporation&#xD;
email:  Katherine.Karbownik@tcrs.ca&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>9C93354F-62C5-44C6-B585-D1F65AE76DB4</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-17T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Database Analyst position</title>
</post>
