<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>This must be of CIBC...&#xD;
&#xD;
------------------------&#xD;
We are presently seeking a Application Consultant - DT a permanent position for a major financial institution located in Toronto, ON. &#xD;
&#xD;
Your name came up in a search and we wanted to know if you are presently available and interested in a permanent opportunity.&#xD;
&#xD;
Here is a link to the position on our website http://www.symbioticgroup.com/fr_viewjobs.htm , it is titled Advisory Application Developer.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested please reply via email with your current CV and a convenient time that we can speak.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kind regards,&#xD;
&#xD;
Agnes N. Maison -&#xD;
Symbiotic Group Inc.&#xD;
2020 Winston Park Drive, Suite 100&#xD;
Oakville ON L6H 6X7&#xD;
Phone: 905-287-5595&#xD;
Fax: 905-287-5599&#xD;
Mobile: 416-820-8873&#xD;
email: agnes.maison@symbioticgroup.com&#xD;
Web: www.symbioticgroup.com&#xD;
Jobs: http://www.symbioticgroup.com/fr_viewjobs.htm&#xD;
Office Location: http://maps.google.ca/maps?ie=UTF8&amp;q=2020+winston+park+drive,+oakville+ontario+canada&amp;ll=43.508099,-79.668067&amp;spn=0.014971,0.038452&amp;z=15&#xD;
Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/in/agnesnmaison&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Position: Application Consultant - DT&#xD;
Mandatory Skills: See below&#xD;
Location: GTA&#xD;
Rate/Salary: Negotiable&#xD;
Start Date: ASAP  &#xD;
&#xD;
    Job Category: Information Technology&#xD;
    Job Type: Full Time&#xD;
    Location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada&#xD;
    No.Openings: 3&#xD;
    Travel%: 0&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Description:&#xD;
&#xD;
Application Consultant - DT&#xD;
&#xD;
Business Unit Description:&#xD;
Technology: responsible for the delivery of technology in support of all the Bank businesses and customers. Directly aligns to the Bank's businesses, with a technology team for each business. Delivers world class solutions in support of business strategies, through a combination of in-house systems development and working with leading technology partners. This group also manages The Bank's core computing facilities, telecommunications and networks globally.&#xD;
&#xD;
Retail Markets Technology: plans, delivers and supports end-to-end technology solutions for the various distribution channels and full range of products that service all of The Bank's Retail clients: The Bank's retail branch network, Internet, Automated Banking Machines (ABM's), telephone banking, credit products, GICs, Deposit Accounts, Global Payments and Wealth Management/Investment Products.&#xD;
&#xD;
Relevant Job Criteria:&#xD;
. There are three (3) regular full time positions available.&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Overview:&#xD;
PURPOSE OF JOB:&#xD;
As an integral part of Strategy team, you will provide strategic direction in the technical evolution of our application portfolio in 3-5 year outlook.&#xD;
&#xD;
You have 5-10 years of experience in end-to-end design and implementation of software solutions on large-scale projects. You are big picture visionary as well as, hands-on implementation guru. You enjoy keeping on top of technology trends, standards and processes.&#xD;
&#xD;
MAJOR ACTIVITIES:&#xD;
. Forms and evolves strategic direction in the technical evolution of application portfolio&#xD;
. Performs research and POC evaluations into technology, product and tooling viability&#xD;
. Elaborates and maintains Roadmaps for application portfolio&#xD;
. Communicates strategic direction to application stakeholders&#xD;
. Ensures application design and development artifacts comply with strategic direction&#xD;
&#xD;
Requirements:&#xD;
KNOWLEDGE/SKILL REQUIREMENTS:&#xD;
. Demonstrates initiative, drive and innovation&#xD;
. Very good conceptual and implementation skills and ability to bridge both&#xD;
. Very good analytical and research skills&#xD;
. Experience designing and implementing solutions for large-scale projects&#xD;
. Familiarity with all phases of SDLC and exposure to formal SDLC frameworks (RUP, XP)&#xD;
. In-depth understanding of software design, UML, design patterns and best practices&#xD;
. In-depth understanding of solutions architecture&#xD;
. Extensive and recent hands-on implementation experience including Java or C++/C#&#xD;
. Experience in Service Oriented Architecture, including REST&#xD;
. Desktop application development experience (Swing, Winforms/WPF etc.)&#xD;
. Web application development experience, exposure to RIA (Flex, Silverlight and HTML5)&#xD;
. Very good verbal and written communication skills&#xD;
. Team player&#xD;
&#xD;
MUST HAVES:&#xD;
. Enterprise level application development (6 years)&#xD;
. Development team lead (4 years)&#xD;
. Team building experience (3 years)&#xD;
&#xD;
NICE TO HAVE:&#xD;
. Exposure to enterprise information systems (EIS) integration&#xD;
. Java/J2EE experience (WLS, WAS)&#xD;
. Spring experience&#xD;
. OSGi, PRISM, CAB or other modular frameworks experience&#xD;
. .NET experience&#xD;
&#xD;
CONTACTS:&#xD;
. Peers and middle to senior management&#xD;
&#xD;
PHYSICAL DEMANDS/WORKING CONDITIONS:&#xD;
. Normal office environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
ATTRIBUTES:&#xD;
. Analytic/Systematic Thinking&#xD;
. Results Orientation&#xD;
. Communication&#xD;
. Accountability&#xD;
. Teamwork &amp; Partnering&#xD;
. Building Trust&#xD;
&#xD;
Location of Position(s) :&#xD;
Toronto&#xD;
&#xD;
Technology &amp; Operations&#xD;
&#xD;
    Skills:&#xD;
        Accountability&#xD;
        Analytic/Systematic Thinking&#xD;
        Building Trust&#xD;
        Communication&#xD;
        Consulting&#xD;
        Influencing &amp; Negotiating&#xD;
        Problem Solving &amp; Decision Making&#xD;
        Process Engineering/Process Design&#xD;
        Results Orientation&#xD;
        Service Orientation&#xD;
        Teamwork &amp; Partnering&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
About Symbiotic Group Inc.&#xD;
&#xD;
Symbiotic Group is a Human Resource Solutions company specializing in IT recruitment and Aboriginal Recruitment (IT &amp; Non-IT positions).&#xD;
&#xD;
Our focus is on building a customized recruitment approach that enables us to clearly understand the needs of our clients, search our detailed database quickly and accurately and customize a recruitment approach that enhances our client's processes - saving clients time and money.&#xD;
&#xD;
Symbiotic Group is committed to workplace diversity and is able to provide resources to assist firms to meet their Aboriginal and non-Aboriginal resource requirements.&#xD;
&#xD;
We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed. However, only suitable candidates will be contacted further.&#xD;
&#xD;
Please submit your most recent resume to: agnes.maison@symbioticgroup.com</content>
    <postId>9D460E81-7629-4764-95C2-6A0F84A63DDF</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-15T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Application Consultant - DT - Permanent Position</title>
</post>
