<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>You know me as Thomas Lee. I am a father of 1.5 kids and 43 years old plus the hubby of Diane also being in Canada for long time. That is external package of me.&#xD;
Internally I am very self-oriented, confrontational, hard to be convinced, not good listener and many many other bad attitudes.&#xD;
&#xD;
However I am comfortable with myself finally. I have pretended I was comfortable. Hindsight I was not sure about myself. I  was very insecure. I was always looking for other people's approval. Even though I didn't need it.&#xD;
&#xD;
I did not have clear direction of where I was going. I was going with flow. And told myself I will set the direction when I have time. You know one way or the other I found other execuse to procrastinate the decision. Finally time has come that I could not procrastinate anymore.  I am thinking about what I want to do daily while I am running. Now I am very beginning stage of knowing myself. I realized everthing begins within myself. Most of time the root cause of my failure was me not other reasons. &#xD;
&#xD;
These are what I am going to do from now on. My old attitude was if I made mistakes, I asked for forgiveness. If my apology was not accepted, that was too bad and that was not my problems. However the reason othe people did not accept my apology was I was not sincere enough. I was full of myself.  I did not realize why I was not accepted by other people. Because I was not sincere enough. This was what I should do " I will go back and will apologise until they will accept my apology." Then I have done my job. This is only a example.&#xD;
&#xD;
It is my interpretation of "Doing the best"&#xD;
- I will do whatever necessary to resolve the potential issues.&#xD;
- If I still can't find the solution, I will think again and again until time runs out.&#xD;
- From that point I will come up with the best solution  I can think of. Then I will think more until the final second.&#xD;
- Then I consider myself I have done my best.&#xD;
After this process I can honestly ask myself "Have I done the best I could ?"    </content>
    <postId>9E84B620-F05E-4EB5-ABEC-0A4E37BE135A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-30T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>DOing the best</title>
</post>
