<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>If these roles are not for you, I was hoping to network with you to see if there is anyone you might know. Please see the details below on the roles that I am currently pursuing for my clients:&#xD;
 &#xD;
Front-End Web Developer - Toronto - Contract - (skills) - 3 + years hands-on web development experience. Some backend experience. Must have HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, JSP and JSTL experience. Knowledge of DHTML, DOM scripting and cross-browser compatibility issues. 2+ years programming experience in Java, XML, object-oriented programming and Servlet. Experience with PHP, MySQL, JDBC, SQL, Oracle and Unix (Solaris) or Linux environment. Excellent design skills, with the ability to transform concepts into working models and product solutions. Experience programming in JSTL and JSP including the ability to write simple JSP tags. Experience with svn/git or another version control system. Knowledge of CSS3, HTML5, Flash (ActionScript), microformats and API design an asset. &#xD;
BCP Project Manager – Toronto – Full time – (skills) – 5+ years experience as a PM. Must have PMP. Hands on experience with Business Continuity Planning. Developing and implementing an Enterprise Wide Business Continuity Program. Managing the development of business continuity plans and assist business recovery teams in defining resumption plans in preparation for a system or facility outage. Develop and implement BCP governance. Development of tools and templates, and facilitation of completion and coordination. Project work plan, project administration and control project scope. Mentoring experience an asset.&#xD;
 &#xD;
IT Project Manager – Toronto - Full time – (skills) – PMP is required. 3-5 years experience in planning, managing and successfully project managing the execution of large, technical projects and managing technical staff or working with technical teams. 5+ years experience working with relevant technologies and network environments. Very strong knowledge of key tools required for this role. This includes Microsoft Project, the Microsoft Office Suite of products (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook), Microsoft Visio and any other applications that are considered important for managing projects, portfolios of projects and communicating with stakeholders. Comfortable following, formal project management methodologies to ensure projects stay within scope and on budget. Experience in building or managing a Project Management Office is an asset. 2+ years experience in managing a portfolio of projects and successfully employing portfolio management tools and techniques to keep all projects in the portfolio on track with successful results. Law firm environment.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
MS Exchange consultant - Toronto - Full time – (skills) – Intermediate, 5-7 years experience. Expert level knowledge in the administration, configuration, implementation and support of Microsoft office technologies (including, but not limited to: Active Directory, MS Exchange, and Windows Server OS). Strong technical experience in the administration, monitoring, configuration, implementation and support of different technologies (for example Blackberry Enterprise Server, EMC SAN, Cisco, etc)&#xD;
Pro services environment. Law firm environment.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
Ed Rix&#xD;
Resource Planning&#xD;
Watercrest&#xD;
Business Technology Solutions&#xD;
TF:  1-888-244-7550 ext.110&#xD;
ed@watercrest.net</content>
    <postId>A04FDF79-FD23-49BE-BECE-822CBC169D6D</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Several Jobs</title>
</post>
