<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>the opportunity&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client has built a future friendly national team, one that embraces change and initiates opportunity, has a passion for growth, believes in spirited teamwork and has the courage to innovate. Our success is based as much on the dedication and hard work of our team as it is on the innovative wireless solutions we offer.&#xD;
&#xD;
Our commitment to providing our clients with unsurpassed coverage, cool phones, great rates and outstanding client care, is what we're all about. Join our team of wireless professionals working in one of Canada's fastest-growing industries and make your future friendly too.&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Overview:&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is looking for qualified and seasoned professionals to fill numerous Systems Analyst positions in our Information Systems Development team in Scarborough. As a Systems Analyst, you will provide e-Business application and systems design, development, project management and implementation for projects related to the support of e-Business initiatives for our business partner. &#xD;
&#xD;
Our current Systems Analyst opportunities are available in the following areas:&#xD;
·Systems for Sales and Distribution&#xD;
·Systems for Client Operations&#xD;
·Systems for Application Infrastructure and Standards&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
·Lead the design of data, application and technology elements of technical designs supporting a variety of business requirements. &#xD;
·Ensure technical designs of applications are architected to be flexible, scalable, maintainable, and open in our clients n-tier environment. &#xD;
·Team with Business Systems Analysts to review business requirements and functional designs. &#xD;
·Work with highly talented colleagues in a fun, fast paced team to deliver significant business changing applications. &#xD;
·Identify, review and refine the processing requirements of systems to define appropriate application architectures. &#xD;
·Identify, review and refine the technology requirements of systems to define appropriate technology architectures (technology, platform, hardware/software components). &#xD;
·Take a lead role in making necessary changes to the architecture to resolve systems issues. &#xD;
·Deliver high quality, thoroughly tested applications, that will sustain current and expected loads. Re-evaluate the designs of such systems routinely to ensure that they are scalable to meet the growth of the business needs. &#xD;
·Assume a consulting role during the System Development, System and User Acceptance Testing and Production implementation phases to ensure that the system is developed and implemented as per requirements and the defined architecture. &#xD;
·Assume other roles as required such as project management, team leadership, QA planner/coordinator, etc.&#xD;
&#xD;
qualifications&#xD;
&#xD;
·Min. 5 years of progressive systems development and analysis experience in a telecommunications environment is strongly preferred. &#xD;
·Extensive experience delivering application design, including object oriented analysis and design, component based Web architectures and data structure design. &#xD;
·Thorough understanding of technology in a distributed architecture environment including UNIX, Windows 2000, Web Application Server, Application Server, and Oracle required. &#xD;
·Highly experienced in J2EE platform, Java, Java applets/Java servlets, EJBs, and HTML/XML. &#xD;
·Experience with a formalized System Development Lifecycle including requirements definition, functional design, detailed design, source control, change control, and integration testing. &#xD;
·Highly organized, analytical, detail and action oriented.&#xD;
·Superior leadership, facilitation, communication and interpersonal skills. &#xD;
·Ability to handle multiple projects efficiently and effectively. &#xD;
·Post secondary degree in Computer Science or Engineering.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Matt Zweig&#xD;
Client Sales and Solutions &#xD;
Pegasus Consulting Inc. &#xD;
matt@pegsoft.com &#xD;
WWW.pegsoft.com &lt;http://WWW.pegsoft.com&gt; &#xD;
416-488-7007 X 232 (local) &#xD;
877-688-8818 X 232 (Toll Free) &#xD;
55 Eglinton Avenue East, Suite 208 &#xD;
Toronto, ON&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>A25D00DF-D691-4C3D-BDFD-4B8235A4062E</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-08-12T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Systems Analyst </title>
</post>
