<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>제가 아는 에이전트로 부터 받은 이메일의 일부입니다. 관심있으시거나, 혹시 주변에 아시는 분 중에서 관심 있으신 분은 참조하시기 바랍니다. &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
In the meantime, I am looking for 2 AIX Unix Administrators.  Who could you recommend?  If you don't feel comfortable mentioning it to them, please give me their names and where they work and I will call them directly.  It is for a really good company.  Here is the job description.  Have them contact me via email right away or they can call me at 416-863-0154 x263.&#xD;
Responsibilities&#xD;
&#xD;
As a member of the UNIX Systems Administration team your responsibilities will include the following:&#xD;
&#xD;
· Administration of 30+ UNIX servers (AIX);&#xD;
· System monitoring, troubleshooting and capacity management;&#xD;
· Provide hardware and operating system technical knowledge to other UNIX administrators, DBA's and systems developers; and&#xD;
· Participate in upgrades, tuning and development initiatives.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Must Have:&#xD;
· College or University degree in Computer Science or relevant experience;&#xD;
· Minimum of 6-9 years experience as a Unix Systems Administrator (preferably AIX);&#xD;
· Extensive Shell scripting experience;&#xD;
· Good Communications skills; &#xD;
· In-depth understanding of RS6000 hardware;&#xD;
· Self-directed team player with a strong drive to succeed and a high degree of enthusiasm and vision; and&#xD;
· On call pager support and some weekend work required.&#xD;
· Experience supporting and maintaining web servers &#xD;
· Extensive experience in HACMP environment &#xD;
 &#xD;
Good to Have:&#xD;
· Expert in apache/IHS and iPlanet/SunONE web server&#xD;
· Experience in WebSphere application server and J2EE applications&#xD;
· Experience in web application security and infrastructure&#xD;
· Exposure to: Application server: WebSphere 5.0.x/4.0.x/3.5.x; sapphire 7.x/5.x and Tomcat 4.x&#xD;
· Web Server: apache /2.0.x/1.3.x; IHS 2.0.x/1.3.x; iPlanet/SunONE 6.0/4.1.x/3.6.x&#xD;
· LDAP server: iPlanet LDAP server 5.x/4.12; IBM SecureWay Directory 5.1/4.1/3.2.2Reports to: Database and Systems Manager, Technical Services&#xD;
Thanking you in advance, &#xD;
&#xD;
Joanne Boucher &#xD;
Manager, Keith Bagg I.T. Search&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>A2666A85-8DA9-40F7-9593-8C6FCFBC875A</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-04-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>2 AIX Unix Administrators</title>
</post>
