<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Sapphire Canada, a division of Randstad Interim Inc., is one of North America's premier technology staffing firms, offering hundreds of permanent and contract opportunities across all roles, levels and platforms. Our Web-based tools simplify and accelerate your search for opportunities. When you're ready to interview we'll meet with you in person and help you build your career path. Visit www.sapphireca.com to get started!&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Weblogic Middleware Consultants (#127260)&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is currently seeking Middleware Consultants to join their team.&#xD;
&#xD;
The suitable candidate for this role possesses the following key skills:&#xD;
- Web Logic&#xD;
- Vignette&#xD;
- Apache&#xD;
- IIS&#xD;
- SiteMinder&#xD;
&#xD;
The successful applicant for this role possesses numerous Middleware skills. The ideal candidate must also have excellent presentation and communication skills. For more information, don’t delay, please apply online today!&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
Middleware (Must Have)&#xD;
WebLogic (Must Have)&#xD;
WebSphere (Must Have)&#xD;
Web Server (Must Have)&#xD;
IIS (Must Have)&#xD;
Siteminder (Must Have)&#xD;
Problem determination and resolution (Must Have)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Click here to apply&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Why work with Sapphire Canada?&#xD;
&#xD;
Every year, Sapphire Canada places approximately 4000 technology workers in more positions across the country, more often than any of our competitors. Our clients include 65% of the companies listing on the S&amp;P TSX 60, offering our job seekers access to a full range of career opportunities. Yet at Sapphire Canada, we're committed to more than numbers. We offer a personalized approach to your career development, simplified job search and application process, fair market rates and streamlined payment as well as value-added programs. For more information please visit www.sapphireca.com&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are ready to explore your next challenge, apply today.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sapphire Canada hires on the basis of merit and is committed to employment equity. We encourage all qualified persons to apply.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sapphire Canada is a division of Randstad Interim Inc. Randstad is the second largest staffing organization in the world with revenues in excess of $27 billion.  Randstad has 28,000 employees working from 4,300 branches who employ over 450,000 people every day. For more information, please visit www.randstad.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
Sapphire Canada is a part of the Randstad Canada Group</content>
    <postId>A34687ED-8A41-48CF-B392-69EDBDA1C4B2</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-11-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Weblogic Middleware Consultants (#127260)</title>
</post>
