<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>There are a lot of things I do not do because of fear. However in order to justify my own actions I tell myself I can do it when time comes or I need more time or provide other lame excuses.&#xD;
&#xD;
But I realize other facts. If I can not do it right now, how can I do it when time comes. If I am not prepared, how could I delivery ? I've give up a lot of things due to lack of preparation.&#xD;
&#xD;
For instance there is a new immigrant person is struggling to get a job due to communication difficulty.  Do you think "Is it only reason ?". The other hand other immigrants are getting hired daily bases. Communication is only the part of the qualifications. Of cause it is the big part. In order to improve the communication it takes some time. Some cases it takes years. Can you afford that time or Is it another lame excuse to justify ? Try to find where you can make improvement. It could be very small step but it will add up. &#xD;
&#xD;
From my own estimation also from the successful people's experience only way you can overcome any difficult jobs is confronting or facing your own fears or problems. Let's not kid ourselves.&#xD;
&#xD;
Let's find the space we can improve and let's face our fears whatever it could be. I believe we could be anybody we wish to be with right goal and plan. Let's knock the wall, fear, down. There will be other world at the other side of the wall.&#xD;
&#xD;
Please do the followings&#xD;
- Pick up the piece of blank paper&#xD;
- Write down the ideal person you want to be or goal at the left hand side&#xD;
- Write down what you have honestly at the right hand side&#xD;
- Mark the items you are missing from left to right&#xD;
* There are your fears in front of your face&#xD;
&#xD;
Good Luck. Remember : Only people can control their own fears will be the persons the best they can be&#xD;
        &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>A4609A03-BB62-4F36-84FA-A76683D4A36D</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Fear Factor</title>
</post>
