<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이종화</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Junior / Intermediate UNIX (Linux primary, AIX preferred) SA with 2-3 years experience only.  Windows (AD) exposure will help too.  simply the UNIX / Windows knowledge needed. The expected start time is October. There is also a possibility to convert the person into permanent after 6 months of contract. &#xD;
&#xD;
Looking for someone with strong Communication skills with interacting with customers in Capital markets, Risk management and Information Management areas in the bank which this tams supports. The manager will train candidate on the environment but he needs a liaison with these customers. Very complex environment 20+ projects running in 1 server environment – Duration: 6 month then convert to perm &#xD;
&#xD;
Intermediate DB Technical Analyst - minimum 3-4 yrs exp..Banking or large enterprise environment ORACLE/Solaris/RHEL ACCOUNTABILITIES    Manage the help ticket system: approve requests, assign tickets to resources, research problems noted in the tickets, resolve problems, close out tickets, and correspond with the ticket creator throughout the lifecycle of the ticket.    Perform day-to-day maintenance tasks on the database.  Ensure that the data in the database is accurate and there is no loss of integrity.  Troubleshoot problems quickly as they arise.    Participate in annual survey refreshes.  This may include performing the database related refresh tasks, or working with external vendors to complete the database aspects of the project.    Perform regular data transfers with the primary service line funding partner. Maintain the database mapping per the funding partner’s instructions. Generate, format and send data transfer files to the funding partner’s designated point-of-contact.    Manage outsourced contractors by assisting in functionality requirements, implementation, and testing of work products.    Respond to ad hoc customer requests (internal and external) and work with them to meet their needs.    Assist other research projects and managers with relevant data collection efforts.  Specific tasks may including querying the database for submissions, importing bulk submissions and performing mass changes to the data.    Document technical processes and procedures used to support systems, tools, and processes.    Perform other appropriate tasks as requested.     Serve as the liaison between the business owners, development teams, and end users.    Communicate and collaborate with external and internal customers to analyze needs and requirements, and deliver the following as needed: use cases, wireframe designs, functional requirements, system requirements specifications, and process diagrams.    Successfully engage in multiple projects simultaneously.  Team here is a further update on the role I released yesterday. Plus the location has changed to Yonge and Sheppard Title of the position:        Intermediate Development Systems Support Analyst Qualifications:                the individual should have recent working knowledge and experience in supporting Linux environments (including application deployment and troubleshooting); working knowledge of Windows server environment; Websphere and BO (Business Object) experience or knowledge are optional; Have strong troubleshooting and analyzing skill in UNIX; good communication and interpersonal skills; able to handle tasks with little supervision or training. duration:          6 months and will probably get extended &#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
Miguel Allamani&#xD;
Senior Consultant&#xD;
TES-The Employment Solution&#xD;
(416) 482 2420 ext. 283&#xD;
(800) 818 4744 ext. 283&#xD;
Fax (416) 482 9282&#xD;
miguela@tes.net &#xD;
www.tes.net</content>
    <postId>A90BE3AF-612A-45F2-8C07-38838094B59A</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-09-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>3 open roles with BMO (refrence Ricky Lee)</title>
</post>
