<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I am writing to inquire as to whether you may be interested in / suited for the following role advertised with one of our clients. Details are following and if you are suited &amp; interested please respond with a most recent resume ASAP. Please forward this information around to your network as well if there may be people suited for it.&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client located in Toronto is looking for a Java Team Lead for a permanent opportunity.&#xD;
&#xD;
They are looking for someone to be accountable and responsible for the development of applications under the corporate umbrella. The role will include systems analysis, design, coding and unit / integration testing of identified systems. They are seeking advanced skill in J2EE and A minimum of five years experience in a JAVA development arena including at least one year in a similar lead role.&#xD;
&#xD;
Type: Permanent Full time&#xD;
Rate: 85K base salary +&#xD;
Start: Immediate&#xD;
&#xD;
As always, I can also be found on LinkedIn, if we aren't already connected please add me as I keep relevant work opportunities posted and I openly network with it. Click here:  http://ca.linkedin.com/in/lucasrobbins&#xD;
&#xD;
Cheers,&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Lucas Robbins&#xD;
Senior Recruitment Consultant&#xD;
Recruiting experts in Information Technology&#xD;
&#xD;
HAYS Recruiting experts worldwide&#xD;
&#xD;
701-201City Centre Drive&#xD;
Mississauga ON L5B 2T4&#xD;
&#xD;
D: 905 366 4527&#xD;
T: 905 848 HAYS (4297) x222&#xD;
&#xD;
M: 905 805 6872&#xD;
F: 905 566 8877&#xD;
E: lrobbins@hays.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
hays.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
Connect with me via LinkedIn: http://ca.linkedin.com/in/lucasrobbins</content>
    <postId>A99F6E2B-D05D-4068-8C91-459C787775C8</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-09-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>HAYS IT - J2EE Team Lead Job Opportunity</title>
</post>
