<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김민</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Procommers! &#xD;
&#xD;
The position below is currently available through Procom. If you meet the qualifications and are interested in this opportunity please apply as per the instructions below. Please note, this automated email has been sent to you as the result of a successful keyword search on your resume within our database. Please use discretion by only applying to positions that best suit your qualifications. If you wish to remove yourself from future mailings, please click the link supplied below. &#xD;
&#xD;
Procom KW is recruiting on behalf of our Kitchener-Waterloo client, a Software Development company and a leader in their niche industry. They are creating a new development team and need to start with two Java Developers. In this role you will be responsible for server-side development and analysis and coding of business/enterprise applications. &#xD;
&#xD;
Mandatory Skills: &#xD;
&#xD;
5+ years Java, Server side Development &#xD;
4+ years Servlets, SOAP, Tomcat, Oracle and XML &#xD;
3+ yearsSQL &#xD;
&#xD;
* It is also very important to note that this particular development shop uses Java Servlet vs EJB and our client requires experience with Enterprise Applications development. &#xD;
&#xD;
Location: Kitchener- Waterloo &#xD;
Duration: Permanent &#xD;
Rate/Salary: Very competitive base salary, benefits and options &#xD;
Start Date: Immediate &#xD;
&#xD;
PROCOM SERVICES &#xD;
&#xD;
All submissions will be assessed and all applicants WILL RECEIVE A RESPONSE within 2 business days. I thank you in advance for your interest. If you meet the mandatory requirements and are interested in these roles; submit your most recent resume to: kathrync@procom.ca quoting 12400 in the subject line. &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>A9B21637-6A7B-4080-BB20-6E1B9C2B622C</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-12-21T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Kitchener- Waterloo 's  Java Developers Position via Procom</title>
</post>
