<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김중수</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>어디서 구하셨습니까? 아줌마.&#xD;
정말 재미있군요.&#xD;
근데 Newfi는 New fundland에 사는 사람들인가요?&#xD;
문맥의 내용으로 봐서 그런것 같네요..&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
강윤정 wrote:&#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke #1&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; A Canadian is walking down the street with a case of beer under his arm.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; His friend Doug stops him and asks, "Hey Bob! Whacha get the case of beer&#xD;
&gt; for?"&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; "I got it for my wife, eh." answers Bob.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; "Oh!" exclaims Doug, "Good trade."&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke #2&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; An Ontarian wanted to become a Newfie. He went to a neurosurgeon and asked&#xD;
&gt; "Is there anything you can do to me that would make me into a Newfie?"&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; "Sure, it's easy." replied the neurosurgeon. "All I have to do is cut out&#xD;
&gt; 1/3 of your brain, and you'll be a Newfie."&#xD;
&gt; The Ontarian was very pleased, and immediately underwent the operation.&#xD;
&gt; However, the surgeon's knife slipped, and instead of cutting out 1/3 of the&#xD;
&gt; patient's brain, the surgeon accidentally cut out 2/3 of the patient's&#xD;
&gt; brain. He was terribly remorseful, and waited impatiently beside the&#xD;
&gt; patient's bed as the patient recovered from the anesthetic.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; As soon as the patient was conscious, the neurosurgeon said to him, "I'm&#xD;
&gt; terribly sorry, but there was a ghastly accident. Instead of cutting out 1/3&#xD;
&gt; of your brain, I accidentally cut out 2/3 of your brain."&#xD;
&gt; The patient replied "Qu'est-ce que vous avez dit, monsieur?"&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke # 3&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; Did you hear about the war between Newfoundland and Nova Scotia? The Newfies&#xD;
&gt; were lobbing hand grenades. The Nova Scotians were pulling the pins and&#xD;
&gt; throwing them back.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke #4&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; In Canada we have two Seasons.. six months of winter and six months of poor&#xD;
&gt; snowmobiling.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke #5&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; One day an Englishman, an American, and a Canadian walked into a pub&#xD;
&gt; together. They proceeded to each buy a pint of Molson Canadian. Just as they&#xD;
&gt; were about to enjoy their beverage three flies landed in each  of their&#xD;
&gt; pints.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; The Englishman pushed his beer away from him in disgust.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; The American fished the offending fly out of his beer and continued drinking&#xD;
&gt; it as if nothing had happened.&#xD;
&gt; The Canadian picked the fly out of his drink and started shaking it over the&#xD;
&gt; pint, yelling, "SPIT IT OUT, SPIT IT OUT YOU S-O-B!!!"&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke #6&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; A French guest, staying in a hotel in Edmonton phoned room service for some&#xD;
&gt; pepper.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; "Black pepper, or white pepper?" asked the concierge.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; "Toilette pepper!"&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke # 7&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; An American, a Scot and a Canadian were in a terrible car accident. They&#xD;
&gt; were all brought to the same emergency room, but all three of them died&#xD;
&gt; before they arrived. Just as they were about to put the toe tag on the&#xD;
&gt; American, he stirred and opened his eyes.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Astonished, the doctors and nurses present asked him what happened.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; "Well, "said the American, "I remember the crash, and then there was a&#xD;
&gt; beautiful light, and then the Canadian and the Scot and I were standing at&#xD;
&gt; the gates of heaven. St. Peter approached us and said that we were all too&#xD;
&gt; young to die, and that for a donation of $50, we could return to the earth.&#xD;
&gt; So of course I pulled out my wallet and gave him the $50, and the next thing&#xD;
&gt; I knew I was back here."&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; "That's amazing!" said one of the doctors, "But what happened to the other&#xD;
&gt; two?"&#xD;
&gt; "Last I saw them," replied the American, "the Scot was haggling over the&#xD;
&gt; price and the Canadian was waiting for the government to pay for his."&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Canadian Joke # 8&#xD;
&gt; -----------------&#xD;
&gt; The Canadian Transportation Safety Board recently divulged that they had&#xD;
&gt; covertly funded a project with an auto maker for the past five years,&#xD;
&gt; whereby the auto makers were installing black boxes in four-wheel drive&#xD;
&gt; pick-up trucks in an effort to determine, in fatal accidents, the&#xD;
&gt; circumstances in the last 15 seconds before the crash.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; They were surprised to find in almost all areas of Canada, the last words of&#xD;
&gt; drivers in 61.2 percent of fatal crashes were, "Oh, God!" Only the Nova&#xD;
&gt; Scotia's were different, where 89.3 percent of the final words were: "Hold&#xD;
&gt; my beer and watch this".&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Never Underestimate the Power of a Woman&#xD;
&gt; -----------------------------------------&#xD;
&gt; There were 11 people-ten were men and one woman- hanging onto a rope that&#xD;
&gt; came down from a helicopter.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; They all decided that one person should get off because if they didn't the&#xD;
&gt; rope would break and everyone would die.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; No one could decide who should go so finally the woman gave a really&#xD;
&gt; touching speech saying how she would give up her life to save the others,&#xD;
&gt; because women were used to giving up things for their husbands and children,&#xD;
&gt; giving in to men, and not receiving anything in return.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; When she finished speaking, all the men started clapping.&#xD;
&gt; &#xD;
&gt; Never underestimate the power of a woman.&#xD;
&gt; </content>
    <postId>ACA94FDD-6002-4D9A-9E8D-8A8D7A6CE8CB</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-09-26T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>정말 재미있군요...우리 회사애들한테 모두 보내야겠어요..</title>
</post>
