<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이홍식</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>POSTED AT 8:41 AM EDT Tuesday, September 17&#xD;
Corporate News&#xD;
By RICHARD BLOOM&#xD;
Globe and Mail Update&#xD;
&#xD;
&amp;#8226; Investment bank UBS Warburg on Tuesday lowered its 2003 and 2004 earnings forecast on Oracle Corp., the world's second-biggest software company, according to sources Tuesday morning. The sources told Reuters that UBS speculated first-quarter results, expected after the close on Tuesday, would be in line with consensus estimates but said management may give more cautious guidance. &#xD;
&#xD;
Investment bank UBS가 2003,2004년의 Oracle Corp 예상수익을 낯추었답니다. (이 정보의)출처는 Reuters에 UBS가 화요일 폐장후 기대되는 (Oracle의) 1사분기 실적은 기대치에 부합할 것으로 추측하나 (수익해석에 있어) 경영진이 좀 더 조심스러운 해석을 내 놓게 될 것이라고 전하였습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
Speculate라는 단어의 근본의미는 추측(guess)이나 상당한 고민끝에 나온 추측(speculate)입니다. 그러나 영영사전에서 풀이한 것 처럼 사실에 근거한 단언/확언과는 거리가 멉니다. 깊이 생각한 끝에 어떤 사람은 억측을 펼 수도 있겠지요. Guess가 구어적 표현이라면 Speculate는 좀 더 격식을 차린 문어적 추측이겠습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
야후사전...&#xD;
spec·u·late &#xD;
－ v.i. (-lat·ed, -lat·ing)&#xD;
&#xD;
1 [Ⅰ([부])] [Ⅱthat[절] / wh-[절] / wh- to do]&#xD;
⑴ (…에 대하여) 심사 숙고하다, 사색하다(meditate)&lt;about, on, upon, as to ‥&gt;.&#xD;
ㆍ ∼ about the meaning of life 인생의 의의에 대해서 골똘히 생각하다.&#xD;
&#xD;
⑵ (…이라고) 추측[억측]하다&lt;about, on, as to ‥&gt;.&#xD;
ㆍ ∼ on where the satellite will fall 인공 위성의 낙하 지점을 추측하다.&#xD;
ㆍ We ∼d that the two might be engineers. 그 두 사람은 기술자일 것이라고 추측했다.&#xD;
&#xD;
2 [Ⅰ([부])] (주식·토지 등에) 투기하다&lt;in ‥&gt;, (…을) 시세를 예측하고 사다[팔다]&lt;on ‥&gt;.&#xD;
ㆍ ∼ in real estate 부동산에 손을 대다.&#xD;
ㆍ ∼ on the devaluation of the dollar 달러의 평가 절하를 예측하고 투기를 하다.&#xD;
&#xD;
[어원]&#xD;
☞ 라틴어 speculatus에서. (specere 보다 ＋ -atus ＝관찰되다 → 숙고하다). ▷ SPECIES, SPECTER, SPECIMEN&#xD;
&#xD;
Cambridge Dictionary...&#xD;
speculate (GUESS)&#xD;
verb &#xD;
to form opinions about something without having the necessary information or facts; to make guesses &#xD;
I don't really know what happened - I'm just speculating. [I]&#xD;
So far, the police can only speculate on the possible motives for the killing. [I]&#xD;
A spokesperson declined to speculate on the cause of the train crash. [I]&#xD;
Journalists are speculating about whether interest rates will be cut. [I]&#xD;
I wouldn't like to speculate how much that car must have cost him. [+ wh- word]&#xD;
It would be wrong to speculate why she resigned. [+ wh- word]&#xD;
It has been speculated that dinosaurs became extinct because the Earth's climate changed. [+ that clause]&#xD;
&#xD;
m-w dictionary...&#xD;
1 : to take to be true on the basis of insufficient evidence : THEORIZE &lt;speculated that a virus caused the disease&gt;&#xD;
2 : to be curious or doubtful about : WONDER &lt;speculates whether it will rain all vacation&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>B04BB9C1-B60A-4E5E-915D-25020D485DDB</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>speculate</title>
</post>
