<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello! I'm reaching out to you as I have a really great opportunity for a client of ours in the Kitchener/Waterloo area that might be of interest to you. I've pasted the details below so please take a look! They are looking for someone who has experience working in the healthcare field on integration projects. There is some travel involved as some of these projects are deployed across Canada. I realize that you might not fit this requirement but am hoping that you will send this onto anyone that you might know that would benefit from hearing about this opportunity. &#xD;
&#xD;
Position: Technical Application Consultant &#xD;
&#xD;
Mandatory Skills: &#xD;
-5+ years experience in technical and complex IT solutions &#xD;
-Strong experience working with integration projects throughout the lifecycle &#xD;
-Intermediate to Advanced knowledge of networking, hardware, and operating systems, databases, remote connectivity, security and image processing. &#xD;
-Strong knowledge of Windows XP, UNIX, SQL, Oracle and other databases -Scripting knowledge such as XML, TCL,VB.NET is required &#xD;
-Experience with DICOM and HL7 -Proven process design and documentation skills (scripts and interface &#xD;
parameters) &#xD;
-Experience within the hospital or healthcare environment is an asset. &#xD;
-Demonstrated continuous learning orientation, particularly around new technologies, applications and medical developments and healthcare industry standards. &#xD;
-Bilingual (French/English) &#xD;
-Undergraduate degree in Computer Science discipline is required &#xD;
&#xD;
Location: Kitchener/Waterloo (Ontario, Canada) &#xD;
Duration: Permanent &#xD;
Rate/Salary: Negotiable &#xD;
Start Date: Immediate &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description: On behalf of our Client, Procom KW is searching for a Technical Applications Project Manager. As part of the integration services team, the successful Candidate will be responsible for the successful delivery/support of the Company's Integration Services (including RIS and Cardio). Reporting to the Manager, Integration Services, the incumbent of this role works as a team to provide project, product and technical expertise and manages the execution of customer HE software integration, migration, upgrade or consulting projects. &#xD;
&#xD;
Main responsibilities include: &#xD;
-Possess a deep technical knowledge within a specific product, clinical or technical domain area required within the Applications Team. &#xD;
-Participates as a technical expert for Integrations Services working with the customer and the Internal team to integrate and implement HE solutions. &#xD;
-Manages assigned projects, communication and collaborating with internal and external stakeholders. &#xD;
-As a component of managing the project, analyze customer needs and develop site-specific workflow requirements for software configuration &#xD;
-Conducts analysis of the integration requirements during pre- and post-sales phases of projects. &#xD;
-Writes and submits for approval the functional requirements documentation and Statements of Work (SOW) for each software project (which may include customization and training). &#xD;
-Provides technical and/or professional coordination and leadership in the execution of software project update activities. &#xD;
-Participates and may lead integration workshops with internal and external parties as applicable to design integration specifications within projects. &#xD;
-Provides technical expertise and collaborate with external vendors for customer installations. &#xD;
-Understands and clearly communicates the implications of system functionality and technical changes and their impact on clinical and business operations within the hospital environment. &#xD;
-Support hospital RIS Go-Live environments in the capacity of technical and application functionality resource. &#xD;
&#xD;
PROCOM SERVICES &#xD;
A leading provider of IT services in North America, PROCOM and PROCOM SERVICES currently have more than 2700 consultants on assignment and place hundreds of people in permanent positions annually. For over 28 years, we have been finding high-quality jobs for our candidates. Our policies of maintaining open communication with both clients and candidates consistently make us the IT Firm of Choice. &#xD;
&#xD;
We would like to thank you for your interest. Please note that all submissions will be assessed and all applicants will receive a follow up within 2 business days. &#xD;
&#xD;
Please submit your most recent resume to: cindyw@procom.ca</content>
    <postId>B2E94E2E-FA5E-4446-B357-B275718AA663</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-04-06T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[PERM] Waterloo/Kitchner, Technical Application Consultant</title>
</post>
