<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Date : May 22nd, 2003&#xD;
&#xD;
   Annika Played her inaugural PGA tour round today. As far as her score is concerned she should be satisfied with her score. But think about all the pressure she has to deal with. For instance if I bet $1 per stroke while I play, my golf swing changes due to the pressure. &#xD;
&#xD;
    I am sorry I should explain what happened last week. There were few noted happenings last 10 days. V.J. Singh and Nick Price, both are well renowned professional golfers, had negative comments about Annika playing in men’s tour.  V.J. Said, “She does not belong here. She has no business to come men’s office.” It could be acceptable comment if it was private chatting. But it wasn't politically correct. In a way it caused extra media circus on this week PGA tour. Also Tiger Wood helped the hoopla. He is on Annika’s side. Tiger called her couple of times and gave her how to deal with over focused media and course management insight of Colonial, this particular week site. He is not playing this week because he is in Europe right now. But he played the media perfectly. He is not only #1 player but also he knows how to play the media. For those two players are against Annika, I do not think their market price raised. I believe Tiger’s value went up if there is any room for improvement.&#xD;
&#xD;
   Her score was 1 over par today. Let me give your more realistic figure. She is in the middle of the group. If she keeps up, she will make the cut. That means she will play through the weekend. It will be astonishing accomplishment for a lady and it could open the door for many other ladies like Se Ri Pak and 13 years old second generation Korean sensation Michelle Wie. But score itself could mislead what she had to deal with such as extra distance, deeper rough, steep green and most of all tremendous pressure. She said, “Worst could happen is I will learn something from the experience and I am ready for the opportunity.”&#xD;
&#xD;
    Probably how she is handling herself and her outlook are what I like to discuss with you. Even though it is the pressure packed experience but she is taking advantage of the situation. She is not worrying about the worst-case scenario. She will deal with it when it comes and she will make right choices to turn the challenges into the opportunities. &#xD;
&#xD;
   It is what we all should do. Do not stay in comfort zone and look for the challenges. Go places we haven’t gone before. If I stay in the places I know I will be safe, are there any fun or personal growth ? Proactively searching for potential problems. When rainy day comes we will be ready. We know what we can do.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ps : I was talking to James yesterday about Weblogic seminar held on this week. James told me Weblogic likes to start user group in Toronto. Let’s expand our network. Please join the user group and if possible, become a board member. If you like to in mainstream Java programmer group, it is the chance. Go places you haven’t gone before. </content>
    <postId>B590B9F1-FC06-4EE9-966F-6E91E716DA71</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Annika Sorenstam Story 2</title>
</post>
