<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hello Scott,&#xD;
 &#xD;
Thanks for taking the time to speak with me this afternoon. As I mentioned, I am currently looking for a Java Developer for a contract position in Ottawa. If you know someone that would be interested please let me know.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Take care,&#xD;
Teresa&#xD;
 &#xD;
Java Developer Job Description:&#xD;
TEKsystems is currently looking for a Java web developer with strong web interface experience. This is a 6 month contract in Kanata.&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is looking for someone to join a team in the IP Division Customer Support and Design Engineering group responsible for:&#xD;
&#xD;
-Web application development in support of a business division. &#xD;
-Working in a fast-paced environment with design architects to implement OSS solutions for customers by integrating existing tools and developing custom solutions. &#xD;
-Design and development of web applications core to the IP Division customer support and design engineering business. &#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities and Required Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
- The developer will be responsible for creating and maintaining web application interfaces using standard browser technologies and open source libraries.&#xD;
- Understanding of principles of graphic and interaction design, experience with image manipulation &#xD;
- Familiarity with Web 2.0 and rich web client concepts.&#xD;
- Solid experience with Spring/Hybernate frameworks&#xD;
- Strong UNIX experience&#xD;
- Experience building web portals&#xD;
- IP networking experience&#xD;
- XML experience&#xD;
- Bachelor degree in computer / electrical engineering, computer science, or equivalent &#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested in this position please apply as soon as possible as this is a time sensitive job opportunity.&#xD;
&#xD;
*TEKsystems would like to thank all those who apply however, only short listed candidates will be contacted. Two managerial references are required for anyone wishing to work with TEKsystems. Please be prepared to provide them.*&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Teresa Malfara  Technical Recruiter&#xD;
40 Hines Road Suite 120, Kanata, ON, K2K 2M5800.759.3855  T               613.254.5015         613.254.5015&#xD;
F 613.254.5090  &#xD;
http://www.linkedin.com/in/teresamalfara</content>
    <postId>B8D5CD14-4325-4B90-A78E-63856C647EB5</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-10-09T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Developer for a contract position in Ottawa</title>
</post>
