<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김경용</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>에이전시에게 받은 메일을 올립니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Hi James,&#xD;
one of our clients located in St. Catharines has recently requested a short list of consultants from our firm for their future project. I believe that this opportunity may be of interest to you. If you are interested in this contract opportunity (or you know anyone from the circle of your friends), please respond to this email with all submission requirements by no later than Monday 2 p.m. &#xD;
&#xD;
Note: Submissions with missing information will not be considered. &#xD;
&#xD;
For further details, please contact our consultant support line at 416.767.4323.&#xD;
&#xD;
Thank you,&#xD;
Steve&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Steve&#xD;
HR Consultant&#xD;
RecruiterSquad&#xD;
Tel: 416.767.4323&#xD;
Website: www.recruitersquad.com &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
=================================================&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Title: &#xD;
Web Developer - Programmer Analyst &#xD;
&#xD;
City &amp; Province Location of the Job: &#xD;
St. Catharines, Ontario &#xD;
&#xD;
Submission Requirements: (submissions with incomplete information will not be considered): &#xD;
. In 3 to 5 sentences, describe your understanding of the project requirements. &#xD;
. Complete the Skills Matrix. &#xD;
. You must submit a comprehensive resume. You resumes should focus on how your previous work experience and knowledge would be relevant to this project. You must also demonstrate that you meet or exceed the mandatory skills requirements. &#xD;
. Confirm that you will be available for the duration of the contract. &#xD;
. References: Provide no less than three (3) references. References must be provided in the following format: Name, Title, Organization, Phone Number, Email. &#xD;
. Desired Hourly Rate: Provide your hourly rate in CAD dollars. &#xD;
. Corporate Status: Confirm that you are incorporated. &#xD;
. Security Screening: Provide your Contractor Security Screening Clearance number. If you do not have the security screening number, confirm that should you become the successful candidate for this project, you agree to undergo the Level 1 CPIC clearance security screening as requested by the client. &#xD;
Position Summary:&#xD;
Project Start Date: May 11, 2009&#xD;
Project End Date: September 25, 2009 (to a maximum of 100 working days) &#xD;
&#xD;
Purpose of Assignment:&#xD;
Our client is interested in offering to the members of their organization an online view of the IT Service Desk's current volume statistics, offer help for their clients without having to call and/or email the Service Desk by providing clients facing knowledge, FAQ's, hints, tips as well as, training videos. Our client is also looking to develop and an ITS internal presence to deliver training videos, provide knowledge sharing capabilities, online views of change calendar, major incidents and documentation. In order to do so a website needs to be developed. &#xD;
&#xD;
Assignment description: &#xD;
The Consultant will be responsible for providing support by performing the following tasks:&#xD;
1. Design, Develop and populate MSSQL database&#xD;
2. Develop Custom Style Sheets (CSS)&#xD;
3. Nice to Have - Develop integration with IM Aware (www.awareim.com)&#xD;
4. Nice to Have - Develop integration with Remedy Change Module (online change calendar)&#xD;
5. Nice to Have - Develop integration with Remedy Profile tables for VIP/Executive status flag updates&#xD;
6. Nice to Have - Develop integration with Remedy Locations tables for correlation with VIP/Executive locations&#xD;
7. Nice to Have - Develop integration with Remedy WhiteBoard&#xD;
8. Nice to Have - Develop integration with Remedy Knowledge Base for WIKI style knowledge sharing&#xD;
9. Nice to Have - Develop integration with SQUAD tool &#xD;
10. Develop integration with Crystal Reports for real-time report access&#xD;
11. Develop integration for RSS feed&#xD;
12. Port all current content from Service Desk website&#xD;
a. Manager Blog&#xD;
b. Daily Debrief&#xD;
c. User Profiles (with changes)&#xD;
d. Training Manual (with changes)&#xD;
13. Integrate searching capabilities for entire site&#xD;
14. Develop integration for training: Q&amp;A, Hints, Tips and Video training&#xD;
15. Develop file sharing capabilities&#xD;
16. Develop section for release management and internal project activity tracking &#xD;
17. Develop section for broadcasting SM branch operational plan&#xD;
18. Develop section for career pathing and tracking methods for SM staff&#xD;
19. Develop section for tracking staff training initiatives and associated costs&#xD;
&#xD;
You will also be asked to assist with:&#xD;
. Create administrators guide and support documentation for the web application(s)&#xD;
. User acceptance testing of the tool(s)&#xD;
&#xD;
Working Hours: &#xD;
The Client's normal working hours are 7.25 hours per day. &#xD;
&#xD;
Working Hours: &#xD;
Billing and Payment Process - The Consultant is required to submit an invoice on a monthly basis (2nd business day of the following month) along with a timesheet to:</content>
    <postId>BC24608F-267A-4047-83F5-1BCA9410BA8E</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-05-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Contract Opportunity in St. Catharines, Ontario</title>
</post>
