<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Contract:  6 Months+&#xD;
 MUST HAVE JBOSS OR WEBLOGIC VERSION 10&#xD;
Overview:&#xD;
Design, develop, and implement software applications on a 24X7 web based client facing application.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
Develop detailed program specifications &#xD;
Unit test code.&#xD;
Develop and maintain application code&#xD;
Participate in integration and regression testing&#xD;
Prepare technical documentation.&#xD;
Implement security policies&#xD;
 &#xD;
Interpersonal and Technical Skills&#xD;
Must have excellent verbal and written communication skills in English.&#xD;
Must be a good team player with positive attitude.&#xD;
Self-starter with the ability to learn quickly, has good problem-solving skills and&#xD;
can meet tight deadlines&#xD;
 &#xD;
Qualifications:&#xD;
Bachelor’s degree in computer science, engineering, or a related discipline&#xD;
At least 8 years of experience in systems development with 5+ years in Internet&#xD;
environment.&#xD;
Excellent front end and backend development skills.&#xD;
Experience developing client facing, W3C standards compliant, web applications supporting multiple browsers and operating systems.     &#xD;
Strong knowledge of concepts, practices and procedures of systems development&#xD;
life cycle. Relies on experience and judgment to plan and accomplish goals.&#xD;
Excellent technical skills and experience with the environments and tools identified below.  &#xD;
Systems Environment:&#xD;
Multi-tier web based solutions, wide variety of hardware and operating systems&#xD;
(Linux, AIX, Windows, etc), Oracle, and MS SQL, Agile and RUP (development&#xD;
methodology), Rational suite of products to manage development life cycle,&#xD;
Replication Server Technology, Remedy, Spectrum, Patrol, Networking fundamentals,&#xD;
PKI, Intrusion Detection, X.500 Directory&#xD;
 &#xD;
Development Environment and Tools:&#xD;
Java, J2EE, Spring, hibernate, JDBC, SOA, XSLT, FLEX, JSON, CSS, XML, HTML,&#xD;
Debugging tools, application servers(Weblogic, JBOSS), Apache, Linux, scripting&#xD;
tools and languages, Oracle, Eclipse, ClearCase, ClearQuest, UML, Knowledge of&#xD;
modeling tools. Hailstorm for vulnerability testing and Fortify for code security scanning.  &#xD;
Dale Borrmann, Technical Recruiter&#xD;
Eagle Professional Resources Inc.&#xD;
W: (416) 861-1492 ext 2275&#xD;
Toll free: (888)-999-7311</content>
    <postId>C1A34467-A810-4DA2-A77F-8C40286D7B9B</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Java Developer</title>
</post>
