<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title:  Financial J2EE Technical Lead  &#xD;
Skills:  J2EE, J2SE, JDBC, EJB (Session, Entity, Message driven beans), JMS, Ant, Struts, Financial Experience &#xD;
  &#xD;
Date:  9-13-2003 &#xD;
Location:  Toronto, CDA Canada &#xD;
Area code:  416 &#xD;
  &#xD;
Tax term:  CON_W2 &#xD;
Pay rate:  Senior/Hour &#xD;
Length:  Temp &#xD;
  &#xD;
Position ID:  300168 &#xD;
Dice ID:  teksyst &#xD;
  &#xD;
Job description: &#xD;
Our client a leader in the financial industry is currently seeking a&#xD;
Senior Financial J2EE Technical Lead for a 6 month plus extension&#xD;
contract. This person will be responsible for:&#xD;
&#xD;
* Understand and translate business requirements into design&#xD;
specifications&#xD;
* Lead and mentor small development teams to develop applications&#xD;
* Assist and code complex functionalities&#xD;
* Document the developed applications and code such the code is&#xD;
maintainable&#xD;
* Support applications in their deployment phases&#xD;
* Application Enhancements&#xD;
&#xD;
Technical Must Haves:&#xD;
&#xD;
* J2EE&#xD;
* J2SE&#xD;
* EJB (Senior Entity, Session &amp; Message Driven Beans)&#xD;
* JMS (Strong Security)&#xD;
* XML&#xD;
* JSP with Oracle&#xD;
* CVS&#xD;
* Design Patterns (Ant, UML, XML &amp; Jakarta STRUTS)&#xD;
&#xD;
Join TEKsystems, one of the leading IT consulting and services providers in Canada and the United States. As a result of our rapid growth and merger with our sister company, Maxim Group, we are constantly searching for talented technical professionals with all levels of information technology and communications skills. From the&#xD;
personal delivery of your weekly cheques, to our dedication at finding you the next project, we take care of our people. TEKsystems knows that every professional has different needs, so we'll work together to determine a suitable benefits package. We offer our team members&#xD;
medical, dental, provisions for vacation and holiday pay, EAP (Employee Assistance Plan), Lawline (24 hour Legal Assistance), FoneMed (24 hour Health Advice), and technical and professional training.&#xD;
 &#xD;
  &#xD;
Travel required:  none &#xD;
Telecommute:  no &#xD;
  &#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Contact for more information:&#xD;
Ferguson,Brian&#xD;
TEKsystems&#xD;
5975 Whittle Road Suite 200&#xD;
&#xD;
Mississauga, ON 431&#xD;
&#xD;
Phone: (905) 501-2872 &#xD;
Fax: (602) 605-7090 &#xD;
 &#xD;
E-mail: brfergus@teksystems.com &#xD;
Web: http://www.teksystems.com/ &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>C41C34CF-DF99-4314-BA77-8A490CB71B4C</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-09-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Financial J2EE Technical Lead  - Toronto</title>
</post>
