<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&#xD;
Position: 		Collections Quality Assurance Analyst&#xD;
	&#xD;
Location:		 TCRS - 3 Concorde Gate, Don Mills	&#xD;
&#xD;
Posting Date:	Tuesday March 9, 2004		Closing Date:	Friday March 12, 2004&#xD;
&#xD;
	This position is responsible for the overall quality control of the collection area, and for evaluating, monitoring and reviewing 	programs, processes, policies and procedures to ensure compliance.  This position will also create and review collection reports to 	make suggestions for maximizing department efficiency.&#xD;
&#xD;
	Position Responsibilities&#xD;
&#xD;
	Creates, maintains and updates various reports &#xD;
	Identifies and documents trends for coaching opportunities and department effectiveness&#xD;
	Acts upon trends observed through analysis of reports to make proposals for process improvement and work flow management&#xD;
	Identifies productivity inefficiencies   &#xD;
	Documents results and reports &#xD;
	Completes delegated special assignments when required&#xD;
&#xD;
	Primarily regular office hours, Monday to Friday&#xD;
	Must be flexible with availability&#xD;
&#xD;
	Required Knowledge, Experience, Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
	Three years of retail collection experience or equivalent work experience	Thorough knowledge of provincial and federal legislation regarding collections &#xD;
	High proficiency with Microsoft Excel, Word and Power Point&#xD;
	Working knowledge of Microsoft Access&#xD;
	Strong analytical ability and good understanding of statistics for business&#xD;
	Familiarity with Davox and TSO&#xD;
	Excellent organizational, investigative, and problem solving skills  &#xD;
	Strong verbal and written communication skills  &#xD;
	Strong facilitation and presentation skills  &#xD;
	Must be goal oriented and be able to work independently and in a team atmosphere within a deadline driven environment &#xD;
	Flexible, adaptable and open to change&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
For those candidates who qualify for this Full Time opportunity please contact  Marisa Bucci, Employee Relations at x5317&#xD;
&#xD;
Reminder to internal applicants that you must complete an Application for Transfer form to submit with your resume.&#xD;
&#xD;
Don't forget the Employee  Referral Award program.  &#xD;
Do you know someone who may have the qualifications for this position?  If so, talk to them about applying.  &#xD;
You could earn $$$$$!!!&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>C44EAB1D-4294-4839-96CF-FFDC6AC2184E</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-03-09T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Quality Assurance Analyst</title>
</post>
