<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>The Software IT industry is a farce and most people working in programming are not geniuses by any means.  90 percent of programmers resumes consist of 90 percent lies.  It doesn't take a university degree or any post secondary education to be a programmer.&#xD;
&#xD;
  Below is some samples of how con-artists have successfully taken over the programming field.  The people and companies  cannot be named for obvious reasons.&#xD;
&#xD;
Part 1)&#xD;
&#xD;
  A Person took a Java certification course, he memorized a summarized list of most often asked Java questions.  At a company, during the interview process, he took a Java test.  It was multiple choice, which proves he can recite the list.  This person has no ingenuity, no logic and has never actually written, debugged or compiled a single line of  Java code.  This person was hired.  He is now making $60 per hour.&#xD;
&#xD;
Part 2)&#xD;
&#xD;
  My colleagues and I had acquired a person's resume. We had worked with her before and we came to a consensus that her resume was 90% false.  She had put on her resume, everything under the sun.  It was the kind of resume that only 3 people in the entire world could truly possibly have.  Through certain channels we found that at least one of her projects/companies on her resume was fake and the reference was bought.&#xD;
  There are companies who's business is selling fake references and projects to put on your resume.  She paid the company a few hundred dollars to allow her to put a job description on her resume, that they have sold thousands of times.  When the fake company gets a call regarding her name they look it up in their database&#xD;
and if she is paid up, she gets a good reference.&#xD;
  There are thousands of people with the same project on their resumes.  That must be one heck of a program by now. &#xD;
She was hired, without being asked any technical questions.  The man interviewing her said "I trust you".  She is working at a very large corporation, making $50 per hour.&#xD;
&#xD;
Part 3)&#xD;
&#xD;
  A person enrolled in a two month Java course which cost 800 dollars.&#xD;
On completion of the course she had memorized some Java theory, but she had never compiled a Java application.  She went on an interview where she recited a list of major topics on Java, that the so called "training center" had given her.  She passed the interview with ease.&#xD;
She is now making 56K/Year.  On her first day of work she called her friend who was making almost 50% less than she is, and asked him how to set up the Java compile environment.&#xD;
&#xD;
Part 4)&#xD;
&#xD;
  Another person pulled a similar scheme as in part 3.&#xD;
In his case he had taken a Powerbuilder course at a training center.  He memorized some of the theory, and a month later he had passed an interview.  He&#xD;
is now making 55K/Year.  On his resume he had stated 8 years of programming experience.  The truth is, he has actually been a chemical engineer with zero years of programming experience.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Conclusion.&#xD;
&#xD;
  Many training centers advertize high employment success rates for their "graduates".  The experience on the graduates resumes are sold to them by the training center for large amounts of money.  Along with a prefabricated project description the students will also receive a reference by a phoney employer.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
  I hope this letter helps to change things.  I love programming and I hate to see people with genuine talent lose their futures to con-artists.&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>C524DD6B-1A8B-4B1E-AC46-4FAFE75AE891</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-25T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>이력서의 허와 실(퍼온글)</title>
</post>
