<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2003-11-11T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>I'm not certain if I can answer all the questions at this session, but I will try to prepare 'something' dedicating to your issue.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Here I introduce simple address book application. This application starts with login page, http://www3.sympatico.ca/scottlee/temp/login.htm and displays main lookup page, http://www3.sympatico.ca/scottlee/temp/main.htm&#xD;
. &#xD;
Main menu consists of a listbox and &#xD;
1. Find - search person from listbox&#xD;
2. New - add new person&#xD;
3. Edit - edit existing person profile&#xD;
4. Delete - delete a person from list&#xD;
5. Report - display read only list for printing&#xD;
&#xD;
When 'New' or 'Edit' button is clicked, &#xD;
http://www3.sympatico.ca/scottlee/temp/entry.htm&#xD;
will be displayed. &#xD;
On 'report' button, &#xD;
http://www3.sympatico.ca/scottlee/temp/report.htm will be displayed. &#xD;
All data will be saved in a relational database. &#xD;
&#xD;
This is pretty standard and simple web application. If we build this application with Struts framework, how do we design?&#xD;
&#xD;
Some people will prefer tutorial style solution for example, AddressbookForm, AddressbookAction and RDB.&#xD;
1. How many FormBean or Action do we have to create in total?&#xD;
2. Do we need to create business object class separately from Action class?&#xD;
3. How can we apply MVC pattern from web page to database?&#xD;
4. Can we apply one generic Action class for this application?&#xD;
5. If we apply Validator plug in, can we reduce number of Form beans?&#xD;
6. If we use JNDI style user access control in future, how do you design?&#xD;
7. If we have wireless user interface in future, how do you design?&#xD;
8. If we add EJB at backend in future, how do you design?&#xD;
&#xD;
이상에 관한 여러분들의 경험을 듣고 싶습니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>C65040A6-63A1-418E-9F1F-5C4AB5BA7EA2</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-11-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Struts framework design problem</title>
</post>
