<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2009-04-20T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>요즘 정말 취업이메일이 오지 않습니다. 이민와서 이런 경우 처음입니다. 뉴스에 보니 사스카추안에서는 사람이 모자란다고 하네요. 지난 주 Global and mail에 미시사가의 전산회사에서 해고된 사람이 사스카추안에 가서 취업한 기사가 나왔습니다. 제 아내가 다니는 회사였습니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Middleware Specialist &#xD;
Mississauga, ON Open &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Middleware Specialist Our Mississauga based client is currently seeking a Middleware Specialist who will be responsible for detail designing, building, unit testing and level 2/3 software support of Middleware across all hardware and server platforms. The successful candidate will be required to demonstrate an expert level understanding of all elements to successfully manage, tune, and resolve issues in a complex Web based environment. Must have hands-on working knowledge and experience with: WebSphere Application Server WebSphere Portal Apache Web Server IBM Web Server (IHS) J2EE programming model database technologies (DB2, Oracle or MS SQL Server) z/OS and Mainframe technologies UNIX (Linux/Solaris/AIX) and/or Windows operating systems. Demonstrated experience building, deploying and administering WebSphere Application Server solutions. Demonstrated expert level knowledge of the following: IHS Web Server WebSphere Portal MQ SSL XML Unix Shell Scripting WSADMIN Scripting including JYTHON. Advanced problem determination skills to identify and resolve Application Server problems running on multiple platforms in a large complex environment (AIX, Linux, Windows). The following qualifications are considered as assets : 1. Technical knowledge of Web applications 2. Familiarity with Pega/Filenet Systems products, 3. Familiarity with the other Web and Application Servers and workflow infrastructure 4. Past experience coaching/developing other team members on technical aspects of   [view full job] &#xD;
 &#xD;
  &#xD;
Type Permanent &#xD;
Advertiser ProVision IT Resources Ltd (Employment Agency) &#xD;
Contact Human Resources Department &#xD;
Ref JS2889 &#xD;
Date 15/04/2009 04:44:17 &#xD;
Apply Now         Add To Basket</content>
    <postId>C799DBC2-E179-4E57-8406-E65DA633A979</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-04-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Middleware Specialist Mississauga, ON Open</title>
</post>
