<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Global leaders in specialist recruitment&#xD;
&#xD;
Hays places professional candidates in permanent, temporary and contract positions across all industries. Below is just one of the great roles we are helping our clients to fill:&#xD;
 &#xD;
Solution/Application Architect - Banking Sector&#xD;
$110k - Permanent&#xD;
Experienced with all aspects of architecture including application, data, security and infrastructure. Total IT experience of at least 15 years out of which 5 years doing solution architectures on large projects. Proven experience at leading architecture of a large program from initiation to implementation Strong leadership skills (not a follower), comfortable managing large cross functional technical teams and ability to define, influence and impact the technical direction. Ability to quickly evaluate options, make decisions and execute within an intense high-tech environment. Solid experiences with a variety of technologies/approaches including J2EE, .NET, mainframe platform, packaged applications, multi-platforms applications, human workflow, EAI, SOA. Experienced with program/projects involving complex integration of disparate types of technologies/platforms. Solid understanding of RUP, UML and UML tools. Knowledge of Enterprise Architecture frameworks: TOGAF, Zachman etc.&#xD;
Reference # [Enter reference number here - 50 character limit]&#xD;
&#xD;
If you are interested in this position, please call us:&#xD;
 &#xD;
Jeff Wedge, Business Manager&#xD;
Hays Information Technology&#xD;
Suite 701, 201 City Centre Drive, Mississauga, ON L5B 2T4&#xD;
T: 905-366-8602E: jwedge@hays.ca&#xD;
 &#xD;
All introductions will be subject to our Terms of Business.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Specialist Recruitment   hays.ca</content>
    <postId>C9BCD1CC-59D0-45EE-8BED-515726D58685</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Solution/Application Architect - Banking Sector</title>
</post>
