<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I am looking for a suitable consultant for below said job description that we have with our clients. Hope you would be interested. Please forward you updated detailed resume. If you are not available, I would really appreciate if you could please refer me your friend or a colleague.&#xD;
&#xD;
TITLE:  APPLICATION DEVELOPER&#xD;
TYPE:  CONTRACT&#xD;
DURATION:  6 months&#xD;
CITY:  TORONTO&#xD;
&#xD;
DESCRIPTION:  Description:&#xD;
       It's a development role to help with multiple prime brokerage and GEF projects. You will have to have experience with supporting a production system and have strong troubleshooting and analytical skills.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
EXPERIENCE:  Skills experience:&#xD;
       Oracle, Some Sybase, Strong Unix, Java, Web technologies, experience in Windows environment, and MUST have Financial Exp&#xD;
       Added skills:&#xD;
       Bonus: Experience with applications on Equity Finance and Prime Brokerage area&#xD;
       Bonus: Experience with a vendor (LineData) product called "Fund Manager".&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
NOTES:&#xD;
* Please ignore this email if you do not fit into this position. Your resume was picked up on the skills keywords search. As a result you have received this email. We regret inconvenience.&#xD;
* When you reply, please put the job title in the subject line.&#xD;
* If you do not have an up dated resume with us, please attach one to your reply.&#xD;
* If you know anyone else who may be interested have them send a resume to me.&#xD;
* Please monitor our web site for other job/contract openings at http://www.tdm.ca/&#xD;
&#xD;
Thank You&#xD;
&#xD;
Recruiter:  KETAN PATEL&#xD;
300-3 Church St.  Toronto  Ontario M5E 1M2  Canada&#xD;
TDM@TDMTECH.COM  WWW.TDMTECH.COM&#xD;
TEL: 416-777-0007  FAX: 416-777-1117</content>
    <postId>CA47BBC8-8D42-43C8-BF43-EABB057B56B1</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-07-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Oracle Developer - Contract - TDM</title>
</post>
