<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>80:20 Rule&#xD;
&#xD;
You must have heard about the 80 : 20 rule. It is a very common phrase that often gets used, such as 20 % of the people do 80 % of the work or a 20 % effort gets 80 % the core PGM work done. &#xD;
&#xD;
There could be &amp;#8211;are--other examples, but I would like to talk about this rule under different circumstances, the "Personal effort or work habits" from an article I read. The average person uses 80 % of their energies dealing with things that might happen such as what other people are going to think, what I should do or&amp;#8212;and-- shouldn't do and &amp;#8211;delete--etc. The average person only uses 20% of their total resources to do productive things.  Rather than worrying about things that might happen, let's concentrate on things that do happen. &#xD;
&#xD;
For example there are persons &amp;#8211;people--that worry about their job security. Rather than worrying about their job security the persons are more contributing &amp;#8211;they should be contributing more to their team or their company. Those individuals&amp;#8212;If they do this, they  will have better job security than others because they are more valuable. Even if they are let go by the company, they are better prepared for their next job or challenges--delete. &#xD;
&#xD;
In my own estimation all the &amp;#8211;delete--successful persons had&amp;#8212;people have-- the ability to convert negative energies to positive ones. Successful persons&amp;#8212;people-- are optimistic and enthusiastic. Let's be a doer rather than a worrier. Let's change the 80:20 rule to 70:30 even 60:40. When you are in the 60:40 bracket you are twice as productive than&amp;#8212;as the  average. &#xD;
&#xD;
PS : &#xD;
·	Let's do one thing you do not like to do, or that you forgot to do, every day.  Don't  try  to do many, just one  things in one day. Let's do one things you don't like to or things you forgot. &amp;#8211;delete&#xD;
	&#xD;
·	Create a “big things to do list” in your computer or on blank paper. List all the things you like to or don’t like to do. Delete them or cross them out if you've done&amp;#8212;as you do- them or &amp;#8211;and--add new things if you forgot or new.&amp;#8212;as well as items you have forgotten.   Keeping a record like this will You will see&amp;#8212;show you how much you are doing. Things could be work related or home related.&amp;#8212;You could have a list for work and home. By doing this, you will see big changes in your life and you could &amp;#8211;will--enjoy your life a lot more. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Sincerely Yours&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>CA57D1C6-26D1-4F9B-874B-90310A68CAB0</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-07-11T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Modified Version by my English Instructor</title>
</post>
