<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>GreetingsJoshua&#xD;
&#xD;
My name is Youssef and I'm an IT recruiter at IBM Canada. Our records show that you are an experienced IT professional  and your experience is relevant to one of my current openings.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is looking for a Java developer to create forms templates based on approved form layouts and data retrieval.&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:     Toronto&#xD;
&#xD;
Duration:     ASAP till end of 2010&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Project description:&#xD;
&#xD;
-A fully functional Forms Management module to handle the full life cycle of forms in the case file and that can be accessible and administered through the one of the client’s application.&#xD;
&#xD;
-The selected vendor must deliver a working solution. Responses that propose an alternative such as a ¨Dscope &amp; approach¡¬ or ¨Danalysis &amp; design&#xD;
&#xD;
-In addition to developing the Forms Mgmt component, the selected vendor will document conceptual, logical and physical designs by following the guidelines defined in the OPS Enterprise Architecture Framework, to be used as part of the overall CIMS documentation package for the relevant Ent. Architecture Checkpoints.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Required skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
-          Java / J2EE&#xD;
&#xD;
-          WAS&#xD;
&#xD;
-          XML&#xD;
&#xD;
-          Web Svcs coding&#xD;
&#xD;
-          Lotus Quickr API&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
If you are qualified, available, interested, planning to make a change, or know of a friend who might have the required qualifications and interest, please contact me ASAP at berrada@ca.ibm.comeven if we have spoken recently about a different position. If you do respond via e-mail please include a daytime phone number so I can reach you. In considering candidates, time is of the essence, so please respond ASAP. Thank you.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sincerely yours,&#xD;
Youssef Berrada&#xD;
berrada@ca.ibm.com</content>
    <postId>CB71EA45-C44B-4190-96F1-39B66A24455E</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-09-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java developer</title>
</post>
