<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Nityo Infotech Services Pte Ltd&#xD;
&#xD;
Nityo Infotech Corporation (www.nityo.com) is a global provider of IT services and end-to-end solutions designed to help clients improve their competitiveness and efficiency. Nityo Infotech has operations in 6 countries across globe in North America, UK, Singapore and India. Its portfolio of solutions and services includes outsourcing, system integration, Application Software development, IT consulting and Quality Assurance &amp; Training. Nityo provides services to several clients located across the world, including many Fortune 1000 and Global 2000 companies, in the commercial, industrial and government sectors - across key vertical markets, like financial services, life sciences and healthcare, telecommunications and utilities, and independent software vendors.&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Requirements:&#xD;
&#xD;
· IBM WebSphere Portal Server 5.1, 6.0 &amp; 6.1&#xD;
· IBM Workplace Web Content Management 5.1, 6.0 &amp; 6.1&#xD;
· IBM WebSphere Application Server 5.1, 6.0 &amp; 6.1&#xD;
· IBM Rational Application Developer 6.0, 7.0&#xD;
· Framework based Portal development&#xD;
· CA Siteminder&#xD;
· Experience in AIX operating system&#xD;
· Experience in WPS migration from 5.1 to 6.1&#xD;
· Building Portlets based on JSR 168 standards and JSR 286&#xD;
· Integration through Web Services and EJB&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
· WebSphere Portal / Web Content management design&#xD;
· Lead and mentor the team with the best practices in WebSphere Portal and Content management with hands on experience in all the facets of Portal project.&#xD;
· Hands on development experience using IBM API, IBM Workplace API, JSR 168 and Java development&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Warm regards,&#xD;
&#xD;
Julliete L. Parico&#xD;
Nityo Infotech Services Pte. Ltd&#xD;
260 Tanjong Pagar Road&#xD;
#08-02/03 Singapore&#xD;
(65) 63277238 Phone&#xD;
(65) 96778104 Mobile&#xD;
Email: yet@nityo.com&#xD;
www.nityo.com</content>
    <postId>CE19D6BD-DDAC-41A1-8C6C-09B149625D3A</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-08-06T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>IBM WebSphere Portal Server developer</title>
</post>
