<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Toronto, Ontario   &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Job Description: At BMO Financial Group, we believe in our people, and we provide them with a positive environment in which they can reach their full potential. As one of North America's highly diversified financial services providers, we are always looking for new and exciting ways to serve our clients. It is a dynamic work environment that makes good business sense. MANDATE Reporting to the Senior Manager of E-business, a Content Developer's responsibilities include Web development/analysis, coding, QA testing, and maintaining existing Websites and applications. Candidate will be involved in multiple projects with various degrees of priority, and will be expected to work in Tandem with other developers; requiring the ability to monitor his/her progress and ensure milestones are reached. The candidate is expected not only to be an expert in his/her existing technology skill sets, but also to be able to adapt to changing technology needs, learn new programming languages and work across various technology platforms. The successful candidate will be highly innovative, motivated, and customer oriented. KEY AREAS OF ACCOUNTABILITY: 1. Information architecture, development and execution of Websites. 2. Advanced coding for rich Internet applications. 3. Researching new techniques and innovate Web standards. ACCOUNTABILITY: 1. Information architecture, development and execution of Websites. Create client-side/Server Side scripts based on project requirements. Development of Web   [view full job] &#xD;
 &#xD;
  &#xD;
Type Permanent &#xD;
Advertiser Bank of Montreal (Employment Agency) &#xD;
Contact Bank Of Montreal &#xD;
Ref JS41542 &#xD;
Date 16/04/2009 05:54:40 &#xD;
Apply Now         Add To Basket</content>
    <postId>D128C218-41D7-48DB-AAA6-558B8EE31859</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-04-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Web Content Developer</title>
</post>
