<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권경화</author>
    <comments/>
    <content> Tuesday, December 09, 2008 (EST) - ASP.NET AJAX, Silverlight and the Future of Web De&#xD;
&#xD;
location: MISSISSAUGA CONVENTION CENTRE at 75 Derry Road Mississauga&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
ASP.NET AJAX, Silverlight and the Future of Web Development featuring Todd Anglin. Registration for this event will open in late November.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
ASP.NET AJAX, Silverlight, and the Future of Web Development&#xD;
&#xD;
Understanding the future is critical for web developers. Decisions you make today need to be aware of what's coming if you're going to be successful on web. In this session, we'll examine ASP.NET AJAX and Silverlight to gain a deep understanding of how these technologies can help us solve the problems of a rich, ajaxified Internet. From the rich client-side library in ASP.NETAJAX that changes the way you write JavaScript to the power of .NET in the browser with Silverlight, understanding how to leverage these technologies is key for future ASP.NET applications. We'll also examine the future of web browsers and seek to understand how they will affect the applications we build.&#xD;
&#xD;
Speaker Bio:&#xD;
&#xD;
Todd Anglin is an active .NET community member, President of the North Houston .NET User Group, an O’Reilly author, and Telerik's Chief Technical Evangelist. At Telerik, Todd is responsible for building Telerik's global community of developers and helping ensure Telerik's products serve the needs of .NET developers around the world. In the general .NET community, Todd is most involved with ASP.NET and Silverlight, contributing articles and speaking on these topics regularly. Before joining Telerik, Todd worked as a developer in a Fortune 200 financial services company. He is also an avid entrepreneur with previous experience running a small .NET SaaS company. </content>
    <postId>D1536671-111B-49FB-838A-998E8B619EC5</postId>
    <pubDate>2008-10-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Toronto .NET Users Group : ASP.NET AJAX, Silverlight and the Future </title>
</post>
