<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이석준</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2011-04-18T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>It will be better if a contact or direction is posted together.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Position Purpose: &#xD;
The Strategic Data Services team is in the process of building various “Golden Copy” data services for trade, position, client, issuer, counterparty, security, book and people reference data. In addition, the team has various data centric projects either in development or planned, that will leverage this consolidated data infrastructure. &#xD;
We currently have an opportunity for a Technical Systems Analyst to assist in the creation and enhancement of the SDS services and projects. The candidate will be an experienced TSA with a minimum of 5 years progressive responsibility in the role. Capital markets experience is highly desirable. Experience with RBC Capital Markets, or another RBC division, would be an advantage.&#xD;
TECBAC or Trade Execution, Clearing, Brokerage and Analytics Costs, is one of these critical and high profile IT system which will be the primary project for this role. This project will involve the procurement or development of an IT solution to capture, reconcile and post to the sub-ledger many third party invoices related to business execution in Capital Markets.&#xD;
Working as part of the Strategic Data Services team, this role involves managing the technical analysis aspects of architecture, design, development, and implementation planning of the project to build an enterprise quality IT solution for 3rd party invoice capture, reconciliation and approval.  Upon the release of the application, this role will also be required to provide day-to-day support of the application.  The position will involve working with business, vendor and IT staff seamlessly and managing deliverables.  This position will report directly to an Associate Director. &#xD;
&#xD;
Key Accountabilities: &#xD;
Application Development and 2nd / 3rd Level Application Support&#xD;
Primary Responsibilities&#xD;
 Provide accurate estimates for assigned work to managers&#xD;
 Code &amp; test programs of moderate to high complexity according to RBC standards&#xD;
 Ensure adherence to the solutions architecture&#xD;
 Continually identify and escalate risks&#xD;
 Provide timely and accurate information to project managers and managers&#xD;
 Prepare unit and system test documentation and data&#xD;
 Provide technical support during implementation of application components, as assigned&#xD;
 Clearly document components as per project standards&#xD;
 Create specifications and technical documentation&#xD;
 Develop and maintain strong working relationships with team members and analysts in associated areas&#xD;
Secondary Responsibilities&#xD;
 Perform the technical analysis and design technical specifications from business requirements for application components / programs / enhancements of simple to moderate complexity&#xD;
 Provide input to technical design reviews to ensure that business requirements are met&#xD;
 Provide input to code and test plan reviews &amp; walkthroughs&#xD;
 Perform testing thoroughly &amp; accurately including interfaces to other systems and assist in the preparation of user acceptance testing &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Requirements: (Knowledge/ Experience): &#xD;
Systems Knowledge (some required at expert level):&#xD;
Our minimum requirements to ensure your success in this role are:&#xD;
 SDLC (from analysis of requirements, design, coding, unit testing, integration testing, user acceptance testing to deployment), Agile Development Methodology&#xD;
 Must have strong skills and experience in:  Java, J2EE, Spring, XML, XML Parsing(SAX/DOM), XSLT, SQL and Database stored procedures, Eclipse, ANT, UNIX scripting, and UNIX Tools.&#xD;
 Strong experience in Perl, Python, WebLogic 8.1 &amp; 10.3, and JMS Messaging is also beneficial.&#xD;
 Strong understanding of design patterns, IoC and other best practices of software development/testing&#xD;
 Knowledge of service oriented architecture, enterprise service bus and EAI patterns&#xD;
 Experience in performance monitoring, benchmarking and tuning&#xD;
 Relational databases (esp. SQLServer)&#xD;
 Version Control and Workflow Management Software (e.g. MKS, Subversion/JIRA/Confluence, CVS, VSS)&#xD;
Development &amp; Coaching&#xD;
 Continually enhances skills and builds knowledge in all aspects of the organization, the business and information systems&#xD;
 Ideal candidate would be a quick learner and highly adaptable to new project environment&#xD;
&#xD;
Knowledge / Experience &#xD;
 Professional with experience on applications with multiple functions&#xD;
 Excellent communication skills both written and verbal&#xD;
 Able to critically evaluate and manage information gathered from multiple sources&#xD;
 Analytical thinking – able to solve problems in complex environments&#xD;
 Able to interact effectively with sophisticated business clients&#xD;
 Self-motivated, able to work independently or in teams&#xD;
 Focused on delivering results&#xD;
 Able to manage multiple priorities&#xD;
 Professional experience in a capital market environment an asset&#xD;
 Proven competence in delivering and supporting large and highly complex projects&#xD;
 Previous working experience in large corporations and familiar with processes and documentations requirements from large corporations such as architecture document and system design&#xD;
&#xD;
Process Knowledge&#xD;
 Communication Skills&#xD;
 Facilitation Skills&#xD;
 Conflicts and issues resolution and escalation&#xD;
 Worked in Project Framework like setting&#xD;
 Version, Release and Change Management&#xD;
&#xD;
Business Knowledge&#xD;
 Ideal candidate would possess some business knowledge in Capital Markets arena, specifically Client and Securities reference data. &#xD;
&#xD;
Required Skills/ Competencies/ Attributes: &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Education: &#xD;
BA/BSc&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Required Accreditation(s): &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Special Conditions: &#xD;
N/A &#xD;
&#xD;
Diversity: &#xD;
Diversity in the workplace, one of our shared values, lies at the heart of our rewarding, open, supportive and inclusive work environment. We respect and respond to the many competing and evolving priorities in our lives so you can focus on what you can do best – put clients first.</content>
    <postId>D17194E0-272B-49A5-B7CA-427E2FEEDDD8</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-04-15T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Yeung - Technical Systems Analyst (Java- Capital Markets)</title>
</post>
