<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Joshua,&#xD;
&#xD;
My name is Arjun Asoka, an IT recruiter with TEKsystems in Toronto. I hope things are going well on your end. I wanted to reach out to you for some assistance on an opportunity I am currently recruiting on. I have attached the details of the position for your review. I believe that good IT people know other good IT people, so if you do know someone who would be interested or even someone I could network with, I would greatly appreciate it. Thanks for your time&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client in the insurance industry is currently in need of a J2EE Designer for a 6 month contract to work on a major Business Intelligence initiative.  This initiative is to develop data services that will interface with the Operational Data Store.&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
-Take a lead role in the design of complex applications&#xD;
&#xD;
-Develops solutions consistent with the target architecture and standards, that are of high quality, cost effective and that produce the desired results&#xD;
&#xD;
- Understands the options for implementing service oriented architecture and operational data environment&#xD;
- Provides input to decisions on realization of services&#xD;
&#xD;
- Performs all levels of testing, including unit, integration, regression, system, and user acceptance testing to ensure that applications will perform error free and according to business specifications&#xD;
&#xD;
-Provides guidance and support for the resolution of complex production problems&#xD;
&#xD;
-Identifies opportunities to ensure high quality in all deliverables and continuous improvement in application development&#xD;
&#xD;
Requirements:&#xD;
&#xD;
-Seven years of progressive experience in information services&#xD;
&#xD;
-At least 5 years of experience in J2EE programming&#xD;
&#xD;
-At least 5 years of SOA experience&#xD;
&#xD;
-Previous experience in Project Development using a system development lifecycle methodology&#xD;
&#xD;
-Strong technical skills and ability in a Java/J2EE environment&#xD;
&#xD;
-Excellent analytical, problem solving and decision making skills&#xD;
&#xD;
-Ability to organize and plan tasks effectively&#xD;
&#xD;
-Fluent in application development within the J2EE environment (i.e. JMS, EJB, RAD, Hibernate, Spring, web services, JSP, etc.), with DataStage or mainframe knowledge an asset&#xD;
&#xD;
-In depth knowledge of an Information Services environment (e.g., Websphere, Java, Oracle)&#xD;
&#xD;
-Previous experience from P&amp;C Insurance Industry background in required&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client in the insurance industry is currently in need of a J2EE Designer for a 6 month contract to work on a major Business Intelligence initiative.  This initiative is to develop data services that will interface with the Operational Data Store.&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities:&#xD;
&#xD;
-Take a lead role in the design of complex applications&#xD;
&#xD;
-Develops solutions consistent with the target architecture and standards, that are of high quality, cost effective and that produce the desired results&#xD;
&#xD;
- Understands the options for implementing service oriented architecture and operational data environment&#xD;
- Provides input to decisions on realization of services&#xD;
&#xD;
- Performs all levels of testing, including unit, integration, regression, system, and user acceptance testing to ensure that applications will perform error free and according to business specifications&#xD;
&#xD;
-Provides guidance and support for the resolution of complex production problems&#xD;
&#xD;
-Identifies opportunities to ensure high quality in all deliverables and continuous improvement in application development&#xD;
&#xD;
Requirements:&#xD;
&#xD;
-Seven years of progressive experience in information services&#xD;
&#xD;
-At least 5 years of experience in J2EE programming&#xD;
&#xD;
-At least 5 years of SOA experience&#xD;
&#xD;
-Previous experience in Project Development using a system development lifecycle methodology&#xD;
&#xD;
-Strong technical skills and ability in a Java/J2EE environment&#xD;
&#xD;
-Excellent analytical, problem solving and decision making skills&#xD;
&#xD;
-Ability to organize and plan tasks effectively&#xD;
&#xD;
-Fluent in application development within the J2EE environment (i.e. JMS, EJB, RAD, Hibernate, Spring, web services, JSP, etc.), with DataStage or mainframe knowledge an asset&#xD;
&#xD;
-In depth knowledge of an Information Services environment (e.g., Websphere, Java, Oracle)&#xD;
&#xD;
-Previous experience from P&amp;C Insurance Industry background in required&#xD;
&#xD;
Arjun Asokakumar  TECHNICAL RECRUITER&#xD;
150 YORK STREET, SUITE 1206&#xD;
&#xD;
TORONTO, ONTARIO  M5H 3S5&#xD;
877.342.5004      T 416.342.5004&#xD;
F 416.342.5070</content>
    <postId>D447B7DF-1D63-489B-9EC7-4EC3592A5D2A</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-09-08T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>J2ee designer (SOA and Insurance experience) - CONTRACT</title>
</post>
