<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>신민용</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Sourcing Office : Toronto&#xD;
Title : Senior Systems Developer&#xD;
Project Description : Our Client is in the business of providing over 1.3 million Canadians with group and individual health and dental benefits. As one of the best in health care and social service benefits administration and related technology solutions they set the standard for flexible, cost-efficient, quality services that exceed their clients' expectations.&#xD;
&#xD;
Key Job Responsibilities: &#xD;
&#xD;
The Systems Developer is an advanced level position and generally intended for a highly skilled developer with several years’ experience who is capable of working with minimal supervision and direction. Requiring advanced analytical and application development skills, the Systems Developer may also be responsible for system design activities. &#xD;
&#xD;
The Systems Developer is highly skilled in current design concepts and the use of a number of online and batch programming languages and tools. This position may have technical control responsibility over other Program Developers and Systems Developers on a small team (typically 1-5 developers) and be responsible for system design, development and integration testing activities for that team, working under the direction of a Project Manager. &#xD;
&#xD;
Application design and development initiatives assigned to the Systems Developer will range in size and complexity and he/she may act as the interface to the internal client in the business department in resolving project or day to day application problems and questions. He/she would be expected to participate in design and code reviews of their own work and other developers’ work.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Systems Developer will perform unit testing, support system testing and plan and conduct integration testing.  Automated testing techniques will be applied, where appropriate. &#xD;
&#xD;
The Systems Developer assures that the software programs and associated tasks to which he/she is assigned are designed, developed, tested and completed according to department standards and defined client requirements. &#xD;
&#xD;
The Systems Developer must be effective in working in a collaborative team environment and possess excellent communication and interpersonal skills in order to facilitate design and development reviews and to support all aspects of the system development life cycle. &#xD;
&#xD;
Qualifications: &#xD;
•    University Degree or a Community College Certificate in Computer Science or equivalent experience &#xD;
•    At least 5-6 years of complex business application design and programming experience &#xD;
•    Requires a unique blend of design, development, technical and time management skills along with strong interpersonal and communication skills, a demonstrated ability to lead and a demonstrated proficiency for problem solving &#xD;
•    Has interpersonal skills to deal effectively with internal client personnel at various levels of the organization and with other I.T. staff in team situations &#xD;
•    Must possess exceptional problem solving skills and a systematic approach to decision making, taking into consideration the impact of each decision &#xD;
•    Must have demonstrated leadership skills to lead junior Program Developers and/or Systems Developers in all areas of the system development life cycle. &#xD;
•    Must be able to build consensus for all decisions and be receptive to feedback and constructive criticism from the internal client, peers and other I.T. staff/management &#xD;
•    Must act as an on-going resource to other Developers and/or Engineers and be able to assist internal clients in resolving day-to-day application problems and questions &#xD;
•    Must be able to present technical options and alternatives &#xD;
•    Must be able to perform full unit testing on all components of a system to which he/she has been assigned &#xD;
•    Must be able to plan and perform integration testing on a collection of system components &#xD;
•    Must be fully versed and competent in the use of automated testing tools and utilities &#xD;
•    Must be able to produce documentation for all designs and programs created or changed and able to write or assist in writing user and operational documentation &#xD;
•    Provides resource estimates for various components of the software development process in support of project planning and scheduling tasks &#xD;
•    Designs and develops modules of logic, including data base access methods, for online and batch applications in a number of current and legacy programming environments including .NET, C++, C#, Visual Basic, SQL, Java and other languages as required&#xD;
&#xD;
Specialization and Skills :&#xD;
    -  Software Development&#xD;
          - C# .NET  (5 - 7 years)&#xD;
          - C++  (2 - 4 years)&#xD;
          - Java  (2 - 4 years)&#xD;
          - SQL  (2 - 4 years)&#xD;
          - Visual Basic  (2 - 4 years)&#xD;
&#xD;
Additional Requirements :&#xD;
    - •    University Degree or a Community College Certificate in Computer Science or equivalent experience (Mandatory) &#xD;
    - •    Designs and develops modules of logic, including data base access methods, for online and batch applications in a number of current and legacy programming environments including .NET, C++, C#, Visual Basic, SQL, Java and other languages as required (Proficient) &#xD;
&#xD;
Start Date : May 02, 2011&#xD;
&#xD;
Rate : Negotiable&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Thank you for your time and consideration Andrew!&#xD;
&#xD;
Best Regards,&#xD;
Sam Sarvari,&#xD;
S.i. Systems - Toronto</content>
    <postId>D44EC8C0-AC62-42B0-8ED5-29966EFDDC35</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior Systems Developer(C#,Java)</title>
</post>
