<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>고상호</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>고상호</author>
            <date>2004-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>client who is currently&#xD;
looking for strong individuals in the java world and they should have team&#xD;
lead experience.&#xD;
</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Are you interested in this position?&#xD;
The agent looks at person who has over 5 years Canadian experience.&#xD;
You can mention my name if you want to apply for the position.&#xD;
&#xD;
===========================================================&#xD;
www.comnetix.com                                                Location:&#xD;
Mississauga/Oakville&#xD;
&#xD;
ComnetiX' principal business is the provision of advanced biometric,&#xD;
hardware-independent, FBI standards-based verification and identification&#xD;
software solutions. Since its inception in 1980, the company has become a&#xD;
leader in the development of state of the art networked criminal&#xD;
intelligence systems. ComnetiX' mission is to provide positive&#xD;
identification solutions and by doing so we hope to empower private,&#xD;
corporate, and government departments by providing them with industry&#xD;
proven multi-mode biometric identification solutions.&#xD;
&#xD;
This position will be part of the Engineering Department and will report to&#xD;
the Director of Development.  This person will help build and maintain any&#xD;
current and new products that are required by the company.  Needing a&#xD;
candidate to have good experience and would like a senior person who can&#xD;
lead projects.&#xD;
&#xD;
To qualify, candidates must have the following technical requirements:&#xD;
minimum of 5yrs technical experience with Java/J2EE, HTML, XML/XSL,&#xD;
JavaScript, Struts framework; design patterns, UML; Oracle.  Candidate must&#xD;
have a university diploma, minimum 5yrs experience with object oriented&#xD;
methodologies, and a minimum 5yrs experience working with Project&#xD;
management methodology.  Candidate must be familiar with application&#xD;
maintenance methodologies, techniques and tools and must have the ability&#xD;
to work in a high paced environment.  Candidate must also have strong&#xD;
leadership ability.  Candidates must be able to lead small development&#xD;
teams and have experience leading projects of similar scope.&#xD;
&#xD;
SKILLS:  Java, J2EE (JSP, Servlet, EJB, etc), Struts, XML/XSL, HTML,&#xD;
Javascript, Oracle &amp; SQL, UML, VC++, WebServices, JBoss/Websphere/WebLogic,&#xD;
Performance Tuning &amp; Clustering, .Net&#xD;
&#xD;
Angeline&#xD;
__________________________________________________________________&#xD;
Angeline Yuen-Pitre&#xD;
Senior Staffing Consultant, Information Technology&#xD;
(416) 483-7424 ext. 257&#xD;
FAX: (416) 483-7676&#xD;
&#xD;
__________________________________________________________________&#xD;
DATALIST    55 Eglinton Avenue East, Suite 605, Toronto, Ontario M4P 2H9&#xD;
INTERSECTION: Yonge &amp; Eglinton &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>D9135546-2BC9-4F91-B795-FB8C4163AD45</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>minimum of 5yrs technical experience with Java/J2EE, HTML, XML/XSL etc.</title>
</post>
