<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>백재진</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>How to Deal with SARS&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
  My friends,&#xD;
&#xD;
  The fact of the mysterious pneumonia has been widely  spread in HK&#xD;
drives me to do a literature review on&#xD;
  the suspected cause (i.e. coronavirus) of the SARS  (Severe Acute&#xD;
Respiratory Syndrome). As a biomedical&#xD;
  researcher, let me show you my concern and make the following&#xD;
suggestions.&#xD;
&#xD;
  The basic mechanism of viral attack is that the viruses replicate&#xD;
themselves using the host's (in this case is "our") DNA genetic&#xD;
  replication system. By doing this, our body couldn't function well due&#xD;
to the massive viral replication. Supposing, the immune&#xD;
  cells in our body will fight off the infected viruses quickly.&#xD;
However, the viruses are so smart that they could be able to&#xD;
  produce some chemical substances to cause our immune cells to die.&#xD;
Besides, this coronavirus is a new kind of virus which&#xD;
  belongs to a mutated strain and our body cannot recognize it.&#xD;
&#xD;
  No antibiotics have been proved to be 100%  effective in treating&#xD;
viral infection so far. The only effective way to get rid of it&#xD;
  is by ourselves. It likes a prolonged battle between the viruses and&#xD;
our immune response. In fact, viruses couldn't kill all the&#xD;
  immune cells in a health individual. The stronger the immune function&#xD;
you have, the less the viral injury you get. Therefore, the&#xD;
  degree of sickness after infection and the rate of recovery mainly&#xD;
depends on how strong your immune function is.&#xD;
&#xD;
  You cannot avoid the infection unless you avoid from those infected&#xD;
individuals/area. But, you can try your&#xD;
  best to boost up your immune function by several regimes. Make sure&#xD;
you are "extremely healthy" at least during this critical&#xD;
  period. Stronger immune function could keep the viral damage minimal&#xD;
even you were so unluckily being infected.&#xD;
&#xD;
  Also, stronger immune function delays the onset of any detrimental&#xD;
effects from the viral infection. Scientists are now working&#xD;
  on tracking the treatment  and so make sure you are still surviving&#xD;
until an effective treatment occurs. The following&#xD;
  suggestions aim to strengthen your immune function within a short&#xD;
period of time.&#xD;
&#xD;
  1) Antioxidant nutraceuticals: Antioxidants are chemicals found in&#xD;
foods which exert a great value in strengthening our immune&#xD;
  system. Boost up your immune function by taking a cocktail of&#xD;
antioxidant supplements.&#xD;
&#xD;
  - Vitamin E 1000 IU per day. Alpha-tocopherol is the biological active&#xD;
form of vitamin E. There are two forms of it:&#xD;
  d-tocopherol and dl-tocopherol. d- is the natural form and dl- is the&#xD;
synthetic form. Try to get&#xD;
  the d- form because it is absorbed faster in our body.&#xD;
&#xD;
  - Vitamin C (ascorbic acid) 1000 milligram (mg) daily.&#xD;
  Instead of taking supplement, you can take 2 pieces of  citrus fruits&#xD;
(e.g. orange) a day to get the vitamin C.&#xD;
  - Beta-carotene, not more than 10000 IU daily&#xD;
  - Selenium, 200 microgram daily&#xD;
  - Zinc, not more than 500 milligram (mg) daily&#xD;
  - Lipoic acid, 50 mg daily&#xD;
  - Glutathione, 50 mg daily&#xD;
&#xD;
  No adverse effects have been reported from the above suggested&#xD;
supplementation dose.&#xD;
&#xD;
  2)   Let green tea to be your daily beverage because it  contains&#xD;
tremendous amount of antioxidant flavonoid,  catechins.&#xD;
  - Eat more tomatoes, broccoli or fruits and vegetables  in red and&#xD;
dark green color. They carry a huge amount  of antioxidant&#xD;
  carotenoids, lycopene and carotene.&#xD;
&#xD;
  3) No intense physical activities during this critical period! It has&#xD;
been shown that intense exercise will  suppress your immune&#xD;
  function (related to the upper respiratory infection) even several&#xD;
days following&#xD;
  your workout.&#xD;
  Instead of intense exercise, light-to-moderate workout  helps if you&#xD;
have been training regularly.&#xD;
&#xD;
  4) Make sure you get enough carbohydrate foods (e.g.  rice, food&#xD;
concentrated in starch... etc) because  carbohydrate is the&#xD;
  primary food for immune cells . Do  some Gatorade or Pocari if needed&#xD;
since they are&#xD;
  both good sources of carbohydrate.&#xD;
&#xD;
  5) Make sure you get enough sleep and don't make  yourself so&#xD;
stressful! Anxiety, depression, and tried  will influence your&#xD;
  body's stress hormones&#xD;
  (e.g.  catecholamine and glucocorticoids) and so suppress your immune&#xD;
status.&#xD;
&#xD;
  6) Mouth-mask helps despite it is not 100% effective.  But it can&#xD;
still decrease the chance from infection.&#xD;
&#xD;
  All the above information are supported by  peer-reviewed biomedical&#xD;
literatures, that means they are credible and reliable!&#xD;
  God bless and I really hope that none of you will get infected and I&#xD;
will pray for all of you in every moment!&#xD;
&#xD;
  Good luck and take extremely care.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
  Parco M. Siu, MPhil, PhD Candidate&#xD;
  West VirginiaUniversitySchool of Medicine</content>
    <postId>DA3E35CB-973D-4AB6-A404-C9AF92E04923</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-04-02T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>How to Deal with SARS</title>
</post>
