<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2003-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>XDoclet은 우리가 EJB 또는 Struts와 같이 패턴과 지켜야할 문법, 규율이 복잡한 프로그램에 적합하다는 생각이 들었습니다. 그외의 다른 종류의 프로그램에는 어떻게 도움이 될지 바로 판단이 되지 않는군요. 다양한 도구와 룰들이 나오는데, 그것이 적용되기 좋은 환경에 대한 정보도 많았으면 좋겠습니다. 이번에 제가 소개하는 디자인은 EJB도 아니고 Struts도 사용하지 않은 것입니다. </content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Date : May 23rd, 2003&#xD;
&#xD;
    I talked to three persons yesterday about Weblogic new product seminar held on May 21st. I heard it was the product announcement and meeting to initiate Toronto Weblogic user group. I had the three different feedbacks. One said, “It was like combination of Min Kim’s EIA and James’s Xdoclet.” Second person said, “It is not going to work because it had tried before and it will not be accepted by the developers.” Last one said, “It is going to right direction but still lots of room for improvement.” I supposed they are all right in their own experience because we can only conclude our own ideas from our own experiences.&#xD;
&#xD;
   If you allow me, let me bore you with the stuffs you have already known for long time.&#xD;
History of Computer Programming&#xD;
- Spaghetti Code : because of GOTO and shortest code was the best&#xD;
- Structure Code : realized maintenance is required for any codes&#xD;
- Procedure/Modular : little bit of reusable idea plus group work required modularization&#xD;
- OO design : more reusable and expandable code due to increase complication of business and technologies&#xD;
- Java Code : platform and device independent idea emerged finally&#xD;
- Future of Java : if monkeys can write, it will be perfect&#xD;
&#xD;
    Now we encounter two mainstream of programming paradigms. One is Java based open concept and other is MS driven .NET world. Which is better or will survive, nobody knows. But we can come up with educated guess. It is my guess.&#xD;
&#xD;
Let’s me give you the my guess in different angle &amp;#8211; Political angle. &#xD;
- MS is in dictatorship by Bill Gates. As long as Bill is there in his domain MS will do great. But if post Bill is not as good as Bill, there will be the problems. Let assume I only consider the future in 5 years. I think MS has done marvelous job so far and they have no place to go in S/W. That is the reason why they are going into H/W market. In short few years MS windows will be almost powerful as Unix if not it will be close. When it happens, all the nice tools MS has will explode in front of our faces. Even monkeys will come up with the products we haven’t seen it before if monkeys have the business knowledge.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Java is in democratic political situation. It will take long time to come up with consensus products due to political climate. There are two groups in Java world, open concept worshipers and vendors. They have 5 years to complete their mission. Mission is business centric solutions instead of technology centric solutions. MS has been successful  because they knew what customers want/need. Java did not help the business sectors because of the complications. If every single Java developers have the mission to write OO concept and design, we should have the better results. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
But world is not perfect. We need both dictatorship and democratic leader in the same time. It is the irony and paradox of our lives. It is the time to vendors to come with the products like Xdoclet. Otherwise doomsday will come into Java World. At least it is what I think. &#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>DDF7FD66-376D-4E72-9625-96430F94E2AD</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>XDoctlet is the right path</title>
</post>
