<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>황대현</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Oracle Database Administrator (Production Support) (Brampton)&#xD;
&#xD;
Date: 2009-11-03, 4:29PM EST&#xD;
Reply to: sgodwin@tundratechnical.ca [Errors when replying to ads?]&#xD;
&#xD;
Position Title - Database Administrator (Production Support) &#xD;
&#xD;
Location - Brampton &#xD;
&#xD;
Description &#xD;
Our client is currently seeking; &#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities: &#xD;
&#xD;
• Installation and configuration of Oracle server software on Red Hat Linux Server and SQL server &#xD;
• Create Manual database with proper Physical, Logical and Memory Structure &#xD;
• Production Infrastructure DBA Support - Responsible for administration of instances sizes up to 300Gb+ and 500Gb+. &#xD;
• Design and creation of database backup solutions taking into account disk space consumption, data transfer latencies, scheduling, I/O performance. &#xD;
• Creation of database maintenance plans, rebuild/defrag indexes, integrity checks &#xD;
• Restoring databases as requested. Recover/restore as necessary trouble shoot databases with data consistency. &#xD;
• Monitoring disk space utilizations, sizing, and capacity planning. &#xD;
• Adjusting database sizes and restricting maximum size appropriately. &#xD;
• Running of performance monitor, querying server to identify performance problems on servers experiencing bottlenecks. &#xD;
• Collaboration with development, production teams to implement certain projects. &#xD;
• Creation of change management documents/tickets during production change. &#xD;
• Documentation of oracle server standard operations, procedures. &#xD;
• Oracle DBA infrastructure support Production and development servers in all over Canada, clustered/non clustered environment DBMS Maintenance, backup and recovery Implement, configure, administer replication and log shipping Installation/upgrade, patch application, db migration. &#xD;
• Implement SQL Server/Oracle related change requests Provide documentations for all implementations, setup and configuration Constant collaboration with offshore DBAs, operations and for project owners as needed. DBMS Maintenance Apply maintenance releases and upgrades to the DBMS Provide diagnosis to DBMS vendor to resolve problems. &#xD;
• Apply emergency maintenance fixes to the DBMS Database Backup &amp; Recovery Execute the database backup Procedures as required per the backup &amp; recovery policy Ensure current logs are available for database recovery of the production databases, in the event of system or failure . &#xD;
• Point-in-time Recovery of the production databases, in the event of application failure. &#xD;
• Database Security Ensure all production databases are access restricted Provide production next level support to Security team Production Database Support Ensure production databases are available as defined in the Service Level Agreement Monitor database production utility jobs for errors, correct problems and upgrade as required &#xD;
• Manage data storage, including datafile placement, compression and migration Apply application release upgrades Apply major, minor application changes to production database Monitor, test and control the completeness, accuracy and validity of data. &#xD;
• Ensuring that all databases are backed up on a regular basis by monitoring full, archive and cold backups for OLTP, warehouse, and business object repositories. Fix backup failures, address and implement resolutions. &#xD;
• Implement Autosys for scheduling backup and replication jobs using Company's standards. &#xD;
&#xD;
Environment: &#xD;
&#xD;
Operating System: Red Hat Linux, AIX, Windows 2000/2003, SQL,and SQL Clustering &#xD;
RDBMS : Oracle 8i,9i,10g &#xD;
Software : SQL*Plus ,Oracle Enterprise Manager, DBArtisan 8.5.3 &#xD;
Other Information: &#xD;
Interested Candidates please send a copy of your resume to: sgodwin@tundratechnical.ca &#xD;
&#xD;
Tundra Technical Solutions would like to thank you for the interest you have demonstrated in this opportunity. However, only candidates with the required skills will be contacted. &#xD;
&#xD;
Tundra Technical Solutions is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer. We welcome and encourage diversity in our workplace.&#xD;
&#xD;
Not interested in this position, but know somebody who might be? Check out our Referral Reward Program, referrals are a big secret behind our success. As always, we’re on the lookout for great people. And we know that you know great people. Simply click on ‘Tell a Friend’ option to refer a friend. &#xD;
Tundra Technical Solutions is among North America’s leading providers of Information Technology and Engineering staffing and consulting services. Our success and our clients’ success are built on a foundation of service excellence. Rather than continually trying to sell to new clients and companies and simply filling databases with candidates, we focus on developing stronger relationships and deeper knowledge of our existing clients’ challenges and opportunities. &#xD;
OPEN EARS. OPEN MINDS. OPEN FUTURES &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Location: Brampton&#xD;
Compensation: market rate&#xD;
Principals only. Recruiters, please don't contact this job poster.&#xD;
Please, no phone calls about this job!&#xD;
Please do not contact job poster about other services, products or commercial interests.&#xD;
PostingID: 1450082891&#xD;
&#xD;
Copyright © 2009 craigslist, inc. terms of use privacy policy feedback forum&#xD;
&lt;br&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&#xD;
Oracle DBA (Toronto )&#xD;
&#xD;
Date: 2009-10-24, 12:22PM EDT&#xD;
Reply to: job-tm798-1435730104@craigslist.org [Errors when replying to ads?]&#xD;
&#xD;
Our client is looking for a Oracle DBA. This is a 6 month contract role that will convert into a Perm role. &#xD;
&#xD;
RESPONSIBILITIES: &#xD;
&#xD;
-Implementation of several critical applications &#xD;
&#xD;
-Design and Architect &#xD;
&#xD;
-Performance tooling &#xD;
&#xD;
-Scripting &#xD;
&#xD;
-Provide recommendations as required ie. ways to configure database &#xD;
&#xD;
-Speak with vendors and other users/management team. &#xD;
&#xD;
SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: &#xD;
&#xD;
-Experience in a Windows environment &#xD;
&#xD;
-Experience with Oracle &#xD;
&#xD;
-Experience with SQL &#xD;
&#xD;
- Entertainment Industry experience is an asset. &#xD;
&#xD;
-May be some 24X7 support depending on how many applications to support. Will provide a blackberry if required &#xD;
&#xD;
-Excellent organizational, project and time management skills. &#xD;
&#xD;
-Excellent interpersonal skills with the ability to communicate effectively at all levels. &#xD;
&#xD;
-Good communication skills - both verbal and written. &#xD;
&#xD;
Please send resume in word format. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Location: Toronto&#xD;
Compensation: doe&#xD;
Principals only. Recruiters, please don't contact this job poster.&#xD;
Please, no phone calls about this job!&#xD;
Please do not contact job poster about other services, products or commercial interests.&#xD;
PostingID: 1435730104&#xD;
&#xD;
Copyright © 2009 craigslist, inc. terms of use privacy policy feedback forum&#xD;
&lt;br&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
DBAs – One (1) Oracle DBA and One (1) MS SQL DBA (North York, Toronto)&#xD;
&#xD;
Date: 2009-10-23, 4:51PM EDT&#xD;
Reply to: job-bh2ph-1434781020@craigslist.org [Errors when replying to ads?]&#xD;
&#xD;
Title: DBAs – One (1) Oracle DBA and One (1) MS SQL DBA &#xD;
Type: Permanent full time &#xD;
Location: North York &#xD;
Salary: 75-80K base plus benefits &#xD;
Number of positions: Two (2) – One (1) Oracle DBA and One (1) MS SQL DBA &#xD;
&#xD;
Responsibilities &#xD;
&#xD;
• Install New relational database servers and instances &#xD;
• Troubleshoots full spectrum of database issues; solves root issue after treating symptom &#xD;
• Interfaces independently with third party support groups &#xD;
• Performs data migrations &#xD;
• Executes, schedules and monitors database maintenance &#xD;
• Analyzes business problems and recommends best possible solution with respect to database resources &#xD;
• Makes recommendations for new technology adoption &#xD;
&#xD;
Must Have &#xD;
&#xD;
• Computer Science degree or equivalent working experience &#xD;
• At least 5 years experience DBA experience in either Oracle or MS SQL &#xD;
Please note that there are two roles: One Oracle DBA and One MS SQL DBA &#xD;
• Candidates with experience in financial/ investment industry will be given preference. &#xD;
&#xD;
Personality &#xD;
&#xD;
• Excellent organizational, analytical and problem solving skills &#xD;
• Excellent communication skills &#xD;
• Independent, Motivated and having strong initiative to take the lead in business and technology projects &#xD;
• Customer service orientation. &#xD;
&#xD;
(Note: The role will require overtime/after hours and weekend work) &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Location: North York, Toronto&#xD;
Compensation: Salary: 75-80K base plus benefits&#xD;
Principals only. Recruiters, please don't contact this job poster.&#xD;
Please, no phone calls about this job!&#xD;
Please do not contact job poster about other services, products or commercial interests.&#xD;
PostingID: 1434781020</content>
    <postId>DE968502-9651-4B47-A873-9059203133A4</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-11-06T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>취업관련 사이트를 보다가 oracle 관련 사항이 나와서 적습니다.(3개의 포스팅을 한번에 올립니다)</title>
</post>
