<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi ,&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
If this role is not for you, I was hoping to network with you to see if there is anyone you might know. Please see the details below on the role that I am currently pursuing for my client:  If you are interested in this opportunity, please attach an updated resume.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Senior SAP BI/BW Consultant – Toronto – Contract – (skills) -  Senior SAP Business Intelligence (business warehousing) expert.  Experience with SAP version 7 and above.  Must be able to look at the massive amount of critical consumer data, business reports, and data reports and come up with ideas to make it more efficient.  Experience working with business units along with IT units to achieve this and properly capture data reports. Must be highly analytical with a financial background.&#xD;
&#xD;
Java Consultant – Toronto – Contract – (skills) - Java (J2SE): at least five year’s experience.&#xD;
Oracle - Must have used Oracle DB in the context of a java project.  Spring framework, JSP, Javascript, struts, ect… Cassandra - familiarity with the Apache Cassandra NoSQL database is highly desirable or must be willing to do some study on own time.&#xD;
&#xD;
Intermediate Consultant - Business and Systems Analyst – Toronto – Contract – (skills) – Must have ADP experience. Strong knowledge in RUP development and Object Oriented methodology. Demonstrated experience in business process re-engineering. Expertise in all stages of systems development life cycle. Expert level experience with business methodologies and tools. Extensive experience with data modeling. Good knowledge of data, application and technology architectures. Knowledge of the ADP business and operations as well as the existing ADP system.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
Ed Rix&#xD;
Resource Planning&#xD;
Watercrest&#xD;
Business Technology Solutions&#xD;
TF:  1-888-244-7550 ext.110&#xD;
ed@watercrest.net&#xD;
www.watercrest.net</content>
    <postId>DFDF519A-3853-4198-AB4A-767E20DC6456</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-06-03T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>SAP BI/BW, Java, Int BA/SA Consultants</title>
</post>
