<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이계영</author>
            <date>2009-11-19T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>Newmarket 이네요</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>근무시간에 대해 말하는 걸 보니... 좀 살벌한 계약직이네요. 저는 아직 기한이 좀 남아서 어차피 월요일에 일을 시작하지는 못하지만요.&#xD;
&#xD;
Int. to Sr.급 개발자라는데, Inc'되어 있어야 합니다. 정확한 장소는 모르는데, 토론토 지역일 겁니다. 보수는 요즘 상황에 비하면 나쁘지는 않을 듯.&#xD;
&#xD;
--------------&#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks Brendan!!!&#xD;
 &#xD;
NOTES:&#xD;
Client will not see anyone who have any holidays planned.  Only stat holidays will be given.  They are under huge time constraints and candidates will be expected to work 12-16 hour days, plus weekends.  Of course, they will be paid for all hours.&#xD;
 &#xD;
I know this is very short notice but candidates need to be available tomorrow and Friday for an EIO in the RH Office and also be ready to start on Monday.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Rate is $50 per hour  (incorporated).  All 8 candidates will be doing the same work .&#xD;
 &#xD;
Also - hours will be nuts.  They are deadline driven to the end of the year so those with lots of holidays booked won't be good fits.  They have a deadline for Dec. 31st due.  We want strong professional consultants that are used to jumping in and doing it all.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Location is Newmarket.&#xD;
 &#xD;
   &#xD;
&#xD;
Must Have Skills:&#xD;
Java - (&gt;5Y)&#xD;
JavaScript - (&gt;5Y)&#xD;
JDeveloper - (&gt;5Y)&#xD;
Oracle 10g - (&gt;5Y)&#xD;
&#xD;
Nice To Have Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
Internal Description:&#xD;
URGENT&#xD;
&#xD;
 Interviews tomorrow and Friday.&#xD;
&#xD;
8 candidates will be selected to start Monday, Nov. 23rd for a period of 3 mths or more.&#xD;
&#xD;
Rates are the same - all at 50 per hour (INC'd) as they will all be doing the exact same job.&#xD;
&#xD;
The must have skills are exactly that - MUST HAVE. The rest is in the job description.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
MAJOR RESPONSIBLITIES:&#xD;
The technical environment includes AIX and Windows operating systems running on top of VMware residing on IBM hardware. The ERP software is Oracle eBusiness integrated with 3rd party routing and optimization software. Anticipated development environments include Oracle, J2EE and Windows, GIS primarily delivering thin-client solutions.&#xD;
&#xD;
• Participate in the development and enhancement of existing and new core business systems&#xD;
• Maintain software through review and modification of existing code&#xD;
• Maintain vision for product enhancements and provide appropriate recommendations&#xD;
• Take ownership of problems and deal with them effectively to ensure resolution&#xD;
• Liaise with appropriate staff to analyze and debug system failure&#xD;
• Participate in peer reviews and knowledge sharing workshops&#xD;
• Participate in testing of newly developed software components&#xD;
• Develop and/or maintain operational documentation for new programs as well as modifications to existing programs&#xD;
&#xD;
KNOWLEDGE AND QUALIFICATIONS:&#xD;
&#xD;
• University degree or College diploma in Computer Science or Engineering, or the equivalent combination of education, training, and experience&#xD;
• Minimum 4 years of specific, job experience performing applications development&#xD;
• Working knowledge of Oracle 10g database, including SQL, PL/SQL, Forms and BI Publisher.&#xD;
• Practical multi-tier application architecture experience&#xD;
• Technically fluent in development technologies including C#, VB, Java, J2EE, SQL, PL/SQL, BPEL, BAM, BPM, AJAX , Oracle Fusion and SOA.&#xD;
• Development experience with enterprise software, (prefer Oracle eBusiness Suite (EBS)) including development, customization, configuration and integration.&#xD;
• Development experience with web techniques, including CSS, HTML, Java Script, DOM, HttpRequest, AJAX, JSON, XML, XSLT and XSD.&#xD;
• Experience with source code management system.&#xD;
• Experience with geographic information systems or other spatial data.&#xD;
• Working knowledge of network and PC operating systems, including Windows and AIX.&#xD;
&#xD;
SKILLS AND ABILITIES:&#xD;
&#xD;
• Proven communication and problem-solving related to the design, development, and deployment of mission-critical business and software systems&#xD;
• Excellent verbal and written communication skills&#xD;
• Strong interpretative skills to understand and relate design requirements&#xD;
• Good root cause analysis skills&#xD;
• Ability to communicate effectively to both technical and non-technical audiences&#xD;
• Ability to conduct research into development issues, techniques and methodologies&#xD;
• Proven analytical and creative problem-solving abilities&#xD;
• Highly motivated and self directed, with keen attention to detail&#xD;
• Experience working in a team-oriented, collaborative environment&#xD;
&#xD;
   &#xD;
Christine Tsui&#xD;
&#xD;
CTsui@sapphireca.com&#xD;
&#xD;
Sapphire Canada, A Randstad Company&#xD;
T 905.882.1044 x3904</content>
    <postId>E082AAA6-AFE4-419E-B90D-060C7FCB6677</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-11-18T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>[Urgent] 자바 중상급 개발자/계약/INC-내일까지 접수, 내주 월요일에 시작</title>
</post>
