<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>권상하</author>
            <date>2004-07-14T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>구직자를 위하여 잡포스팅을 올리시는 것에 &#xD;
감사를 표합니다.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>JOB POSTING&#xD;
&#xD;
          TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE - TORONTO, CANADA&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Established in 1986, Geosoft stands for integrity and best practice in earth science mapping and exploration technology.  Today, Geosoft software is helping to simplify geospatial data access and analysis for improved understanding, knowledge development and business decision-making in industries such as mineral exploration, oil and gas, government, and in environmental investigations and UXO (Unexploded Ordnance) detection.&#xD;
&#xD;
The company is headquartered in downtown Toronto, Canada, with offices in South America, Europe, South Africa and Australia. Geosoft's partner network provides additional coverage throughout the United States and across the globe, in Russia, India and China.  Geosoft provides a quality work environment that is informal but professional, friendly and supportive. We have a motivated and dedicated workforce that delivers excellent software and responsive service to an international customer base. &#xD;
&#xD;
JOB TITLE:                   Technical Support Representative&#xD;
&#xD;
            &#xD;
&#xD;
REPORTS TO:              Manager, Technical Support and Testing&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
JOB SUMMARY:           To provide technical support and solutions to our clients and regional offices.  &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Technical Support&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Conduct appropriate diagnostic procedures to determine issues&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Provide accurate and timely technical support to clients and regional offices, primarily by telephone and email&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Efficiently prioritize technical support requests based on the issues presented&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Liaise with other team members to resolve larger issues&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Log all support incidents into thel tracking software&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Other duties as required.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Testing:&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Assist with product testing and training as required&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE:&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Post secondary education in Earth Sciences &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Two to four years field experience an asset &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Knowledge of Geosoft products required&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Excellent computer skills; strength in PC applications is essential.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS AND ABILITIES:&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Strong analytical and problem solving skills &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Communication skills applied in technical support environment&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Ability to handle multiple tasks and attention to detail&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Excellent customer-service orientation with professional and courteous phone manner.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
PLEASE NOTE:  Applications accepted from Canadian nationals only.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Please send your CV and cover letter by email to jobs@geosoft.com with subject header TSR.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Closing date for applications:  July 30th, 2004 &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>E2EE1951-3591-42AA-B847-1FC74C636F33</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-07-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE - TORONTO, CANADA</title>
</post>
