<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2002-09-09T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Ooops~! Are both of you gonna get married? What do you mean by "let's get married"? ^^; haha</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>I have known Andrew since 3 years ago. I always like his passion and his energetic intension. He is very candid. &#xD;
What you see is what you get from Andrew. He is very friendly and sensitive. &#xD;
&#xD;
His presentation on last Friday demonstrates his in-depth knowledge of DB and well tracked experiences. &#xD;
Using date as Primary key shows me I have long way to go to understand DB. &#xD;
&#xD;
Not only his knowledge impressed me also his good command of English impressed me more. &#xD;
He set very high standard presentation skill to other Community one members. He was as good as I had seen. &#xD;
&#xD;
I look back how was my command of English in my first three years. I do not believe he got his English skill overnight. &#xD;
He put a lot of effort. I have seen many persons with longer tenure in Candana &#xD;
but a lot less command of English. Just like anything else practice makes improvement. &#xD;
&#xD;
If you observe Andrew carefully, he has done his share of commitment. &#xD;
He went to North Bay for a year. &#xD;
He took numerous presentation and communication courses. I like to ask to other members. &#xD;
"Have you take any those kind of courses ? and how is your command of English ?". &#xD;
If you are not happy with the situation, maybe it is time to take action." &#xD;
&#xD;
Less you use Korean it will provide more opportunity to improve your English. &#xD;
If you think of it, how much time do you spend daily base speaking English. &#xD;
Let say you go to Korean church on Sunday and other bible study on other weekdays. &#xD;
You are not giving any favors to your English. If you believe in God, God is presented in all kind churches not only in Korean church. &#xD;
&#xD;
Anyway I am writing this letter to Andrew to encourage. Looks like he is in control of his Canadian life &#xD;
and like to improve. But there is one thing missing in his life. "Wife" &#xD;
&#xD;
It is time for you to make decision. Time is not in your side for this case. I like to suggest three steps of action. &#xD;
&#xD;
- Decide your mind : What do you like the most of woman ? &#xD;
Is it sex, good communication or financial freedom ? &#xD;
I like to suggest good communication at the top of the list. Sex and money will come and go. But if you are looking a person you can share your idea, dream and frustration for, good communication is very important. I will command a week to decide. A week is long enough. Besides any longer that a week it will confuse you. &#xD;
&#xD;
- After decision act on it. &#xD;
give a person a call or visit and tell them what are you looking for and need &#xD;
&#xD;
- Then get married &#xD;
Getting married is like picking up watermelon. You win some and lose some. &#xD;
&#xD;
Life is like box of chocolate in the wrap. You never know what you are going to get. Rule of thumb of good marriage is not the person you are going to get get married. Attitude towards marriage is more important. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>E3186EC3-F6BD-40DE-BB2A-2969EBFAECDE</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-09T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Letter to Andrew Shin</title>
</post>
