<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>권상하</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Weblogic Admnistrator/Analyst (contract) &#xD;
Toronto (GTA)   &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Job Description Our client in the GTA is currently looking for a Weblogic Administrator to join their team. This is a 6 month contract role with a possibility of extension. You will be: - Responsible for the infrastructure that supports over 100 dynamic Websites and Web service Middleware - Install, configure, maintain, monitor and support Web Servers and Java application Servers for development, testing, production, and disaster recovery environments - Provide Middleware expertise to application support teams in all environments for design and troubleshooting - 7x24 on-call support Qualifications: - Excellent knowledge of BEA Weblogic products including WebLogic Server, WebLogic Portal, WebLogic Integration and AquaLogic Service Bus - Excellent knowledge of Web servers, preferably Apache - Good knowledge of Unix operating systems, preferably Redhat Linux 4 and HP-UX 11 - Good knowledge of databases including Oracle, Microsoft SQL Server, and MYSQL - Experience supporting large environments (5000+ users) Connecting you + Quantum: With our contacts and your skills, we're a winning combination. Put Quantum on your team and apply today!We appreciate all expressed interest in this position, however, only the candidates selected for interview will be contacted. You will certainly be contacted before we submit your resume to any of our clients.Quantum is an equal opportunity employer.   [view full job] &#xD;
 &#xD;
Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location &#xD;
  &#xD;
Type Permanent &#xD;
Advertiser QUANTUM (Employment Agency) &#xD;
Contact Harneet Maggu &#xD;
Email Harneet.Maggu.D3DDC.13937@mail.jobserve.com &#xD;
Phone 416-366-3660 &#xD;
Ref JSHAM15827 &#xD;
Date 11/06/2009 04:22:41</content>
    <postId>E415E508-1252-4C17-93C6-3CCA857B6784</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Weblogic Admnistrator/Analyst (contract)</title>
</post>
