<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Title: Senior Software Developer&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
   Location: Toronto&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Our client is one of the leading edge technology firms at the forefront of mobile payments innovation. We are building a revolutionary mobile commerce platform that caters to the needs of the mass market. &#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
      POSITION OVERVIEW&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Our client is looking for a Senior Software Developer who has a growing skilled team that is responsible for a large-scale financial payment processing platform.  The ideal candidate will be responsible for designing and evaluating requirements, development of new features, and ensuring high levels of performance.  A refactoring of the payments system will also be a core task.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
Aid in the development of the Payment Processing Platform&#xD;
Maintain the current codebase with bug fixes, patches, and feature requests&#xD;
Write technical documents that detail the functional requirement/design of code&#xD;
Contribute to brainstorming sessions for new features&#xD;
Unit testing of code to ensuring acceptable levels of unit testing&#xD;
Assist in deployment of web applications, and development of deployment plans&#xD;
Creation and maintenance of database structures&#xD;
 &#xD;
REQUIREMENTS&#xD;
&#xD;
Personal Skill Requirements&#xD;
&#xD;
Strong problem solving skills&#xD;
Motivated, self starter&#xD;
Excellent communication skills&#xD;
Team player&#xD;
Technical Skill Requirements&#xD;
&#xD;
At least 3 years of Java experience (JDK1.5+)&#xD;
At least 3 years of J2EE experience (Servlets, JSP, EJB’s, etc)&#xD;
Experience with web services&#xD;
Extensive experience with HTML, XML (SAX/DOM/XSLT/etc)&#xD;
General relational database experience (comfortable with SQL DDL, DML)&#xD;
Database experience using MySQL 5+&#xD;
Experience using database technologies (JDBC, Hibernate, etc)&#xD;
Struts 1 experience&#xD;
Experience using Eclipse&#xD;
Other Valueable Skills&#xD;
&#xD;
Mobile experience&#xD;
Financial or payments experience&#xD;
Experience using Axis and other Apache Java libraries&#xD;
Solid web skills (JavaScript, HTML, AJAX, etc)&#xD;
Experience using build technologies (ANT, Maven, etc)&#xD;
Experience using subversion&#xD;
 &#xD;
To  Apply: &#xD;
 &#xD;
If you or know of someone who is interested in this opportunity please submit your resume to hotjobs@acchuman.com.  Acchuman wishes to thank all applicants but only those suitable will be contacted for an interview.  Please ask about our referral program. (Mention Brendan Kim as your referral)&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Ross Campbell &#xD;
campbell@acchuman.com &#xD;
executive search consultant &#xD;
416-369-1515 x104</content>
    <postId>E47BAC30-C9EF-4DBA-8C77-362903C95352</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-09T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[PERM] Senior Software Developer</title>
</post>
