<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Account: Financial Industry&#xD;
&#xD;
Location:  Downtown Toronto&#xD;
&#xD;
Duration:  Contract&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
This Software Developer III - Java will be supporting the Websphere Upgrade and upgrade to Content Site. The Content Site will need to interface between the Content Site and interface to web banking. The second phase of Websphere deals with EasyWeb and Content Site.&#xD;
A seasoned Java developer with good leadership skills would be an asset.&#xD;
It would be nice to have a candidate who has Object Grid experience and who may have worked with Content Site.&#xD;
&#xD;
Develop and host web enabled and database driven applications in Java. Apply analytical skills to resolve problems and deliver solutions. Design and develop quality solutions for systems issues consistent with project objectives. Develop, implement and maintain solutions that maximize system availability. Periodic scope assistance Oversee other developers. Troubleshoot coding issues. Ensure coding continuity.&#xD;
As a senior developer, he/she will eventually contribute to future enhancement, support and maintenance post-delivery. Prime responsibility will be to develop detailed design specifications, create and review code and assess impact on other applications. Role will work closely with other team members to ensure consistency in coding standards and approaches and to optimize any synergy and re-use opportunities.&#xD;
Key accountabilities are:&#xD;
• Responsible for leading technical aspects of project from inception through to deployment. Participate in analysis and system design specification sessions. Documentation of design options and solutions according to System Development Life Cycle (SDLC) methodology. Ensure that solutions adhere to development best practices and architectural principles.&#xD;
• Apply analytical skills to resolve problems and deliver viable solutions. Anticipate obstacles and execute proactive approaches to issues. Active participation in issue resolution.&#xD;
• Provide detailed development estimates to Project Manager for development effort as well as weekly status reporting and budget forecasting.&#xD;
• Configuration management for the sub projects within the release.&#xD;
• Responsible for coding, testing, packaging, deployment and support of builds as code is promoted from development, system, acceptance and production environments. May lead code reviews.&#xD;
• Work closely with System Test Environment Management Team (STEMT) to ensure that environments are fully functional and that builds are properly deployed.&#xD;
• Participate in development of test strategy, test plans, test cases and testing efforts (unit testing and integration testing of code).&#xD;
• Provide technical support to business and testing team during testing phases. Track defects, defect triage and resolution.&#xD;
• Data set up and environment shake down.&#xD;
• Coaching / mentoring of junior developers.&#xD;
• Knowledge transfer within group.&#xD;
• Ensure required documentation is housed in the project repository and that knowledge transfer has occurred to full time staff upon completion of contract term. SKILLS: Development experience in distributed windows or Java&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Regards,&#xD;
&#xD;
Jamie K Martin Technical Recruiter&#xD;
TEKsystems&#xD;
150 York St. Suite 1206&#xD;
Toronto, ON&#xD;
(T) 416.342.5008&#xD;
(F) 416.342.5070&#xD;
jammarti@teksystems.ca</content>
    <postId>E5402E46-5049-469B-8300-8E3F970AAB48</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-10-02T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>TEKsystems -Contract - Job Opportunity</title>
</post>
