<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>최덕선</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&gt;Subject: JUG News:  March 2004 Meeting Reminder&#xD;
&gt;Date: Fri, 27 Feb 2004 12:44:14 -0500&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;                                 WWW.JUG.ORG&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;Our next monthly meeting will be held on Tuesday March 2nd in&#xD;
&gt;Ryerson's Rogers Communications Centre (2nd Floor), room RCC-201&#xD;
&gt;(across the hall from the Eaton Theatre).&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;TheServerSide's Floyd Marinsecu will be presenting a talk titled&#xD;
&gt;"What's new in J2EE 1.4 and what's brewing for the future".&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;This will be a comprehensive session that covers all the changes in&#xD;
&gt;the upcoming J2EE 1.4 platform and why they matter to J2EE developers.&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;Each API that makes up the J2EE platform will be looked at, going into&#xD;
&gt;all the major changes. J2EE 1.4 adds new features aimed at changing&#xD;
&gt;the web app ballgame, important enhancements that will trigger a&#xD;
&gt;maturity in the J2EE tools market, and extensions to J2EE that will&#xD;
&gt;improve integration capabilities as well as the extendibility of J2EE&#xD;
&gt;appservers.&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;Finally, new JSRs from Sun are adding a lot of changes to the Java&#xD;
&gt;language that will have a positive impact on the J2EE API's including&#xD;
&gt;metadata, autoboxing, enumerations, generics, and more. The talk will&#xD;
&gt;conclude with a speculative look at current trends in the industry&#xD;
&gt;including SOA, AOP, light weight containers, EJB 3.0, and how these&#xD;
&gt;trends may change the way we code enterprise Java applications.&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;Floyd Marinescu is author of the best seller "EJB Design Patterns"&#xD;
&gt;(2002, John Wiley and Sons), and General Manager of TheServerSide&#xD;
&gt;Communities, which include TheServerSide.com &amp; Symposium conferences,&#xD;
&gt;the Java industry's source for news, discussions, patterns, reviews&#xD;
&gt;and articles. TheServerSide is run by The Middleware Company,&#xD;
&gt;specializing in J2EE training and consulting. Floyd has contributed&#xD;
&gt;heavily to the J2EE platform community by building and running&#xD;
&gt;TheServerSide.com, where he regularly reports on industry news and&#xD;
&gt;events.&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
&gt;&#xD;
&gt;  For more information on this presentation, check out the Toronto JUG&#xD;
&gt;  web site at www.jug.org.&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>E5C7304F-C36D-4988-9B4A-3B8CA6730D4B</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-03-01T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Toronto Java User Group meeting</title>
</post>
