<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>제가 지원할까말까 고민하고 있는 중인 잡포지션인데요, 고민하는 이유는 바로 비자문제 때문이죠 뭐. 이거 하나마나 아닐까 싶어서... 아마 이 정도 스펙이 되시는 분들은 꽤 계시리라 생각되며 여기 올려봅니다. 오늘 CNN 뉴스보니까 미국의 경제 지표가 상승곡선을 타고 있는 것 같던데 좀 좋아지려나요?&#xD;
---------------------------------------------&#xD;
&#xD;
EER SYSTEMS INC.&#xD;
&#xD;
PROGRAMMER-DATABASE ENGINEER POSITION IN OUR ATLANTA BRANCH&#xD;
&#xD;
PLEASE SEND YOUR RESUME AND SALARY REQUIREMENT TO:&#xD;
RAY STONE&#xD;
EER SYSTEMS INC.&#xD;
TEL: (888) 564-8226&#xD;
EMAIL:  ray.stone@eer.com&#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description: Initially support maintenance of the current CPRS system. As part of the&#xD;
enterprise architecture team, develops and maintains database applications in support of&#xD;
business needs, develops a functional, data and technical architecture on a high visibility&#xD;
project. Serves as an internal consultant to users and development team.&#xD;
Responsibilities include:&#xD;
-Designs, develops, and maintains a detailed (blue-print level) functional architecture model&#xD;
for the entire business process. Provides review and consultation on the functional architecture&#xD;
(Use Cases) and develops detailed blueprints that will ensure enterprise level integration of&#xD;
developed systems.&#xD;
-Consults with users in departments including accounting/billing, sales/sales support,&#xD;
marketing/product development, customer care, and other functions to understand and gather user&#xD;
requirements for data collection needs.&#xD;
-Ensures that the functional architecture is implemented in the application design and&#xD;
development.&#xD;
-Uses various J2EE technologies develop technical models and prototypes.&#xD;
-Works to design and implement logical data storage architectures that will meet current and&#xD;
future needs of the organization.&#xD;
-Reviews and evaluates current DBMS and makes recommendations for solutions, performance tuning,&#xD;
and other methods to optimize database application.&#xD;
-Conducts performance tuning and analyzes database capacity issues, replication, and other&#xD;
distributed data issues.&#xD;
-Implements data models and database designs, data access codes and table maintenance codes.&#xD;
-Identifies data sources, constructs data flow diagrams, and documents the process.&#xD;
-Codes for database access, modifications, and stored procedures.&#xD;
-Analyzes, troubleshoots, and resolves issues related to database management system in a timely&#xD;
manner.&#xD;
-Performs work related to importing and exporting data, file structures, etc., from other&#xD;
systems.&#xD;
-Ensures database connectivity and oversees database on-going upgrades and new builds.&#xD;
-Acts as liaison or the point of contact with development, management, systems operations,&#xD;
vendors, and other groups in key decisions.&#xD;
-Serves as second or third-tier for programming support to development efforts.&#xD;
-Performs other duties as assigned.&#xD;
-Individual must be willing to work in a 24-7 environment that includes a weekly on call&#xD;
rotation. &#xD;
Required Skills: -Bachelor's degree in CS, Information Systems or equivalent.&#xD;
-Apache Web Server and Tomcat-Oracle 8.0 and higher.&#xD;
-Solaris 9.0 and higher.&#xD;
-4+ years experience in programmer role, to include designing, developing, and implementing data&#xD;
storage structures and applications.&#xD;
-2+ years experience reviewing and evaluating DBMS, administering, maintaining, developing, and&#xD;
implementing procedures related to DBMS.&#xD;
-Minimum of 3+ years experience collaborating with users across departments/functions within a&#xD;
firm, including overseeing data acquisition and data management needs for internal/external&#xD;
customers.&#xD;
-Minimum of 3+ years experience with installation, data access, security, capacity planning,&#xD;
performance tuning, monitoring, maintenance and support of Oracle 8i on UNIX. &#xD;
-Proficient in Oracle database maintenance (Reorgs, backups, recovery, capacity planning and&#xD;
space management).&#xD;
-Must possess strong logical and physical data modeling and design background.&#xD;
-Multiple years experience object oriented design utilizing Use Cases.&#xD;
-A strong knowledge of SQL and use of stored procedures and triggers.&#xD;
-A strong knowledge and experience with backup/recovery techniques.&#xD;
-Minimum of 3+ years experience with Microsoft Office Products.&#xD;
-Must possess good communication and interpersonal skills. &#xD;
Minimum Years of experience needed for required skills: 3-4 &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>E8E524CB-F2A1-45D5-9E46-D6DC89399533</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-08-21T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>US job - PROGRAMMER-DATABASE ENGINEER</title>
</post>
