<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Hi Brendan,&#xD;
 &#xD;
Please find the RFS details below.&#xD;
 &#xD;
.1        CLIENT &amp; CONTACT INFORMATION&#xD;
 &#xD;
Client:                          Ministry of Transportation&#xD;
 &#xD;
Branch:                       Road User Safety Solutions Branch&#xD;
                                                                                         &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
1.2        PROJECT INFORMATION&#xD;
 &#xD;
Project Name:                           Enhanced Driver’s Licence Project (EDL)&#xD;
 &#xD;
Computing Environment            Java/J2EE, UNIX&#xD;
Category:                     &#xD;
 &#xD;
Project Start Date:                     April 6, 2009&#xD;
 &#xD;
Project End Date:                      July 31, 2009&#xD;
 &#xD;
Resource Requirements:            One (1) Senior Programmer/Analyst&#xD;
 &#xD;
Number of Days:                       80 days&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
1.3               BACKGROUND INFORMATION&#xD;
 &#xD;
The Western Hemisphere Travel Initiative (WHTI) requires all citizens of the United States (US), Canada, Mexico, and Bermuda to have a passport or other accepted document that establishes the bearer’s identity and nationality in order to enter or re?enter the US from within the Western Hemisphere.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ontario is concerned that not enough people have or can get a passport prior to the full implementation of WHTI anticipated in June 2009 and so has been advocating the acceptance of existing forms of identification other than a passport under WHTI.  Our efforts have been successful and neighbouring US border states of New York and Michigan have publicly announced they will be creating enhanced driver’s licences for their residents.  Reciprocal benefits to Ontario require that we develop a similar licence. This initiative supports MTO’s mandated priority to work with the Ministry of Intergovernmental Affairs (MIA) to encourage formal acceptance by U.S. Department of Homeland Security (DHS) of an EDL as an alternative identity document under WHTI.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ministry of Transportation will implement an enhanced driver’s licence (EDL) card as alternative identity document under the Western Hemisphere Travel Initiative (WHTI) for United States (US) land and sea border crossings.  Ontario is committed to strengthening border security while ensuring the efficient flow of legitimate cross-border travel and trade to maintain a strong economy.&#xD;
 &#xD;
The EDL project has adopted a phased implementation approach consisting of 2 phases.&#xD;
 &#xD;
·         Phase 1 is targeting March 2009 to deliver&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Secure architecture and software security&#xD;
·         Data security and protection of privacy&#xD;
·         Integration with the on-line corporate self-serve appointment booking system&#xD;
·         EDL card application processing and production&#xD;
·         Integration with Photo Comparison Technology (PCT) for fraud prevention&#xD;
·         Operational, management, audit and financial reconciliation reports&#xD;
·         Notification forms/letters&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
·         Phase 2 is targeting September 2009 to deliver&#xD;
&#xD;
·         Additional EDL card application processing features&#xD;
·         Enhanced operational and management reporting&#xD;
·         Scanning and storage of documents submitted by EDL applicant&#xD;
·         Automated data exchange with other Ministries and Federal Government&#xD;
·         Additional notification forms/letters&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
1.4 CLIENT’S REQUIREMENTS&#xD;
 &#xD;
Scope of Services: The Services to be provided by the Vendor will include the following:&#xD;
 &#xD;
This assignment requires the services for one (1) Senior/Programmer Analyst. The candidate will be part of an existing system development team for the design, development and unit/integration/systems/user acceptance support activities for the Enhanced Driver Licence project (EDL) phase 2 within the Road User Safety Division. Implementation and Post Implementation activities will be carried out in a separate assignment.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Deliverables: The Senior Programmer Analyst will be responsible for the development, maintenance and enhancement activities for applications that support the Enhanced Driver Licence (EDL) project phase 2 for the Road User Safety Division.  This assignment will include the completion of the systems/user acceptance testing support activities. This will include:&#xD;
 &#xD;
1.                  Work with a Business/Systems Analyst and architect to prepare detailed Technical Specifications and Design documents as required.&#xD;
 &#xD;
2.                  Create object-oriented models in UML as design artefacts using tools such as Power Designer.&#xD;
 &#xD;
3.                  Provide assistance in preparation of test strategy and test plan for unit and integration testing.&#xD;
 &#xD;
4.                  Develop/enhance systems using J2EE (Java, EJB, JSP, Servlets, JDBC), XML (DOM, SAX, XSLT), DHTML/HTML, Web Service, Weblogic, Toplink, Oracle. &#xD;
 &#xD;
5.                  Prepare fully documented operational procedures for system and production system support staff as required.&#xD;
 &#xD;
6.                  Test the system and meet the acceptance requirements of the implementation.&#xD;
 &#xD;
7.                  Problem resolution support to databases staff, system and user acceptance test teams, and other staff members.&#xD;
 &#xD;
8.                  Co-ordination of automated system development activities and technical consultative support to other staff members.&#xD;
 &#xD;
9.                  Effective knowledge transfer to ministry staff at all stages of this assignment.&#xD;
 &#xD;
10.              Provide consultation to other team members as required.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &#xD;
Work Requirements:&#xD;
 &#xD;
The Solutions Engineering Office is looking for one (1) Senior Programmer Analyst for the Enhanced Driver’s License project.&#xD;
 &#xD;
The Senior Programmer Analyst must be able to work in a multi-project, multi-disciplinary enterprise environment seeking input and comment from other major initiatives.&#xD;
 &#xD;
The skills required must include:&#xD;
·         Solid experience in development of N-tier applications, middleware and gateways.&#xD;
·         Knowledge of, and experienced with the following computing environments:&#xD;
TCP/IP, WAN/LAN environment&#xD;
Database: Oracle&#xD;
Operating Platforms: Solaris, AIX, Windows&#xD;
Web/Application Servers: WebLogic, Microsoft IIS&#xD;
Object to Relational Mapping: e.g. Toplink&#xD;
IMS Connect&#xD;
LDAP&#xD;
Web Services&#xD;
·         Experience with Object Oriented Analysis &amp; Design (UML – Use Case/Class Sequence/Collaboration/State)&#xD;
·         Experience in developing web-based applications using J2EE (Java, EJB, JSP, Servlets, JDBC, JNDI), XML (DOM, SAX, XSLT), DHTML/HTML, Struts, Javascript, Web Services.&#xD;
·         Working experience with Java/J2EE Design Patterns.&#xD;
·         Working experience with toolsets that support object oriented languages and web application development including:&#xD;
o        Configuration/Builds: CVS, VSS, Harvest, Ant&#xD;
o        Rational Rose&#xD;
o        Eclipse&#xD;
o        JUnit, Log4J&#xD;
o        JProfiler&#xD;
·         Familiar with UI design principles and guidelines.&#xD;
·         Excellent analytical, problem solving, communication (verbal and written), and interpersonal skills.&#xD;
·         A team player with the ability to coordinate multiple projects with competing priorities and strict deadlines.&#xD;
·         Proven ability to complete assignment of high magnitude and complexity.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Nice-to-Have Skills:&#xD;
 &#xD;
·         Ontario Provincial Government experience (web-based applications) is desirable&#xD;
·         Familiarity with Ontario Government Intranet and Internet standards and style guides&#xD;
·         Experience with software based load balancing and clustering&#xD;
·         Knowledge of PKI&#xD;
·         Knowledge of Government processes&#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks,&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Robert&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Robert Sabry&#xD;
www.dynalync.ca&#xD;
robert@dynalync.ca&#xD;
Dir    (416) 642 9193&#xD;
Tel:  (416) 398-2000</content>
    <postId>E904555C-FC50-4540-BDC9-59A6F655948A</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-20T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[Cont.] Senior Programmer Analyst, MTO, 16 weeks</title>
</post>
