<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>임기순</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>이성기</author>
            <date>2009-03-10T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>여러교통수단을 사용하여 출퇴근하는 사람들을 위한 transit tax credit이 있어서 15.5% 되돌려 준다고 합니다. 문제는 monthly pass를 구매한 사람에 한해. http://www.google.com/search?sourceid=navclient&amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;rls=RNWE,RNWE:2006-20,RNWE:en&amp;q=ontario+tax+credit+transportation</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>http://www.budget.gc.ca/2009/pdf/pamphlet-depliant3-eng.pdf&#xD;
&#xD;
Thinking of home renovations?  New federal tax credits can help. &#xD;
Springtime is all about new beginnings, and sprucing up your living space can be just thing to shake off winter.  For many Canadians, new incentives recently announced in the federal budget will make a home renovation project more attractive.  &#xD;
The federal budget announced in January includes a home renovation tax credit of 15 per cent of the cost of your project, up to $1,350.  To qualify, your project has to be more than $1,000 and the credit tops out at a $10,000 ceiling.  This is a non-refundable credit, which means it will reduce your taxes owing, but you don’t receive cash if you have a positive balance.  Also, the materials and labour for the project need to be purchased before February 1, 2010.    &#xD;
If you go green with your renos, you can “double dip” – the renovation credit can be claimed on projects that also qualify for up to $5,000 with the federal ecoEnergy Retrofit Program. &#xD;
Note that these proposed tax credits will not come into effect until the federal budget receives royal assent, expected later this spring.&#xD;
Examples of HRTC Eligible&#xD;
and Ineligible Expenditures&#xD;
Eligible&#xD;
• Renovating a kitchen, bathroom, or basement&#xD;
• New carpet or hardwood floors&#xD;
• Building an addition, deck, fence or retaining wall&#xD;
• A new furnace or water heater&#xD;
• Painting the interior or exterior of a house&#xD;
• Resurfacing a driveway&#xD;
• Laying new sod&#xD;
&#xD;
Ineligible&#xD;
• Furniture and appliances (refrigerator, stove, couch)&#xD;
• Purchase of tools&#xD;
• Carpet cleaning&#xD;
• Maintenance contracts (furnace cleaning, snow&#xD;
removal, lawn care, pool cleaning, etc.)</content>
    <postId>EA8B9E36-BB60-4B08-8277-10B487C7991B</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-10T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>home renovation tax credit - new for 2009</title>
</post>
