<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이성기</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김경환</author>
            <date>2009-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>정말 너무 심하네요 우리일은 딱히 정해진 근무시간만 일하는것도 아닌데 말이죠.... 빨리 경제가 회복되어야 될텐데</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>정말 가격이 많이 내려갔습니다. architect를 시간당 $51불에 구하기도 합니다. 이러면, 우리같은 사람들 살기힘듭니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Description&#xD;
Department Overview: &#xD;
Business Banking has launched a strategic enablement initiative intended to re-architect its Sales and Loan Origination capabilities with the objective of efficiently exceeding market growth and increasing the Bank’s share of the Canadian business banking market through streamlined credit origination and fulfillment, and more effective client relationship/sales management capabilities. The end-state vision for the Sales and Loan Origination platform is centered on an integrated view of Business Banking customers and the ability to map customer account portfolios against TD’s product offerings to easily identify likely sales opportunities and seamlessly originate new products. &#xD;
&#xD;
As part of this initiative, this candidate will act as a deployment analyst to join the operational stream of the program to contribute and learn all aspects of the new platform, including direct involvement in the delivery of the various releases, and potentially involve in the platform's future enhancement, support and maintenance post-delivery. &#xD;
&#xD;
Job Description/Accountabilities: &#xD;
As a key member of this team, the incumbent will be expected to take ownership of the following accountabilities: &#xD;
• Work with the Deployment Lead and architects to define and support deployment requirements. &#xD;
• Participate in managing cross release/unit deployment issues and interdependencies. &#xD;
• Prepare associated deployment document (instructions) that describes the steps involved in deploying all code, configurations to the various environments (e.g. Production Acceptance, Production). &#xD;
• Apply analytical skills to resolve problems and deliver viable solutions. &#xD;
• Anticipate obstacles and execute proactive approaches to issues. &#xD;
• Improve solutions/processes that maximize system availability, efficiency/effectiveness and minimize/prevent problems/issues. &#xD;
• Comply with the TD system development life cycle (SDLC) and project management methodology (PMLC) by participating in scope assessment, risk and cost analysis. Completion of Requirements, Design, and Deploy documents. &#xD;
&#xD;
Other Qualifications/Skills/Experience: &#xD;
• Proven workplace development skills using JAVA, J2EE, Object Oriented, and related technologies. &#xD;
• Experience in deploying web applications and clear understanding of version control procedures. &#xD;
• Ability to research, analyze, design and resolve problems for assigned programs. &#xD;
• Strong analytical and problem solving skills. &#xD;
• Ability to work effectively in a fast paced team environment with minimal supervision. &#xD;
• Excellent communication skills, both verbal and written. &#xD;
• Financial Institution or similar experience is preferred. &#xD;
• Working knowledge of IBM WebSphere application servers. &#xD;
• Familiarity with Struts, XML, ePlatform architecture, SOA, DAO framework, and XSLT. &#xD;
• Familiarity with CRM applications such as Siebel or PeopleSoft. &#xD;
• Experience working with Business clients in a consulting or support capacity is preferred. &#xD;
• Experience working with Commercial or Small Business Banking is an asset. &#xD;
&#xD;
Specific Educational Requirements/Accreditations: &#xD;
- College / University or equivalent work experience&#xD;
&#xD;
Ashley Hyslop&#xD;
Provision IT Resources LTD.&#xD;
IT Specialist - Private Sector&#xD;
Office: 416-777-1708 ext 242&#xD;
Toll Free: 1-866-797-7717&#xD;
Fax: 416-777-1708&#xD;
Email: Ashley.Hyslop@provisionit.ca&#xD;
Website: Provisionit.ca</content>
    <postId>EAA5070D-AC47-42B7-AE32-82F0DCBA4EDB</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>6 month contract. $46/hr, TD bank at downtown</title>
</post>
