<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이명심</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>손영란</author>
            <date>2009-10-29T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>It seems to make sense to me and I think it's cut onion, not unpeeled onion. Because I have heard that onions absorb some bad substance in air. That is why I have a kind of habbit to wrap leftover onions quickly when i cook and put it in fridge right away.&#xD;
&#xD;
Actually my daughter has cold and taking tamiflu now. Why not? No harm doing that! So I cut onions in half and put them in rooms. &#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks for the tip!</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>캐나다에도 신종플루가 점점더 심각하게 이슈화되고있는것같네요.  아래글을한번 읽어보세요.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
This is interesting.It might work well too.I'm going to try it!&#xD;
&#xD;
A very interesting tip received from a dear friend!  With swine flu becoming a real threat, it's worth considering.  Let me know if it works. &#xD;
&#xD;
Flu In 1919 when the flu killed 40 million&#xD;
people there was this Doctor that visited the many farmers to see if he could help them combat the flu... &#xD;
&#xD;
Many of the farmers and their family had contracted it and many died. &#xD;
The doctor came upon this one farm and to his surprise, everyone was very healthy.  When&#xD;
the doctor asked what the farmer was doing that was different the wife replied that she had placed an unpeeled onion in a dish in the rooms of the home, (probably only two rooms back then).  The doctor&#xD;
couldn't believe it and asked if he could have one of the onions and place it under the microscope.  She gave him one and when he did this, he did find the flu virus in the onion.  It obviously absorbed the bacteria, therefore, keeping the family healthy.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Now, I heard this story from my hairdresser in AZ.  She said that several years ago many of her employees were coming down with the flu and so were many of her customers.  The next year she placed several bowls with onions around in her shop.  To her surprise, none of her staff got sick.  It must work.  (And no, she is not in the onion business.)&#xD;
&#xD;
Let's buy some onions and place them in&#xD;
bowls around your home.  If you work at a desk,&#xD;
place one or two in your office or under your desk or even on top somewhere.  Try it and see what&#xD;
happens.   We did it last year and we never got the flu. &#xD;
&#xD;
If this helps you and your loved ones from getting sick, all the better.  If you do get the flu, it just might be a mild case.. &#xD;
Whatever, what have you to lose?  Just a few bucks on&#xD;
onions!!!!!! !!!!!!!!</content>
    <postId>F0B5875C-4193-464E-9DCC-91159F436E16</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-10-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>신종플루 tip</title>
</post>
