<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>Site Admin</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Former Chapters head blasts new owner Reisman &#xD;
Steve Erwin&#xD;
CANADIAN PRESS &#xD;
Chapters Online Inc. announced another 41 job cuts yesterday and the departure of chief operating officer David Hainline.&#xD;
&#xD;
The cuts, primarily in Web site development and merchandising, come on top of the 58 customer-service jobs cut in late February and 130 jobs eliminated from Chapters' wholesale book distributor, Pegasus Wholesale.&#xD;
&#xD;
The changes complete a restructuring plan begun last November, the company said. &#xD;
&#xD;
They also follow vociferous remarks from the new owner of Chapters Online and Chapters Inc., Heather Reisman, who told a House of Commons heritage committee in Ottawa this week that she has uncovered large, unexpected financial and operational problems inside Chapters since the takeover.&#xD;
&#xD;
In response, former Chapters chief executive Larry Stevenson criticized Reisman yesterday, emphatically denying her ``stunning'' suggestions that the bookstore chain was nearly bankrupt before it was taken over.&#xD;
&#xD;
Stevenson said Reisman's statement that she and husband Gerald Schwartz ``overpaid considerably'' in the $121 million deal is ``outrageous.''&#xD;
&#xD;
If Reisman believes Chapters is in trouble, she should sell it back, Stevenson said.&#xD;
&#xD;
``If she really does believe that they made a drastic mistake in buying Chapters at $17 (per share), then turn around and sell it back to me at $17,'' Stevenson said from his vacation home northwest of Toronto.&#xD;
&#xD;
``If they really would like to go back and run the money-losing Indigo chain that they built and compete against us again, we would love to do that.''&#xD;
&#xD;
Reisman and Schwartz, through Trilogy Retail Enterprises LP, won control of Chapters last month and are awaiting approval from the federal Competition Bureau to merge Chapters' 77 superstores with Reisman's 15-store Indigo Books Music &amp; More Inc. &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>F1FFA045-8782-4E57-A09B-57BBE54A2498</postId>
    <pubDate>2001-03-15T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Chapters.ca cuts more jobs </title>
</post>
