<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>바야흐로 좋은 시절이 오고 있습니다. 특히 계약직들에게는요... &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Hi Brendan (Sungwook),&#xD;
&#xD;
I came across your profile through our Procom database. A large client of ours is looking for Java Application Support Specialist for 6 month contract. Should you be available and interested in this opportunity then forward me your updated copy resume along with your availability. In case of your unavailability for this contract you can forward my email to your friends or colleagues who would be a good fit for this role.&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
JOB DESC:&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Java Application Support Specialist&#xD;
&#xD;
This role is focused on Java Application Support. The Java Application Support Specialist coordinates with vendors to troubleshoot, maintain and upgrade software and assists service users with application support (third level).&#xD;
• Provides support, maintenance, and configuration services for ESAS (Enterprise Shared Application Services) Hosted Services, i.e. Document Ingestion Services (DIS), Document Management Services (DMS) and BPM.&#xD;
• Provide advanced technical skills in monitoring, troubleshooting, maintenance, and enhancements of ESAS Hosted Services.&#xD;
• Ensures that application documentation needed for code release and support is accurate, tested, and complete.&#xD;
• Provide technical expertise and perform tasks for all related projects where application releases across QA and Production environments are necessary (including Disaster Recovery and Business Continuity)&#xD;
• Work closely with ITS and outside vendors to effectively plan, deploy, document, and maintain the ESAS Services and environment additions and changes.&#xD;
• Initiate and participate in timely communication to all stakeholders as necessary during release and incident processes.&#xD;
• Provides technical support for applications including health checks, scheduling, infrastructure and vendor support, system remediation and testing for software upgrades/patches, problem management, change management and compliance.&#xD;
• Monitors test and production application environments for health, responds to problem tickets, ensures triage of problems to root cause, and adherence to SLA.&#xD;
• Enters and manages all support requests in a central Service Management application&#xD;
• Participates in planning and testing for disaster recovery of critical ESAS applications.&#xD;
• Analyzes and documents trends on application, content, and database server utilization.&#xD;
• Maintains and enhances application documentation.&#xD;
• May enhance existing software from general requirements and specifications.&#xD;
• Works with technical staff to understand problems with software and resolve them.&#xD;
• Resolves users’ complaints with software and responds to suggestions for improvements and enhancements.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Qualifications / Skills / Experience:&#xD;
&#xD;
• 5+ years of experience in Information Technology in a variety of roles related to business applications support; experience in supporting hosted applications is a plus.&#xD;
• Demonstrated technical experience supporting and configuring application and web servers.&#xD;
• Proven technical experience in Java J2EE / J2SE development, build and deploy application using Ant Tool&#xD;
• Solid knowledge of application code repositories and functions ( MKS, CVS or Subversion )&#xD;
• Working Experience with WebSphere Application Server (WAS).&#xD;
• Working Experience with SOAP/XML and WSDL.&#xD;
• Demonstrated experience supporting multi-tier applications.&#xD;
• Previous experience working in a help desk and/or customer support environment.&#xD;
• Knowledge of ITIL service management concepts.&#xD;
• Experience with HP QC and QTP.&#xD;
• Knowledge of WebSphere MQ an asset.&#xD;
• Knowledge of SOAP UI an asset.&#xD;
• Understanding of shared software concepts and business applications.&#xD;
• Proven track record of delivering results ensuring operational, reputational, and proprietary risks are minimized.&#xD;
• Strong organizational skills, with the ability to work in a fast paced environment.&#xD;
• Strong customer orientation and a professional approach with the ability to interact with all levels within the organization.&#xD;
• Highly developed critical thinking, analytical and problem solving skills.&#xD;
• Excellent communication skills (both written and verbal).&#xD;
• Promote and support an environment that encourages productivity, innovation, teamwork, and a high level of professionalism.&#xD;
• Continuously enhance knowledge/expertise in own area and keep current with industry and/or business trends.&#xD;
• Self motivated team player with high energy and ability to work independently as well as within a team. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
Thanks...&#xD;
&#xD;
Meghayu Dave&#xD;
&#xD;
Technical Recruiter&#xD;
&#xD;
Procom Consultants Group Ltd.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tel: (647) 288-5181&#xD;
&#xD;
Fax: (416) 483-8102&#xD;
&#xD;
meghayud@procom.ca&#xD;
&#xD;
www.procom.ca</content>
    <postId>F23AF91B-D90D-4955-9D7F-9D90F15E48EC</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-05-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Java Application Support-6 month</title>
</post>
