<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김경용</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>마이크로소프트 캐나다(미시시가)에서 아래와 같은 Free 이벤트가 열립니다. 관심있는 분들께 도움이 되었으면 합니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
Please visit www.microsoft.com/canada/events and enter Event ID - 1032442876&#xD;
&#xD;
The theme for this Architect Forum is an end-to-end look at Building and Deploying Clients that Consume Cloud Services – we’ll concentrate on the architectural patterns to be successful in projects that need to leverage client, data centre server, web and cloud resources and how services can be leveraged in each of these tiers. We’ll also look at Microsoft development tools you can use to improve your productivity and manageability of your projects. &#xD;
  &#xD;
This forum will be cross-cutting areas of concern: we’ll discuss Enterprise Architecture impacts of these patterns as well as dive into the Infrastructure and Solution Architecture aspects of solutions. We’ll strive to give you a forward look at the roadmap of the Microsoft Platform from a number of vantage points: technologies, products and capabilities. We will also pay particular attention to how these capabilities can be integrated together or with other technology infrastructure. &#xD;
  &#xD;
The following topics will be covered at this forum: &#xD;
·          Patterns in Synchronization &amp; Communication for Semi-Connected Solutions &#xD;
·          What’s new in ASP.NET, AJAX and RIA Technologies &#xD;
·          Challenges in Deployment of Operating System Refreshes on the Client and in the Data Centre &#xD;
·          Tooling for targeting the Data Centre and the Cloud &#xD;
·          Microsoft Collaboration Technologies – From Development to the Data Centre to the Cloud &#xD;
  &#xD;
Please join Microsoft and your peers at the Financial Services Architect Forum. This unique forum has been specifically designed to provide an opportunity for top enterprise, solution, infrastructure architects, and technical decision makers to discuss the realities of executing IT projects within their financial services organizations. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
  &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
There is no cost for attending the forum, but seating is limited and is by invitation only. Please register at your earliest convenience to reserve your spot. &#xD;
Please forward this invitation to others in your organization who you think appropriate and who could benefit from the forum. &#xD;
&#xD;
  &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
  &#xD;
  &#xD;
&#xD;
We hope you'll join us on Monday, March 12, 2010 for this informative event. Register today to ensure your space; and please don’t hesitate to contact me with any questions you might have. &#xD;
&#xD;
Regards, &#xD;
  &#xD;
&#xD;
Dave Remmer&#xD;
Architect Advisor&#xD;
(905) 363-8477&#xD;
dremmer@microsoft.com</content>
    <postId>F43EAC94-4DDD-4D02-9209-1EA532098178</postId>
    <pubDate>2010-03-05T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>March 12th for the Financial Services Archite</title>
</post>
