<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>이계영</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>김성욱</author>
            <date>2004-04-19T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>얼마전에 올라온 포지션과 동일한 내용이군요. 이 회사 사람 엄청나게 까다롭게 고르나 봅니다. 벌써 2달 전부터 이걸 하고 있으니... ㅎㅎ</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Hi James,&#xD;
&#xD;
This position just became available and I thought you might have some interest in it.&#xD;
If you are interested please send me a word version of your resume and I will get back to you with more information. If you are not interested please feel free to forward this along to a colleague who is qualified.&#xD;
&#xD;
Here is what we are recruiting for:&#xD;
&#xD;
JOB TITLE: Java Developers - 2 Positions REPORTS TO: Integration Architect&#xD;
Salary: up to 75k&#xD;
JOB PURPOSE&#xD;
To design and develop business applications in Java for  DataSmart Solutions division.&#xD;
&#xD;
KEY JOB FUNCTIONS&#xD;
- Work closely in a software development team to develop high-quality Java software for critical business applications in an evolving, fast-paced environment.&#xD;
· Be involved in all aspects of the software development, including process design, software design, software implementation, documentation, quality assurance, deployment and production support.&#xD;
· Provide technical leadership and expertise in the design/development of new applications and enhancement of existing applications.&#xD;
· Help establish methologies for ensuring code quality and overall project success.&#xD;
· Make application architecture recommendations to management and the development team.&#xD;
· Assist in definining technical interfaces and processes with clients and partners.&#xD;
· Act as a technical advisor and mentor to less experienced Java developers.&#xD;
· Participate in special projects and ad hoc analyses as necessary.&#xD;
·Investigate system problems and propose solutions and/or design improvements.&#xD;
·Remain abreast of relevant technology developments.&#xD;
·Participate in the rotating on-call program.&#xD;
&#xD;
QUALIFICATIONS&#xD;
Education: Masters or Bachlor's Degree in Computer Science, or equivalent combination of training and on the job experience.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tools: Java, Eclipse, CVS, Ant, Torque, Oracle&#xD;
Yrs. of Experience:	5 plus years experience designing and implementing mission-critical enterprise software using object-oriented programming languages &amp; concepts&#xD;
Experience implementing applications using Java, RDBMs, XML, TCP/IP technologies Experience with Extreme Programming or other agile development practices Proven technical proficiency Top-notch problem solving skills, demonstrated ability to perform high quality work Previous experience in the print and/or financial industry is an asset&#xD;
&#xD;
Communication Skills: Above Average - Excellent teamwork skills and a service-oriented attitude are essential. Must be able to speak with management and clients and present technical information in a clear, concise manner. Must create and maintain positive peer and client relationships. Requires the ability to speak with non-technical staff about technical issues. Interacts with all levels of the organization.&#xD;
&#xD;
Roy Andrade&#xD;
Alliance Search Group Inc.&#xD;
416-265-9688 Direct&#xD;
roy@alliancesearch.net&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>F4CD0731-979B-4A31-9728-4FDE900710A3</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-04-19T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>2 Java Developers</title>
</post>
