<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>These are the famous quote I share with my team member weekly base&#xD;
&#xD;
 March&#xD;
“ Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself.” - Leo Tolstoy&#xD;
&#xD;
April&#xD;
“laughter is the best medicine &amp;#8211; unknown” &#xD;
&#xD;
“You can’t win an argument &amp;#8211; Dale Carnegie” &#xD;
&#xD;
“ When you smile, whole world, it smiles with you" &amp;#8211;  commercial  &#xD;
&#xD;
May&#xD;
“"Challenges are what make life interesting; overcoming them is what makes life meaningful." -Joshua J. Marine  &#xD;
&#xD;
"The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams." - Eleanor Roosevelt&#xD;
&#xD;
"It is not fair to ask of others what you are not willing to do yourself." - Eleanor Roosevelt  &#xD;
&#xD;
"My advice to you is get married: if you find a good wife you’ll be happy; if not, you’ll become a philosopher." -Socrates &#xD;
&#xD;
“It's no the size of the dog in the fight, it's the size of the fight in the dog.” - Commercial&#xD;
&#xD;
June&#xD;
"I have not failed. I’ve just found 10,000 ways that don’t work."&#xD;
-Thomas Alva Edison  &#xD;
&#xD;
No pessimist ever discovered the secret of the stars, or sailed to an uncharted land, or opened a new doorway for the human spirit." &#xD;
-Helen Keller &#xD;
&#xD;
July&#xD;
"Work is the true elixir of life. The busiest man is the happiest man." -Sir Theodore Martin&#xD;
&#xD;
"A person with the right ATTITUDE is always a WINNER." Spencer Hwang&#xD;
&#xD;
"When I hear somebody sigh, 'Life is hard,' I am always tempted to ask, 'Compared to what?" -Sydney Harris &#xD;
&#xD;
August&#xD;
"If you want to make an apple pie from scratch, you must first create the universe."  - Carl Sagan&#xD;
&#xD;
“The only thing we have to fear is fear itself."&#xD;
      -Franklin D. Roosevelt, First inaugural address&#xD;
&#xD;
“Change what you can. Accept what you can’t change. Ask for wisdom to tell what they are."  -Prayer of St. Francis&#xD;
&#xD;
Do you have any quotes like to share ?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>F4CFA6CB-2C18-49F2-AB69-872387C9724A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-09-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Quote of the Week</title>
</post>
