<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김성욱</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>CA-ON-Toronto/GTA-Senior J2EE Developer :. &#xD;
&#xD;
Status:  Full Time, Employee  Salary:  CAD 68,000.00 to CAD 70,000.00 per year  Reference Code:  Senior J2EE Developer  &#xD;
&#xD;
ENGINEERING.com Incorporated [CDNX: EGN] is the developer-owner of the www.ENGINEERING.com Web site and Internet-based software and business, being developed to become the ultimate resource tool for the global engineering community and to provide a leading business-to-business Internet marketplace for engineering products and services. We are currently looking for a Senior J2EE Developer. The candidate will be responsible to develop, integrate, document and deploy e-business applications in a J2EE environment using WebSphere tools and technologies.&#xD;
&#xD;
The minimum job specific requirements are as follows:&#xD;
&#xD;
?College/University Degree in Computer Science or equivalent&#xD;
?Minimum 4 years experience in Java&#xD;
?Experience in J2EE development using structured methodologies for development, design implementation and maintenance of applications&#xD;
?Experience with package system implementations&#xD;
?Experience with high volume/high availability systems preferably in an applications service provider environment&#xD;
?Experience with the use of information retrieval packages using SQL&#xD;
?Experience with DB2 technologies&#xD;
&#xD;
Bonus Requirements are as follows:&#xD;
&#xD;
?Experience with Lotus technologies&#xD;
?Experience with MQ series&#xD;
?Strong Visual Basic&#xD;
?Biztalk experience an asset on integration projects&#xD;
?Deployment experience with IBMxSeries hardware and Linux (RedHat) OS&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
We offer a competitive compensation and benefits package. Qualified candidates are invited to forward their r?um?with salary expectations to ENGINEERING.com? Corporate Human Resources at websphere@engineering.com &#xD;
&#xD;
NO FAXES PLEASE!&#xD;
&#xD;
We thank all applicants in advance for their interest but only those applicants who are to be considered will be contacted.&#xD;
&#xD;
ENGINEERING.com is an equal opportunity employer.&#xD;
 &#xD;
....................................................................................................................................................................&#xD;
 Contact Information :.&#xD;
Roger Smith&#xD;
websphere@engineering.com&#xD;
ENGINEERING.com  &#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>F5CFD027-ED5A-4384-812D-645BBF02CE88</postId>
    <pubDate>2003-10-18T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Senior J2EE Developer</title>
</post>
