<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>thomas lee</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>I just became the second time father. It is very late compare to other people. My father in-law told me that he had my wife at very late age. Still he was 7 years younger than I was. I like to accept this daunting challenge gladly. I welcome the opportunity. Because I was not good father first time. Fatherhood or parenthood did not come with the manual. I was not prepared or ready. Beside my fatherhood project had changed daily basis. Infant, kindergarten, elementary school and high school.&#xD;
&#xD;
Now I know what not to do. &#xD;
- I should be a friend not a teacher.&#xD;
- My authority is not very important&#xD;
- My kids follow what I do not what I tell them to do&#xD;
- If I have bad habits, there are very high chances they will have the same bad habits.&#xD;
- My kids are my mirror images of me&#xD;
- I should negotiate with my kids not command&#xD;
- Some say it’s not quantity but quality of time spent together. It is quantity in my opinion.&#xD;
- I have to tell my kids how much I love them. Not just think about it&#xD;
- Hug is the best medicine in most of time.&#xD;
- I should enjoy the moment and the journey.&#xD;
- Manual can be generated if I and my kids talk&#xD;
- My influence is overly greater than all the teaches my kids will ever meet&#xD;
- There are absolutely no room for physical purnishment at any conditions &#xD;
&#xD;
Here are the questions.&#xD;
- How can I be a friend not a teacher ?&#xD;
- How to talk to my own kid without getting uptight ?&#xD;
- Can we produce the basic manual among ourselves ?&#xD;
- Do I need family mission or vision like business ?&#xD;
- What kinds of values should I  preach to my kids ?&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
I am waiting for your highly regarded ideas.&#xD;
&#xD;
</content>
    <postId>F6C08ED1-B564-4AC3-9238-7BBA1FD5B9C7</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-12-23T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>RE: Workshop : How to raise our kids ?</title>
</post>
