<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김중수</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>제가 있는 회사에서 오래동안 Senior급 DBA를 찾고 있는데&#xD;
아직 못찾은것 같습니다.&#xD;
오늘 사장보고자리에서 Human Resource부문에서 걱정을 하더군요&#xD;
&#xD;
ORACLE및 SQL-Server DBA에 경험이 있으신 분은 Apply해 &#xD;
보세요.&#xD;
&#xD;
위치 : 나이아가라&#xD;
Position : ORACLE, MS-SQL DBA. &#xD;
연락처 : www.acresprotech.com &#xD;
다음은 Job Spec입니다.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Computer Scientist -- Database Expertise&#xD;
· University degree in Computer Science/Mathematics or Computer Science/Engineering. &#xD;
· Senior position requires 5+ years of experience in C++ development AND database implementation. Intermediate position requires 3+ years of experience. &#xD;
· Experience with Oracle7 or 8 is a necessity. Exposure to MS SQL Server also an asset. &#xD;
· Skill set must include data modeling, relational database design, RDBMS installation/configuration, and integration of SQL with analytic engines. Experience should include use of PL/SQL, explicit cursors, stored procedures and functions. &#xD;
· Knowledge of managing Oracle on Windows NT, and experience with UNIX and other types of databases such as time-series or object-oriented, will be an advantage. &#xD;
· Communication skills are very important -- applicant must be able to communicate well with the development team and with clients. &#xD;
&#xD;
Software Developers &#xD;
· Skill set must include object-oriented principles &amp; design, working with C++ base classes, programming with SQL.&#xD;
· Senior position requires 5+ years of experience in C++ development. Intermediate position requires 3+ years of experience. &#xD;
· Experience developing technical and business applications for a client/server environment.&#xD;
· Experience with integration of SQL with analytic engines.&#xD;
· Experience in development of GUIs, using tools such as MFC.&#xD;
· Communication skills are very important -- applicant must be able to communicate well with the development team and with clients. &#xD;
&#xD;
Water Resource Optimization Specialist &#xD;
· Applied scientist with a university degree in Applied Mathematics/Physics or Applied Engineering, with strong background in optimization theory.&#xD;
· 10+ years of experience in optimization analyses. &#xD;
· Experience or understanding of water resources modeling would be a definite asset. &#xD;
· Must be highly skilled in development of C++ code, and must be intimately familiar with use of large-scale LP solvers, such as ILOG/CPLEX. Knowledge of other OR methods such as DP and integer programming, will be an advantage. &#xD;
&#xD;
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&#xD;
Copyright &amp;copy; 2000-2001. Acres Productive Technologies Inc. All Rights Reserved.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
제게 연락주시면 제가 이력서 손을 좀 보고, Manager 에게 &#xD;
보내겠습니다. &#xD;
</content>
    <postId>FB5BCBFD-0077-4196-8C0B-793B614BF90A</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-03-22T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>DBA (ORACLE,MS-SQL_server)</title>
</post>
