<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;h2&gt;Workflow and user interface design review&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;br&gt;2006-01-12 (Thu.) 7:00 PM &amp;#8211; 9:00 PM&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attendees: Mr. Ko (BJ), Ms. Lee(SS) , Mr. Heo (HO) , Mr. Park (KJ), Mr. Boo (KH)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Workflow review&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;User interface review&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Database change&lt;br&gt;&amp;#8226;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Tasks assignment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Workflow review&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br&gt;HO started with the business scenario (http://studygroup.wikispaces.com/srs.html#toc13).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br&gt;HO presented the storyboard (http://studygroup.wikispaces.com/sdd.html).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;User Interface review&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 12&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KJ: Should we allow a user to delete the courses from 12? &lt;br&gt;(Note that the numbers represent relevant screenshots in the storyboard)&lt;br&gt;HO: There may be a case where a user adds a course by mistake and it would be OK to delete the course as long as the course has not been referenced anywhere yet.&lt;br&gt;KH: The system will have to popup a deletion confirmation message before deleting a course.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 16&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KH: From 16, it would be better to display the list of available course types in a dropdown list (as opposed to current radio buttons). This is because new course types would have to be added in the future. &lt;br&gt;KJ: Agreed&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 25&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KJ: From 25, course deletion should be done selectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KB: From 2, we need to use first and last name (as opposed to name) for student search.&lt;br&gt;KJ: For the search result fields, I’d like to see student number, first name, last name, and a telephone number.&lt;br&gt;KB: The search type does not need to include 'all' so that a student search can be done throughout the entire search category?&lt;br&gt;KJ: We don’t need it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 3&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KJ: In 3, two addresses need to be shown. Add a radio button in between to indicate whether or not the two addresses are identical. If so, the system will copy the values of the first address to the second one.&lt;br&gt;KJ: Let’s change the date of birth (DOB) format to mm/dd/yyyy. &lt;br&gt;KJ: Change the Reference section to use a free format textbox (from the current radio buttons)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 6&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KJ: In 6, is a user allowed to delete the course information items and why?&lt;br&gt;KJ: Remove the dropdown list of courses and add a term column in the course information instead. &lt;br&gt;HO: What is a maximum number of terms a student would attend?&lt;br&gt;KJ: About 15 terms, and 50 courses&lt;br&gt;HO: Need to add an edit button in 6.&lt;br&gt;BJ: Remove the delete button from 6 and add an edit button for updating the courses or adding a new course,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 7&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KJ: In 7, use the term ‘Register’ rather than ‘Taken’ for the checkboxes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 15&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 15, the course types should be listed in a dropdown list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 23&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KJ: In 23, make it to list the course history only. Add a dropdown list to list available terms.&lt;br&gt;BJ: I will code encryption/decryption functions for user password.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen 32&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KH: Users will be authorized based on their roles assigned. There will be 4 levels of privileges initially.&lt;br&gt;BJ: I don’t see a difference from the current checkbox (task) based authorization.&lt;br&gt;SS: An advantage of the role based authorization is that the UI screens are pre-determined as soon as a user logs in to the system. The functions a user does not need may be grayed out or not displayed at all. &lt;br&gt;KH: By using task based authorization, there would be a maintenance problem because the list of tasks are likely to change continuously in the future even not frequently.&lt;br&gt;KH: Let’s use only one role &amp;#8211; i.e. supervisor &amp;#8211; for the initial development phase.&lt;br&gt;SS: This will be omitted from the UI testing item as well then.&lt;br&gt;KH: Agreed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Database change&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;KJ: I have a second thought that I need to keep detailed info for instructors - last name, first name, address, two phone numbers, SIN, email, hired date, and additional notes.&lt;br&gt;KJ: I need a teaching history of the instructors provided by the system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Tasks assignment&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;HO: JSPs and Struts configuration&lt;br&gt;KH: Database, model, and Hibernate mapping&lt;br&gt;SS: Ruby/Watir&lt;br&gt;BJ: JUnit for persistence testing&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>30DAF570-63A7-4DA7-8A4B-A18FAC89EEA9</postId>
    <pubDate>2006-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>Meeting minutes - 1/12 UI design review</title>
</post>
