<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>허현옥</author>
            <date>2005-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>That's a great idea. by the way, since this week off-line meeting seems too hard to do for everybody. So people who has a time(Kwon, Hwang and Heo) in a day time met today and we discuss about our ERD and Data. We changed our ERD and I think we better discuss with Mr.Park about Data. I will call him personally and get some more information for our ERD. I am sure why we all are confused by each other is from unsure data definition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  I will put up new ERD to our WIKI tonight then we can talk about it on our meeting tomorrow.</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>허현옥</author>
            <date>2005-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>As I talked to Mr.bu on the phone. we will meet Mr.Park tomorrow. I will not put the new ERD tonight..&lt;br&gt;  Tomorrow night I will put up new ERD or I will explain and put new ERD the day after tomorrow</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>KB</author>
            <date>2005-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>Try not to break the sample data the customer provided in the requirements doc, or my UML model would collapse down :-)</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>허현옥</author>
            <date>2005-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>We are not going to but, if client's requirements are different we will have no choice. If the situation drive you to change your UML that will also change ERD and StoryBoard too. So, Don't worry about it too much..^^ But, I am sure there will be a little change. so.. take a deep breath ;-)</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>권칠환</author>
            <date>2005-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>I think that we need to verify the sample data and even the name of entity after meeting the client.</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>KB</author>
            <date>2005-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>OK. Try to clarify things (including the sample data) as much as possible then.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>Based on the customer's reply, I updated the UML model regarding CourseHistory and Transcript. Please review and give me feedback.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It still does not match with the ER diagram so we will need further discussion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have one suggestion on this online review process: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each of us posts a list of questions against the others' work products. For example, I would post questions on the ERD (Mr. Kwon), Storyboard (Mr. Heo), and Installation Guide (Mr. Hwang).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We will need to try our best to make the questions &amp; answers logical and backed up by proven theories or best practices when available (but bear in mind that there will be no definitive answers).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Or, is it too much? How do you think?</content>
    <postId>4E6E8752-42C2-4E27-9AF7-69826A783083</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>CourseHistory &amp; Transcript</title>
</post>
