<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>허현옥</author>
            <date>2005-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>아... 우선은 Transcript는 "성적증명서"라는 말로 더 많이 쓴다다네요.. 저희가 어제 미팅에서 얘기했던것처럼 Transcript라고 하는 테이블은 ReportCard로 대체하기로 하였습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  그리고, 이따가 미팅에서 말씀드리겠지만, Course와 CourseHistory리의 관계는 말그대로 Course에 대한 History만 couresHistory가 갖게 됩니다. 무슨말인가 하면.... Course에 해당과목에 대한 필수내용만 들어가고.. CourseHistory에는 그 과목이 언제 언제 개설되었고, 선생님은 누구였는지정도의 데이타만 기록하고 다른 테이블과의 연관관계는 전혀없습니다. &lt;br&gt;  학생의 성적을 낼때도 Course 테이블과 ReportCard 테이블만 가지고 제어하게 되구요. 한마디로 저희가 생각하던 CouresHistory가 아닌거죠..^^ (Course 에대한 commentary 정도의 역할만 하네요.)</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>KB</author>
            <date>2005-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>Ouch! If everthing is decided already, why are we having a meeting? Is it simply to inform me about the decision made?</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>KB</author>
            <date>2005-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</date>
            <content>커뮤니케이션 문제가 있는것 같아서 좀 시간이 걸려도 한글을 타이프 해야겠네요. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;트랜스크립트 - 해석을 요구한게 아니고, 이 성적 증명서는 데이타 테이블이 필요 없다는 의견이죠. 이유는 다른 테이블에서 모든 필요 데이타를 갖고 올수 있기 때문에. 이럴경우 일반적으로 "테이블이 아니라 "뷰"를 사용하죠 (혹은 "조인"을 이용한 스토어드 프로시듀어도 가능하고). 제 포인트는 RDB 이론에 의하여 테이블을 만들면 안되는 것이라는 생각 (데이타 불필요 중복 보관이 되죠). 이것은 노말라이제이션을 따라서 해보시면 금방 밝혀질 거예요 아마도.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Course 와 Course History는 제가 한말을 또 그대로 하신것 같은데. 현재의 Course는 불완전한 데이타이죠. 개설시기와 교재 혹은 강사가 없으니까요. 그런점에서 현재의 Course History가 우리가 일반적으로 예기하는 Course라는 예기이죠. 또하나 틀린점은 현재의 Course는 Course 라기 보다는 Course 후보들을 보관하는 장소라는 생각. Course에 개설가능한 100개의 과목후보를 가질 수 있으나, 한 학기에 개설되는 실재 과목은 10개만 일 수 있죠. 이런점에서 Course 와 Course History라는 어휘선택이 제 마음에 안든다는 말이었읍니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;더욱 자세히는 미팅에서.</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>I did some homework in preparation for tonight’s meeting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 -1) Missing fields from Student and sample data&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Major&amp;gt; e.g. Acupuncture , found from the sample transcript&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Applying for&amp;gt; e.g. Initial Entry &amp; Transfer, found from the sample application form. note this is different from &amp;lt;Applied Diploma&amp;gt;.&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Emergency contact&amp;gt; e.g. contact person and phone number, found from the sample application form&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;DOB&amp;gt; e.g. born in YYYY-MM-DD&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Email&amp;gt; e.g. foo.bar@foobar.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Course Language&amp;gt; this rather belongs to Course than Student. note that this may have meant Preferred Language of a student.&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;English level&amp;gt; this field is not used anywhere&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Initial contact made&amp;gt; this may be redundant as Mr. Kwon mentioned earlier. see consulting date in Consulting History.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 - 2) Missing fields from Education&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;From&amp;gt; e.g. 95/03, found from the sample application form&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;To&amp;gt; e.g. 99/02, found from the sample application form&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Degree&amp;gt; e.g. BA, found from the sample application form&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 - 3) Missing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;entity &lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Work History&amp;gt; found from the sample application form&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 - 4) Missing fields from Course&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Diploma type, or Program type&amp;gt; e.g. course code A110 is for the TCM Practitioner program. course code W910 is open for the Doctor of TCM program, found from the sample course form.&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;Course language&amp;gt; this field should be moved from Student&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2) Terminologies&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 - 1) Misunderstanding of Transcript&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am starting to realize that Transcript is rather a derived “view” than a “table”. The Transcript view (or a dynamic query result) is constructed from the tables including Student, Course, and Course History (see the customer’s sample Transcript) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 - 2) Course and Course History&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is tough. Currently we define Course and Course History like the following.&lt;br&gt;The Course contains generic descriptions of the available courses and The Course History contains actual course openings in a specified term. The Course History has extra info such as a book title and instructor. However, this entity may be rather called Course and the current Course being renamed to Course Template or Course Pool since this has incomplete info of the courses. I think this is the area we need to consult with Tiffiny, Mr. Heo?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 -3) Academic Record&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So, there is a student and the courses he/she registered for a semester.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At the end of the term, a grade for each course should be recorded somewhere. Currently the UML captures this in Transcript but using the word “Transcript” is a wrong choice so I would like to change the word to something like “Academic Record” or “Course Credit Record”. Maybe we need help from Tiffiny here as well. As always good wording is one of the most tough tasks ;-(&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>5C435523-4C20-48B4-B60C-1EEA469E200A</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</pubDate>
    <title>My homework for tonight\\'s meeting</title>
</post>
