<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>박재홍</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>Demonstration / protest is planned for tomorrow (June 30) by various groups opposed to the "occupation" of Iraq and the related change over to the Iraqi Government.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This protest is planned to begin around 2:00 p.m. and extend to 6:00 p.m. or beyond. There may also be attempts to disrupt rush hour traffic as people begin to leave their offices in preparation of the Canada Day holiday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AGENDA:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; (please note that the order of rally points and parade march times may change):&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 pm - Meet at King and Bay Streets, picket "Interhealth" @ 357 Bay&lt;br&gt;2 pm - Mass Delegation at @ 151 Yonge Street, picket.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It is believed that this will include attempts to picket U.S. firms,located in the area, that are participating in the re-building of Iraq including Rockwell and General Electric.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4 pm - Student Takeover @ College &amp; University Ave:&lt;br&gt;The groups on Bay and Yonge streets are expected to move west along multiple paths in order to assemble at or near College &amp; University.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It is the intention of the group to block all traffic at the intersection so as to generate commuter frustration on the eve of the July 1 holiday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5 pm - Rally at US Consulate (@ 360 University Ave)&lt;br&gt;They will then move south to the USA Consulate to hold a rally, which is again expected to significantly affect traffic in the area.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6 pm - March through downtown core (financial district)&lt;br&gt;A parade march will then take place, for which a permit has been given. The parade route is expected to be north along University onto Dundas Street; east across Dundas to Yonge Street; south on Yonge Street to Queen Street; west on Queen Street back to University Avenue; then back to the USA Consulate.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>105F21A3-9396-4EB4-A6B0-03CF39BEA18A</postId>
    <pubDate>2004-06-29T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Avoid downtown on June 30</title>
</post>
