<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>박경종</author>
            <date>2005-05-05T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>자원봉사자 여러분 수고 하셨습니다</content>
        </comment>
        <comment>
            <author>KIM Nam Soo</author>
            <date>2005-07-05T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>Hats Off to our volunteers!! Much appreciation for your dedicated commitment to COSKA!</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>For the last few years, our volunteers have been contributing to the society by providing private/semi-private computer training courses to the elderly and handicapped people. It would have been the time to harvest the outcome of their hard work. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to the Korean Senior Citizens Society of Toronto, the COSKA has received recognition from the City of Toronto. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is something not only we but all Korean-Canadians would be proud of, and this would be a small but nevertheless a bold step toward becoming more vibrant and contributing member to the Canadian society. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congratulations to all the members and our board of directors!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;=============&lt;br&gt;CITY OF TORONTO MAYOR DAVID MILLER AND MEMBERS OF TORONTO CITY COUNCIL EXTEND THEIR SINCERE APPRECIATION TO COSKA-COMPUTER SCIENCE KOREAN ASSOCIATION &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;in honour of your valuable contribution as a volunteer. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Volunteers regard themselves as ordinary people but, in fact, are our greatest resource and the heart and soul of our warm and caring City. As volunteers, you can be extremely proud of the important role you play and the support you provide to your organization. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Your generous gift of time together with your dedication, enthusiasm, and selfless commitment to our communities, have made a difference in many lives. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;We thank you for caring and giving. &lt;br&gt;You are one of the reasons why Toronto is such a great place to live! &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Mayor David Miller &lt;br&gt;April 2005 </content>
    <postId>202A82AA-4D21-4004-A990-5C0BF288EE3A</postId>
    <pubDate>2005-05-05T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>From Mayor David Miller &amp; Members of Toronto City Council</title>
</post>
