<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>dslee28</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;수고하신 모든 분들께 박수를 보냅니다.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;고생 많으셨습니다. 다음은 마켓에 등록될 내용입니다.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;###### Flying Dishes ######&lt;br /&gt;This is a proto type of Android game from COSKA(&lt;a href="http://www.coska.com"&gt;http://www.coska.com&lt;/a&gt;) and CommunityOne.&lt;br /&gt;*** If you are a public Android user, this is not what you are looking for. If you are a beginner Android developer this might be helpful resource. ***&lt;br /&gt;This was experimental open source project from 2 developer groups(COSKA &amp;amp; CommunityOne).&lt;br /&gt;The source code will be released as soon as we finish cleaning up the code :)&lt;br /&gt;--- Game Play ---&lt;br /&gt;-Hit "Start" button&lt;br /&gt;-Press the button at bottom-right corner and hold&lt;br /&gt;-When you release the button the chef will jump&lt;br /&gt;-You can touch the chef and drag and release from right to left&lt;br /&gt;-Dish will shoot out of the chef and hit the bubbles.&lt;br /&gt;-When you hit all the items that are displayed on the left of the screen, you clear the round before time run out.&lt;br /&gt;This project is developed by all volunteers.&lt;br /&gt;--- Project Designed &amp;amp; Developed by ---&lt;br /&gt;Alex Lee (이창준) &lt;br /&gt;Brian Heo (허현옥)&lt;br /&gt;Byung Yong Kim (김병용)&lt;br /&gt;Chang Jeon Lee (이창전)&lt;br /&gt;Chulgun Lee (이철건)&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Ki (김경환)&lt;br /&gt;Ki Hup Boo (부기흡)&lt;br /&gt;Miyoung Chung (정미영)&lt;br /&gt;Ritchie Hwang (황대현)&lt;br /&gt;Sooyong Sim (심수용)&lt;br /&gt;Spencer Hwang (황성규)&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Kim (김형태)&lt;br /&gt;*** Whitecat Software Inc did not involved on this particular project. Whitecat Software Inc is lending the publishing account to those group(COSKA &amp;amp; CommunityOne) for temporary. This app will be removed from Whitecat Software Inc publication list as soon as those group(COSKA &amp;amp; CommunityOne) setup their own account. ***&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <postId>5A838086-ECFB-431F-B776-5F1A1C4215D4</postId>
    <pubDate>2011-09-23T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>드뎌 안드로이드용 게임 Flying Dishes 가 마켓에 등록 되었습니다. </title>
</post>
