<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>박만식</author>
    <comments>
        <comment>
            <author>권혁준</author>
            <date>2009-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</date>
            <content>안녕하세요 첨부된 파일이 어디있는지좀 가르쳐 주세요. :)</content>
        </comment>
    </comments>
    <content>KOTRA(대한 무역투자 진흥공사)에서 우수인력 발굴지원사업을 추진하고 있습니다.&lt;br&gt;한국의 IT업체 혹은 Canada현지의 한국업체에 취업및 사업을 알선/지원및 정보교환하는 행사로서 관심있으신 회원들께서는 적극참여 바랍니다&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;또한 인적교류및 상호우호증진을 위한 상견례겸 저녁만찬이 준비되므로 참석하실 분들께서는 사전연락 혹은 본글에 Memo(Name, Phone#)를 남겨주시길 바랍니다.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;일시:&amp;nbsp;5월 13일(수) 저녁 6:30&lt;br&gt;장소: Dufferin 서울관&lt;br&gt;연락처 : 박 만식 (416-618-9031, augustine.park@rogers.com)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;상세 내용은 KOTRA 이 창화씨의 아래 이메일 참조바랍니다.&lt;br&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;KOTRA 토론토 무역관 이창화 입니다. &lt;br&gt;저는 금년부터 시작된 새로운 프로젝트인 Contact Korea을 담당하고 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;Contact Korea는 한국기업의 경쟁력 강화를 위해, 한국정부가 금년부터 시작한 우수인력 발굴지원사업으로 해외에 있는 한인교포를 포함한 외국인의 한국취업을 지원하고 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;지원범위는 주로 High Skilled person을 위주로 국내기업의 수요를 발굴하여, 적절한 해외인재를 발굴, 인터뷰지원, 출국지원까지 수행하고 있습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;당초에는 한국주재희망자만을 대상으로 지원하였으나, 최근에는 한국글로벌 기업의 해외법인에 대한 취업지원도 병행하고 있어, 더욱 더 많은 취업정보 및 기회를 여러분들께 제공해 드릴 수 있을 것으로 기대합니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;그러나, 저희 KBC (구, 무역관)에서 국내기업의 수요를 파악 적정한 인재를 발굴하여, Match-making을 수행하는데 있어 취업희망자 발굴에 많은 어려움이 있어, 금번에 Contact Korea Initiative라는 행사를 기획하게 되었습니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;행사목적은 자동차부품, IT산업분야에서 종사하고 계시는 한인인재 여러분들과의 정기적인 Networking을 위한 모임을 결성하고 이 모임을 통해 앞으로 진행되는 한국기업의 구인정보를 제공해 드릴 예정입니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;우선 동 Networking 모임에 참가희망여부를 알려주시기 바라며, 가능하시다면 첨부의 GTR도 작성해 주시면 감사하겠습니다. 동 모임을 기념하기 위해서, 5월13일 저녁 만찬을 통해 상견례하는 시간도 가질 예정이며, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;본사와 협력하여 5월11일부터 15일 1주일간 한국기업과의 취업 인터뷰도 주선하는 행사를 가질 예정입니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;두서없이 여러 가지 말씀 드렸습니다만, &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;아래의 세가지 사항에 대한 회신을 부탁드립니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Contact Korea Initiative참가희망여부 : Yes or No&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 만찬참석여부 : Yes or No&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; GTR 작성여부 : Yes or No&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;감사합니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;이창화 배상&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hello Everyone,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is Chris Lee from KOTRA Toronto, commercial section of the Korean consulate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;KOTRA has launched a new project, called Contact Korea, in 2009, and I am responsible for this project for the Eastern Canada area.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In order to increase the Korean companies’ competitiveness and strength, the Korean government has initiated this Contact Korea project in 2009 and is supporting Korean companies to hire/attract foreign talents including Korean-Canadians.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we do is, find Korean companies’ demand for foreign talents, mainly high skilled people, then seek relevant candidates, thereafter arrange/support job interview, and finally support their departure to Korea .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initially, we seek only foreign talents who are willing to relocate to S. Korea for employment, however recently we also support the recruiting process for Korean global companies’ foreign subsidies. Therefore we are looking forward to providing you with more career information and opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, KOTRA Toronto is now experiencing difficulty in finding suitable and qualified candidates for the match-making process. To overcome this difficulty, we are planning to hold an event, Contact Korea Initiative. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The main purpose of this event is to create a network among Korean Canadian professionals in the Automotive and IT industry, and we would like to provide you with career opportunity information of within Korean Companies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please inform us as to whether you will attend this Korean-Canadian professionals Network event. In addition, it would be appreciated if you can fill out the GTR(Global talent registration) form.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To celebrate this gathering of professionals we are planning to have a networking reception with dinner on May 13th. In addition we are planning to hold a job fair(cyber interview) with Korean companies cooperating with the KOTRA HQ from May 11th to May 15th.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It would be appreciated if you could respond regarding the following 3 things.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Willingness to attend Contact Korea Initiative : Yes or No&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Willingness to join for dinner: Yes or No&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Willingness to fill out GTR(Global talent registration form): Yes or No&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Lee&lt;br&gt;Business Development Officer&lt;br&gt;KOTRA Toronto&lt;br&gt;Korea Trade-Investment Promotion Agency&lt;br&gt;Consulate General of the Republic of Korea , Commercial Section&lt;br&gt;T: 416.368.3399 x 228&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; F: 416.368.2893 &lt;br&gt;Website: http://www.kotrana.org&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>AC820B56-7DEC-4980-B067-E760F2889A66</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-05-07T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>KOTRA 우수인력 발굴지원사업 행사지원요청 (IT취업알선, Interview, 구인정보교환)</title>
</post>
