<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>부기흡</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>IBM Canada Lab Linux Community&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linux is the fastest growing operating system available today and continues to gain additional market and mind-share each year. As Linux is an important strategy for IBM, the IBM Canada Labs Linux Community endeavors to promote the usage of Linux and provide an informal atmosphere for sharing Linux related knowledge and experience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you are new to Linux or are a regular kernel contributor, everyone is welcome to join the Linux community! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto Linux User Group Meeting - Mar 24, 2009&lt;br&gt;When : Mar 24, 2009, 7 - 10pm&lt;br&gt;Where : IBM Canada, 3600 Steeles Ave. E&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Important**&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This meeting is free and all are welcome, however, all attendees will be required to have a security badge. Badges should be prepared in advance. If you plan to attend, please send your name to Paul (off-list at &amp;lt;pmora@ca.ibm.com&amp;gt;) and please be sure to return badges to the front reception at the end of the session.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Topic: DNS - Domain Name System / Service&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presenter: Paul Mora&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- What is DNS, and why do we need it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- How does name resolution work&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- How do you register your own domain, and how much does it cost?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Once it's registered, how do you use it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Basic software choices and configuration&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Troubleshooting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A demonstration of DNS would follow all the talking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apr&amp;egrave;s-meet:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the meeting some will adjourn to a local coffee shop for continued discussion and general world problem solving. &lt;br&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto Linux User Group Meeting - Jan. 27, 2009&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto Linux User Group Meeting - Nov. 25, 2008&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto Linux User Group Meeting - Oct. 28, 2008&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;LPI Exam and Study Material&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To join the SWG Canada Linux Community please send an email to :&lt;br&gt;Patrick Sweitzer/Toronto/IBM &lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>B06B79AE-E5AF-4375-BEED-0EBCCCCA05C1</postId>
    <pubDate>2009-03-24T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>Toronto Linux User Group Meeting - Mar 24, 2009</title>
</post>
