<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
    <author>김세환</author>
    <comments/>
    <content>The question is not clear enough....however,...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I thought about some concerns and questions..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;House **&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. There are many different types of residences. For example,&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; there are Detached, Semi-detached, Town-house(Villa ?),Condomini줄이&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;2. The price of house varies depending on Location (area).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. The average house price in Greater Toronto area is somewhere&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;between $250,000 - $300,000 (guessing).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. It is a common practice to make a 25% downpayment and &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the rest is financed (Mortgage) by a bank if you are qualified.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; (Less down payment means more monthly Mortgage payment.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. When you buy a commercial or business, generally you need to &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; put more down payment than residential. (about 33 % minimum.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;** business **&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. I have No knowledge about the price of a business,&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it all depends on the sales, expense, in consequence, the profit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Are you capable of running a business as a new comer ?&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i.e. Communication, Culture, business Know-How ?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. What kind of fast food store are you thinking of ?&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i.e. Sandwich, Coffee, etc &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. The destination you are moving to is NOT known to me, however,&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; generally, again generally, a bigger city has a better &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; chance of surviving or success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Also it will cost relatively more for you to acquire a business.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. In case , you are NOT ready to do any business immediately,&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; do you have enough budget to survive 1 or 2 years until you are&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; ready or confident to do anything.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are few things I thought about...there could be more..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please try to be specific with your questions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope it is some help to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;SK&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;지금제가 1억5천을 가지고 집을사서 그걸로 모기지를 얻어서 조그만 페스트푸드점을 운영을 하려고 하는데&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 얼마나 모자란가요?&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt;캘로나나 펜팅턴등 주로 시골스러운 곳에서 하려고 하는데요....&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <postId>82160593-3CDD-4B1D-B575-E2CA6CCFC091</postId>
    <pubDate>2002-06-14T00:00:00-04:00</pubDate>
    <title>[re] 자금에대한 조언을 구합니다</title>
</post>
